{"question": "Solve: (137 * 110.56) + 90.89", "answer": "The result of (137 * 110.56) + 90.89 is 15237.61", "a": 137, "b": 110.56, "c": 90.89, "op1": "*", "op2": "+", "result": 15237.61}
{"question": "Solve: (182.96 - 172) + 168.03", "answer": "The result of (182.96 - 172) + 168.03 is 178.99", "a": 182.96, "b": 172, "c": 168.03, "op1": "-", "op2": "+", "result": 178.99}
{"question": "Solve: (112 / 80.76) * 80", "answer": "The result of (112 / 80.76) * 80 is 110.95", "a": 112, "b": 80.76, "c": 80, "op1": "/", "op2": "*", "result": 110.95}
{"question": "Solve: (9 + 123) * 172.92", "answer": "The result of (9 + 123) * 172.92 is 22825.44", "a": 9, "b": 123, "c": 172.92, "op1": "+", "op2": "*", "result": 22825.44}
{"question": "Solve: (125.73 - 100) - 162.14", "answer": "The result of (125.73 - 100) - 162.14 is -136.41", "a": 125.73, "b": 100, "c": 162.14, "op1": "-", "op2": "-", "result": -136.41}
{"question": "Solve: (186.32 - 120) * 78", "answer": "The result of (186.32 - 120) * 78 is 5172.96", "a": 186.32, "b": 120, "c": 78, "op1": "-", "op2": "*", "result": 5172.96}
{"question": "Solve: (152.66 / 99) * 71", "answer": "The result of (152.66 / 99) * 71 is 109.48", "a": 152.66, "b": 99, "c": 71, "op1": "/", "op2": "*", "result": 109.48}
{"question": "Solve: (152 - 86) * 50.56", "answer": "The result of (152 - 86) * 50.56 is 3336.96", "a": 152, "b": 86, "c": 50.56, "op1": "-", "op2": "*", "result": 3336.96}
{"question": "Solve: (42 + 4) - 4", "answer": "The result of (42 + 4) - 4 is 42", "a": 42, "b": 4, "c": 4, "op1": "+", "op2": "-", "result": 42}
{"question": "Solve: (63 + 136.43) + 139.16", "answer": "The result of (63 + 136.43) + 139.16 is 338.59", "a": 63, "b": 136.43, "c": 139.16, "op1": "+", "op2": "+", "result": 338.59}
{"question": "Solve: (135.65 + 198) / 101", "answer": "The result of (135.65 + 198) / 101 is 3.3", "a": 135.65, "b": 198, "c": 101, "op1": "+", "op2": "/", "result": 3.3}
{"question": "Solve: (154 / 191) + 121", "answer": "The result of (154 / 191) + 121 is 121.81", "a": 154, "b": 191, "c": 121, "op1": "/", "op2": "+", "result": 121.81}
{"question": "Solve: (54.41 / 170) + 118", "answer": "The result of (54.41 / 170) + 118 is 118.32", "a": 54.41, "b": 170, "c": 118, "op1": "/", "op2": "+", "result": 118.32}
{"question": "Solve: (59.76 + 91) + 199", "answer": "The result of (59.76 + 91) + 199 is 349.76", "a": 59.76, "b": 91, "c": 199, "op1": "+", "op2": "+", "result": 349.76}
{"question": "Solve: (45 - 130.08) + 19", "answer": "The result of (45 - 130.08) + 19 is -66.08", "a": 45, "b": 130.08, "c": 19, "op1": "-", "op2": "+", "result": -66.08}
{"question": "Solve: (103 + 30) - 81", "answer": "The result of (103 + 30) - 81 is 52", "a": 103, "b": 30, "c": 81, "op1": "+", "op2": "-", "result": 52}
{"question": "Solve: (100 + 124) + 54", "answer": "The result of (100 + 124) + 54 is 278", "a": 100, "b": 124, "c": 54, "op1": "+", "op2": "+", "result": 278}
{"question": "Solve: (39 / 97) - 140", "answer": "The result of (39 / 97) - 140 is -139.6", "a": 39, "b": 97, "c": 140, "op1": "/", "op2": "-", "result": -139.6}
{"question": "Solve: (127 - 167) * 74", "answer": "The result of (127 - 167) * 74 is -2960", "a": 127, "b": 167, "c": 74, "op1": "-", "op2": "*", "result": -2960}
{"question": "Solve: (98 * 178) * 194", "answer": "The result of (98 * 178) * 194 is 3384136", "a": 98, "b": 178, "c": 194, "op1": "*", "op2": "*", "result": 3384136}
{"question": "Solve: (77 + 19) * 102", "answer": "The result of (77 + 19) * 102 is 9792", "a": 77, "b": 19, "c": 102, "op1": "+", "op2": "*", "result": 9792}
{"question": "Solve: (22 / 77) + 160.7", "answer": "The result of (22 / 77) + 160.7 is 160.99", "a": 22, "b": 77, "c": 160.7, "op1": "/", "op2": "+", "result": 160.99}
{"question": "Solve: (191 + 13) / 7.73", "answer": "The result of (191 + 13) / 7.73 is 26.39", "a": 191, "b": 13, "c": 7.73, "op1": "+", "op2": "/", "result": 26.39}
{"question": "Solve: (118 + 63) - 138.22", "answer": "The result of (118 + 63) - 138.22 is 42.78", "a": 118, "b": 63, "c": 138.22, "op1": "+", "op2": "-", "result": 42.78}
{"question": "Solve: (173 - 93) - 3", "answer": "The result of (173 - 93) - 3 is 77", "a": 173, "b": 93, "c": 3, "op1": "-", "op2": "-", "result": 77}
{"question": "Solve: (168.26 / 166) - 190", "answer": "The result of (168.26 / 166) - 190 is -188.99", "a": 168.26, "b": 166, "c": 190, "op1": "/", "op2": "-", "result": -188.99}
{"question": "Solve: (28 - 178) - 44", "answer": "The result of (28 - 178) - 44 is -194", "a": 28, "b": 178, "c": 44, "op1": "-", "op2": "-", "result": -194}
{"question": "Solve: (156 * 158.87) / 161.8", "answer": "The result of (156 * 158.87) / 161.8 is 153.18", "a": 156, "b": 158.87, "c": 161.8, "op1": "*", "op2": "/", "result": 153.18}
{"question": "Solve: (53 - 50.76) - 123.57", "answer": "The result of (53 - 50.76) - 123.57 is -121.33", "a": 53, "b": 50.76, "c": 123.57, "op1": "-", "op2": "-", "result": -121.33}
{"question": "Solve: (130.86 + 79) * 82", "answer": "The result of (130.86 + 79) * 82 is 17208.52", "a": 130.86, "b": 79, "c": 82, "op1": "+", "op2": "*", "result": 17208.52}
{"question": "Solve: (112.2 * 113) * 9", "answer": "The result of (112.2 * 113) * 9 is 114107.4", "a": 112.2, "b": 113, "c": 9, "op1": "*", "op2": "*", "result": 114107.4}
{"question": "Solve: (18 - 123.76) + 110.25", "answer": "The result of (18 - 123.76) + 110.25 is 4.49", "a": 18, "b": 123.76, "c": 110.25, "op1": "-", "op2": "+", "result": 4.49}
{"question": "Solve: (77 - 23.49) * 64", "answer": "The result of (77 - 23.49) * 64 is 3424.64", "a": 77, "b": 23.49, "c": 64, "op1": "-", "op2": "*", "result": 3424.64}
{"question": "Solve: (72.52 / 91) - 79.48", "answer": "The result of (72.52 / 91) - 79.48 is -78.68", "a": 72.52, "b": 91, "c": 79.48, "op1": "/", "op2": "-", "result": -78.68}
{"question": "Solve: (104 - 81) * 173", "answer": "The result of (104 - 81) * 173 is 3979", "a": 104, "b": 81, "c": 173, "op1": "-", "op2": "*", "result": 3979}
{"question": "Solve: (30.79 - 66) - 61", "answer": "The result of (30.79 - 66) - 61 is -96.21", "a": 30.79, "b": 66, "c": 61, "op1": "-", "op2": "-", "result": -96.21}
{"question": "Solve: (124 - 133) + 116.05", "answer": "The result of (124 - 133) + 116.05 is 107.05", "a": 124, "b": 133, "c": 116.05, "op1": "-", "op2": "+", "result": 107.05}
{"question": "Solve: (59 * 153.64) * 22", "answer": "The result of (59 * 153.64) * 22 is 199424.72", "a": 59, "b": 153.64, "c": 22, "op1": "*", "op2": "*", "result": 199424.72}
{"question": "Solve: (88 * 156) - 106", "answer": "The result of (88 * 156) - 106 is 13622", "a": 88, "b": 156, "c": 106, "op1": "*", "op2": "-", "result": 13622}
{"question": "Solve: (67.35 * 113) - 15", "answer": "The result of (67.35 * 113) - 15 is 7595.55", "a": 67.35, "b": 113, "c": 15, "op1": "*", "op2": "-", "result": 7595.55}
{"question": "Solve: (65 - 158) + 178", "answer": "The result of (65 - 158) + 178 is 85", "a": 65, "b": 158, "c": 178, "op1": "-", "op2": "+", "result": 85}
{"question": "Solve: (103 * 131) / 104.61", "answer": "The result of (103 * 131) / 104.61 is 128.98", "a": 103, "b": 131, "c": 104.61, "op1": "*", "op2": "/", "result": 128.98}
{"question": "Solve: (183 / 158.93) * 108.41", "answer": "The result of (183 / 158.93) * 108.41 is 124.83", "a": 183, "b": 158.93, "c": 108.41, "op1": "/", "op2": "*", "result": 124.83}
{"question": "Solve: (33 / 16) - 4", "answer": "The result of (33 / 16) - 4 is -1.94", "a": 33, "b": 16, "c": 4, "op1": "/", "op2": "-", "result": -1.94}
{"question": "Solve: (25.98 * 91.65) + 42", "answer": "The result of (25.98 * 91.65) + 42 is 2423.07", "a": 25.98, "b": 91.65, "c": 42, "op1": "*", "op2": "+", "result": 2423.07}
{"question": "Solve: (172 - 133) / 70", "answer": "The result of (172 - 133) / 70 is 0.56", "a": 172, "b": 133, "c": 70, "op1": "-", "op2": "/", "result": 0.56}
{"question": "Solve: (41.59 - 132) / 82", "answer": "The result of (41.59 - 132) / 82 is -1.1", "a": 41.59, "b": 132, "c": 82, "op1": "-", "op2": "/", "result": -1.1}
{"question": "Solve: (63.42 - 64) / 158", "answer": "The result of (63.42 - 64) / 158 is -0.0", "a": 63.42, "b": 64, "c": 158, "op1": "-", "op2": "/", "result": -0.0}
{"question": "Solve: (38 - 179.54) / 104.33", "answer": "The result of (38 - 179.54) / 104.33 is -1.36", "a": 38, "b": 179.54, "c": 104.33, "op1": "-", "op2": "/", "result": -1.36}
{"question": "Solve: (25.18 / 185.2) * 34.95", "answer": "The result of (25.18 / 185.2) * 34.95 is 4.75", "a": 25.18, "b": 185.2, "c": 34.95, "op1": "/", "op2": "*", "result": 4.75}
{"question": "Solve: (189 * 95) - 175.76", "answer": "The result of (189 * 95) - 175.76 is 17779.24", "a": 189, "b": 95, "c": 175.76, "op1": "*", "op2": "-", "result": 17779.24}
{"question": "Solve: (38.91 + 200) * 94", "answer": "The result of (38.91 + 200) * 94 is 22457.54", "a": 38.91, "b": 200, "c": 94, "op1": "+", "op2": "*", "result": 22457.54}
{"question": "Solve: (180 * 193.65) / 27", "answer": "The result of (180 * 193.65) / 27 is 1291.0", "a": 180, "b": 193.65, "c": 27, "op1": "*", "op2": "/", "result": 1291.0}
{"question": "Solve: (8.87 / 158) / 191", "answer": "The result of (8.87 / 158) / 191 is 0.0", "a": 8.87, "b": 158, "c": 191, "op1": "/", "op2": "/", "result": 0.0}
{"question": "Solve: (124 + 54.37) + 179", "answer": "The result of (124 + 54.37) + 179 is 357.37", "a": 124, "b": 54.37, "c": 179, "op1": "+", "op2": "+", "result": 357.37}
{"question": "Solve: (85 + 175) / 78", "answer": "The result of (85 + 175) / 78 is 3.33", "a": 85, "b": 175, "c": 78, "op1": "+", "op2": "/", "result": 3.33}
{"question": "Solve: (114.27 / 89) / 14", "answer": "The result of (114.27 / 89) / 14 is 0.09", "a": 114.27, "b": 89, "c": 14, "op1": "/", "op2": "/", "result": 0.09}
{"question": "Solve: (63 + 91.68) / 112", "answer": "The result of (63 + 91.68) / 112 is 1.38", "a": 63, "b": 91.68, "c": 112, "op1": "+", "op2": "/", "result": 1.38}
{"question": "Solve: (179.51 + 157) + 186", "answer": "The result of (179.51 + 157) + 186 is 522.51", "a": 179.51, "b": 157, "c": 186, "op1": "+", "op2": "+", "result": 522.51}
{"question": "Solve: (127 + 185) + 114", "answer": "The result of (127 + 185) + 114 is 426", "a": 127, "b": 185, "c": 114, "op1": "+", "op2": "+", "result": 426}
{"question": "Solve: (146 * 124) - 17", "answer": "The result of (146 * 124) - 17 is 18087", "a": 146, "b": 124, "c": 17, "op1": "*", "op2": "-", "result": 18087}
{"question": "Solve: (79 - 21) * 97", "answer": "The result of (79 - 21) * 97 is 5626", "a": 79, "b": 21, "c": 97, "op1": "-", "op2": "*", "result": 5626}
{"question": "Solve: (103 - 98.79) - 78", "answer": "The result of (103 - 98.79) - 78 is -73.79", "a": 103, "b": 98.79, "c": 78, "op1": "-", "op2": "-", "result": -73.79}
{"question": "Solve: (90.18 - 124) + 31", "answer": "The result of (90.18 - 124) + 31 is -2.82", "a": 90.18, "b": 124, "c": 31, "op1": "-", "op2": "+", "result": -2.82}
{"question": "Solve: (93 * 104.23) + 134.8", "answer": "The result of (93 * 104.23) + 134.8 is 9828.19", "a": 93, "b": 104.23, "c": 134.8, "op1": "*", "op2": "+", "result": 9828.19}
{"question": "Solve: (106 / 188) + 83.5", "answer": "The result of (106 / 188) + 83.5 is 84.06", "a": 106, "b": 188, "c": 83.5, "op1": "/", "op2": "+", "result": 84.06}
{"question": "Solve: (8 * 199) / 175", "answer": "The result of (8 * 199) / 175 is 9.1", "a": 8, "b": 199, "c": 175, "op1": "*", "op2": "/", "result": 9.1}
{"question": "Solve: (80 / 176.07) - 143", "answer": "The result of (80 / 176.07) - 143 is -142.55", "a": 80, "b": 176.07, "c": 143, "op1": "/", "op2": "-", "result": -142.55}
{"question": "Solve: (47 * 132) - 135", "answer": "The result of (47 * 132) - 135 is 6069", "a": 47, "b": 132, "c": 135, "op1": "*", "op2": "-", "result": 6069}
{"question": "Solve: (199 + 58.02) / 7.69", "answer": "The result of (199 + 58.02) / 7.69 is 33.42", "a": 199, "b": 58.02, "c": 7.69, "op1": "+", "op2": "/", "result": 33.42}
{"question": "Solve: (62 * 150) + 143", "answer": "The result of (62 * 150) + 143 is 9443", "a": 62, "b": 150, "c": 143, "op1": "*", "op2": "+", "result": 9443}
{"question": "Solve: (105.02 / 153.66) + 29", "answer": "The result of (105.02 / 153.66) + 29 is 29.68", "a": 105.02, "b": 153.66, "c": 29, "op1": "/", "op2": "+", "result": 29.68}
{"question": "Solve: (138 + 148.38) - 130.63", "answer": "The result of (138 + 148.38) - 130.63 is 155.75", "a": 138, "b": 148.38, "c": 130.63, "op1": "+", "op2": "-", "result": 155.75}
{"question": "Solve: (72 / 189) - 109", "answer": "The result of (72 / 189) - 109 is -108.62", "a": 72, "b": 189, "c": 109, "op1": "/", "op2": "-", "result": -108.62}
{"question": "Solve: (81 + 93) / 2", "answer": "The result of (81 + 93) / 2 is 87.0", "a": 81, "b": 93, "c": 2, "op1": "+", "op2": "/", "result": 87.0}
{"question": "Solve: (187 * 149) + 121", "answer": "The result of (187 * 149) + 121 is 27984", "a": 187, "b": 149, "c": 121, "op1": "*", "op2": "+", "result": 27984}
{"question": "Solve: (84.72 - 173.38) * 147", "answer": "The result of (84.72 - 173.38) * 147 is -13033.02", "a": 84.72, "b": 173.38, "c": 147, "op1": "-", "op2": "*", "result": -13033.02}
{"question": "Solve: (35 * 94) + 159", "answer": "The result of (35 * 94) + 159 is 3449", "a": 35, "b": 94, "c": 159, "op1": "*", "op2": "+", "result": 3449}
{"question": "Solve: (10 * 122.93) * 120.34", "answer": "The result of (10 * 122.93) * 120.34 is 147933.96", "a": 10, "b": 122.93, "c": 120.34, "op1": "*", "op2": "*", "result": 147933.96}
{"question": "Solve: (70 + 1.88) + 101", "answer": "The result of (70 + 1.88) + 101 is 172.88", "a": 70, "b": 1.88, "c": 101, "op1": "+", "op2": "+", "result": 172.88}
{"question": "Solve: (26 - 31) - 165", "answer": "The result of (26 - 31) - 165 is -170", "a": 26, "b": 31, "c": 165, "op1": "-", "op2": "-", "result": -170}
{"question": "Solve: (104.23 * 104) * 100", "answer": "The result of (104.23 * 104) * 100 is 1083992.0", "a": 104.23, "b": 104, "c": 100, "op1": "*", "op2": "*", "result": 1083992.0}
{"question": "Solve: (60.76 + 86) / 81.49", "answer": "The result of (60.76 + 86) / 81.49 is 1.8", "a": 60.76, "b": 86, "c": 81.49, "op1": "+", "op2": "/", "result": 1.8}
{"question": "Solve: (96 / 41) + 166.63", "answer": "The result of (96 / 41) + 166.63 is 168.97", "a": 96, "b": 41, "c": 166.63, "op1": "/", "op2": "+", "result": 168.97}
{"question": "Solve: (192 / 143.91) / 117.38", "answer": "The result of (192 / 143.91) / 117.38 is 0.01", "a": 192, "b": 143.91, "c": 117.38, "op1": "/", "op2": "/", "result": 0.01}
{"question": "Solve: (198.35 * 55) - 47.65", "answer": "The result of (198.35 * 55) - 47.65 is 10861.6", "a": 198.35, "b": 55, "c": 47.65, "op1": "*", "op2": "-", "result": 10861.6}
{"question": "Solve: (197 * 172) * 190", "answer": "The result of (197 * 172) * 190 is 6437960", "a": 197, "b": 172, "c": 190, "op1": "*", "op2": "*", "result": 6437960}
{"question": "Solve: (57.93 / 82) - 55", "answer": "The result of (57.93 / 82) - 55 is -54.29", "a": 57.93, "b": 82, "c": 55, "op1": "/", "op2": "-", "result": -54.29}
{"question": "Solve: (35.97 * 142) - 110", "answer": "The result of (35.97 * 142) - 110 is 4997.74", "a": 35.97, "b": 142, "c": 110, "op1": "*", "op2": "-", "result": 4997.74}
{"question": "Solve: (152 / 147) - 125", "answer": "The result of (152 / 147) - 125 is -123.97", "a": 152, "b": 147, "c": 125, "op1": "/", "op2": "-", "result": -123.97}
{"question": "Solve: (90 - 68) + 37.52", "answer": "The result of (90 - 68) + 37.52 is 59.52", "a": 90, "b": 68, "c": 37.52, "op1": "-", "op2": "+", "result": 59.52}
{"question": "Solve: (11.98 * 164.0) - 108.9", "answer": "The result of (11.98 * 164.0) - 108.9 is 1855.82", "a": 11.98, "b": 164.0, "c": 108.9, "op1": "*", "op2": "-", "result": 1855.82}
{"question": "Solve: (176.35 - 57.32) - 169", "answer": "The result of (176.35 - 57.32) - 169 is -49.97", "a": 176.35, "b": 57.32, "c": 169, "op1": "-", "op2": "-", "result": -49.97}
{"question": "Solve: (143 - 92.77) - 77", "answer": "The result of (143 - 92.77) - 77 is -26.77", "a": 143, "b": 92.77, "c": 77, "op1": "-", "op2": "-", "result": -26.77}
{"question": "Solve: (129.59 / 103) / 104.88", "answer": "The result of (129.59 / 103) / 104.88 is 0.01", "a": 129.59, "b": 103, "c": 104.88, "op1": "/", "op2": "/", "result": 0.01}
{"question": "Solve: (44 * 175) - 199", "answer": "The result of (44 * 175) - 199 is 7501", "a": 44, "b": 175, "c": 199, "op1": "*", "op2": "-", "result": 7501}
{"question": "Solve: (42 + 1.82) * 174", "answer": "The result of (42 + 1.82) * 174 is 7624.68", "a": 42, "b": 1.82, "c": 174, "op1": "+", "op2": "*", "result": 7624.68}
{"question": "Solve: (164 * 157) * 119", "answer": "The result of (164 * 157) * 119 is 3064012", "a": 164, "b": 157, "c": 119, "op1": "*", "op2": "*", "result": 3064012}
{"question": "Solve: (62 + 176) / 68", "answer": "The result of (62 + 176) / 68 is 3.5", "a": 62, "b": 176, "c": 68, "op1": "+", "op2": "/", "result": 3.5}
{"question": "Solve: (188 / 184) - 148", "answer": "The result of (188 / 184) - 148 is -146.98", "a": 188, "b": 184, "c": 148, "op1": "/", "op2": "-", "result": -146.98}
{"question": "Solve: (77 * 120.94) - 134", "answer": "The result of (77 * 120.94) - 134 is 9178.38", "a": 77, "b": 120.94, "c": 134, "op1": "*", "op2": "-", "result": 9178.38}
{"question": "Solve: (54.86 + 167) + 124", "answer": "The result of (54.86 + 167) + 124 is 345.86", "a": 54.86, "b": 167, "c": 124, "op1": "+", "op2": "+", "result": 345.86}
{"question": "Solve: (79.41 - 52) - 17", "answer": "The result of (79.41 - 52) - 17 is 10.41", "a": 79.41, "b": 52, "c": 17, "op1": "-", "op2": "-", "result": 10.41}
{"question": "Solve: (96 * 161) * 178.82", "answer": "The result of (96 * 161) * 178.82 is 2763841.92", "a": 96, "b": 161, "c": 178.82, "op1": "*", "op2": "*", "result": 2763841.92}
{"question": "Solve: (30 * 146.06) + 45", "answer": "The result of (30 * 146.06) + 45 is 4426.8", "a": 30, "b": 146.06, "c": 45, "op1": "*", "op2": "+", "result": 4426.8}
{"question": "Solve: (48 + 175) - 37", "answer": "The result of (48 + 175) - 37 is 186", "a": 48, "b": 175, "c": 37, "op1": "+", "op2": "-", "result": 186}
{"question": "Solve: (21.02 + 112.62) - 47.35", "answer": "The result of (21.02 + 112.62) - 47.35 is 86.29", "a": 21.02, "b": 112.62, "c": 47.35, "op1": "+", "op2": "-", "result": 86.29}
{"question": "Solve: (196 / 53) * 55.46", "answer": "The result of (196 / 53) * 55.46 is 205.1", "a": 196, "b": 53, "c": 55.46, "op1": "/", "op2": "*", "result": 205.1}
{"question": "Solve: (186 - 125.99) + 89", "answer": "The result of (186 - 125.99) + 89 is 149.01", "a": 186, "b": 125.99, "c": 89, "op1": "-", "op2": "+", "result": 149.01}
{"question": "Solve: (85.73 + 30.39) - 86.9", "answer": "The result of (85.73 + 30.39) - 86.9 is 29.22", "a": 85.73, "b": 30.39, "c": 86.9, "op1": "+", "op2": "-", "result": 29.22}
{"question": "Solve: (45 - 170.14) + 51.5", "answer": "The result of (45 - 170.14) + 51.5 is -73.64", "a": 45, "b": 170.14, "c": 51.5, "op1": "-", "op2": "+", "result": -73.64}
{"question": "Solve: (126.58 + 102) - 179", "answer": "The result of (126.58 + 102) - 179 is 49.58", "a": 126.58, "b": 102, "c": 179, "op1": "+", "op2": "-", "result": 49.58}
{"question": "Solve: (123 * 169) - 111", "answer": "The result of (123 * 169) - 111 is 20676", "a": 123, "b": 169, "c": 111, "op1": "*", "op2": "-", "result": 20676}
{"question": "Solve: (161 / 132.98) - 87", "answer": "The result of (161 / 132.98) - 87 is -85.79", "a": 161, "b": 132.98, "c": 87, "op1": "/", "op2": "-", "result": -85.79}
{"question": "Solve: (102 / 66.45) / 26.15", "answer": "The result of (102 / 66.45) / 26.15 is 0.06", "a": 102, "b": 66.45, "c": 26.15, "op1": "/", "op2": "/", "result": 0.06}
{"question": "Solve: (50 - 110) - 50", "answer": "The result of (50 - 110) - 50 is -110", "a": 50, "b": 110, "c": 50, "op1": "-", "op2": "-", "result": -110}
{"question": "Solve: (19 - 96) * 12.42", "answer": "The result of (19 - 96) * 12.42 is -956.34", "a": 19, "b": 96, "c": 12.42, "op1": "-", "op2": "*", "result": -956.34}
{"question": "Solve: (169 + 69) - 161", "answer": "The result of (169 + 69) - 161 is 77", "a": 169, "b": 69, "c": 161, "op1": "+", "op2": "-", "result": 77}
{"question": "Solve: (130.64 * 120) - 116", "answer": "The result of (130.64 * 120) - 116 is 15560.8", "a": 130.64, "b": 120, "c": 116, "op1": "*", "op2": "-", "result": 15560.8}
{"question": "Solve: (86 - 133) - 163.76", "answer": "The result of (86 - 133) - 163.76 is -210.76", "a": 86, "b": 133, "c": 163.76, "op1": "-", "op2": "-", "result": -210.76}
{"question": "Solve: (27 * 188) * 155.13", "answer": "The result of (27 * 188) * 155.13 is 787439.88", "a": 27, "b": 188, "c": 155.13, "op1": "*", "op2": "*", "result": 787439.88}
{"question": "Solve: (2.5 * 31) - 42", "answer": "The result of (2.5 * 31) - 42 is 35.5", "a": 2.5, "b": 31, "c": 42, "op1": "*", "op2": "-", "result": 35.5}
{"question": "Solve: (187.1 / 25.94) - 194", "answer": "The result of (187.1 / 25.94) - 194 is -186.79", "a": 187.1, "b": 25.94, "c": 194, "op1": "/", "op2": "-", "result": -186.79}
{"question": "Solve: (192.95 + 20) + 26", "answer": "The result of (192.95 + 20) + 26 is 238.95", "a": 192.95, "b": 20, "c": 26, "op1": "+", "op2": "+", "result": 238.95}
{"question": "Solve: (154 - 154) + 62.2", "answer": "The result of (154 - 154) + 62.2 is 62.2", "a": 154, "b": 154, "c": 62.2, "op1": "-", "op2": "+", "result": 62.2}
{"question": "Solve: (160 - 30) * 182", "answer": "The result of (160 - 30) * 182 is 23660", "a": 160, "b": 30, "c": 182, "op1": "-", "op2": "*", "result": 23660}
{"question": "Solve: (188 - 53.99) * 192", "answer": "The result of (188 - 53.99) * 192 is 25729.92", "a": 188, "b": 53.99, "c": 192, "op1": "-", "op2": "*", "result": 25729.92}
{"question": "Solve: (13 + 174.93) - 49", "answer": "The result of (13 + 174.93) - 49 is 138.93", "a": 13, "b": 174.93, "c": 49, "op1": "+", "op2": "-", "result": 138.93}
{"question": "Solve: (182 - 71) + 197.08", "answer": "The result of (182 - 71) + 197.08 is 308.08", "a": 182, "b": 71, "c": 197.08, "op1": "-", "op2": "+", "result": 308.08}
{"question": "Solve: (32.18 + 169.54) * 135", "answer": "The result of (32.18 + 169.54) * 135 is 27232.2", "a": 32.18, "b": 169.54, "c": 135, "op1": "+", "op2": "*", "result": 27232.2}
{"question": "Solve: (89.57 + 9) * 48.95", "answer": "The result of (89.57 + 9) * 48.95 is 4825.0", "a": 89.57, "b": 9, "c": 48.95, "op1": "+", "op2": "*", "result": 4825.0}
{"question": "Solve: (105 - 114) - 152", "answer": "The result of (105 - 114) - 152 is -161", "a": 105, "b": 114, "c": 152, "op1": "-", "op2": "-", "result": -161}
{"question": "Solve: (160 / 167) - 128", "answer": "The result of (160 / 167) - 128 is -127.04", "a": 160, "b": 167, "c": 128, "op1": "/", "op2": "-", "result": -127.04}
{"question": "Solve: (176 - 62) * 67", "answer": "The result of (176 - 62) * 67 is 7638", "a": 176, "b": 62, "c": 67, "op1": "-", "op2": "*", "result": 7638}
{"question": "Solve: (189 - 170) + 57", "answer": "The result of (189 - 170) + 57 is 76", "a": 189, "b": 170, "c": 57, "op1": "-", "op2": "+", "result": 76}
{"question": "Solve: (181.16 * 116) / 67", "answer": "The result of (181.16 * 116) / 67 is 313.65", "a": 181.16, "b": 116, "c": 67, "op1": "*", "op2": "/", "result": 313.65}
{"question": "Solve: (36 / 53) + 149", "answer": "The result of (36 / 53) + 149 is 149.68", "a": 36, "b": 53, "c": 149, "op1": "/", "op2": "+", "result": 149.68}
{"question": "Solve: (88.18 - 145) + 117", "answer": "The result of (88.18 - 145) + 117 is 60.18", "a": 88.18, "b": 145, "c": 117, "op1": "-", "op2": "+", "result": 60.18}
{"question": "Solve: (132.41 / 5) + 196", "answer": "The result of (132.41 / 5) + 196 is 222.48", "a": 132.41, "b": 5, "c": 196, "op1": "/", "op2": "+", "result": 222.48}
{"question": "Solve: (40.65 + 138) + 89.33", "answer": "The result of (40.65 + 138) + 89.33 is 267.98", "a": 40.65, "b": 138, "c": 89.33, "op1": "+", "op2": "+", "result": 267.98}
{"question": "Solve: (135 - 128) + 45", "answer": "The result of (135 - 128) + 45 is 52", "a": 135, "b": 128, "c": 45, "op1": "-", "op2": "+", "result": 52}
{"question": "Solve: (135 - 45) - 78.89", "answer": "The result of (135 - 45) - 78.89 is 11.11", "a": 135, "b": 45, "c": 78.89, "op1": "-", "op2": "-", "result": 11.11}
{"question": "Solve: (185 - 81.03) + 102.26", "answer": "The result of (185 - 81.03) + 102.26 is 206.23", "a": 185, "b": 81.03, "c": 102.26, "op1": "-", "op2": "+", "result": 206.23}
{"question": "Solve: (15.95 + 51) - 152", "answer": "The result of (15.95 + 51) - 152 is -85.05", "a": 15.95, "b": 51, "c": 152, "op1": "+", "op2": "-", "result": -85.05}
{"question": "Solve: (154 + 19) * 44.19", "answer": "The result of (154 + 19) * 44.19 is 7644.87", "a": 154, "b": 19, "c": 44.19, "op1": "+", "op2": "*", "result": 7644.87}
{"question": "Solve: (90 / 1) * 188", "answer": "The result of (90 / 1) * 188 is 16920.0", "a": 90, "b": 1, "c": 188, "op1": "/", "op2": "*", "result": 16920.0}
{"question": "Solve: (186.99 + 102.5) - 138", "answer": "The result of (186.99 + 102.5) - 138 is 151.49", "a": 186.99, "b": 102.5, "c": 138, "op1": "+", "op2": "-", "result": 151.49}
{"question": "Solve: (62 / 35.62) + 41", "answer": "The result of (62 / 35.62) + 41 is 42.74", "a": 62, "b": 35.62, "c": 41, "op1": "/", "op2": "+", "result": 42.74}
{"question": "Solve: (191.27 / 120) * 168", "answer": "The result of (191.27 / 120) * 168 is 267.78", "a": 191.27, "b": 120, "c": 168, "op1": "/", "op2": "*", "result": 267.78}
{"question": "Solve: (143 / 20.59) + 183", "answer": "The result of (143 / 20.59) + 183 is 189.95", "a": 143, "b": 20.59, "c": 183, "op1": "/", "op2": "+", "result": 189.95}
{"question": "Solve: (118 + 102) / 27", "answer": "The result of (118 + 102) / 27 is 8.15", "a": 118, "b": 102, "c": 27, "op1": "+", "op2": "/", "result": 8.15}
{"question": "Solve: (107 + 100) * 178", "answer": "The result of (107 + 100) * 178 is 36846", "a": 107, "b": 100, "c": 178, "op1": "+", "op2": "*", "result": 36846}
{"question": "Solve: (86 - 164.16) * 83.39", "answer": "The result of (86 - 164.16) * 83.39 is -6517.76", "a": 86, "b": 164.16, "c": 83.39, "op1": "-", "op2": "*", "result": -6517.76}
{"question": "Solve: (187 * 200) * 27", "answer": "The result of (187 * 200) * 27 is 1009800", "a": 187, "b": 200, "c": 27, "op1": "*", "op2": "*", "result": 1009800}
{"question": "Solve: (81 * 160) / 157", "answer": "The result of (81 * 160) / 157 is 82.55", "a": 81, "b": 160, "c": 157, "op1": "*", "op2": "/", "result": 82.55}
{"question": "Solve: (92 * 190) - 141", "answer": "The result of (92 * 190) - 141 is 17339", "a": 92, "b": 190, "c": 141, "op1": "*", "op2": "-", "result": 17339}
{"question": "Solve: (103 - 15.19) - 32.31", "answer": "The result of (103 - 15.19) - 32.31 is 55.5", "a": 103, "b": 15.19, "c": 32.31, "op1": "-", "op2": "-", "result": 55.5}
{"question": "Solve: (21.52 * 29.18) + 161.05", "answer": "The result of (21.52 * 29.18) + 161.05 is 789.0", "a": 21.52, "b": 29.18, "c": 161.05, "op1": "*", "op2": "+", "result": 789.0}
{"question": "Solve: (81 - 93) + 62", "answer": "The result of (81 - 93) + 62 is 50", "a": 81, "b": 93, "c": 62, "op1": "-", "op2": "+", "result": 50}
{"question": "Solve: (190 - 160.61) * 147", "answer": "The result of (190 - 160.61) * 147 is 4320.33", "a": 190, "b": 160.61, "c": 147, "op1": "-", "op2": "*", "result": 4320.33}
{"question": "Solve: (14.35 + 167) + 194", "answer": "The result of (14.35 + 167) + 194 is 375.35", "a": 14.35, "b": 167, "c": 194, "op1": "+", "op2": "+", "result": 375.35}
{"question": "Solve: (28 / 20) * 177.6", "answer": "The result of (28 / 20) * 177.6 is 248.64", "a": 28, "b": 20, "c": 177.6, "op1": "/", "op2": "*", "result": 248.64}
{"question": "Solve: (39.37 - 151.45) - 62", "answer": "The result of (39.37 - 151.45) - 62 is -174.08", "a": 39.37, "b": 151.45, "c": 62, "op1": "-", "op2": "-", "result": -174.08}
{"question": "Solve: (40 - 50) + 95", "answer": "The result of (40 - 50) + 95 is 85", "a": 40, "b": 50, "c": 95, "op1": "-", "op2": "+", "result": 85}
{"question": "Solve: (97.99 / 53.73) - 142.87", "answer": "The result of (97.99 / 53.73) - 142.87 is -141.05", "a": 97.99, "b": 53.73, "c": 142.87, "op1": "/", "op2": "-", "result": -141.05}
{"question": "Solve: (131 * 194) + 20.29", "answer": "The result of (131 * 194) + 20.29 is 25434.29", "a": 131, "b": 194, "c": 20.29, "op1": "*", "op2": "+", "result": 25434.29}
{"question": "Solve: (123 - 145.59) - 40", "answer": "The result of (123 - 145.59) - 40 is -62.59", "a": 123, "b": 145.59, "c": 40, "op1": "-", "op2": "-", "result": -62.59}
{"question": "Solve: (10 * 133) * 74.98", "answer": "The result of (10 * 133) * 74.98 is 99723.4", "a": 10, "b": 133, "c": 74.98, "op1": "*", "op2": "*", "result": 99723.4}
{"question": "Solve: (184 / 166) + 35", "answer": "The result of (184 / 166) + 35 is 36.11", "a": 184, "b": 166, "c": 35, "op1": "/", "op2": "+", "result": 36.11}
{"question": "Solve: (178 + 179.04) + 191", "answer": "The result of (178 + 179.04) + 191 is 548.04", "a": 178, "b": 179.04, "c": 191, "op1": "+", "op2": "+", "result": 548.04}
{"question": "Solve: (10 - 77.71) - 70", "answer": "The result of (10 - 77.71) - 70 is -137.71", "a": 10, "b": 77.71, "c": 70, "op1": "-", "op2": "-", "result": -137.71}
{"question": "Solve: (44.36 - 31) * 174", "answer": "The result of (44.36 - 31) * 174 is 2324.64", "a": 44.36, "b": 31, "c": 174, "op1": "-", "op2": "*", "result": 2324.64}
{"question": "Solve: (80 + 190) - 62.88", "answer": "The result of (80 + 190) - 62.88 is 207.12", "a": 80, "b": 190, "c": 62.88, "op1": "+", "op2": "-", "result": 207.12}
{"question": "Solve: (85 - 16) + 132.16", "answer": "The result of (85 - 16) + 132.16 is 201.16", "a": 85, "b": 16, "c": 132.16, "op1": "-", "op2": "+", "result": 201.16}
{"question": "Solve: (114 - 60.65) / 65.5", "answer": "The result of (114 - 60.65) / 65.5 is 0.81", "a": 114, "b": 60.65, "c": 65.5, "op1": "-", "op2": "/", "result": 0.81}
{"question": "Solve: (7 * 17) - 22", "answer": "The result of (7 * 17) - 22 is 97", "a": 7, "b": 17, "c": 22, "op1": "*", "op2": "-", "result": 97}
{"question": "Solve: (145 + 69) - 115.1", "answer": "The result of (145 + 69) - 115.1 is 98.9", "a": 145, "b": 69, "c": 115.1, "op1": "+", "op2": "-", "result": 98.9}
{"question": "Solve: (196 - 170) - 77", "answer": "The result of (196 - 170) - 77 is -51", "a": 196, "b": 170, "c": 77, "op1": "-", "op2": "-", "result": -51}
{"question": "Solve: (139 + 168) * 112.52", "answer": "The result of (139 + 168) * 112.52 is 34543.64", "a": 139, "b": 168, "c": 112.52, "op1": "+", "op2": "*", "result": 34543.64}
{"question": "Solve: (72 * 28) * 32.83", "answer": "The result of (72 * 28) * 32.83 is 66185.28", "a": 72, "b": 28, "c": 32.83, "op1": "*", "op2": "*", "result": 66185.28}
{"question": "Solve: (138.79 + 61) * 143.7", "answer": "The result of (138.79 + 61) * 143.7 is 28709.82", "a": 138.79, "b": 61, "c": 143.7, "op1": "+", "op2": "*", "result": 28709.82}
{"question": "Solve: (186 - 17) * 7.6", "answer": "The result of (186 - 17) * 7.6 is 1284.4", "a": 186, "b": 17, "c": 7.6, "op1": "-", "op2": "*", "result": 1284.4}
{"question": "Solve: (194 - 141.06) * 34.47", "answer": "The result of (194 - 141.06) * 34.47 is 1824.84", "a": 194, "b": 141.06, "c": 34.47, "op1": "-", "op2": "*", "result": 1824.84}
{"question": "Solve: (10 * 167) / 85", "answer": "The result of (10 * 167) / 85 is 19.65", "a": 10, "b": 167, "c": 85, "op1": "*", "op2": "/", "result": 19.65}
{"question": "Solve: (7 * 32) + 15", "answer": "The result of (7 * 32) + 15 is 239", "a": 7, "b": 32, "c": 15, "op1": "*", "op2": "+", "result": 239}
{"question": "Solve: (110 - 129) + 166", "answer": "The result of (110 - 129) + 166 is 147", "a": 110, "b": 129, "c": 166, "op1": "-", "op2": "+", "result": 147}
{"question": "Solve: (67 + 4.52) - 13.37", "answer": "The result of (67 + 4.52) - 13.37 is 58.15", "a": 67, "b": 4.52, "c": 13.37, "op1": "+", "op2": "-", "result": 58.15}
{"question": "Solve: (135 + 4.95) - 42", "answer": "The result of (135 + 4.95) - 42 is 97.95", "a": 135, "b": 4.95, "c": 42, "op1": "+", "op2": "-", "result": 97.95}
{"question": "Solve: (115.44 * 116.33) - 190", "answer": "The result of (115.44 * 116.33) - 190 is 13239.14", "a": 115.44, "b": 116.33, "c": 190, "op1": "*", "op2": "-", "result": 13239.14}
{"question": "Solve: (139 - 116) * 15", "answer": "The result of (139 - 116) * 15 is 345", "a": 139, "b": 116, "c": 15, "op1": "-", "op2": "*", "result": 345}
{"question": "Solve: (75 * 8) + 93", "answer": "The result of (75 * 8) + 93 is 693", "a": 75, "b": 8, "c": 93, "op1": "*", "op2": "+", "result": 693}
{"question": "Solve: (189 - 56) - 192", "answer": "The result of (189 - 56) - 192 is -59", "a": 189, "b": 56, "c": 192, "op1": "-", "op2": "-", "result": -59}
{"question": "Solve: (107 + 158.53) * 47.85", "answer": "The result of (107 + 158.53) * 47.85 is 12705.61", "a": 107, "b": 158.53, "c": 47.85, "op1": "+", "op2": "*", "result": 12705.61}
{"question": "Solve: (59 * 143) * 106", "answer": "The result of (59 * 143) * 106 is 894322", "a": 59, "b": 143, "c": 106, "op1": "*", "op2": "*", "result": 894322}
{"question": "Solve: (117 + 163) + 179.46", "answer": "The result of (117 + 163) + 179.46 is 459.46", "a": 117, "b": 163, "c": 179.46, "op1": "+", "op2": "+", "result": 459.46}
{"question": "Solve: (59.6 * 161) * 86", "answer": "The result of (59.6 * 161) * 86 is 825221.6", "a": 59.6, "b": 161, "c": 86, "op1": "*", "op2": "*", "result": 825221.6}
{"question": "Solve: (193.88 - 26.74) / 120", "answer": "The result of (193.88 - 26.74) / 120 is 1.39", "a": 193.88, "b": 26.74, "c": 120, "op1": "-", "op2": "/", "result": 1.39}
{"question": "Solve: (89 * 4) * 184", "answer": "The result of (89 * 4) * 184 is 65504", "a": 89, "b": 4, "c": 184, "op1": "*", "op2": "*", "result": 65504}
{"question": "Solve: (48 * 117) - 159", "answer": "The result of (48 * 117) - 159 is 5457", "a": 48, "b": 117, "c": 159, "op1": "*", "op2": "-", "result": 5457}
{"question": "Solve: (146 - 188.47) - 83.66", "answer": "The result of (146 - 188.47) - 83.66 is -126.13", "a": 146, "b": 188.47, "c": 83.66, "op1": "-", "op2": "-", "result": -126.13}
{"question": "Solve: (45 + 44.75) - 128", "answer": "The result of (45 + 44.75) - 128 is -38.25", "a": 45, "b": 44.75, "c": 128, "op1": "+", "op2": "-", "result": -38.25}
{"question": "Solve: (139 * 112) - 44", "answer": "The result of (139 * 112) - 44 is 15524", "a": 139, "b": 112, "c": 44, "op1": "*", "op2": "-", "result": 15524}
{"question": "Solve: (121.44 + 117.29) - 2", "answer": "The result of (121.44 + 117.29) - 2 is 236.73", "a": 121.44, "b": 117.29, "c": 2, "op1": "+", "op2": "-", "result": 236.73}
{"question": "Solve: (41.31 * 65.65) / 20", "answer": "The result of (41.31 * 65.65) / 20 is 135.6", "a": 41.31, "b": 65.65, "c": 20, "op1": "*", "op2": "/", "result": 135.6}
{"question": "Solve: (176.98 - 64.41) + 190.63", "answer": "The result of (176.98 - 64.41) + 190.63 is 303.2", "a": 176.98, "b": 64.41, "c": 190.63, "op1": "-", "op2": "+", "result": 303.2}
{"question": "Solve: (71 * 34) * 184.62", "answer": "The result of (71 * 34) * 184.62 is 445672.68", "a": 71, "b": 34, "c": 184.62, "op1": "*", "op2": "*", "result": 445672.68}
{"question": "Solve: (157 - 172) - 174", "answer": "The result of (157 - 172) - 174 is -189", "a": 157, "b": 172, "c": 174, "op1": "-", "op2": "-", "result": -189}
{"question": "Solve: (145 * 66) / 97", "answer": "The result of (145 * 66) / 97 is 98.66", "a": 145, "b": 66, "c": 97, "op1": "*", "op2": "/", "result": 98.66}
{"question": "Solve: (90.77 / 80) + 107", "answer": "The result of (90.77 / 80) + 107 is 108.13", "a": 90.77, "b": 80, "c": 107, "op1": "/", "op2": "+", "result": 108.13}
{"question": "Solve: (104.52 - 159) - 63", "answer": "The result of (104.52 - 159) - 63 is -117.48", "a": 104.52, "b": 159, "c": 63, "op1": "-", "op2": "-", "result": -117.48}
{"question": "Solve: (157.74 - 148.08) / 177", "answer": "The result of (157.74 - 148.08) / 177 is 0.05", "a": 157.74, "b": 148.08, "c": 177, "op1": "-", "op2": "/", "result": 0.05}
{"question": "Solve: (78.81 - 146) * 72.5", "answer": "The result of (78.81 - 146) * 72.5 is -4871.27", "a": 78.81, "b": 146, "c": 72.5, "op1": "-", "op2": "*", "result": -4871.27}
{"question": "Solve: (168 - 80.98) * 171.9", "answer": "The result of (168 - 80.98) * 171.9 is 14958.74", "a": 168, "b": 80.98, "c": 171.9, "op1": "-", "op2": "*", "result": 14958.74}
{"question": "Solve: (48 + 119.21) - 181.49", "answer": "The result of (48 + 119.21) - 181.49 is -14.28", "a": 48, "b": 119.21, "c": 181.49, "op1": "+", "op2": "-", "result": -14.28}
{"question": "Solve: (57 * 42.67) * 148.48", "answer": "The result of (57 * 42.67) * 148.48 is 361131.57", "a": 57, "b": 42.67, "c": 148.48, "op1": "*", "op2": "*", "result": 361131.57}
{"question": "Solve: (29 / 182) - 113.04", "answer": "The result of (29 / 182) - 113.04 is -112.88", "a": 29, "b": 182, "c": 113.04, "op1": "/", "op2": "-", "result": -112.88}
{"question": "Solve: (178 + 41) * 184", "answer": "The result of (178 + 41) * 184 is 40296", "a": 178, "b": 41, "c": 184, "op1": "+", "op2": "*", "result": 40296}
{"question": "Solve: (123.69 * 34) + 97", "answer": "The result of (123.69 * 34) + 97 is 4302.46", "a": 123.69, "b": 34, "c": 97, "op1": "*", "op2": "+", "result": 4302.46}
{"question": "Solve: (145 / 63) / 82.76", "answer": "The result of (145 / 63) / 82.76 is 0.03", "a": 145, "b": 63, "c": 82.76, "op1": "/", "op2": "/", "result": 0.03}
{"question": "Solve: (187 - 26.15) - 163", "answer": "The result of (187 - 26.15) - 163 is -2.15", "a": 187, "b": 26.15, "c": 163, "op1": "-", "op2": "-", "result": -2.15}
{"question": "Solve: (2 * 66) + 3", "answer": "The result of (2 * 66) + 3 is 135", "a": 2, "b": 66, "c": 3, "op1": "*", "op2": "+", "result": 135}
{"question": "Solve: (177 - 132) + 145", "answer": "The result of (177 - 132) + 145 is 190", "a": 177, "b": 132, "c": 145, "op1": "-", "op2": "+", "result": 190}
{"question": "Solve: (42 / 13) + 100", "answer": "The result of (42 / 13) + 100 is 103.23", "a": 42, "b": 13, "c": 100, "op1": "/", "op2": "+", "result": 103.23}
{"question": "Solve: (184 - 148) - 57", "answer": "The result of (184 - 148) - 57 is -21", "a": 184, "b": 148, "c": 57, "op1": "-", "op2": "-", "result": -21}
{"question": "Solve: (77.06 * 9) + 106", "answer": "The result of (77.06 * 9) + 106 is 799.54", "a": 77.06, "b": 9, "c": 106, "op1": "*", "op2": "+", "result": 799.54}
{"question": "Solve: (120 + 155) + 182", "answer": "The result of (120 + 155) + 182 is 457", "a": 120, "b": 155, "c": 182, "op1": "+", "op2": "+", "result": 457}
{"question": "Solve: (106 + 122) / 38", "answer": "The result of (106 + 122) / 38 is 6.0", "a": 106, "b": 122, "c": 38, "op1": "+", "op2": "/", "result": 6.0}
{"question": "Solve: (50 / 146.54) * 121.97", "answer": "The result of (50 / 146.54) * 121.97 is 41.62", "a": 50, "b": 146.54, "c": 121.97, "op1": "/", "op2": "*", "result": 41.62}
{"question": "Solve: (66.09 + 18) * 24.26", "answer": "The result of (66.09 + 18) * 24.26 is 2040.02", "a": 66.09, "b": 18, "c": 24.26, "op1": "+", "op2": "*", "result": 2040.02}
{"question": "Solve: (29 - 36.5) - 105", "answer": "The result of (29 - 36.5) - 105 is -112.5", "a": 29, "b": 36.5, "c": 105, "op1": "-", "op2": "-", "result": -112.5}
{"question": "Solve: (182.51 + 40) + 63", "answer": "The result of (182.51 + 40) + 63 is 285.51", "a": 182.51, "b": 40, "c": 63, "op1": "+", "op2": "+", "result": 285.51}
{"question": "Solve: (86 / 137) + 12", "answer": "The result of (86 / 137) + 12 is 12.63", "a": 86, "b": 137, "c": 12, "op1": "/", "op2": "+", "result": 12.63}
{"question": "Solve: (114 / 197.3) / 170", "answer": "The result of (114 / 197.3) / 170 is 0.0", "a": 114, "b": 197.3, "c": 170, "op1": "/", "op2": "/", "result": 0.0}
{"question": "Solve: (88 * 93) + 149", "answer": "The result of (88 * 93) + 149 is 8333", "a": 88, "b": 93, "c": 149, "op1": "*", "op2": "+", "result": 8333}
{"question": "Solve: (135 * 127.01) - 91", "answer": "The result of (135 * 127.01) - 91 is 17055.35", "a": 135, "b": 127.01, "c": 91, "op1": "*", "op2": "-", "result": 17055.35}
{"question": "Solve: (156.75 + 7) / 131", "answer": "The result of (156.75 + 7) / 131 is 1.25", "a": 156.75, "b": 7, "c": 131, "op1": "+", "op2": "/", "result": 1.25}
{"question": "Solve: (84 + 144.27) - 5.19", "answer": "The result of (84 + 144.27) - 5.19 is 223.08", "a": 84, "b": 144.27, "c": 5.19, "op1": "+", "op2": "-", "result": 223.08}
{"question": "Solve: (57 + 80) + 77", "answer": "The result of (57 + 80) + 77 is 214", "a": 57, "b": 80, "c": 77, "op1": "+", "op2": "+", "result": 214}
{"question": "Solve: (90 - 48) * 72.33", "answer": "The result of (90 - 48) * 72.33 is 3037.86", "a": 90, "b": 48, "c": 72.33, "op1": "-", "op2": "*", "result": 3037.86}
{"question": "Solve: (128.91 / 139) / 193", "answer": "The result of (128.91 / 139) / 193 is 0.0", "a": 128.91, "b": 139, "c": 193, "op1": "/", "op2": "/", "result": 0.0}
{"question": "Solve: (13 * 165) / 78", "answer": "The result of (13 * 165) / 78 is 27.5", "a": 13, "b": 165, "c": 78, "op1": "*", "op2": "/", "result": 27.5}
{"question": "Solve: (64 - 141) + 125", "answer": "The result of (64 - 141) + 125 is 48", "a": 64, "b": 141, "c": 125, "op1": "-", "op2": "+", "result": 48}
{"question": "Solve: (69 * 6) - 118", "answer": "The result of (69 * 6) - 118 is 296", "a": 69, "b": 6, "c": 118, "op1": "*", "op2": "-", "result": 296}
{"question": "Solve: (93 - 135) - 28", "answer": "The result of (93 - 135) - 28 is -70", "a": 93, "b": 135, "c": 28, "op1": "-", "op2": "-", "result": -70}
{"question": "Solve: (171 + 22) - 50.21", "answer": "The result of (171 + 22) - 50.21 is 142.79", "a": 171, "b": 22, "c": 50.21, "op1": "+", "op2": "-", "result": 142.79}
{"question": "Solve: (166 + 163) - 22", "answer": "The result of (166 + 163) - 22 is 307", "a": 166, "b": 163, "c": 22, "op1": "+", "op2": "-", "result": 307}
{"question": "Solve: (43 - 178) * 113", "answer": "The result of (43 - 178) * 113 is -15255", "a": 43, "b": 178, "c": 113, "op1": "-", "op2": "*", "result": -15255}
{"question": "Solve: (155.98 - 4.87) * 105", "answer": "The result of (155.98 - 4.87) * 105 is 15866.55", "a": 155.98, "b": 4.87, "c": 105, "op1": "-", "op2": "*", "result": 15866.55}
{"question": "Solve: (166.6 - 13.26) + 84", "answer": "The result of (166.6 - 13.26) + 84 is 237.34", "a": 166.6, "b": 13.26, "c": 84, "op1": "-", "op2": "+", "result": 237.34}
{"question": "Solve: (137 + 91) * 108", "answer": "The result of (137 + 91) * 108 is 24624", "a": 137, "b": 91, "c": 108, "op1": "+", "op2": "*", "result": 24624}
{"question": "Solve: (6.57 - 68) - 89", "answer": "The result of (6.57 - 68) - 89 is -150.43", "a": 6.57, "b": 68, "c": 89, "op1": "-", "op2": "-", "result": -150.43}
{"question": "Solve: (108 + 10) + 114", "answer": "The result of (108 + 10) + 114 is 232", "a": 108, "b": 10, "c": 114, "op1": "+", "op2": "+", "result": 232}
{"question": "Solve: (74 / 61) * 139.92", "answer": "The result of (74 / 61) * 139.92 is 169.74", "a": 74, "b": 61, "c": 139.92, "op1": "/", "op2": "*", "result": 169.74}
{"question": "Solve: (175 / 58.69) - 193", "answer": "The result of (175 / 58.69) - 193 is -190.02", "a": 175, "b": 58.69, "c": 193, "op1": "/", "op2": "-", "result": -190.02}
{"question": "Solve: (156.2 - 117) + 185.82", "answer": "The result of (156.2 - 117) + 185.82 is 225.02", "a": 156.2, "b": 117, "c": 185.82, "op1": "-", "op2": "+", "result": 225.02}
{"question": "Solve: (131 + 157) + 16.26", "answer": "The result of (131 + 157) + 16.26 is 304.26", "a": 131, "b": 157, "c": 16.26, "op1": "+", "op2": "+", "result": 304.26}
{"question": "Solve: (193.39 / 63) / 148", "answer": "The result of (193.39 / 63) / 148 is 0.02", "a": 193.39, "b": 63, "c": 148, "op1": "/", "op2": "/", "result": 0.02}
{"question": "Solve: (138.2 / 40.93) * 88", "answer": "The result of (138.2 / 40.93) * 88 is 297.13", "a": 138.2, "b": 40.93, "c": 88, "op1": "/", "op2": "*", "result": 297.13}
{"question": "Solve: (179.56 + 21) * 133", "answer": "The result of (179.56 + 21) * 133 is 26674.48", "a": 179.56, "b": 21, "c": 133, "op1": "+", "op2": "*", "result": 26674.48}
{"question": "Solve: (99 * 114) * 127", "answer": "The result of (99 * 114) * 127 is 1433322", "a": 99, "b": 114, "c": 127, "op1": "*", "op2": "*", "result": 1433322}
{"question": "Solve: (118 * 102) - 145.0", "answer": "The result of (118 * 102) - 145.0 is 11891.0", "a": 118, "b": 102, "c": 145.0, "op1": "*", "op2": "-", "result": 11891.0}
{"question": "Solve: (53 + 88) * 22", "answer": "The result of (53 + 88) * 22 is 3102", "a": 53, "b": 88, "c": 22, "op1": "+", "op2": "*", "result": 3102}
{"question": "Solve: (19 * 22) * 30", "answer": "The result of (19 * 22) * 30 is 12540", "a": 19, "b": 22, "c": 30, "op1": "*", "op2": "*", "result": 12540}
{"question": "Solve: (143 / 123) / 44.95", "answer": "The result of (143 / 123) / 44.95 is 0.03", "a": 143, "b": 123, "c": 44.95, "op1": "/", "op2": "/", "result": 0.03}
{"question": "Solve: (124.29 * 71) / 18", "answer": "The result of (124.29 * 71) / 18 is 490.25", "a": 124.29, "b": 71, "c": 18, "op1": "*", "op2": "/", "result": 490.25}
{"question": "Solve: (182 * 83) + 75.25", "answer": "The result of (182 * 83) + 75.25 is 15181.25", "a": 182, "b": 83, "c": 75.25, "op1": "*", "op2": "+", "result": 15181.25}
{"question": "Solve: (15.26 + 162.71) + 190.13", "answer": "The result of (15.26 + 162.71) + 190.13 is 368.1", "a": 15.26, "b": 162.71, "c": 190.13, "op1": "+", "op2": "+", "result": 368.1}
{"question": "Solve: (100.83 / 160) - 193.1", "answer": "The result of (100.83 / 160) - 193.1 is -192.47", "a": 100.83, "b": 160, "c": 193.1, "op1": "/", "op2": "-", "result": -192.47}
{"question": "Solve: (52 - 51) + 182.19", "answer": "The result of (52 - 51) + 182.19 is 183.19", "a": 52, "b": 51, "c": 182.19, "op1": "-", "op2": "+", "result": 183.19}
{"question": "Solve: (35 - 151) - 9", "answer": "The result of (35 - 151) - 9 is -125", "a": 35, "b": 151, "c": 9, "op1": "-", "op2": "-", "result": -125}
{"question": "Solve: (175 * 39.99) * 83", "answer": "The result of (175 * 39.99) * 83 is 580854.75", "a": 175, "b": 39.99, "c": 83, "op1": "*", "op2": "*", "result": 580854.75}
{"question": "Solve: (23 + 11) + 80.48", "answer": "The result of (23 + 11) + 80.48 is 114.48", "a": 23, "b": 11, "c": 80.48, "op1": "+", "op2": "+", "result": 114.48}
{"question": "Solve: (67 / 108) + 82", "answer": "The result of (67 / 108) + 82 is 82.62", "a": 67, "b": 108, "c": 82, "op1": "/", "op2": "+", "result": 82.62}
{"question": "Solve: (86 + 183) - 185", "answer": "The result of (86 + 183) - 185 is 84", "a": 86, "b": 183, "c": 185, "op1": "+", "op2": "-", "result": 84}
{"question": "Solve: (22.53 + 8.05) * 161.78", "answer": "The result of (22.53 + 8.05) * 161.78 is 4947.23", "a": 22.53, "b": 8.05, "c": 161.78, "op1": "+", "op2": "*", "result": 4947.23}
{"question": "Solve: (90 / 52.94) / 162.01", "answer": "The result of (90 / 52.94) / 162.01 is 0.01", "a": 90, "b": 52.94, "c": 162.01, "op1": "/", "op2": "/", "result": 0.01}
{"question": "Solve: (41 + 97) / 35", "answer": "The result of (41 + 97) / 35 is 3.94", "a": 41, "b": 97, "c": 35, "op1": "+", "op2": "/", "result": 3.94}
{"question": "Solve: (132 * 103.08) / 123", "answer": "The result of (132 * 103.08) / 123 is 110.62", "a": 132, "b": 103.08, "c": 123, "op1": "*", "op2": "/", "result": 110.62}
{"question": "Solve: (142 - 132.95) * 22", "answer": "The result of (142 - 132.95) * 22 is 199.1", "a": 142, "b": 132.95, "c": 22, "op1": "-", "op2": "*", "result": 199.1}
{"question": "Solve: (28.38 - 197) + 5", "answer": "The result of (28.38 - 197) + 5 is -163.62", "a": 28.38, "b": 197, "c": 5, "op1": "-", "op2": "+", "result": -163.62}
{"question": "Solve: (136.89 + 29) + 166", "answer": "The result of (136.89 + 29) + 166 is 331.89", "a": 136.89, "b": 29, "c": 166, "op1": "+", "op2": "+", "result": 331.89}
{"question": "Solve: (111 * 22) + 59", "answer": "The result of (111 * 22) + 59 is 2501", "a": 111, "b": 22, "c": 59, "op1": "*", "op2": "+", "result": 2501}
{"question": "Solve: (140 + 174) - 167.89", "answer": "The result of (140 + 174) - 167.89 is 146.11", "a": 140, "b": 174, "c": 167.89, "op1": "+", "op2": "-", "result": 146.11}
{"question": "Solve: (149 * 130) - 41", "answer": "The result of (149 * 130) - 41 is 19329", "a": 149, "b": 130, "c": 41, "op1": "*", "op2": "-", "result": 19329}
{"question": "Solve: (111 - 88) / 99.23", "answer": "The result of (111 - 88) / 99.23 is 0.23", "a": 111, "b": 88, "c": 99.23, "op1": "-", "op2": "/", "result": 0.23}
{"question": "Solve: (33.29 + 136.03) - 58", "answer": "The result of (33.29 + 136.03) - 58 is 111.32", "a": 33.29, "b": 136.03, "c": 58, "op1": "+", "op2": "-", "result": 111.32}
{"question": "Solve: (62 * 2) + 177.75", "answer": "The result of (62 * 2) + 177.75 is 301.75", "a": 62, "b": 2, "c": 177.75, "op1": "*", "op2": "+", "result": 301.75}
{"question": "Solve: (8.28 * 173) + 128", "answer": "The result of (8.28 * 173) + 128 is 1560.44", "a": 8.28, "b": 173, "c": 128, "op1": "*", "op2": "+", "result": 1560.44}
{"question": "Solve: (58 + 127.56) - 33.63", "answer": "The result of (58 + 127.56) - 33.63 is 151.93", "a": 58, "b": 127.56, "c": 33.63, "op1": "+", "op2": "-", "result": 151.93}
{"question": "Solve: (87 + 148.5) + 83", "answer": "The result of (87 + 148.5) + 83 is 318.5", "a": 87, "b": 148.5, "c": 83, "op1": "+", "op2": "+", "result": 318.5}
{"question": "Solve: (29 / 16) + 78.94", "answer": "The result of (29 / 16) + 78.94 is 80.75", "a": 29, "b": 16, "c": 78.94, "op1": "/", "op2": "+", "result": 80.75}
{"question": "Solve: (37 * 114.04) + 41.91", "answer": "The result of (37 * 114.04) + 41.91 is 4261.39", "a": 37, "b": 114.04, "c": 41.91, "op1": "*", "op2": "+", "result": 4261.39}
{"question": "Solve: (103.09 + 58) - 103", "answer": "The result of (103.09 + 58) - 103 is 58.09", "a": 103.09, "b": 58, "c": 103, "op1": "+", "op2": "-", "result": 58.09}
{"question": "Solve: (86 + 176.23) + 14", "answer": "The result of (86 + 176.23) + 14 is 276.23", "a": 86, "b": 176.23, "c": 14, "op1": "+", "op2": "+", "result": 276.23}
{"question": "Solve: (39 + 10) + 155", "answer": "The result of (39 + 10) + 155 is 204", "a": 39, "b": 10, "c": 155, "op1": "+", "op2": "+", "result": 204}
{"question": "Solve: (10 / 71) + 65.67", "answer": "The result of (10 / 71) + 65.67 is 65.81", "a": 10, "b": 71, "c": 65.67, "op1": "/", "op2": "+", "result": 65.81}
{"question": "Solve: (182 - 5) + 130", "answer": "The result of (182 - 5) + 130 is 307", "a": 182, "b": 5, "c": 130, "op1": "-", "op2": "+", "result": 307}
{"question": "Solve: (187 + 105) + 188.88", "answer": "The result of (187 + 105) + 188.88 is 480.88", "a": 187, "b": 105, "c": 188.88, "op1": "+", "op2": "+", "result": 480.88}
{"question": "Solve: (194 / 133) - 13", "answer": "The result of (194 / 133) - 13 is -11.54", "a": 194, "b": 133, "c": 13, "op1": "/", "op2": "-", "result": -11.54}
{"question": "Solve: (152.42 + 121) / 85", "answer": "The result of (152.42 + 121) / 85 is 3.22", "a": 152.42, "b": 121, "c": 85, "op1": "+", "op2": "/", "result": 3.22}
{"question": "Solve: (138 / 59) - 166", "answer": "The result of (138 / 59) - 166 is -163.66", "a": 138, "b": 59, "c": 166, "op1": "/", "op2": "-", "result": -163.66}
{"question": "Solve: (34.11 - 74.91) * 104", "answer": "The result of (34.11 - 74.91) * 104 is -4243.2", "a": 34.11, "b": 74.91, "c": 104, "op1": "-", "op2": "*", "result": -4243.2}
{"question": "Solve: (157 + 166) * 153", "answer": "The result of (157 + 166) * 153 is 49419", "a": 157, "b": 166, "c": 153, "op1": "+", "op2": "*", "result": 49419}
{"question": "Solve: (122 / 77) + 162", "answer": "The result of (122 / 77) + 162 is 163.58", "a": 122, "b": 77, "c": 162, "op1": "/", "op2": "+", "result": 163.58}
{"question": "Solve: (126.8 * 46) * 85.02", "answer": "The result of (126.8 * 46) * 85.02 is 495904.66", "a": 126.8, "b": 46, "c": 85.02, "op1": "*", "op2": "*", "result": 495904.66}
{"question": "Solve: (109 - 182.36) - 34", "answer": "The result of (109 - 182.36) - 34 is -107.36", "a": 109, "b": 182.36, "c": 34, "op1": "-", "op2": "-", "result": -107.36}
{"question": "Solve: (171.92 - 153.12) - 15", "answer": "The result of (171.92 - 153.12) - 15 is 3.8", "a": 171.92, "b": 153.12, "c": 15, "op1": "-", "op2": "-", "result": 3.8}
{"question": "Solve: (53.32 * 5) * 99.55", "answer": "The result of (53.32 * 5) * 99.55 is 26540.03", "a": 53.32, "b": 5, "c": 99.55, "op1": "*", "op2": "*", "result": 26540.03}
{"question": "Solve: (191 * 155) * 110", "answer": "The result of (191 * 155) * 110 is 3256550", "a": 191, "b": 155, "c": 110, "op1": "*", "op2": "*", "result": 3256550}
{"question": "Solve: (117.82 + 195) + 169", "answer": "The result of (117.82 + 195) + 169 is 481.82", "a": 117.82, "b": 195, "c": 169, "op1": "+", "op2": "+", "result": 481.82}
{"question": "Solve: (73.97 * 17) + 25", "answer": "The result of (73.97 * 17) + 25 is 1282.49", "a": 73.97, "b": 17, "c": 25, "op1": "*", "op2": "+", "result": 1282.49}
{"question": "Solve: (31.84 + 71) * 54.21", "answer": "The result of (31.84 + 71) * 54.21 is 5574.96", "a": 31.84, "b": 71, "c": 54.21, "op1": "+", "op2": "*", "result": 5574.96}
{"question": "Solve: (89 * 24) + 13", "answer": "The result of (89 * 24) + 13 is 2149", "a": 89, "b": 24, "c": 13, "op1": "*", "op2": "+", "result": 2149}
{"question": "Solve: (153 * 18) - 97.08", "answer": "The result of (153 * 18) - 97.08 is 2656.92", "a": 153, "b": 18, "c": 97.08, "op1": "*", "op2": "-", "result": 2656.92}
{"question": "Solve: (85.42 / 200) + 36", "answer": "The result of (85.42 / 200) + 36 is 36.43", "a": 85.42, "b": 200, "c": 36, "op1": "/", "op2": "+", "result": 36.43}
{"question": "Solve: (188 + 52) - 34.58", "answer": "The result of (188 + 52) - 34.58 is 205.42", "a": 188, "b": 52, "c": 34.58, "op1": "+", "op2": "-", "result": 205.42}
{"question": "Solve: (178.96 + 158.44) * 146", "answer": "The result of (178.96 + 158.44) * 146 is 49260.4", "a": 178.96, "b": 158.44, "c": 146, "op1": "+", "op2": "*", "result": 49260.4}
{"question": "Solve: (99 - 6) * 15", "answer": "The result of (99 - 6) * 15 is 1395", "a": 99, "b": 6, "c": 15, "op1": "-", "op2": "*", "result": 1395}
{"question": "Solve: (146 + 83) - 161", "answer": "The result of (146 + 83) - 161 is 68", "a": 146, "b": 83, "c": 161, "op1": "+", "op2": "-", "result": 68}
{"question": "Solve: (160.71 - 48) * 11", "answer": "The result of (160.71 - 48) * 11 is 1239.81", "a": 160.71, "b": 48, "c": 11, "op1": "-", "op2": "*", "result": 1239.81}
{"question": "Solve: (139 * 145) + 112", "answer": "The result of (139 * 145) + 112 is 20267", "a": 139, "b": 145, "c": 112, "op1": "*", "op2": "+", "result": 20267}
{"question": "Solve: (172.81 + 78) - 182", "answer": "The result of (172.81 + 78) - 182 is 68.81", "a": 172.81, "b": 78, "c": 182, "op1": "+", "op2": "-", "result": 68.81}
{"question": "Solve: (117 * 76) - 177", "answer": "The result of (117 * 76) - 177 is 8715", "a": 117, "b": 76, "c": 177, "op1": "*", "op2": "-", "result": 8715}
{"question": "Solve: (168.93 * 114.51) + 110.71", "answer": "The result of (168.93 * 114.51) + 110.71 is 19454.88", "a": 168.93, "b": 114.51, "c": 110.71, "op1": "*", "op2": "+", "result": 19454.88}
{"question": "Solve: (161 + 76) / 119.04", "answer": "The result of (161 + 76) / 119.04 is 1.99", "a": 161, "b": 76, "c": 119.04, "op1": "+", "op2": "/", "result": 1.99}
{"question": "Solve: (48 / 122) + 36", "answer": "The result of (48 / 122) + 36 is 36.39", "a": 48, "b": 122, "c": 36, "op1": "/", "op2": "+", "result": 36.39}
{"question": "Solve: (177 - 166.28) * 66", "answer": "The result of (177 - 166.28) * 66 is 707.52", "a": 177, "b": 166.28, "c": 66, "op1": "-", "op2": "*", "result": 707.52}
{"question": "Solve: (121 + 27) / 126.5", "answer": "The result of (121 + 27) / 126.5 is 1.17", "a": 121, "b": 27, "c": 126.5, "op1": "+", "op2": "/", "result": 1.17}
{"question": "Solve: (118 + 26) - 154", "answer": "The result of (118 + 26) - 154 is -10", "a": 118, "b": 26, "c": 154, "op1": "+", "op2": "-", "result": -10}
{"question": "Solve: (19 * 80) + 174", "answer": "The result of (19 * 80) + 174 is 1694", "a": 19, "b": 80, "c": 174, "op1": "*", "op2": "+", "result": 1694}
{"question": "Solve: (119 - 84) * 77", "answer": "The result of (119 - 84) * 77 is 2695", "a": 119, "b": 84, "c": 77, "op1": "-", "op2": "*", "result": 2695}
{"question": "Solve: (162 / 187) + 9.91", "answer": "The result of (162 / 187) + 9.91 is 10.78", "a": 162, "b": 187, "c": 9.91, "op1": "/", "op2": "+", "result": 10.78}
{"question": "Solve: (180.01 + 140) - 70", "answer": "The result of (180.01 + 140) - 70 is 250.01", "a": 180.01, "b": 140, "c": 70, "op1": "+", "op2": "-", "result": 250.01}
{"question": "Solve: (165 / 20.02) + 68.21", "answer": "The result of (165 / 20.02) + 68.21 is 76.45", "a": 165, "b": 20.02, "c": 68.21, "op1": "/", "op2": "+", "result": 76.45}
{"question": "Solve: (118 / 148) + 57.1", "answer": "The result of (118 / 148) + 57.1 is 57.9", "a": 118, "b": 148, "c": 57.1, "op1": "/", "op2": "+", "result": 57.9}
{"question": "Solve: (90 - 196.35) - 67", "answer": "The result of (90 - 196.35) - 67 is -173.35", "a": 90, "b": 196.35, "c": 67, "op1": "-", "op2": "-", "result": -173.35}
{"question": "Solve: (21.88 / 59) - 181", "answer": "The result of (21.88 / 59) - 181 is -180.63", "a": 21.88, "b": 59, "c": 181, "op1": "/", "op2": "-", "result": -180.63}
{"question": "Solve: (173 * 177.7) + 142", "answer": "The result of (173 * 177.7) + 142 is 30884.1", "a": 173, "b": 177.7, "c": 142, "op1": "*", "op2": "+", "result": 30884.1}
{"question": "Solve: (75.24 + 4) + 58.08", "answer": "The result of (75.24 + 4) + 58.08 is 137.32", "a": 75.24, "b": 4, "c": 58.08, "op1": "+", "op2": "+", "result": 137.32}
{"question": "Solve: (81 + 53.76) - 112", "answer": "The result of (81 + 53.76) - 112 is 22.76", "a": 81, "b": 53.76, "c": 112, "op1": "+", "op2": "-", "result": 22.76}
{"question": "Solve: (12 - 50) - 79", "answer": "The result of (12 - 50) - 79 is -117", "a": 12, "b": 50, "c": 79, "op1": "-", "op2": "-", "result": -117}
{"question": "Solve: (80.12 - 182) * 17.67", "answer": "The result of (80.12 - 182) * 17.67 is -1800.22", "a": 80.12, "b": 182, "c": 17.67, "op1": "-", "op2": "*", "result": -1800.22}
{"question": "Solve: (44 / 193) + 149", "answer": "The result of (44 / 193) + 149 is 149.23", "a": 44, "b": 193, "c": 149, "op1": "/", "op2": "+", "result": 149.23}
{"question": "Solve: (20 + 42) * 7.43", "answer": "The result of (20 + 42) * 7.43 is 460.66", "a": 20, "b": 42, "c": 7.43, "op1": "+", "op2": "*", "result": 460.66}
{"question": "Solve: (57 / 1) * 137", "answer": "The result of (57 / 1) * 137 is 7809.0", "a": 57, "b": 1, "c": 137, "op1": "/", "op2": "*", "result": 7809.0}
{"question": "Solve: (175.98 * 126) - 79", "answer": "The result of (175.98 * 126) - 79 is 22094.48", "a": 175.98, "b": 126, "c": 79, "op1": "*", "op2": "-", "result": 22094.48}
{"question": "Solve: (23 / 3) - 138", "answer": "The result of (23 / 3) - 138 is -130.33", "a": 23, "b": 3, "c": 138, "op1": "/", "op2": "-", "result": -130.33}
{"question": "Solve: (139.15 - 2) + 195", "answer": "The result of (139.15 - 2) + 195 is 332.15", "a": 139.15, "b": 2, "c": 195, "op1": "-", "op2": "+", "result": 332.15}
{"question": "Solve: (195 * 147) * 95.88", "answer": "The result of (195 * 147) * 95.88 is 2748400.2", "a": 195, "b": 147, "c": 95.88, "op1": "*", "op2": "*", "result": 2748400.2}
{"question": "Solve: (189.21 + 127.72) - 38", "answer": "The result of (189.21 + 127.72) - 38 is 278.93", "a": 189.21, "b": 127.72, "c": 38, "op1": "+", "op2": "-", "result": 278.93}
{"question": "Solve: (53 + 94.25) - 57", "answer": "The result of (53 + 94.25) - 57 is 90.25", "a": 53, "b": 94.25, "c": 57, "op1": "+", "op2": "-", "result": 90.25}
{"question": "Solve: (26.31 / 160) * 158", "answer": "The result of (26.31 / 160) * 158 is 25.98", "a": 26.31, "b": 160, "c": 158, "op1": "/", "op2": "*", "result": 25.98}
{"question": "Solve: (144 + 70) * 186", "answer": "The result of (144 + 70) * 186 is 39804", "a": 144, "b": 70, "c": 186, "op1": "+", "op2": "*", "result": 39804}
{"question": "Solve: (29 - 125) + 76", "answer": "The result of (29 - 125) + 76 is -20", "a": 29, "b": 125, "c": 76, "op1": "-", "op2": "+", "result": -20}
{"question": "Solve: (154.38 + 154) * 197", "answer": "The result of (154.38 + 154) * 197 is 60750.86", "a": 154.38, "b": 154, "c": 197, "op1": "+", "op2": "*", "result": 60750.86}
{"question": "Solve: (133 * 133) + 193.86", "answer": "The result of (133 * 133) + 193.86 is 17882.86", "a": 133, "b": 133, "c": 193.86, "op1": "*", "op2": "+", "result": 17882.86}
{"question": "Solve: (140.55 + 89) - 9", "answer": "The result of (140.55 + 89) - 9 is 220.55", "a": 140.55, "b": 89, "c": 9, "op1": "+", "op2": "-", "result": 220.55}
{"question": "Solve: (62 / 175) * 135", "answer": "The result of (62 / 175) * 135 is 47.83", "a": 62, "b": 175, "c": 135, "op1": "/", "op2": "*", "result": 47.83}
{"question": "Solve: (184 * 61) + 99.16", "answer": "The result of (184 * 61) + 99.16 is 11323.16", "a": 184, "b": 61, "c": 99.16, "op1": "*", "op2": "+", "result": 11323.16}
{"question": "Solve: (48.96 - 34.53) - 169", "answer": "The result of (48.96 - 34.53) - 169 is -154.57", "a": 48.96, "b": 34.53, "c": 169, "op1": "-", "op2": "-", "result": -154.57}
{"question": "Solve: (34.77 + 52.07) + 87", "answer": "The result of (34.77 + 52.07) + 87 is 173.84", "a": 34.77, "b": 52.07, "c": 87, "op1": "+", "op2": "+", "result": 173.84}
{"question": "Solve: (198 + 51) + 163", "answer": "The result of (198 + 51) + 163 is 412", "a": 198, "b": 51, "c": 163, "op1": "+", "op2": "+", "result": 412}
{"question": "Solve: (153 * 12) / 165", "answer": "The result of (153 * 12) / 165 is 11.13", "a": 153, "b": 12, "c": 165, "op1": "*", "op2": "/", "result": 11.13}
{"question": "Solve: (154 + 112) - 144", "answer": "The result of (154 + 112) - 144 is 122", "a": 154, "b": 112, "c": 144, "op1": "+", "op2": "-", "result": 122}
{"question": "Solve: (170.01 - 127) * 124", "answer": "The result of (170.01 - 127) * 124 is 5333.24", "a": 170.01, "b": 127, "c": 124, "op1": "-", "op2": "*", "result": 5333.24}
{"question": "Solve: (97 + 183) + 117", "answer": "The result of (97 + 183) + 117 is 397", "a": 97, "b": 183, "c": 117, "op1": "+", "op2": "+", "result": 397}
{"question": "Solve: (88 + 187.56) * 98", "answer": "The result of (88 + 187.56) * 98 is 27004.88", "a": 88, "b": 187.56, "c": 98, "op1": "+", "op2": "*", "result": 27004.88}
{"question": "Solve: (115 - 116) - 152", "answer": "The result of (115 - 116) - 152 is -153", "a": 115, "b": 116, "c": 152, "op1": "-", "op2": "-", "result": -153}
{"question": "Solve: (97.54 + 137) - 48", "answer": "The result of (97.54 + 137) - 48 is 186.54", "a": 97.54, "b": 137, "c": 48, "op1": "+", "op2": "-", "result": 186.54}
{"question": "Solve: (87 - 103) * 14", "answer": "The result of (87 - 103) * 14 is -224", "a": 87, "b": 103, "c": 14, "op1": "-", "op2": "*", "result": -224}
{"question": "Solve: (158 / 192.63) + 191.96", "answer": "The result of (158 / 192.63) + 191.96 is 192.78", "a": 158, "b": 192.63, "c": 191.96, "op1": "/", "op2": "+", "result": 192.78}
{"question": "Solve: (72 - 134) / 2", "answer": "The result of (72 - 134) / 2 is -31.0", "a": 72, "b": 134, "c": 2, "op1": "-", "op2": "/", "result": -31.0}
{"question": "Solve: (5 * 77) * 65.25", "answer": "The result of (5 * 77) * 65.25 is 25121.25", "a": 5, "b": 77, "c": 65.25, "op1": "*", "op2": "*", "result": 25121.25}
{"question": "Solve: (103 - 143) / 137", "answer": "The result of (103 - 143) / 137 is -0.29", "a": 103, "b": 143, "c": 137, "op1": "-", "op2": "/", "result": -0.29}
{"question": "Solve: (40 + 174.55) / 43", "answer": "The result of (40 + 174.55) / 43 is 4.99", "a": 40, "b": 174.55, "c": 43, "op1": "+", "op2": "/", "result": 4.99}
{"question": "Solve: (19 - 33.37) + 156.91", "answer": "The result of (19 - 33.37) + 156.91 is 142.54", "a": 19, "b": 33.37, "c": 156.91, "op1": "-", "op2": "+", "result": 142.54}
{"question": "Solve: (61 - 85) - 16.61", "answer": "The result of (61 - 85) - 16.61 is -40.61", "a": 61, "b": 85, "c": 16.61, "op1": "-", "op2": "-", "result": -40.61}
{"question": "Solve: (111 - 18) + 197", "answer": "The result of (111 - 18) + 197 is 290", "a": 111, "b": 18, "c": 197, "op1": "-", "op2": "+", "result": 290}
{"question": "Solve: (187.89 - 174) - 154.76", "answer": "The result of (187.89 - 174) - 154.76 is -140.87", "a": 187.89, "b": 174, "c": 154.76, "op1": "-", "op2": "-", "result": -140.87}
{"question": "Solve: (36.66 - 108) * 63.52", "answer": "The result of (36.66 - 108) * 63.52 is -4531.52", "a": 36.66, "b": 108, "c": 63.52, "op1": "-", "op2": "*", "result": -4531.52}
{"question": "Solve: (79 + 73) + 156", "answer": "The result of (79 + 73) + 156 is 308", "a": 79, "b": 73, "c": 156, "op1": "+", "op2": "+", "result": 308}
{"question": "Solve: (31 + 167) - 158", "answer": "The result of (31 + 167) - 158 is 40", "a": 31, "b": 167, "c": 158, "op1": "+", "op2": "-", "result": 40}
{"question": "Solve: (28 - 62) * 147", "answer": "The result of (28 - 62) * 147 is -4998", "a": 28, "b": 62, "c": 147, "op1": "-", "op2": "*", "result": -4998}
{"question": "Solve: (61.15 - 136.07) - 101.57", "answer": "The result of (61.15 - 136.07) - 101.57 is -176.49", "a": 61.15, "b": 136.07, "c": 101.57, "op1": "-", "op2": "-", "result": -176.49}
{"question": "Solve: (164 * 3) + 29.27", "answer": "The result of (164 * 3) + 29.27 is 521.27", "a": 164, "b": 3, "c": 29.27, "op1": "*", "op2": "+", "result": 521.27}
{"question": "Solve: (93 + 189) - 42", "answer": "The result of (93 + 189) - 42 is 240", "a": 93, "b": 189, "c": 42, "op1": "+", "op2": "-", "result": 240}
{"question": "Solve: (89 / 24) + 186.87", "answer": "The result of (89 / 24) + 186.87 is 190.58", "a": 89, "b": 24, "c": 186.87, "op1": "/", "op2": "+", "result": 190.58}
{"question": "Solve: (47.97 * 197.55) * 187", "answer": "The result of (47.97 * 197.55) * 187 is 1772100.54", "a": 47.97, "b": 197.55, "c": 187, "op1": "*", "op2": "*", "result": 1772100.54}
{"question": "Solve: (112 + 75) * 103", "answer": "The result of (112 + 75) * 103 is 19261", "a": 112, "b": 75, "c": 103, "op1": "+", "op2": "*", "result": 19261}
{"question": "Solve: (197 + 50) - 48", "answer": "The result of (197 + 50) - 48 is 199", "a": 197, "b": 50, "c": 48, "op1": "+", "op2": "-", "result": 199}
{"question": "Solve: (45 - 137) * 138", "answer": "The result of (45 - 137) * 138 is -12696", "a": 45, "b": 137, "c": 138, "op1": "-", "op2": "*", "result": -12696}
{"question": "Solve: (182.63 - 15.12) + 72.29", "answer": "The result of (182.63 - 15.12) + 72.29 is 239.8", "a": 182.63, "b": 15.12, "c": 72.29, "op1": "-", "op2": "+", "result": 239.8}
{"question": "Solve: (117 - 118) - 163", "answer": "The result of (117 - 118) - 163 is -164", "a": 117, "b": 118, "c": 163, "op1": "-", "op2": "-", "result": -164}
{"question": "Solve: (196 - 101.36) + 55.41", "answer": "The result of (196 - 101.36) + 55.41 is 150.05", "a": 196, "b": 101.36, "c": 55.41, "op1": "-", "op2": "+", "result": 150.05}
{"question": "Solve: (136 / 146) + 31.87", "answer": "The result of (136 / 146) + 31.87 is 32.8", "a": 136, "b": 146, "c": 31.87, "op1": "/", "op2": "+", "result": 32.8}
{"question": "Solve: (23 / 161) / 151.12", "answer": "The result of (23 / 161) / 151.12 is 0.0", "a": 23, "b": 161, "c": 151.12, "op1": "/", "op2": "/", "result": 0.0}
{"question": "Solve: (65 * 135.76) * 187", "answer": "The result of (65 * 135.76) * 187 is 1650162.8", "a": 65, "b": 135.76, "c": 187, "op1": "*", "op2": "*", "result": 1650162.8}
{"question": "Solve: (127 - 30) * 188", "answer": "The result of (127 - 30) * 188 is 18236", "a": 127, "b": 30, "c": 188, "op1": "-", "op2": "*", "result": 18236}
{"question": "Solve: (100 * 43) * 18.12", "answer": "The result of (100 * 43) * 18.12 is 77916.0", "a": 100, "b": 43, "c": 18.12, "op1": "*", "op2": "*", "result": 77916.0}
{"question": "Solve: (168.42 - 136.64) - 190", "answer": "The result of (168.42 - 136.64) - 190 is -158.22", "a": 168.42, "b": 136.64, "c": 190, "op1": "-", "op2": "-", "result": -158.22}
{"question": "Solve: (200 + 191) + 112", "answer": "The result of (200 + 191) + 112 is 503", "a": 200, "b": 191, "c": 112, "op1": "+", "op2": "+", "result": 503}
{"question": "Solve: (157 + 137) * 143.34", "answer": "The result of (157 + 137) * 143.34 is 42141.96", "a": 157, "b": 137, "c": 143.34, "op1": "+", "op2": "*", "result": 42141.96}
{"question": "Solve: (14.9 * 93) - 109", "answer": "The result of (14.9 * 93) - 109 is 1276.7", "a": 14.9, "b": 93, "c": 109, "op1": "*", "op2": "-", "result": 1276.7}
{"question": "Solve: (183.54 + 194) + 154", "answer": "The result of (183.54 + 194) + 154 is 531.54", "a": 183.54, "b": 194, "c": 154, "op1": "+", "op2": "+", "result": 531.54}
{"question": "Solve: (44 * 137) + 173", "answer": "The result of (44 * 137) + 173 is 6201", "a": 44, "b": 137, "c": 173, "op1": "*", "op2": "+", "result": 6201}
{"question": "Solve: (95.99 + 129) - 161.74", "answer": "The result of (95.99 + 129) - 161.74 is 63.25", "a": 95.99, "b": 129, "c": 161.74, "op1": "+", "op2": "-", "result": 63.25}
{"question": "Solve: (142 / 45) - 130", "answer": "The result of (142 / 45) - 130 is -126.84", "a": 142, "b": 45, "c": 130, "op1": "/", "op2": "-", "result": -126.84}
{"question": "Solve: (85 - 18) * 79", "answer": "The result of (85 - 18) * 79 is 5293", "a": 85, "b": 18, "c": 79, "op1": "-", "op2": "*", "result": 5293}
{"question": "Solve: (55 - 183) * 60", "answer": "The result of (55 - 183) * 60 is -7680", "a": 55, "b": 183, "c": 60, "op1": "-", "op2": "*", "result": -7680}
{"question": "Solve: (5 * 143) * 57", "answer": "The result of (5 * 143) * 57 is 40755", "a": 5, "b": 143, "c": 57, "op1": "*", "op2": "*", "result": 40755}
{"question": "Solve: (194 - 192) - 91.8", "answer": "The result of (194 - 192) - 91.8 is -89.8", "a": 194, "b": 192, "c": 91.8, "op1": "-", "op2": "-", "result": -89.8}
{"question": "Solve: (67 / 104) * 176", "answer": "The result of (67 / 104) * 176 is 113.38", "a": 67, "b": 104, "c": 176, "op1": "/", "op2": "*", "result": 113.38}
{"question": "Solve: (34 * 133) + 11.9", "answer": "The result of (34 * 133) + 11.9 is 4533.9", "a": 34, "b": 133, "c": 11.9, "op1": "*", "op2": "+", "result": 4533.9}
{"question": "Solve: (75.64 + 80.65) - 84", "answer": "The result of (75.64 + 80.65) - 84 is 72.29", "a": 75.64, "b": 80.65, "c": 84, "op1": "+", "op2": "-", "result": 72.29}
{"question": "Solve: (133.5 - 42) + 118", "answer": "The result of (133.5 - 42) + 118 is 209.5", "a": 133.5, "b": 42, "c": 118, "op1": "-", "op2": "+", "result": 209.5}
{"question": "Solve: (111 + 198.07) + 69", "answer": "The result of (111 + 198.07) + 69 is 378.07", "a": 111, "b": 198.07, "c": 69, "op1": "+", "op2": "+", "result": 378.07}
{"question": "Solve: (86 - 189) - 101.52", "answer": "The result of (86 - 189) - 101.52 is -204.52", "a": 86, "b": 189, "c": 101.52, "op1": "-", "op2": "-", "result": -204.52}
{"question": "Solve: (71.26 - 61.27) * 130", "answer": "The result of (71.26 - 61.27) * 130 is 1298.7", "a": 71.26, "b": 61.27, "c": 130, "op1": "-", "op2": "*", "result": 1298.7}
{"question": "Solve: (183 - 53) + 68", "answer": "The result of (183 - 53) + 68 is 198", "a": 183, "b": 53, "c": 68, "op1": "-", "op2": "+", "result": 198}
{"question": "Solve: (24.1 / 60) / 111.77", "answer": "The result of (24.1 / 60) / 111.77 is 0.0", "a": 24.1, "b": 60, "c": 111.77, "op1": "/", "op2": "/", "result": 0.0}
{"question": "Solve: (11 * 179) + 135", "answer": "The result of (11 * 179) + 135 is 2104", "a": 11, "b": 179, "c": 135, "op1": "*", "op2": "+", "result": 2104}
{"question": "Solve: (140 - 36) + 76", "answer": "The result of (140 - 36) + 76 is 180", "a": 140, "b": 36, "c": 76, "op1": "-", "op2": "+", "result": 180}
{"question": "Solve: (55 + 56.19) / 5", "answer": "The result of (55 + 56.19) / 5 is 22.24", "a": 55, "b": 56.19, "c": 5, "op1": "+", "op2": "/", "result": 22.24}
{"question": "Solve: (79 + 169) - 131", "answer": "The result of (79 + 169) - 131 is 117", "a": 79, "b": 169, "c": 131, "op1": "+", "op2": "-", "result": 117}
{"question": "Solve: (178.66 * 106) + 63", "answer": "The result of (178.66 * 106) + 63 is 19000.96", "a": 178.66, "b": 106, "c": 63, "op1": "*", "op2": "+", "result": 19000.96}
{"question": "Solve: (169 + 167) - 128", "answer": "The result of (169 + 167) - 128 is 208", "a": 169, "b": 167, "c": 128, "op1": "+", "op2": "-", "result": 208}
{"question": "Solve: (148.98 + 29) * 22", "answer": "The result of (148.98 + 29) * 22 is 3915.56", "a": 148.98, "b": 29, "c": 22, "op1": "+", "op2": "*", "result": 3915.56}
{"question": "Solve: (147 / 8) + 7", "answer": "The result of (147 / 8) + 7 is 25.38", "a": 147, "b": 8, "c": 7, "op1": "/", "op2": "+", "result": 25.38}
{"question": "Solve: (116 * 192) + 127", "answer": "The result of (116 * 192) + 127 is 22399", "a": 116, "b": 192, "c": 127, "op1": "*", "op2": "+", "result": 22399}
{"question": "Solve: (3 + 172.81) * 169", "answer": "The result of (3 + 172.81) * 169 is 29711.89", "a": 3, "b": 172.81, "c": 169, "op1": "+", "op2": "*", "result": 29711.89}
{"question": "Solve: (84 + 111.49) * 41.53", "answer": "The result of (84 + 111.49) * 41.53 is 8118.7", "a": 84, "b": 111.49, "c": 41.53, "op1": "+", "op2": "*", "result": 8118.7}
{"question": "Solve: (1 / 177) + 126", "answer": "The result of (1 / 177) + 126 is 126.01", "a": 1, "b": 177, "c": 126, "op1": "/", "op2": "+", "result": 126.01}
{"question": "Solve: (134 - 93) + 119", "answer": "The result of (134 - 93) + 119 is 160", "a": 134, "b": 93, "c": 119, "op1": "-", "op2": "+", "result": 160}
{"question": "Solve: (23 - 12) - 97", "answer": "The result of (23 - 12) - 97 is -86", "a": 23, "b": 12, "c": 97, "op1": "-", "op2": "-", "result": -86}
{"question": "Solve: (106 / 193) - 127", "answer": "The result of (106 / 193) - 127 is -126.45", "a": 106, "b": 193, "c": 127, "op1": "/", "op2": "-", "result": -126.45}
{"question": "Solve: (125.16 - 98) - 197", "answer": "The result of (125.16 - 98) - 197 is -169.84", "a": 125.16, "b": 98, "c": 197, "op1": "-", "op2": "-", "result": -169.84}
{"question": "Solve: (109 + 61.26) + 2", "answer": "The result of (109 + 61.26) + 2 is 172.26", "a": 109, "b": 61.26, "c": 2, "op1": "+", "op2": "+", "result": 172.26}
{"question": "Solve: (25 * 132) * 104", "answer": "The result of (25 * 132) * 104 is 343200", "a": 25, "b": 132, "c": 104, "op1": "*", "op2": "*", "result": 343200}
{"question": "Solve: (157 * 57.45) + 41.56", "answer": "The result of (157 * 57.45) + 41.56 is 9061.21", "a": 157, "b": 57.45, "c": 41.56, "op1": "*", "op2": "+", "result": 9061.21}
{"question": "Solve: (111.9 * 183.4) / 140", "answer": "The result of (111.9 * 183.4) / 140 is 146.59", "a": 111.9, "b": 183.4, "c": 140, "op1": "*", "op2": "/", "result": 146.59}
{"question": "Solve: (160 * 25) + 126", "answer": "The result of (160 * 25) + 126 is 4126", "a": 160, "b": 25, "c": 126, "op1": "*", "op2": "+", "result": 4126}
{"question": "Solve: (53.41 - 76) * 105", "answer": "The result of (53.41 - 76) * 105 is -2371.95", "a": 53.41, "b": 76, "c": 105, "op1": "-", "op2": "*", "result": -2371.95}
{"question": "Solve: (185 - 164.7) + 145", "answer": "The result of (185 - 164.7) + 145 is 165.3", "a": 185, "b": 164.7, "c": 145, "op1": "-", "op2": "+", "result": 165.3}
{"question": "Solve: (19.3 * 150.87) - 136.65", "answer": "The result of (19.3 * 150.87) - 136.65 is 2775.14", "a": 19.3, "b": 150.87, "c": 136.65, "op1": "*", "op2": "-", "result": 2775.14}
{"question": "Solve: (23 * 155) - 151", "answer": "The result of (23 * 155) - 151 is 3414", "a": 23, "b": 155, "c": 151, "op1": "*", "op2": "-", "result": 3414}
{"question": "Solve: (88.1 + 91) - 57.73", "answer": "The result of (88.1 + 91) - 57.73 is 121.37", "a": 88.1, "b": 91, "c": 57.73, "op1": "+", "op2": "-", "result": 121.37}
{"question": "Solve: (181 * 63.1) - 145", "answer": "The result of (181 * 63.1) - 145 is 11276.1", "a": 181, "b": 63.1, "c": 145, "op1": "*", "op2": "-", "result": 11276.1}
{"question": "Solve: (187 + 188.72) - 172", "answer": "The result of (187 + 188.72) - 172 is 203.72", "a": 187, "b": 188.72, "c": 172, "op1": "+", "op2": "-", "result": 203.72}
{"question": "Solve: (86 * 149) + 109", "answer": "The result of (86 * 149) + 109 is 12923", "a": 86, "b": 149, "c": 109, "op1": "*", "op2": "+", "result": 12923}
{"question": "Solve: (20 - 186) + 72", "answer": "The result of (20 - 186) + 72 is -94", "a": 20, "b": 186, "c": 72, "op1": "-", "op2": "+", "result": -94}
{"question": "Solve: (9 * 46.27) + 7.0", "answer": "The result of (9 * 46.27) + 7.0 is 423.43", "a": 9, "b": 46.27, "c": 7.0, "op1": "*", "op2": "+", "result": 423.43}
{"question": "Solve: (108 + 84.46) / 68.41", "answer": "The result of (108 + 84.46) / 68.41 is 2.81", "a": 108, "b": 84.46, "c": 68.41, "op1": "+", "op2": "/", "result": 2.81}
{"question": "Solve: (97 - 135) - 132", "answer": "The result of (97 - 135) - 132 is -170", "a": 97, "b": 135, "c": 132, "op1": "-", "op2": "-", "result": -170}
{"question": "Solve: (86 / 39.95) + 43", "answer": "The result of (86 / 39.95) + 43 is 45.15", "a": 86, "b": 39.95, "c": 43, "op1": "/", "op2": "+", "result": 45.15}
{"question": "Solve: (42 + 34.12) - 132", "answer": "The result of (42 + 34.12) - 132 is -55.88", "a": 42, "b": 34.12, "c": 132, "op1": "+", "op2": "-", "result": -55.88}
{"question": "Solve: (150.52 + 34.68) * 130", "answer": "The result of (150.52 + 34.68) * 130 is 24076.0", "a": 150.52, "b": 34.68, "c": 130, "op1": "+", "op2": "*", "result": 24076.0}
{"question": "Solve: (61 + 11) + 161", "answer": "The result of (61 + 11) + 161 is 233", "a": 61, "b": 11, "c": 161, "op1": "+", "op2": "+", "result": 233}
{"question": "Solve: (95 + 63) + 120", "answer": "The result of (95 + 63) + 120 is 278", "a": 95, "b": 63, "c": 120, "op1": "+", "op2": "+", "result": 278}
{"question": "Solve: (20 + 11.64) + 36", "answer": "The result of (20 + 11.64) + 36 is 67.64", "a": 20, "b": 11.64, "c": 36, "op1": "+", "op2": "+", "result": 67.64}
{"question": "Solve: (96.87 + 99.91) * 162", "answer": "The result of (96.87 + 99.91) * 162 is 31878.36", "a": 96.87, "b": 99.91, "c": 162, "op1": "+", "op2": "*", "result": 31878.36}
{"question": "Solve: (190.04 / 35.75) + 55.91", "answer": "The result of (190.04 / 35.75) + 55.91 is 61.23", "a": 190.04, "b": 35.75, "c": 55.91, "op1": "/", "op2": "+", "result": 61.23}
{"question": "Solve: (56 * 23.67) / 97", "answer": "The result of (56 * 23.67) / 97 is 13.67", "a": 56, "b": 23.67, "c": 97, "op1": "*", "op2": "/", "result": 13.67}
{"question": "Solve: (33 * 75) / 54", "answer": "The result of (33 * 75) / 54 is 45.83", "a": 33, "b": 75, "c": 54, "op1": "*", "op2": "/", "result": 45.83}
{"question": "Solve: (158 * 72) / 71", "answer": "The result of (158 * 72) / 71 is 160.23", "a": 158, "b": 72, "c": 71, "op1": "*", "op2": "/", "result": 160.23}
{"question": "Solve: (162.07 - 18) * 180.69", "answer": "The result of (162.07 - 18) * 180.69 is 26032.01", "a": 162.07, "b": 18, "c": 180.69, "op1": "-", "op2": "*", "result": 26032.01}
{"question": "Solve: (117 / 49.01) * 118", "answer": "The result of (117 / 49.01) * 118 is 281.7", "a": 117, "b": 49.01, "c": 118, "op1": "/", "op2": "*", "result": 281.7}
{"question": "Solve: (125.27 + 116) - 124", "answer": "The result of (125.27 + 116) - 124 is 117.27", "a": 125.27, "b": 116, "c": 124, "op1": "+", "op2": "-", "result": 117.27}
{"question": "Solve: (54 / 176.95) - 15", "answer": "The result of (54 / 176.95) - 15 is -14.69", "a": 54, "b": 176.95, "c": 15, "op1": "/", "op2": "-", "result": -14.69}
{"question": "Solve: (16 * 183) * 103.86", "answer": "The result of (16 * 183) * 103.86 is 304102.08", "a": 16, "b": 183, "c": 103.86, "op1": "*", "op2": "*", "result": 304102.08}
{"question": "Solve: (48 + 195) + 134", "answer": "The result of (48 + 195) + 134 is 377", "a": 48, "b": 195, "c": 134, "op1": "+", "op2": "+", "result": 377}
{"question": "Solve: (155 / 109) / 1.44", "answer": "The result of (155 / 109) / 1.44 is 0.99", "a": 155, "b": 109, "c": 1.44, "op1": "/", "op2": "/", "result": 0.99}
{"question": "Solve: (90 - 147) * 15", "answer": "The result of (90 - 147) * 15 is -855", "a": 90, "b": 147, "c": 15, "op1": "-", "op2": "*", "result": -855}
{"question": "Solve: (50 * 119) - 137", "answer": "The result of (50 * 119) - 137 is 5813", "a": 50, "b": 119, "c": 137, "op1": "*", "op2": "-", "result": 5813}
{"question": "Solve: (117 - 1) * 110.11", "answer": "The result of (117 - 1) * 110.11 is 12772.76", "a": 117, "b": 1, "c": 110.11, "op1": "-", "op2": "*", "result": 12772.76}
{"question": "Solve: (80.62 * 74.63) - 152", "answer": "The result of (80.62 * 74.63) - 152 is 5864.67", "a": 80.62, "b": 74.63, "c": 152, "op1": "*", "op2": "-", "result": 5864.67}
{"question": "Solve: (154 - 172) - 193", "answer": "The result of (154 - 172) - 193 is -211", "a": 154, "b": 172, "c": 193, "op1": "-", "op2": "-", "result": -211}
{"question": "Solve: (18 * 108) + 194.78", "answer": "The result of (18 * 108) + 194.78 is 2138.78", "a": 18, "b": 108, "c": 194.78, "op1": "*", "op2": "+", "result": 2138.78}
{"question": "Solve: (196 - 103) + 168.15", "answer": "The result of (196 - 103) + 168.15 is 261.15", "a": 196, "b": 103, "c": 168.15, "op1": "-", "op2": "+", "result": 261.15}
{"question": "Solve: (1 - 87) - 169", "answer": "The result of (1 - 87) - 169 is -255", "a": 1, "b": 87, "c": 169, "op1": "-", "op2": "-", "result": -255}
{"question": "Solve: (122 + 42) + 175", "answer": "The result of (122 + 42) + 175 is 339", "a": 122, "b": 42, "c": 175, "op1": "+", "op2": "+", "result": 339}
{"question": "Solve: (129 + 33) / 41.41", "answer": "The result of (129 + 33) / 41.41 is 3.91", "a": 129, "b": 33, "c": 41.41, "op1": "+", "op2": "/", "result": 3.91}
{"question": "Solve: (23 - 106) + 161", "answer": "The result of (23 - 106) + 161 is 78", "a": 23, "b": 106, "c": 161, "op1": "-", "op2": "+", "result": 78}
{"question": "Solve: (16 + 172) + 104", "answer": "The result of (16 + 172) + 104 is 292", "a": 16, "b": 172, "c": 104, "op1": "+", "op2": "+", "result": 292}
{"question": "Solve: (68 + 128) * 160", "answer": "The result of (68 + 128) * 160 is 31360", "a": 68, "b": 128, "c": 160, "op1": "+", "op2": "*", "result": 31360}
{"question": "Solve: (57 * 117) + 89.31", "answer": "The result of (57 * 117) + 89.31 is 6758.31", "a": 57, "b": 117, "c": 89.31, "op1": "*", "op2": "+", "result": 6758.31}
{"question": "Solve: (170 + 39.02) * 33.72", "answer": "The result of (170 + 39.02) * 33.72 is 7048.15", "a": 170, "b": 39.02, "c": 33.72, "op1": "+", "op2": "*", "result": 7048.15}
{"question": "Solve: (60 + 163) + 41.58", "answer": "The result of (60 + 163) + 41.58 is 264.58", "a": 60, "b": 163, "c": 41.58, "op1": "+", "op2": "+", "result": 264.58}
{"question": "Solve: (184.16 - 57) + 99", "answer": "The result of (184.16 - 57) + 99 is 226.16", "a": 184.16, "b": 57, "c": 99, "op1": "-", "op2": "+", "result": 226.16}
{"question": "Solve: (37 * 178) + 47", "answer": "The result of (37 * 178) + 47 is 6633", "a": 37, "b": 178, "c": 47, "op1": "*", "op2": "+", "result": 6633}
{"question": "Solve: (55 * 191) - 132.84", "answer": "The result of (55 * 191) - 132.84 is 10372.16", "a": 55, "b": 191, "c": 132.84, "op1": "*", "op2": "-", "result": 10372.16}
{"question": "Solve: (17 * 6.29) * 85", "answer": "The result of (17 * 6.29) * 85 is 9089.05", "a": 17, "b": 6.29, "c": 85, "op1": "*", "op2": "*", "result": 9089.05}
{"question": "Solve: (43 + 61) + 157.54", "answer": "The result of (43 + 61) + 157.54 is 261.54", "a": 43, "b": 61, "c": 157.54, "op1": "+", "op2": "+", "result": 261.54}
{"question": "Solve: (73 * 15) + 36", "answer": "The result of (73 * 15) + 36 is 1131", "a": 73, "b": 15, "c": 36, "op1": "*", "op2": "+", "result": 1131}
{"question": "Solve: (144 + 23.3) - 98", "answer": "The result of (144 + 23.3) - 98 is 69.3", "a": 144, "b": 23.3, "c": 98, "op1": "+", "op2": "-", "result": 69.3}
{"question": "Solve: (60.99 * 141.4) - 117", "answer": "The result of (60.99 * 141.4) - 117 is 8506.99", "a": 60.99, "b": 141.4, "c": 117, "op1": "*", "op2": "-", "result": 8506.99}
{"question": "Solve: (199 + 70.0) * 138", "answer": "The result of (199 + 70.0) * 138 is 37122.0", "a": 199, "b": 70.0, "c": 138, "op1": "+", "op2": "*", "result": 37122.0}
{"question": "Solve: (95 / 199) - 7.55", "answer": "The result of (95 / 199) - 7.55 is -7.07", "a": 95, "b": 199, "c": 7.55, "op1": "/", "op2": "-", "result": -7.07}
{"question": "Solve: (10 / 83) / 91.26", "answer": "The result of (10 / 83) / 91.26 is 0.0", "a": 10, "b": 83, "c": 91.26, "op1": "/", "op2": "/", "result": 0.0}
{"question": "Solve: (153.88 / 143) / 108.29", "answer": "The result of (153.88 / 143) / 108.29 is 0.01", "a": 153.88, "b": 143, "c": 108.29, "op1": "/", "op2": "/", "result": 0.01}
{"question": "Solve: (51.27 / 103) - 178", "answer": "The result of (51.27 / 103) - 178 is -177.5", "a": 51.27, "b": 103, "c": 178, "op1": "/", "op2": "-", "result": -177.5}
{"question": "Solve: (33 / 188) * 7.76", "answer": "The result of (33 / 188) * 7.76 is 1.36", "a": 33, "b": 188, "c": 7.76, "op1": "/", "op2": "*", "result": 1.36}
{"question": "Solve: (83 / 62) - 182", "answer": "The result of (83 / 62) - 182 is -180.66", "a": 83, "b": 62, "c": 182, "op1": "/", "op2": "-", "result": -180.66}
{"question": "Solve: (191 * 160) / 164", "answer": "The result of (191 * 160) / 164 is 186.34", "a": 191, "b": 160, "c": 164, "op1": "*", "op2": "/", "result": 186.34}
{"question": "Solve: (22 + 67) - 199.86", "answer": "The result of (22 + 67) - 199.86 is -110.86", "a": 22, "b": 67, "c": 199.86, "op1": "+", "op2": "-", "result": -110.86}
{"question": "Solve: (168 - 58) / 111", "answer": "The result of (168 - 58) / 111 is 0.99", "a": 168, "b": 58, "c": 111, "op1": "-", "op2": "/", "result": 0.99}
{"question": "Solve: (84 * 108.84) / 188", "answer": "The result of (84 * 108.84) / 188 is 48.63", "a": 84, "b": 108.84, "c": 188, "op1": "*", "op2": "/", "result": 48.63}
{"question": "Solve: (98 + 139) * 153", "answer": "The result of (98 + 139) * 153 is 36261", "a": 98, "b": 139, "c": 153, "op1": "+", "op2": "*", "result": 36261}
{"question": "Solve: (195 * 12.02) + 85.41", "answer": "The result of (195 * 12.02) + 85.41 is 2429.31", "a": 195, "b": 12.02, "c": 85.41, "op1": "*", "op2": "+", "result": 2429.31}
{"question": "Solve: (182 + 99) * 22", "answer": "The result of (182 + 99) * 22 is 6182", "a": 182, "b": 99, "c": 22, "op1": "+", "op2": "*", "result": 6182}
{"question": "Solve: (2 / 6) + 156", "answer": "The result of (2 / 6) + 156 is 156.33", "a": 2, "b": 6, "c": 156, "op1": "/", "op2": "+", "result": 156.33}
{"question": "Solve: (114.97 * 143.77) - 100", "answer": "The result of (114.97 * 143.77) - 100 is 16429.24", "a": 114.97, "b": 143.77, "c": 100, "op1": "*", "op2": "-", "result": 16429.24}
{"question": "Solve: (195 + 167) - 9.66", "answer": "The result of (195 + 167) - 9.66 is 352.34", "a": 195, "b": 167, "c": 9.66, "op1": "+", "op2": "-", "result": 352.34}
{"question": "Solve: (61 + 158.32) + 58", "answer": "The result of (61 + 158.32) + 58 is 277.32", "a": 61, "b": 158.32, "c": 58, "op1": "+", "op2": "+", "result": 277.32}
{"question": "Solve: (33 + 165) * 66", "answer": "The result of (33 + 165) * 66 is 13068", "a": 33, "b": 165, "c": 66, "op1": "+", "op2": "*", "result": 13068}
{"question": "Solve: (145 + 121) - 129", "answer": "The result of (145 + 121) - 129 is 137", "a": 145, "b": 121, "c": 129, "op1": "+", "op2": "-", "result": 137}
{"question": "Solve: (97 - 86) / 196.12", "answer": "The result of (97 - 86) / 196.12 is 0.06", "a": 97, "b": 86, "c": 196.12, "op1": "-", "op2": "/", "result": 0.06}
{"question": "Solve: (169 + 63.68) / 120", "answer": "The result of (169 + 63.68) / 120 is 1.94", "a": 169, "b": 63.68, "c": 120, "op1": "+", "op2": "/", "result": 1.94}
{"question": "Solve: (75.6 - 62.32) - 161", "answer": "The result of (75.6 - 62.32) - 161 is -147.72", "a": 75.6, "b": 62.32, "c": 161, "op1": "-", "op2": "-", "result": -147.72}
{"question": "Solve: (165 + 46) + 77", "answer": "The result of (165 + 46) + 77 is 288", "a": 165, "b": 46, "c": 77, "op1": "+", "op2": "+", "result": 288}
{"question": "Solve: (175 + 20) + 62", "answer": "The result of (175 + 20) + 62 is 257", "a": 175, "b": 20, "c": 62, "op1": "+", "op2": "+", "result": 257}
{"question": "Solve: (32 + 105) + 153.94", "answer": "The result of (32 + 105) + 153.94 is 290.94", "a": 32, "b": 105, "c": 153.94, "op1": "+", "op2": "+", "result": 290.94}
{"question": "Solve: (52.19 * 101) * 98", "answer": "The result of (52.19 * 101) * 98 is 516576.62", "a": 52.19, "b": 101, "c": 98, "op1": "*", "op2": "*", "result": 516576.62}
{"question": "Solve: (58 * 20.2) - 16", "answer": "The result of (58 * 20.2) - 16 is 1155.6", "a": 58, "b": 20.2, "c": 16, "op1": "*", "op2": "-", "result": 1155.6}
{"question": "Solve: (101.56 * 103.21) / 163.32", "answer": "The result of (101.56 * 103.21) / 163.32 is 64.18", "a": 101.56, "b": 103.21, "c": 163.32, "op1": "*", "op2": "/", "result": 64.18}
{"question": "Solve: (63 + 96.64) * 133", "answer": "The result of (63 + 96.64) * 133 is 21232.12", "a": 63, "b": 96.64, "c": 133, "op1": "+", "op2": "*", "result": 21232.12}
{"question": "Solve: (151.48 - 112) + 126.84", "answer": "The result of (151.48 - 112) + 126.84 is 166.32", "a": 151.48, "b": 112, "c": 126.84, "op1": "-", "op2": "+", "result": 166.32}
{"question": "Solve: (5 / 118) * 41", "answer": "The result of (5 / 118) * 41 is 1.74", "a": 5, "b": 118, "c": 41, "op1": "/", "op2": "*", "result": 1.74}
{"question": "Solve: (41.84 * 108) / 88.65", "answer": "The result of (41.84 * 108) / 88.65 is 50.97", "a": 41.84, "b": 108, "c": 88.65, "op1": "*", "op2": "/", "result": 50.97}
{"question": "Solve: (2 + 97) - 147", "answer": "The result of (2 + 97) - 147 is -48", "a": 2, "b": 97, "c": 147, "op1": "+", "op2": "-", "result": -48}
{"question": "Solve: (193 - 101.77) + 34", "answer": "The result of (193 - 101.77) + 34 is 125.23", "a": 193, "b": 101.77, "c": 34, "op1": "-", "op2": "+", "result": 125.23}
{"question": "Solve: (117 + 177) - 146", "answer": "The result of (117 + 177) - 146 is 148", "a": 117, "b": 177, "c": 146, "op1": "+", "op2": "-", "result": 148}
{"question": "Solve: (189.15 / 181) + 196.32", "answer": "The result of (189.15 / 181) + 196.32 is 197.37", "a": 189.15, "b": 181, "c": 196.32, "op1": "/", "op2": "+", "result": 197.37}
{"question": "Solve: (188 + 186) * 45", "answer": "The result of (188 + 186) * 45 is 16830", "a": 188, "b": 186, "c": 45, "op1": "+", "op2": "*", "result": 16830}
{"question": "Solve: (187 / 39.97) + 52.38", "answer": "The result of (187 / 39.97) + 52.38 is 57.06", "a": 187, "b": 39.97, "c": 52.38, "op1": "/", "op2": "+", "result": 57.06}
{"question": "Solve: (171 - 124) * 63", "answer": "The result of (171 - 124) * 63 is 2961", "a": 171, "b": 124, "c": 63, "op1": "-", "op2": "*", "result": 2961}
{"question": "Solve: (21.62 * 189) * 122", "answer": "The result of (21.62 * 189) * 122 is 498513.96", "a": 21.62, "b": 189, "c": 122, "op1": "*", "op2": "*", "result": 498513.96}
{"question": "Solve: (44 / 179) + 21", "answer": "The result of (44 / 179) + 21 is 21.25", "a": 44, "b": 179, "c": 21, "op1": "/", "op2": "+", "result": 21.25}
{"question": "Solve: (91 - 89) - 21", "answer": "The result of (91 - 89) - 21 is -19", "a": 91, "b": 89, "c": 21, "op1": "-", "op2": "-", "result": -19}
{"question": "Solve: (12 - 54) * 75", "answer": "The result of (12 - 54) * 75 is -3150", "a": 12, "b": 54, "c": 75, "op1": "-", "op2": "*", "result": -3150}
{"question": "Solve: (194.26 - 39) + 90.78", "answer": "The result of (194.26 - 39) + 90.78 is 246.04", "a": 194.26, "b": 39, "c": 90.78, "op1": "-", "op2": "+", "result": 246.04}
{"question": "Solve: (186 + 50) + 146", "answer": "The result of (186 + 50) + 146 is 382", "a": 186, "b": 50, "c": 146, "op1": "+", "op2": "+", "result": 382}
{"question": "Solve: (74 * 67) - 178.82", "answer": "The result of (74 * 67) - 178.82 is 4779.18", "a": 74, "b": 67, "c": 178.82, "op1": "*", "op2": "-", "result": 4779.18}
{"question": "Solve: (109.36 - 178) + 196", "answer": "The result of (109.36 - 178) + 196 is 127.36", "a": 109.36, "b": 178, "c": 196, "op1": "-", "op2": "+", "result": 127.36}
{"question": "Solve: (27 * 123) - 44.82", "answer": "The result of (27 * 123) - 44.82 is 3276.18", "a": 27, "b": 123, "c": 44.82, "op1": "*", "op2": "-", "result": 3276.18}
{"question": "Solve: (71 / 72) / 120", "answer": "The result of (71 / 72) / 120 is 0.01", "a": 71, "b": 72, "c": 120, "op1": "/", "op2": "/", "result": 0.01}
{"question": "Solve: (99 * 116) / 94", "answer": "The result of (99 * 116) / 94 is 122.17", "a": 99, "b": 116, "c": 94, "op1": "*", "op2": "/", "result": 122.17}
{"question": "Solve: (118.22 - 169.74) - 122", "answer": "The result of (118.22 - 169.74) - 122 is -173.52", "a": 118.22, "b": 169.74, "c": 122, "op1": "-", "op2": "-", "result": -173.52}
{"question": "Solve: (106.34 * 17) + 31", "answer": "The result of (106.34 * 17) + 31 is 1838.78", "a": 106.34, "b": 17, "c": 31, "op1": "*", "op2": "+", "result": 1838.78}
{"question": "Solve: (157 + 170.34) * 173.52", "answer": "The result of (157 + 170.34) * 173.52 is 56800.04", "a": 157, "b": 170.34, "c": 173.52, "op1": "+", "op2": "*", "result": 56800.04}
{"question": "Solve: (81 / 28) / 171.62", "answer": "The result of (81 / 28) / 171.62 is 0.02", "a": 81, "b": 28, "c": 171.62, "op1": "/", "op2": "/", "result": 0.02}
{"question": "Solve: (22 - 129.86) / 127", "answer": "The result of (22 - 129.86) / 127 is -0.85", "a": 22, "b": 129.86, "c": 127, "op1": "-", "op2": "/", "result": -0.85}
{"question": "Solve: (161.04 - 155.32) * 46", "answer": "The result of (161.04 - 155.32) * 46 is 263.12", "a": 161.04, "b": 155.32, "c": 46, "op1": "-", "op2": "*", "result": 263.12}
{"question": "Solve: (193.53 / 167) + 94.21", "answer": "The result of (193.53 / 167) + 94.21 is 95.37", "a": 193.53, "b": 167, "c": 94.21, "op1": "/", "op2": "+", "result": 95.37}
{"question": "Solve: (189 - 55) / 134.51", "answer": "The result of (189 - 55) / 134.51 is 1.0", "a": 189, "b": 55, "c": 134.51, "op1": "-", "op2": "/", "result": 1.0}
{"question": "Solve: (55 + 76) - 40", "answer": "The result of (55 + 76) - 40 is 91", "a": 55, "b": 76, "c": 40, "op1": "+", "op2": "-", "result": 91}
{"question": "Solve: (198 * 40) * 25.81", "answer": "The result of (198 * 40) * 25.81 is 204415.2", "a": 198, "b": 40, "c": 25.81, "op1": "*", "op2": "*", "result": 204415.2}
{"question": "Solve: (88 - 140) - 66", "answer": "The result of (88 - 140) - 66 is -118", "a": 88, "b": 140, "c": 66, "op1": "-", "op2": "-", "result": -118}
{"question": "Solve: (170 + 28) * 180.54", "answer": "The result of (170 + 28) * 180.54 is 35746.92", "a": 170, "b": 28, "c": 180.54, "op1": "+", "op2": "*", "result": 35746.92}
{"question": "Solve: (171 + 134.57) / 53", "answer": "The result of (171 + 134.57) / 53 is 5.77", "a": 171, "b": 134.57, "c": 53, "op1": "+", "op2": "/", "result": 5.77}
{"question": "Solve: (86 * 5.96) + 178.45", "answer": "The result of (86 * 5.96) + 178.45 is 691.01", "a": 86, "b": 5.96, "c": 178.45, "op1": "*", "op2": "+", "result": 691.01}
{"question": "Solve: (41 - 45) + 152", "answer": "The result of (41 - 45) + 152 is 148", "a": 41, "b": 45, "c": 152, "op1": "-", "op2": "+", "result": 148}
{"question": "Solve: (158 + 88.55) * 186.29", "answer": "The result of (158 + 88.55) * 186.29 is 45929.8", "a": 158, "b": 88.55, "c": 186.29, "op1": "+", "op2": "*", "result": 45929.8}
{"question": "Solve: (155 - 95) + 55", "answer": "The result of (155 - 95) + 55 is 115", "a": 155, "b": 95, "c": 55, "op1": "-", "op2": "+", "result": 115}
{"question": "Solve: (61 + 175) + 39", "answer": "The result of (61 + 175) + 39 is 275", "a": 61, "b": 175, "c": 39, "op1": "+", "op2": "+", "result": 275}
{"question": "Solve: (14.49 * 193) - 148", "answer": "The result of (14.49 * 193) - 148 is 2648.57", "a": 14.49, "b": 193, "c": 148, "op1": "*", "op2": "-", "result": 2648.57}
{"question": "Solve: (64 * 35) * 35", "answer": "The result of (64 * 35) * 35 is 78400", "a": 64, "b": 35, "c": 35, "op1": "*", "op2": "*", "result": 78400}
{"question": "Solve: (177 + 19) * 12", "answer": "The result of (177 + 19) * 12 is 2352", "a": 177, "b": 19, "c": 12, "op1": "+", "op2": "*", "result": 2352}
{"question": "Solve: (86 * 5) / 24.41", "answer": "The result of (86 * 5) / 24.41 is 17.62", "a": 86, "b": 5, "c": 24.41, "op1": "*", "op2": "/", "result": 17.62}
{"question": "Solve: (115 / 145) - 125", "answer": "The result of (115 / 145) - 125 is -124.21", "a": 115, "b": 145, "c": 125, "op1": "/", "op2": "-", "result": -124.21}
{"question": "Solve: (32 - 16.07) - 51.82", "answer": "The result of (32 - 16.07) - 51.82 is -35.89", "a": 32, "b": 16.07, "c": 51.82, "op1": "-", "op2": "-", "result": -35.89}
{"question": "Solve: (56 - 36.4) + 142", "answer": "The result of (56 - 36.4) + 142 is 161.6", "a": 56, "b": 36.4, "c": 142, "op1": "-", "op2": "+", "result": 161.6}
{"question": "Solve: (104 + 91) / 122", "answer": "The result of (104 + 91) / 122 is 1.6", "a": 104, "b": 91, "c": 122, "op1": "+", "op2": "/", "result": 1.6}
{"question": "Solve: (176.84 + 86) * 182.66", "answer": "The result of (176.84 + 86) * 182.66 is 48010.35", "a": 176.84, "b": 86, "c": 182.66, "op1": "+", "op2": "*", "result": 48010.35}
{"question": "Solve: (9 + 33.82) * 34", "answer": "The result of (9 + 33.82) * 34 is 1455.88", "a": 9, "b": 33.82, "c": 34, "op1": "+", "op2": "*", "result": 1455.88}
{"question": "Solve: (93 * 186.31) + 177.76", "answer": "The result of (93 * 186.31) + 177.76 is 17504.59", "a": 93, "b": 186.31, "c": 177.76, "op1": "*", "op2": "+", "result": 17504.59}
{"question": "Solve: (89.74 - 12) - 68.2", "answer": "The result of (89.74 - 12) - 68.2 is 9.54", "a": 89.74, "b": 12, "c": 68.2, "op1": "-", "op2": "-", "result": 9.54}
{"question": "Solve: (164 + 62) - 25", "answer": "The result of (164 + 62) - 25 is 201", "a": 164, "b": 62, "c": 25, "op1": "+", "op2": "-", "result": 201}
{"question": "Solve: (180 * 149) * 149", "answer": "The result of (180 * 149) * 149 is 3996180", "a": 180, "b": 149, "c": 149, "op1": "*", "op2": "*", "result": 3996180}
{"question": "Solve: (158 * 165) + 102.91", "answer": "The result of (158 * 165) + 102.91 is 26172.91", "a": 158, "b": 165, "c": 102.91, "op1": "*", "op2": "+", "result": 26172.91}
{"question": "Solve: (117 + 40.48) + 64", "answer": "The result of (117 + 40.48) + 64 is 221.48", "a": 117, "b": 40.48, "c": 64, "op1": "+", "op2": "+", "result": 221.48}
{"question": "Solve: (139 - 81.78) - 4.05", "answer": "The result of (139 - 81.78) - 4.05 is 53.17", "a": 139, "b": 81.78, "c": 4.05, "op1": "-", "op2": "-", "result": 53.17}
{"question": "Solve: (14 / 60) - 129.04", "answer": "The result of (14 / 60) - 129.04 is -128.81", "a": 14, "b": 60, "c": 129.04, "op1": "/", "op2": "-", "result": -128.81}
{"question": "Solve: (54 - 46) + 189", "answer": "The result of (54 - 46) + 189 is 197", "a": 54, "b": 46, "c": 189, "op1": "-", "op2": "+", "result": 197}
{"question": "Solve: (119 + 96.89) / 122", "answer": "The result of (119 + 96.89) / 122 is 1.77", "a": 119, "b": 96.89, "c": 122, "op1": "+", "op2": "/", "result": 1.77}
{"question": "Solve: (144 - 5) - 81.89", "answer": "The result of (144 - 5) - 81.89 is 57.11", "a": 144, "b": 5, "c": 81.89, "op1": "-", "op2": "-", "result": 57.11}
{"question": "Solve: (8 / 200) + 8", "answer": "The result of (8 / 200) + 8 is 8.04", "a": 8, "b": 200, "c": 8, "op1": "/", "op2": "+", "result": 8.04}
{"question": "Solve: (172 / 100.82) - 43", "answer": "The result of (172 / 100.82) - 43 is -41.29", "a": 172, "b": 100.82, "c": 43, "op1": "/", "op2": "-", "result": -41.29}
{"question": "Solve: (127.8 + 124) / 66", "answer": "The result of (127.8 + 124) / 66 is 3.82", "a": 127.8, "b": 124, "c": 66, "op1": "+", "op2": "/", "result": 3.82}
{"question": "Solve: (24 / 147.6) + 174", "answer": "The result of (24 / 147.6) + 174 is 174.16", "a": 24, "b": 147.6, "c": 174, "op1": "/", "op2": "+", "result": 174.16}
{"question": "Solve: (154 * 182) + 26.96", "answer": "The result of (154 * 182) + 26.96 is 28054.96", "a": 154, "b": 182, "c": 26.96, "op1": "*", "op2": "+", "result": 28054.96}
{"question": "Solve: (52.64 / 131) - 195.49", "answer": "The result of (52.64 / 131) - 195.49 is -195.09", "a": 52.64, "b": 131, "c": 195.49, "op1": "/", "op2": "-", "result": -195.09}
{"question": "Solve: (32 * 124) + 145.14", "answer": "The result of (32 * 124) + 145.14 is 4113.14", "a": 32, "b": 124, "c": 145.14, "op1": "*", "op2": "+", "result": 4113.14}
{"question": "Solve: (162.71 / 178) - 73", "answer": "The result of (162.71 / 178) - 73 is -72.09", "a": 162.71, "b": 178, "c": 73, "op1": "/", "op2": "-", "result": -72.09}
{"question": "Solve: (96 - 35) - 92", "answer": "The result of (96 - 35) - 92 is -31", "a": 96, "b": 35, "c": 92, "op1": "-", "op2": "-", "result": -31}
{"question": "Solve: (41 - 91) / 133", "answer": "The result of (41 - 91) / 133 is -0.38", "a": 41, "b": 91, "c": 133, "op1": "-", "op2": "/", "result": -0.38}
{"question": "Solve: (119.06 * 70) + 157.02", "answer": "The result of (119.06 * 70) + 157.02 is 8491.22", "a": 119.06, "b": 70, "c": 157.02, "op1": "*", "op2": "+", "result": 8491.22}
{"question": "Solve: (76.36 * 73) * 6", "answer": "The result of (76.36 * 73) * 6 is 33445.68", "a": 76.36, "b": 73, "c": 6, "op1": "*", "op2": "*", "result": 33445.68}
{"question": "Solve: (19 - 156) - 192", "answer": "The result of (19 - 156) - 192 is -329", "a": 19, "b": 156, "c": 192, "op1": "-", "op2": "-", "result": -329}
{"question": "Solve: (20 + 88) - 5", "answer": "The result of (20 + 88) - 5 is 103", "a": 20, "b": 88, "c": 5, "op1": "+", "op2": "-", "result": 103}
{"question": "Solve: (135 + 133) - 74.61", "answer": "The result of (135 + 133) - 74.61 is 193.39", "a": 135, "b": 133, "c": 74.61, "op1": "+", "op2": "-", "result": 193.39}
{"question": "Solve: (199 / 109.85) - 180.69", "answer": "The result of (199 / 109.85) - 180.69 is -178.88", "a": 199, "b": 109.85, "c": 180.69, "op1": "/", "op2": "-", "result": -178.88}
{"question": "Solve: (187 + 102) - 168", "answer": "The result of (187 + 102) - 168 is 121", "a": 187, "b": 102, "c": 168, "op1": "+", "op2": "-", "result": 121}
{"question": "Solve: (26 - 148) - 52.97", "answer": "The result of (26 - 148) - 52.97 is -174.97", "a": 26, "b": 148, "c": 52.97, "op1": "-", "op2": "-", "result": -174.97}
{"question": "Solve: (8 * 192) + 36", "answer": "The result of (8 * 192) + 36 is 1572", "a": 8, "b": 192, "c": 36, "op1": "*", "op2": "+", "result": 1572}
{"question": "Solve: (172.85 + 143) * 171", "answer": "The result of (172.85 + 143) * 171 is 54010.35", "a": 172.85, "b": 143, "c": 171, "op1": "+", "op2": "*", "result": 54010.35}
{"question": "Solve: (168.69 - 144) + 69", "answer": "The result of (168.69 - 144) + 69 is 93.69", "a": 168.69, "b": 144, "c": 69, "op1": "-", "op2": "+", "result": 93.69}
{"question": "Solve: (141 / 91) / 11", "answer": "The result of (141 / 91) / 11 is 0.14", "a": 141, "b": 91, "c": 11, "op1": "/", "op2": "/", "result": 0.14}
{"question": "Solve: (4 + 16) * 168", "answer": "The result of (4 + 16) * 168 is 3360", "a": 4, "b": 16, "c": 168, "op1": "+", "op2": "*", "result": 3360}
{"question": "Solve: (197 * 26) + 54.71", "answer": "The result of (197 * 26) + 54.71 is 5176.71", "a": 197, "b": 26, "c": 54.71, "op1": "*", "op2": "+", "result": 5176.71}
{"question": "Solve: (6 - 71.94) / 63", "answer": "The result of (6 - 71.94) / 63 is -1.05", "a": 6, "b": 71.94, "c": 63, "op1": "-", "op2": "/", "result": -1.05}
{"question": "Solve: (70.77 + 26) - 133", "answer": "The result of (70.77 + 26) - 133 is -36.23", "a": 70.77, "b": 26, "c": 133, "op1": "+", "op2": "-", "result": -36.23}
{"question": "Solve: (23 * 169) / 1", "answer": "The result of (23 * 169) / 1 is 3887.0", "a": 23, "b": 169, "c": 1, "op1": "*", "op2": "/", "result": 3887.0}
{"question": "Solve: (123 + 50.96) + 53", "answer": "The result of (123 + 50.96) + 53 is 226.96", "a": 123, "b": 50.96, "c": 53, "op1": "+", "op2": "+", "result": 226.96}
{"question": "Solve: (89 + 74.13) / 185", "answer": "The result of (89 + 74.13) / 185 is 0.88", "a": 89, "b": 74.13, "c": 185, "op1": "+", "op2": "/", "result": 0.88}
{"question": "Solve: (167 - 162.2) + 46.76", "answer": "The result of (167 - 162.2) + 46.76 is 51.56", "a": 167, "b": 162.2, "c": 46.76, "op1": "-", "op2": "+", "result": 51.56}
{"question": "Solve: (35 * 136) - 146.11", "answer": "The result of (35 * 136) - 146.11 is 4613.89", "a": 35, "b": 136, "c": 146.11, "op1": "*", "op2": "-", "result": 4613.89}
{"question": "Solve: (20.49 / 6) / 79", "answer": "The result of (20.49 / 6) / 79 is 0.04", "a": 20.49, "b": 6, "c": 79, "op1": "/", "op2": "/", "result": 0.04}
{"question": "Solve: (144.61 * 172.6) - 33", "answer": "The result of (144.61 * 172.6) - 33 is 24926.69", "a": 144.61, "b": 172.6, "c": 33, "op1": "*", "op2": "-", "result": 24926.69}
{"question": "Solve: (4 + 117) - 123.39", "answer": "The result of (4 + 117) - 123.39 is -2.39", "a": 4, "b": 117, "c": 123.39, "op1": "+", "op2": "-", "result": -2.39}
{"question": "Solve: (114 - 6) - 99", "answer": "The result of (114 - 6) - 99 is 9", "a": 114, "b": 6, "c": 99, "op1": "-", "op2": "-", "result": 9}
{"question": "Solve: (67 - 143) + 78", "answer": "The result of (67 - 143) + 78 is 2", "a": 67, "b": 143, "c": 78, "op1": "-", "op2": "+", "result": 2}
{"question": "Solve: (14 + 88) * 71", "answer": "The result of (14 + 88) * 71 is 7242", "a": 14, "b": 88, "c": 71, "op1": "+", "op2": "*", "result": 7242}
{"question": "Solve: (117 * 7) * 3.77", "answer": "The result of (117 * 7) * 3.77 is 3087.63", "a": 117, "b": 7, "c": 3.77, "op1": "*", "op2": "*", "result": 3087.63}
{"question": "Solve: (136.6 + 44) - 111", "answer": "The result of (136.6 + 44) - 111 is 69.6", "a": 136.6, "b": 44, "c": 111, "op1": "+", "op2": "-", "result": 69.6}
{"question": "Solve: (198 + 165) + 65.6", "answer": "The result of (198 + 165) + 65.6 is 428.6", "a": 198, "b": 165, "c": 65.6, "op1": "+", "op2": "+", "result": 428.6}
{"question": "Solve: (30 / 125.13) + 135", "answer": "The result of (30 / 125.13) + 135 is 135.24", "a": 30, "b": 125.13, "c": 135, "op1": "/", "op2": "+", "result": 135.24}
{"question": "Solve: (1 - 161) + 98", "answer": "The result of (1 - 161) + 98 is -62", "a": 1, "b": 161, "c": 98, "op1": "-", "op2": "+", "result": -62}
{"question": "Solve: (117 / 187) * 188", "answer": "The result of (117 / 187) * 188 is 117.63", "a": 117, "b": 187, "c": 188, "op1": "/", "op2": "*", "result": 117.63}
{"question": "Solve: (185.66 / 143.58) + 122", "answer": "The result of (185.66 / 143.58) + 122 is 123.29", "a": 185.66, "b": 143.58, "c": 122, "op1": "/", "op2": "+", "result": 123.29}
{"question": "Solve: (15 - 41) + 84.04", "answer": "The result of (15 - 41) + 84.04 is 58.04", "a": 15, "b": 41, "c": 84.04, "op1": "-", "op2": "+", "result": 58.04}
{"question": "Solve: (55 - 43.42) - 60.18", "answer": "The result of (55 - 43.42) - 60.18 is -48.6", "a": 55, "b": 43.42, "c": 60.18, "op1": "-", "op2": "-", "result": -48.6}
{"question": "Solve: (200 / 174) - 28", "answer": "The result of (200 / 174) - 28 is -26.85", "a": 200, "b": 174, "c": 28, "op1": "/", "op2": "-", "result": -26.85}
{"question": "Solve: (149 / 155) / 7.14", "answer": "The result of (149 / 155) / 7.14 is 0.13", "a": 149, "b": 155, "c": 7.14, "op1": "/", "op2": "/", "result": 0.13}
{"question": "Solve: (12 + 172.7) + 152", "answer": "The result of (12 + 172.7) + 152 is 336.7", "a": 12, "b": 172.7, "c": 152, "op1": "+", "op2": "+", "result": 336.7}
{"question": "Solve: (199 / 17) / 131", "answer": "The result of (199 / 17) / 131 is 0.09", "a": 199, "b": 17, "c": 131, "op1": "/", "op2": "/", "result": 0.09}
{"question": "Solve: (174.96 * 186) / 53", "answer": "The result of (174.96 * 186) / 53 is 614.01", "a": 174.96, "b": 186, "c": 53, "op1": "*", "op2": "/", "result": 614.01}
{"question": "Solve: (169.17 - 53) * 141", "answer": "The result of (169.17 - 53) * 141 is 16379.97", "a": 169.17, "b": 53, "c": 141, "op1": "-", "op2": "*", "result": 16379.97}
{"question": "Solve: (124.85 + 49) * 134", "answer": "The result of (124.85 + 49) * 134 is 23295.9", "a": 124.85, "b": 49, "c": 134, "op1": "+", "op2": "*", "result": 23295.9}
{"question": "Solve: (142 - 141.3) / 33.4", "answer": "The result of (142 - 141.3) / 33.4 is 0.02", "a": 142, "b": 141.3, "c": 33.4, "op1": "-", "op2": "/", "result": 0.02}
{"question": "Solve: (79 * 130) + 115.0", "answer": "The result of (79 * 130) + 115.0 is 10385.0", "a": 79, "b": 130, "c": 115.0, "op1": "*", "op2": "+", "result": 10385.0}
{"question": "Solve: (59 + 51) * 197", "answer": "The result of (59 + 51) * 197 is 21670", "a": 59, "b": 51, "c": 197, "op1": "+", "op2": "*", "result": 21670}
{"question": "Solve: (28 - 86.9) * 125", "answer": "The result of (28 - 86.9) * 125 is -7362.5", "a": 28, "b": 86.9, "c": 125, "op1": "-", "op2": "*", "result": -7362.5}
{"question": "Solve: (87 + 129) / 125.03", "answer": "The result of (87 + 129) / 125.03 is 1.73", "a": 87, "b": 129, "c": 125.03, "op1": "+", "op2": "/", "result": 1.73}
{"question": "Solve: (101.57 + 186) - 23.77", "answer": "The result of (101.57 + 186) - 23.77 is 263.8", "a": 101.57, "b": 186, "c": 23.77, "op1": "+", "op2": "-", "result": 263.8}
{"question": "Solve: (96 - 43) + 94", "answer": "The result of (96 - 43) + 94 is 147", "a": 96, "b": 43, "c": 94, "op1": "-", "op2": "+", "result": 147}
{"question": "Solve: (16.23 + 165) + 87", "answer": "The result of (16.23 + 165) + 87 is 268.23", "a": 16.23, "b": 165, "c": 87, "op1": "+", "op2": "+", "result": 268.23}
{"question": "Solve: (80 / 163) + 82", "answer": "The result of (80 / 163) + 82 is 82.49", "a": 80, "b": 163, "c": 82, "op1": "/", "op2": "+", "result": 82.49}
{"question": "Solve: (162 + 172.46) * 144.14", "answer": "The result of (162 + 172.46) * 144.14 is 48209.06", "a": 162, "b": 172.46, "c": 144.14, "op1": "+", "op2": "*", "result": 48209.06}
{"question": "Solve: (59 + 125) - 4", "answer": "The result of (59 + 125) - 4 is 180", "a": 59, "b": 125, "c": 4, "op1": "+", "op2": "-", "result": 180}
{"question": "Solve: (114.03 - 67.82) - 114", "answer": "The result of (114.03 - 67.82) - 114 is -67.79", "a": 114.03, "b": 67.82, "c": 114, "op1": "-", "op2": "-", "result": -67.79}
{"question": "Solve: (142 * 80) / 187", "answer": "The result of (142 * 80) / 187 is 60.75", "a": 142, "b": 80, "c": 187, "op1": "*", "op2": "/", "result": 60.75}
{"question": "Solve: (33.66 + 28) - 79", "answer": "The result of (33.66 + 28) - 79 is -17.34", "a": 33.66, "b": 28, "c": 79, "op1": "+", "op2": "-", "result": -17.34}
{"question": "Solve: (110 * 7) - 141.11", "answer": "The result of (110 * 7) - 141.11 is 628.89", "a": 110, "b": 7, "c": 141.11, "op1": "*", "op2": "-", "result": 628.89}
{"question": "Solve: (176 * 182.91) / 126", "answer": "The result of (176 * 182.91) / 126 is 255.49", "a": 176, "b": 182.91, "c": 126, "op1": "*", "op2": "/", "result": 255.49}
{"question": "Solve: (71 * 149) + 121", "answer": "The result of (71 * 149) + 121 is 10700", "a": 71, "b": 149, "c": 121, "op1": "*", "op2": "+", "result": 10700}
{"question": "Solve: (34 / 42) + 145.16", "answer": "The result of (34 / 42) + 145.16 is 145.97", "a": 34, "b": 42, "c": 145.16, "op1": "/", "op2": "+", "result": 145.97}
{"question": "Solve: (75 - 50) * 177.2", "answer": "The result of (75 - 50) * 177.2 is 4430.0", "a": 75, "b": 50, "c": 177.2, "op1": "-", "op2": "*", "result": 4430.0}
{"question": "Solve: (13 + 44) + 81.08", "answer": "The result of (13 + 44) + 81.08 is 138.08", "a": 13, "b": 44, "c": 81.08, "op1": "+", "op2": "+", "result": 138.08}
{"question": "Solve: (53 + 188) / 168", "answer": "The result of (53 + 188) / 168 is 1.43", "a": 53, "b": 188, "c": 168, "op1": "+", "op2": "/", "result": 1.43}
{"question": "Solve: (14 - 140.63) - 39.91", "answer": "The result of (14 - 140.63) - 39.91 is -166.54", "a": 14, "b": 140.63, "c": 39.91, "op1": "-", "op2": "-", "result": -166.54}
{"question": "Solve: (178 - 38) * 132", "answer": "The result of (178 - 38) * 132 is 18480", "a": 178, "b": 38, "c": 132, "op1": "-", "op2": "*", "result": 18480}
{"question": "Solve: (12 * 89) - 172", "answer": "The result of (12 * 89) - 172 is 896", "a": 12, "b": 89, "c": 172, "op1": "*", "op2": "-", "result": 896}
{"question": "Solve: (14.82 + 1.95) - 133", "answer": "The result of (14.82 + 1.95) - 133 is -116.23", "a": 14.82, "b": 1.95, "c": 133, "op1": "+", "op2": "-", "result": -116.23}
{"question": "Solve: (171 + 118) / 191", "answer": "The result of (171 + 118) / 191 is 1.51", "a": 171, "b": 118, "c": 191, "op1": "+", "op2": "/", "result": 1.51}
{"question": "Solve: (75 * 143) / 146.07", "answer": "The result of (75 * 143) / 146.07 is 73.42", "a": 75, "b": 143, "c": 146.07, "op1": "*", "op2": "/", "result": 73.42}
{"question": "Solve: (161 / 73) + 93", "answer": "The result of (161 / 73) + 93 is 95.21", "a": 161, "b": 73, "c": 93, "op1": "/", "op2": "+", "result": 95.21}
{"question": "Solve: (122 * 97) - 26", "answer": "The result of (122 * 97) - 26 is 11808", "a": 122, "b": 97, "c": 26, "op1": "*", "op2": "-", "result": 11808}
{"question": "Solve: (70 + 133) - 28", "answer": "The result of (70 + 133) - 28 is 175", "a": 70, "b": 133, "c": 28, "op1": "+", "op2": "-", "result": 175}
{"question": "Solve: (31.24 + 94) + 59.53", "answer": "The result of (31.24 + 94) + 59.53 is 184.77", "a": 31.24, "b": 94, "c": 59.53, "op1": "+", "op2": "+", "result": 184.77}
{"question": "Solve: (192 * 40) / 69", "answer": "The result of (192 * 40) / 69 is 111.3", "a": 192, "b": 40, "c": 69, "op1": "*", "op2": "/", "result": 111.3}
{"question": "Solve: (29.82 - 72.65) * 52.62", "answer": "The result of (29.82 - 72.65) * 52.62 is -2253.71", "a": 29.82, "b": 72.65, "c": 52.62, "op1": "-", "op2": "*", "result": -2253.71}
{"question": "Solve: (62 - 89) + 141", "answer": "The result of (62 - 89) + 141 is 114", "a": 62, "b": 89, "c": 141, "op1": "-", "op2": "+", "result": 114}
{"question": "Solve: (92 + 177.71) * 74", "answer": "The result of (92 + 177.71) * 74 is 19958.54", "a": 92, "b": 177.71, "c": 74, "op1": "+", "op2": "*", "result": 19958.54}
{"question": "Solve: (146 - 156.34) * 21", "answer": "The result of (146 - 156.34) * 21 is -217.14", "a": 146, "b": 156.34, "c": 21, "op1": "-", "op2": "*", "result": -217.14}
{"question": "Solve: (190.82 + 77) + 153.98", "answer": "The result of (190.82 + 77) + 153.98 is 421.8", "a": 190.82, "b": 77, "c": 153.98, "op1": "+", "op2": "+", "result": 421.8}
{"question": "Solve: (169.96 + 36) + 60.65", "answer": "The result of (169.96 + 36) + 60.65 is 266.61", "a": 169.96, "b": 36, "c": 60.65, "op1": "+", "op2": "+", "result": 266.61}
{"question": "Solve: (142 + 142.83) * 39", "answer": "The result of (142 + 142.83) * 39 is 11108.37", "a": 142, "b": 142.83, "c": 39, "op1": "+", "op2": "*", "result": 11108.37}
{"question": "Solve: (185 - 184) - 101.51", "answer": "The result of (185 - 184) - 101.51 is -100.51", "a": 185, "b": 184, "c": 101.51, "op1": "-", "op2": "-", "result": -100.51}
{"question": "Solve: (34 - 38.12) + 183", "answer": "The result of (34 - 38.12) + 183 is 178.88", "a": 34, "b": 38.12, "c": 183, "op1": "-", "op2": "+", "result": 178.88}
{"question": "Solve: (46 * 133) + 123", "answer": "The result of (46 * 133) + 123 is 6241", "a": 46, "b": 133, "c": 123, "op1": "*", "op2": "+", "result": 6241}
{"question": "Solve: (181.18 / 90) / 137", "answer": "The result of (181.18 / 90) / 137 is 0.01", "a": 181.18, "b": 90, "c": 137, "op1": "/", "op2": "/", "result": 0.01}
{"question": "Solve: (71 * 152) / 127.94", "answer": "The result of (71 * 152) / 127.94 is 84.35", "a": 71, "b": 152, "c": 127.94, "op1": "*", "op2": "/", "result": 84.35}
{"question": "Solve: (197.12 + 184) - 138", "answer": "The result of (197.12 + 184) - 138 is 243.12", "a": 197.12, "b": 184, "c": 138, "op1": "+", "op2": "-", "result": 243.12}
{"question": "Solve: (115.34 * 69.95) - 151.3", "answer": "The result of (115.34 * 69.95) - 151.3 is 7916.73", "a": 115.34, "b": 69.95, "c": 151.3, "op1": "*", "op2": "-", "result": 7916.73}
{"question": "Solve: (47.42 / 19) - 61", "answer": "The result of (47.42 / 19) - 61 is -58.5", "a": 47.42, "b": 19, "c": 61, "op1": "/", "op2": "-", "result": -58.5}
{"question": "Solve: (63 - 70) + 146", "answer": "The result of (63 - 70) + 146 is 139", "a": 63, "b": 70, "c": 146, "op1": "-", "op2": "+", "result": 139}
{"question": "Solve: (152 + 58) + 62.44", "answer": "The result of (152 + 58) + 62.44 is 272.44", "a": 152, "b": 58, "c": 62.44, "op1": "+", "op2": "+", "result": 272.44}
{"question": "Solve: (62.32 + 38) * 68", "answer": "The result of (62.32 + 38) * 68 is 6821.76", "a": 62.32, "b": 38, "c": 68, "op1": "+", "op2": "*", "result": 6821.76}
{"question": "Solve: (66 + 128) + 55.38", "answer": "The result of (66 + 128) + 55.38 is 249.38", "a": 66, "b": 128, "c": 55.38, "op1": "+", "op2": "+", "result": 249.38}
{"question": "Solve: (31.99 - 12) + 67", "answer": "The result of (31.99 - 12) + 67 is 86.99", "a": 31.99, "b": 12, "c": 67, "op1": "-", "op2": "+", "result": 86.99}
{"question": "Solve: (52 + 199.17) * 76", "answer": "The result of (52 + 199.17) * 76 is 19088.92", "a": 52, "b": 199.17, "c": 76, "op1": "+", "op2": "*", "result": 19088.92}
{"question": "Solve: (46 - 159.83) / 96", "answer": "The result of (46 - 159.83) / 96 is -1.19", "a": 46, "b": 159.83, "c": 96, "op1": "-", "op2": "/", "result": -1.19}
{"question": "Solve: (55.76 / 190.94) + 23", "answer": "The result of (55.76 / 190.94) + 23 is 23.29", "a": 55.76, "b": 190.94, "c": 23, "op1": "/", "op2": "+", "result": 23.29}
{"question": "Solve: (82 / 143.41) + 115.39", "answer": "The result of (82 / 143.41) + 115.39 is 115.96", "a": 82, "b": 143.41, "c": 115.39, "op1": "/", "op2": "+", "result": 115.96}
{"question": "Solve: (152 * 122) / 67.83", "answer": "The result of (152 * 122) / 67.83 is 273.39", "a": 152, "b": 122, "c": 67.83, "op1": "*", "op2": "/", "result": 273.39}
{"question": "Solve: (187 + 178) * 3", "answer": "The result of (187 + 178) * 3 is 1095", "a": 187, "b": 178, "c": 3, "op1": "+", "op2": "*", "result": 1095}
{"question": "Solve: (107 - 135) - 106", "answer": "The result of (107 - 135) - 106 is -134", "a": 107, "b": 135, "c": 106, "op1": "-", "op2": "-", "result": -134}
{"question": "Solve: (4 - 145) / 2", "answer": "The result of (4 - 145) / 2 is -70.5", "a": 4, "b": 145, "c": 2, "op1": "-", "op2": "/", "result": -70.5}
{"question": "Solve: (57.03 + 146) - 196.53", "answer": "The result of (57.03 + 146) - 196.53 is 6.5", "a": 57.03, "b": 146, "c": 196.53, "op1": "+", "op2": "-", "result": 6.5}
{"question": "Solve: (52.27 + 130) * 81.07", "answer": "The result of (52.27 + 130) * 81.07 is 14776.63", "a": 52.27, "b": 130, "c": 81.07, "op1": "+", "op2": "*", "result": 14776.63}
{"question": "Solve: (107.91 / 187.3) / 25", "answer": "The result of (107.91 / 187.3) / 25 is 0.02", "a": 107.91, "b": 187.3, "c": 25, "op1": "/", "op2": "/", "result": 0.02}
{"question": "Solve: (134 / 162.56) - 78", "answer": "The result of (134 / 162.56) - 78 is -77.18", "a": 134, "b": 162.56, "c": 78, "op1": "/", "op2": "-", "result": -77.18}
{"question": "Solve: (60.92 + 55.46) / 62.3", "answer": "The result of (60.92 + 55.46) / 62.3 is 1.87", "a": 60.92, "b": 55.46, "c": 62.3, "op1": "+", "op2": "/", "result": 1.87}
{"question": "Solve: (150 * 95) / 189", "answer": "The result of (150 * 95) / 189 is 75.4", "a": 150, "b": 95, "c": 189, "op1": "*", "op2": "/", "result": 75.4}
{"question": "Solve: (107 - 104.06) / 170", "answer": "The result of (107 - 104.06) / 170 is 0.02", "a": 107, "b": 104.06, "c": 170, "op1": "-", "op2": "/", "result": 0.02}
{"question": "Solve: (155.11 / 7) - 156.54", "answer": "The result of (155.11 / 7) - 156.54 is -134.38", "a": 155.11, "b": 7, "c": 156.54, "op1": "/", "op2": "-", "result": -134.38}
{"question": "Solve: (149 * 145) - 130", "answer": "The result of (149 * 145) - 130 is 21475", "a": 149, "b": 145, "c": 130, "op1": "*", "op2": "-", "result": 21475}
{"question": "Solve: (16 - 32) - 58", "answer": "The result of (16 - 32) - 58 is -74", "a": 16, "b": 32, "c": 58, "op1": "-", "op2": "-", "result": -74}
{"question": "Solve: (86.24 / 28.28) - 60", "answer": "The result of (86.24 / 28.28) - 60 is -56.95", "a": 86.24, "b": 28.28, "c": 60, "op1": "/", "op2": "-", "result": -56.95}
{"question": "Solve: (79 - 29.41) + 29", "answer": "The result of (79 - 29.41) + 29 is 78.59", "a": 79, "b": 29.41, "c": 29, "op1": "-", "op2": "+", "result": 78.59}
{"question": "Solve: (15 * 33) - 66.22", "answer": "The result of (15 * 33) - 66.22 is 428.78", "a": 15, "b": 33, "c": 66.22, "op1": "*", "op2": "-", "result": 428.78}
{"question": "Solve: (31 + 148.7) * 86", "answer": "The result of (31 + 148.7) * 86 is 15454.2", "a": 31, "b": 148.7, "c": 86, "op1": "+", "op2": "*", "result": 15454.2}
{"question": "Solve: (60.78 + 14.25) - 6", "answer": "The result of (60.78 + 14.25) - 6 is 69.03", "a": 60.78, "b": 14.25, "c": 6, "op1": "+", "op2": "-", "result": 69.03}
{"question": "Solve: (135 * 62) * 124.39", "answer": "The result of (135 * 62) * 124.39 is 1041144.3", "a": 135, "b": 62, "c": 124.39, "op1": "*", "op2": "*", "result": 1041144.3}
{"question": "Solve: (177 - 28) * 139", "answer": "The result of (177 - 28) * 139 is 20711", "a": 177, "b": 28, "c": 139, "op1": "-", "op2": "*", "result": 20711}
{"question": "Solve: (12 - 115) + 57.69", "answer": "The result of (12 - 115) + 57.69 is -45.31", "a": 12, "b": 115, "c": 57.69, "op1": "-", "op2": "+", "result": -45.31}
{"question": "Solve: (183 + 40) + 28", "answer": "The result of (183 + 40) + 28 is 251", "a": 183, "b": 40, "c": 28, "op1": "+", "op2": "+", "result": 251}
{"question": "Solve: (83 * 170) - 182", "answer": "The result of (83 * 170) - 182 is 13928", "a": 83, "b": 170, "c": 182, "op1": "*", "op2": "-", "result": 13928}
{"question": "Solve: (133 * 175) / 73", "answer": "The result of (133 * 175) / 73 is 318.84", "a": 133, "b": 175, "c": 73, "op1": "*", "op2": "/", "result": 318.84}
{"question": "Solve: (141 * 41) + 26", "answer": "The result of (141 * 41) + 26 is 5807", "a": 141, "b": 41, "c": 26, "op1": "*", "op2": "+", "result": 5807}
{"question": "Solve: (197.56 + 157.83) + 46.56", "answer": "The result of (197.56 + 157.83) + 46.56 is 401.95", "a": 197.56, "b": 157.83, "c": 46.56, "op1": "+", "op2": "+", "result": 401.95}
{"question": "Solve: (77 * 45) / 83", "answer": "The result of (77 * 45) / 83 is 41.75", "a": 77, "b": 45, "c": 83, "op1": "*", "op2": "/", "result": 41.75}
{"question": "Solve: (76.16 + 28) / 23.45", "answer": "The result of (76.16 + 28) / 23.45 is 4.44", "a": 76.16, "b": 28, "c": 23.45, "op1": "+", "op2": "/", "result": 4.44}
{"question": "Solve: (101 / 129) * 111", "answer": "The result of (101 / 129) * 111 is 86.91", "a": 101, "b": 129, "c": 111, "op1": "/", "op2": "*", "result": 86.91}
{"question": "Solve: (53 * 38) + 186.29", "answer": "The result of (53 * 38) + 186.29 is 2200.29", "a": 53, "b": 38, "c": 186.29, "op1": "*", "op2": "+", "result": 2200.29}
{"question": "Solve: (67 * 91.1) * 11", "answer": "The result of (67 * 91.1) * 11 is 67140.7", "a": 67, "b": 91.1, "c": 11, "op1": "*", "op2": "*", "result": 67140.7}
{"question": "Solve: (199.94 - 16.51) - 153", "answer": "The result of (199.94 - 16.51) - 153 is 30.43", "a": 199.94, "b": 16.51, "c": 153, "op1": "-", "op2": "-", "result": 30.43}
{"question": "Solve: (71.23 + 190) / 56", "answer": "The result of (71.23 + 190) / 56 is 4.66", "a": 71.23, "b": 190, "c": 56, "op1": "+", "op2": "/", "result": 4.66}
{"question": "Solve: (99 + 142.94) + 53", "answer": "The result of (99 + 142.94) + 53 is 294.94", "a": 99, "b": 142.94, "c": 53, "op1": "+", "op2": "+", "result": 294.94}
{"question": "Solve: (106 + 143) - 151", "answer": "The result of (106 + 143) - 151 is 98", "a": 106, "b": 143, "c": 151, "op1": "+", "op2": "-", "result": 98}
{"question": "Solve: (9 + 101) - 34", "answer": "The result of (9 + 101) - 34 is 76", "a": 9, "b": 101, "c": 34, "op1": "+", "op2": "-", "result": 76}
{"question": "Solve: (37.13 / 93.59) * 120", "answer": "The result of (37.13 / 93.59) * 120 is 47.61", "a": 37.13, "b": 93.59, "c": 120, "op1": "/", "op2": "*", "result": 47.61}
{"question": "Solve: (4 + 153) * 132.42", "answer": "The result of (4 + 153) * 132.42 is 20789.94", "a": 4, "b": 153, "c": 132.42, "op1": "+", "op2": "*", "result": 20789.94}
{"question": "Solve: (198 + 69) - 4.63", "answer": "The result of (198 + 69) - 4.63 is 262.37", "a": 198, "b": 69, "c": 4.63, "op1": "+", "op2": "-", "result": 262.37}
{"question": "Solve: (175 + 92) * 195.76", "answer": "The result of (175 + 92) * 195.76 is 52267.92", "a": 175, "b": 92, "c": 195.76, "op1": "+", "op2": "*", "result": 52267.92}
{"question": "Solve: (116 * 167.63) + 148", "answer": "The result of (116 * 167.63) + 148 is 19593.08", "a": 116, "b": 167.63, "c": 148, "op1": "*", "op2": "+", "result": 19593.08}
{"question": "Solve: (77 + 67) * 30", "answer": "The result of (77 + 67) * 30 is 4320", "a": 77, "b": 67, "c": 30, "op1": "+", "op2": "*", "result": 4320}
{"question": "Solve: (39.69 + 68) / 112", "answer": "The result of (39.69 + 68) / 112 is 0.96", "a": 39.69, "b": 68, "c": 112, "op1": "+", "op2": "/", "result": 0.96}
{"question": "Solve: (8.83 - 137.72) - 6.65", "answer": "The result of (8.83 - 137.72) - 6.65 is -135.54", "a": 8.83, "b": 137.72, "c": 6.65, "op1": "-", "op2": "-", "result": -135.54}
{"question": "Solve: (96 / 180) / 66", "answer": "The result of (96 / 180) / 66 is 0.01", "a": 96, "b": 180, "c": 66, "op1": "/", "op2": "/", "result": 0.01}
{"question": "Solve: (42.1 - 107) - 22", "answer": "The result of (42.1 - 107) - 22 is -86.9", "a": 42.1, "b": 107, "c": 22, "op1": "-", "op2": "-", "result": -86.9}
{"question": "Solve: (38.64 + 11.96) / 33", "answer": "The result of (38.64 + 11.96) / 33 is 1.53", "a": 38.64, "b": 11.96, "c": 33, "op1": "+", "op2": "/", "result": 1.53}
{"question": "Solve: (50 - 167) + 192.43", "answer": "The result of (50 - 167) + 192.43 is 75.43", "a": 50, "b": 167, "c": 192.43, "op1": "-", "op2": "+", "result": 75.43}
{"question": "Solve: (119 - 182.02) * 99", "answer": "The result of (119 - 182.02) * 99 is -6238.98", "a": 119, "b": 182.02, "c": 99, "op1": "-", "op2": "*", "result": -6238.98}
{"question": "Solve: (145 / 99.55) - 102.75", "answer": "The result of (145 / 99.55) - 102.75 is -101.29", "a": 145, "b": 99.55, "c": 102.75, "op1": "/", "op2": "-", "result": -101.29}
{"question": "Solve: (115 / 154.21) + 170.92", "answer": "The result of (115 / 154.21) + 170.92 is 171.67", "a": 115, "b": 154.21, "c": 170.92, "op1": "/", "op2": "+", "result": 171.67}
{"question": "Solve: (47 - 146) + 106", "answer": "The result of (47 - 146) + 106 is 7", "a": 47, "b": 146, "c": 106, "op1": "-", "op2": "+", "result": 7}
{"question": "Solve: (168 * 135.43) + 183", "answer": "The result of (168 * 135.43) + 183 is 22935.24", "a": 168, "b": 135.43, "c": 183, "op1": "*", "op2": "+", "result": 22935.24}
{"question": "Solve: (116 - 79) + 96", "answer": "The result of (116 - 79) + 96 is 133", "a": 116, "b": 79, "c": 96, "op1": "-", "op2": "+", "result": 133}
{"question": "Solve: (51 * 174) - 12", "answer": "The result of (51 * 174) - 12 is 8862", "a": 51, "b": 174, "c": 12, "op1": "*", "op2": "-", "result": 8862}
{"question": "Solve: (40 + 142) - 122", "answer": "The result of (40 + 142) - 122 is 60", "a": 40, "b": 142, "c": 122, "op1": "+", "op2": "-", "result": 60}
{"question": "Solve: (197 + 129.84) - 2", "answer": "The result of (197 + 129.84) - 2 is 324.84", "a": 197, "b": 129.84, "c": 2, "op1": "+", "op2": "-", "result": 324.84}
{"question": "Solve: (3 + 94) + 186", "answer": "The result of (3 + 94) + 186 is 283", "a": 3, "b": 94, "c": 186, "op1": "+", "op2": "+", "result": 283}
{"question": "Solve: (98 * 14) * 56", "answer": "The result of (98 * 14) * 56 is 76832", "a": 98, "b": 14, "c": 56, "op1": "*", "op2": "*", "result": 76832}
{"question": "Solve: (82.35 - 128) * 4", "answer": "The result of (82.35 - 128) * 4 is -182.6", "a": 82.35, "b": 128, "c": 4, "op1": "-", "op2": "*", "result": -182.6}
{"question": "Solve: (183.03 * 95) + 81", "answer": "The result of (183.03 * 95) + 81 is 17468.85", "a": 183.03, "b": 95, "c": 81, "op1": "*", "op2": "+", "result": 17468.85}
{"question": "Solve: (144 * 145.15) - 42", "answer": "The result of (144 * 145.15) - 42 is 20859.6", "a": 144, "b": 145.15, "c": 42, "op1": "*", "op2": "-", "result": 20859.6}
{"question": "Solve: (4 / 111.73) - 95", "answer": "The result of (4 / 111.73) - 95 is -94.96", "a": 4, "b": 111.73, "c": 95, "op1": "/", "op2": "-", "result": -94.96}
{"question": "Solve: (117 + 11) / 200", "answer": "The result of (117 + 11) / 200 is 0.64", "a": 117, "b": 11, "c": 200, "op1": "+", "op2": "/", "result": 0.64}
{"question": "Solve: (15.14 + 90) + 19", "answer": "The result of (15.14 + 90) + 19 is 124.14", "a": 15.14, "b": 90, "c": 19, "op1": "+", "op2": "+", "result": 124.14}
{"question": "Solve: (99 + 116.46) - 170.32", "answer": "The result of (99 + 116.46) - 170.32 is 45.14", "a": 99, "b": 116.46, "c": 170.32, "op1": "+", "op2": "-", "result": 45.14}
{"question": "Solve: (121 / 163) + 103", "answer": "The result of (121 / 163) + 103 is 103.74", "a": 121, "b": 163, "c": 103, "op1": "/", "op2": "+", "result": 103.74}
{"question": "Solve: (2 + 90) + 133", "answer": "The result of (2 + 90) + 133 is 225", "a": 2, "b": 90, "c": 133, "op1": "+", "op2": "+", "result": 225}
{"question": "Solve: (90 - 103) * 109", "answer": "The result of (90 - 103) * 109 is -1417", "a": 90, "b": 103, "c": 109, "op1": "-", "op2": "*", "result": -1417}
{"question": "Solve: (53 - 49.27) + 39", "answer": "The result of (53 - 49.27) + 39 is 42.73", "a": 53, "b": 49.27, "c": 39, "op1": "-", "op2": "+", "result": 42.73}
{"question": "Solve: (140 + 112) * 142.93", "answer": "The result of (140 + 112) * 142.93 is 36018.36", "a": 140, "b": 112, "c": 142.93, "op1": "+", "op2": "*", "result": 36018.36}
{"question": "Solve: (62 + 24) * 56", "answer": "The result of (62 + 24) * 56 is 4816", "a": 62, "b": 24, "c": 56, "op1": "+", "op2": "*", "result": 4816}
{"question": "Solve: (52 * 65) / 91.33", "answer": "The result of (52 * 65) / 91.33 is 37.01", "a": 52, "b": 65, "c": 91.33, "op1": "*", "op2": "/", "result": 37.01}
{"question": "Solve: (44 - 135) + 157", "answer": "The result of (44 - 135) + 157 is 66", "a": 44, "b": 135, "c": 157, "op1": "-", "op2": "+", "result": 66}
{"question": "Solve: (4 + 85) - 196", "answer": "The result of (4 + 85) - 196 is -107", "a": 4, "b": 85, "c": 196, "op1": "+", "op2": "-", "result": -107}
{"question": "Solve: (29 / 106.33) - 50", "answer": "The result of (29 / 106.33) - 50 is -49.73", "a": 29, "b": 106.33, "c": 50, "op1": "/", "op2": "-", "result": -49.73}
{"question": "Solve: (118 - 116) - 2", "answer": "The result of (118 - 116) - 2 is 0", "a": 118, "b": 116, "c": 2, "op1": "-", "op2": "-", "result": 0}
{"question": "Solve: (141 - 122) + 78.23", "answer": "The result of (141 - 122) + 78.23 is 97.23", "a": 141, "b": 122, "c": 78.23, "op1": "-", "op2": "+", "result": 97.23}
{"question": "Solve: (48 + 37) - 198", "answer": "The result of (48 + 37) - 198 is -113", "a": 48, "b": 37, "c": 198, "op1": "+", "op2": "-", "result": -113}
{"question": "Solve: (160.41 / 121.06) + 6", "answer": "The result of (160.41 / 121.06) + 6 is 7.33", "a": 160.41, "b": 121.06, "c": 6, "op1": "/", "op2": "+", "result": 7.33}
{"question": "Solve: (15 + 9) - 39", "answer": "The result of (15 + 9) - 39 is -15", "a": 15, "b": 9, "c": 39, "op1": "+", "op2": "-", "result": -15}
{"question": "Solve: (51 + 172.26) - 195", "answer": "The result of (51 + 172.26) - 195 is 28.26", "a": 51, "b": 172.26, "c": 195, "op1": "+", "op2": "-", "result": 28.26}
{"question": "Solve: (109 - 185) * 14", "answer": "The result of (109 - 185) * 14 is -1064", "a": 109, "b": 185, "c": 14, "op1": "-", "op2": "*", "result": -1064}
{"question": "Solve: (193 / 88) - 117.71", "answer": "The result of (193 / 88) - 117.71 is -115.52", "a": 193, "b": 88, "c": 117.71, "op1": "/", "op2": "-", "result": -115.52}
{"question": "Solve: (175 + 19) * 134.96", "answer": "The result of (175 + 19) * 134.96 is 26182.24", "a": 175, "b": 19, "c": 134.96, "op1": "+", "op2": "*", "result": 26182.24}
{"question": "Solve: (69 - 48) - 179", "answer": "The result of (69 - 48) - 179 is -158", "a": 69, "b": 48, "c": 179, "op1": "-", "op2": "-", "result": -158}
{"question": "Solve: (67 - 27) + 45", "answer": "The result of (67 - 27) + 45 is 85", "a": 67, "b": 27, "c": 45, "op1": "-", "op2": "+", "result": 85}
{"question": "Solve: (82 + 44) - 61.83", "answer": "The result of (82 + 44) - 61.83 is 64.17", "a": 82, "b": 44, "c": 61.83, "op1": "+", "op2": "-", "result": 64.17}
{"question": "Solve: (2 + 112.12) - 64", "answer": "The result of (2 + 112.12) - 64 is 50.12", "a": 2, "b": 112.12, "c": 64, "op1": "+", "op2": "-", "result": 50.12}
{"question": "Solve: (160.97 - 113) + 189", "answer": "The result of (160.97 - 113) + 189 is 236.97", "a": 160.97, "b": 113, "c": 189, "op1": "-", "op2": "+", "result": 236.97}
{"question": "Solve: (59 + 121) + 59", "answer": "The result of (59 + 121) + 59 is 239", "a": 59, "b": 121, "c": 59, "op1": "+", "op2": "+", "result": 239}
{"question": "Solve: (154 + 2) - 122", "answer": "The result of (154 + 2) - 122 is 34", "a": 154, "b": 2, "c": 122, "op1": "+", "op2": "-", "result": 34}
{"question": "Solve: (143 / 167) * 73", "answer": "The result of (143 / 167) * 73 is 62.51", "a": 143, "b": 167, "c": 73, "op1": "/", "op2": "*", "result": 62.51}
{"question": "Solve: (91.71 / 54) + 184.29", "answer": "The result of (91.71 / 54) + 184.29 is 185.99", "a": 91.71, "b": 54, "c": 184.29, "op1": "/", "op2": "+", "result": 185.99}
{"question": "Solve: (123 * 187.6) / 128", "answer": "The result of (123 * 187.6) / 128 is 180.27", "a": 123, "b": 187.6, "c": 128, "op1": "*", "op2": "/", "result": 180.27}
{"question": "Solve: (190 + 86) - 38", "answer": "The result of (190 + 86) - 38 is 238", "a": 190, "b": 86, "c": 38, "op1": "+", "op2": "-", "result": 238}
{"question": "Solve: (22 - 129) * 107", "answer": "The result of (22 - 129) * 107 is -11449", "a": 22, "b": 129, "c": 107, "op1": "-", "op2": "*", "result": -11449}
{"question": "Solve: (145 + 148.31) - 152", "answer": "The result of (145 + 148.31) - 152 is 141.31", "a": 145, "b": 148.31, "c": 152, "op1": "+", "op2": "-", "result": 141.31}
{"question": "Solve: (135 - 183.98) / 151", "answer": "The result of (135 - 183.98) / 151 is -0.32", "a": 135, "b": 183.98, "c": 151, "op1": "-", "op2": "/", "result": -0.32}
{"question": "Solve: (18 / 44.88) + 124", "answer": "The result of (18 / 44.88) + 124 is 124.4", "a": 18, "b": 44.88, "c": 124, "op1": "/", "op2": "+", "result": 124.4}
{"question": "Solve: (129 * 177) - 191.34", "answer": "The result of (129 * 177) - 191.34 is 22641.66", "a": 129, "b": 177, "c": 191.34, "op1": "*", "op2": "-", "result": 22641.66}
{"question": "Solve: (81 * 166.6) - 45.71", "answer": "The result of (81 * 166.6) - 45.71 is 13448.89", "a": 81, "b": 166.6, "c": 45.71, "op1": "*", "op2": "-", "result": 13448.89}
{"question": "Solve: (67 / 69) - 73.5", "answer": "The result of (67 / 69) - 73.5 is -72.53", "a": 67, "b": 69, "c": 73.5, "op1": "/", "op2": "-", "result": -72.53}
{"question": "Solve: (176 - 119) / 183", "answer": "The result of (176 - 119) / 183 is 0.31", "a": 176, "b": 119, "c": 183, "op1": "-", "op2": "/", "result": 0.31}
{"question": "Solve: (47 * 185) - 5", "answer": "The result of (47 * 185) - 5 is 8690", "a": 47, "b": 185, "c": 5, "op1": "*", "op2": "-", "result": 8690}
{"question": "Solve: (26.8 - 24) * 112", "answer": "The result of (26.8 - 24) * 112 is 313.6", "a": 26.8, "b": 24, "c": 112, "op1": "-", "op2": "*", "result": 313.6}
{"question": "Solve: (154 * 175) / 191.81", "answer": "The result of (154 * 175) / 191.81 is 140.5", "a": 154, "b": 175, "c": 191.81, "op1": "*", "op2": "/", "result": 140.5}
{"question": "Solve: (93 - 143.81) * 175", "answer": "The result of (93 - 143.81) * 175 is -8891.75", "a": 93, "b": 143.81, "c": 175, "op1": "-", "op2": "*", "result": -8891.75}
{"question": "Solve: (155.09 * 163.52) + 163.54", "answer": "The result of (155.09 * 163.52) + 163.54 is 25523.86", "a": 155.09, "b": 163.52, "c": 163.54, "op1": "*", "op2": "+", "result": 25523.86}
{"question": "Solve: (138 / 12) + 138", "answer": "The result of (138 / 12) + 138 is 149.5", "a": 138, "b": 12, "c": 138, "op1": "/", "op2": "+", "result": 149.5}
{"question": "Solve: (75 + 49) + 165", "answer": "The result of (75 + 49) + 165 is 289", "a": 75, "b": 49, "c": 165, "op1": "+", "op2": "+", "result": 289}
{"question": "Solve: (118 * 141) * 48.29", "answer": "The result of (118 * 141) * 48.29 is 803449.02", "a": 118, "b": 141, "c": 48.29, "op1": "*", "op2": "*", "result": 803449.02}
{"question": "Solve: (37.47 - 178.43) / 103.99", "answer": "The result of (37.47 - 178.43) / 103.99 is -1.36", "a": 37.47, "b": 178.43, "c": 103.99, "op1": "-", "op2": "/", "result": -1.36}
{"question": "Solve: (123 - 174) - 1", "answer": "The result of (123 - 174) - 1 is -52", "a": 123, "b": 174, "c": 1, "op1": "-", "op2": "-", "result": -52}
{"question": "Solve: (53 + 61) * 128.44", "answer": "The result of (53 + 61) * 128.44 is 14642.16", "a": 53, "b": 61, "c": 128.44, "op1": "+", "op2": "*", "result": 14642.16}
{"question": "Solve: (75 + 101) - 82", "answer": "The result of (75 + 101) - 82 is 94", "a": 75, "b": 101, "c": 82, "op1": "+", "op2": "-", "result": 94}
{"question": "Solve: (106.74 - 139) - 171.5", "answer": "The result of (106.74 - 139) - 171.5 is -203.76", "a": 106.74, "b": 139, "c": 171.5, "op1": "-", "op2": "-", "result": -203.76}
{"question": "Solve: (159 * 73) - 56", "answer": "The result of (159 * 73) - 56 is 11551", "a": 159, "b": 73, "c": 56, "op1": "*", "op2": "-", "result": 11551}
{"question": "Solve: (179 * 73) - 126", "answer": "The result of (179 * 73) - 126 is 12941", "a": 179, "b": 73, "c": 126, "op1": "*", "op2": "-", "result": 12941}
{"question": "Solve: (163.63 / 3) / 96", "answer": "The result of (163.63 / 3) / 96 is 0.57", "a": 163.63, "b": 3, "c": 96, "op1": "/", "op2": "/", "result": 0.57}
{"question": "Solve: (100.42 + 52) - 17", "answer": "The result of (100.42 + 52) - 17 is 135.42", "a": 100.42, "b": 52, "c": 17, "op1": "+", "op2": "-", "result": 135.42}
{"question": "Solve: (125.53 + 92) / 14.23", "answer": "The result of (125.53 + 92) / 14.23 is 15.29", "a": 125.53, "b": 92, "c": 14.23, "op1": "+", "op2": "/", "result": 15.29}
{"question": "Solve: (113.14 - 150) * 115.46", "answer": "The result of (113.14 - 150) * 115.46 is -4255.86", "a": 113.14, "b": 150, "c": 115.46, "op1": "-", "op2": "*", "result": -4255.86}
{"question": "Solve: (89.96 / 135) - 154", "answer": "The result of (89.96 / 135) - 154 is -153.33", "a": 89.96, "b": 135, "c": 154, "op1": "/", "op2": "-", "result": -153.33}
{"question": "Solve: (199.25 * 114) - 30", "answer": "The result of (199.25 * 114) - 30 is 22684.5", "a": 199.25, "b": 114, "c": 30, "op1": "*", "op2": "-", "result": 22684.5}
{"question": "Solve: (45.13 / 67) * 159.58", "answer": "The result of (45.13 / 67) * 159.58 is 107.49", "a": 45.13, "b": 67, "c": 159.58, "op1": "/", "op2": "*", "result": 107.49}
{"question": "Solve: (131.26 - 51) - 134.52", "answer": "The result of (131.26 - 51) - 134.52 is -54.26", "a": 131.26, "b": 51, "c": 134.52, "op1": "-", "op2": "-", "result": -54.26}
{"question": "Solve: (189 + 143) - 142.66", "answer": "The result of (189 + 143) - 142.66 is 189.34", "a": 189, "b": 143, "c": 142.66, "op1": "+", "op2": "-", "result": 189.34}
{"question": "Solve: (146 + 72) - 135", "answer": "The result of (146 + 72) - 135 is 83", "a": 146, "b": 72, "c": 135, "op1": "+", "op2": "-", "result": 83}
{"question": "Solve: (2 * 3) - 88", "answer": "The result of (2 * 3) - 88 is -82", "a": 2, "b": 3, "c": 88, "op1": "*", "op2": "-", "result": -82}
{"question": "Solve: (97 - 56) - 106", "answer": "The result of (97 - 56) - 106 is -65", "a": 97, "b": 56, "c": 106, "op1": "-", "op2": "-", "result": -65}
{"question": "Solve: (35 - 182) - 178", "answer": "The result of (35 - 182) - 178 is -325", "a": 35, "b": 182, "c": 178, "op1": "-", "op2": "-", "result": -325}
{"question": "Solve: (198 - 48) / 148.82", "answer": "The result of (198 - 48) / 148.82 is 1.01", "a": 198, "b": 48, "c": 148.82, "op1": "-", "op2": "/", "result": 1.01}
{"question": "Solve: (195 + 38.25) * 38", "answer": "The result of (195 + 38.25) * 38 is 8863.5", "a": 195, "b": 38.25, "c": 38, "op1": "+", "op2": "*", "result": 8863.5}
{"question": "Solve: (156 * 122) * 8", "answer": "The result of (156 * 122) * 8 is 152256", "a": 156, "b": 122, "c": 8, "op1": "*", "op2": "*", "result": 152256}
{"question": "Solve: (113 + 75) - 115", "answer": "The result of (113 + 75) - 115 is 73", "a": 113, "b": 75, "c": 115, "op1": "+", "op2": "-", "result": 73}
{"question": "Solve: (171 / 103.09) - 128", "answer": "The result of (171 / 103.09) - 128 is -126.34", "a": 171, "b": 103.09, "c": 128, "op1": "/", "op2": "-", "result": -126.34}
{"question": "Solve: (20 * 161) * 105.36", "answer": "The result of (20 * 161) * 105.36 is 339259.2", "a": 20, "b": 161, "c": 105.36, "op1": "*", "op2": "*", "result": 339259.2}
{"question": "Solve: (158.74 - 194.35) + 16", "answer": "The result of (158.74 - 194.35) + 16 is -19.61", "a": 158.74, "b": 194.35, "c": 16, "op1": "-", "op2": "+", "result": -19.61}
{"question": "Solve: (178 / 200) + 58", "answer": "The result of (178 / 200) + 58 is 58.89", "a": 178, "b": 200, "c": 58, "op1": "/", "op2": "+", "result": 58.89}
{"question": "Solve: (6.72 * 188) / 84", "answer": "The result of (6.72 * 188) / 84 is 15.04", "a": 6.72, "b": 188, "c": 84, "op1": "*", "op2": "/", "result": 15.04}
{"question": "Solve: (164.13 + 178) + 181", "answer": "The result of (164.13 + 178) + 181 is 523.13", "a": 164.13, "b": 178, "c": 181, "op1": "+", "op2": "+", "result": 523.13}
{"question": "Solve: (30 + 123) * 174", "answer": "The result of (30 + 123) * 174 is 26622", "a": 30, "b": 123, "c": 174, "op1": "+", "op2": "*", "result": 26622}
{"question": "Solve: (83 + 153) + 109", "answer": "The result of (83 + 153) + 109 is 345", "a": 83, "b": 153, "c": 109, "op1": "+", "op2": "+", "result": 345}
{"question": "Solve: (174.99 - 33) * 132", "answer": "The result of (174.99 - 33) * 132 is 18742.68", "a": 174.99, "b": 33, "c": 132, "op1": "-", "op2": "*", "result": 18742.68}
{"question": "Solve: (46 + 28) + 119", "answer": "The result of (46 + 28) + 119 is 193", "a": 46, "b": 28, "c": 119, "op1": "+", "op2": "+", "result": 193}
{"question": "Solve: (76 * 199) + 56.76", "answer": "The result of (76 * 199) + 56.76 is 15180.76", "a": 76, "b": 199, "c": 56.76, "op1": "*", "op2": "+", "result": 15180.76}
{"question": "Solve: (58 * 164) - 46", "answer": "The result of (58 * 164) - 46 is 9466", "a": 58, "b": 164, "c": 46, "op1": "*", "op2": "-", "result": 9466}
{"question": "Solve: (174 / 164) - 178", "answer": "The result of (174 / 164) - 178 is -176.94", "a": 174, "b": 164, "c": 178, "op1": "/", "op2": "-", "result": -176.94}
{"question": "Solve: (144 + 19) + 181.56", "answer": "The result of (144 + 19) + 181.56 is 344.56", "a": 144, "b": 19, "c": 181.56, "op1": "+", "op2": "+", "result": 344.56}
{"question": "Solve: (122 * 168.65) + 58.79", "answer": "The result of (122 * 168.65) + 58.79 is 20634.09", "a": 122, "b": 168.65, "c": 58.79, "op1": "*", "op2": "+", "result": 20634.09}
{"question": "Solve: (198.04 - 39) - 76", "answer": "The result of (198.04 - 39) - 76 is 83.04", "a": 198.04, "b": 39, "c": 76, "op1": "-", "op2": "-", "result": 83.04}
{"question": "Solve: (82 + 179) + 143", "answer": "The result of (82 + 179) + 143 is 404", "a": 82, "b": 179, "c": 143, "op1": "+", "op2": "+", "result": 404}
{"question": "Solve: (87 * 84) * 75", "answer": "The result of (87 * 84) * 75 is 548100", "a": 87, "b": 84, "c": 75, "op1": "*", "op2": "*", "result": 548100}
{"question": "Solve: (61.15 + 178.72) * 100.32", "answer": "The result of (61.15 + 178.72) * 100.32 is 24063.76", "a": 61.15, "b": 178.72, "c": 100.32, "op1": "+", "op2": "*", "result": 24063.76}
{"question": "Solve: (123 * 63) * 32.04", "answer": "The result of (123 * 63) * 32.04 is 248277.96", "a": 123, "b": 63, "c": 32.04, "op1": "*", "op2": "*", "result": 248277.96}
{"question": "Solve: (142 - 128.61) - 97.71", "answer": "The result of (142 - 128.61) - 97.71 is -84.32", "a": 142, "b": 128.61, "c": 97.71, "op1": "-", "op2": "-", "result": -84.32}
{"question": "Solve: (180 / 46) - 140", "answer": "The result of (180 / 46) - 140 is -136.09", "a": 180, "b": 46, "c": 140, "op1": "/", "op2": "-", "result": -136.09}
{"question": "Solve: (14.93 * 114) * 161.41", "answer": "The result of (14.93 * 114) * 161.41 is 274723.05", "a": 14.93, "b": 114, "c": 161.41, "op1": "*", "op2": "*", "result": 274723.05}
{"question": "Solve: (163 - 96.56) - 18", "answer": "The result of (163 - 96.56) - 18 is 48.44", "a": 163, "b": 96.56, "c": 18, "op1": "-", "op2": "-", "result": 48.44}
{"question": "Solve: (102 + 125) - 112", "answer": "The result of (102 + 125) - 112 is 115", "a": 102, "b": 125, "c": 112, "op1": "+", "op2": "-", "result": 115}
{"question": "Solve: (109 * 107.4) + 100", "answer": "The result of (109 * 107.4) + 100 is 11806.6", "a": 109, "b": 107.4, "c": 100, "op1": "*", "op2": "+", "result": 11806.6}
{"question": "Solve: (120 * 55) + 145.07", "answer": "The result of (120 * 55) + 145.07 is 6745.07", "a": 120, "b": 55, "c": 145.07, "op1": "*", "op2": "+", "result": 6745.07}
{"question": "Solve: (8.81 * 18) + 7.95", "answer": "The result of (8.81 * 18) + 7.95 is 166.53", "a": 8.81, "b": 18, "c": 7.95, "op1": "*", "op2": "+", "result": 166.53}
{"question": "Solve: (69.4 / 184.4) + 64", "answer": "The result of (69.4 / 184.4) + 64 is 64.38", "a": 69.4, "b": 184.4, "c": 64, "op1": "/", "op2": "+", "result": 64.38}
{"question": "Solve: (159 / 80.88) - 185", "answer": "The result of (159 / 80.88) - 185 is -183.03", "a": 159, "b": 80.88, "c": 185, "op1": "/", "op2": "-", "result": -183.03}
{"question": "Solve: (6.28 / 7) / 60", "answer": "The result of (6.28 / 7) / 60 is 0.01", "a": 6.28, "b": 7, "c": 60, "op1": "/", "op2": "/", "result": 0.01}
{"question": "Solve: (21.18 - 32.17) * 139", "answer": "The result of (21.18 - 32.17) * 139 is -1527.61", "a": 21.18, "b": 32.17, "c": 139, "op1": "-", "op2": "*", "result": -1527.61}
{"question": "Solve: (32.63 + 173.22) - 61", "answer": "The result of (32.63 + 173.22) - 61 is 144.85", "a": 32.63, "b": 173.22, "c": 61, "op1": "+", "op2": "-", "result": 144.85}
{"question": "Solve: (194 + 164) * 42", "answer": "The result of (194 + 164) * 42 is 15036", "a": 194, "b": 164, "c": 42, "op1": "+", "op2": "*", "result": 15036}
{"question": "Solve: (163.19 * 164.09) * 112.06", "answer": "The result of (163.19 * 164.09) * 112.06 is 3000725.55", "a": 163.19, "b": 164.09, "c": 112.06, "op1": "*", "op2": "*", "result": 3000725.55}
{"question": "Solve: (84 + 162) / 100.05", "answer": "The result of (84 + 162) / 100.05 is 2.46", "a": 84, "b": 162, "c": 100.05, "op1": "+", "op2": "/", "result": 2.46}
{"question": "Solve: (2 / 10.57) * 69.88", "answer": "The result of (2 / 10.57) * 69.88 is 13.22", "a": 2, "b": 10.57, "c": 69.88, "op1": "/", "op2": "*", "result": 13.22}
{"question": "Solve: (72 + 15) * 188.55", "answer": "The result of (72 + 15) * 188.55 is 16403.85", "a": 72, "b": 15, "c": 188.55, "op1": "+", "op2": "*", "result": 16403.85}
{"question": "Solve: (142 * 149.86) * 37", "answer": "The result of (142 * 149.86) * 37 is 787364.44", "a": 142, "b": 149.86, "c": 37, "op1": "*", "op2": "*", "result": 787364.44}
{"question": "Solve: (60.06 - 61) + 79.89", "answer": "The result of (60.06 - 61) + 79.89 is 78.95", "a": 60.06, "b": 61, "c": 79.89, "op1": "-", "op2": "+", "result": 78.95}
{"question": "Solve: (91 / 25) / 67.74", "answer": "The result of (91 / 25) / 67.74 is 0.05", "a": 91, "b": 25, "c": 67.74, "op1": "/", "op2": "/", "result": 0.05}
{"question": "Solve: (72 + 126) + 15", "answer": "The result of (72 + 126) + 15 is 213", "a": 72, "b": 126, "c": 15, "op1": "+", "op2": "+", "result": 213}
{"question": "Solve: (179.62 - 132) + 189", "answer": "The result of (179.62 - 132) + 189 is 236.62", "a": 179.62, "b": 132, "c": 189, "op1": "-", "op2": "+", "result": 236.62}
{"question": "Solve: (140.71 + 73) - 165", "answer": "The result of (140.71 + 73) - 165 is 48.71", "a": 140.71, "b": 73, "c": 165, "op1": "+", "op2": "-", "result": 48.71}
{"question": "Solve: (8 / 26) - 98", "answer": "The result of (8 / 26) - 98 is -97.69", "a": 8, "b": 26, "c": 98, "op1": "/", "op2": "-", "result": -97.69}
{"question": "Solve: (63 / 15.48) / 129.99", "answer": "The result of (63 / 15.48) / 129.99 is 0.03", "a": 63, "b": 15.48, "c": 129.99, "op1": "/", "op2": "/", "result": 0.03}
{"question": "Solve: (64.39 + 161.96) / 171.02", "answer": "The result of (64.39 + 161.96) / 171.02 is 1.32", "a": 64.39, "b": 161.96, "c": 171.02, "op1": "+", "op2": "/", "result": 1.32}
{"question": "Solve: (136.63 * 20) - 140.19", "answer": "The result of (136.63 * 20) - 140.19 is 2592.41", "a": 136.63, "b": 20, "c": 140.19, "op1": "*", "op2": "-", "result": 2592.41}
{"question": "Solve: (130 - 107) * 67", "answer": "The result of (130 - 107) * 67 is 1541", "a": 130, "b": 107, "c": 67, "op1": "-", "op2": "*", "result": 1541}
{"question": "Solve: (72 * 38) - 25", "answer": "The result of (72 * 38) - 25 is 2711", "a": 72, "b": 38, "c": 25, "op1": "*", "op2": "-", "result": 2711}
{"question": "Solve: (70.6 * 48) * 5", "answer": "The result of (70.6 * 48) * 5 is 16944.0", "a": 70.6, "b": 48, "c": 5, "op1": "*", "op2": "*", "result": 16944.0}
{"question": "Solve: (47 + 131.59) * 98.19", "answer": "The result of (47 + 131.59) * 98.19 is 17535.75", "a": 47, "b": 131.59, "c": 98.19, "op1": "+", "op2": "*", "result": 17535.75}
{"question": "Solve: (80 - 148) - 19", "answer": "The result of (80 - 148) - 19 is -87", "a": 80, "b": 148, "c": 19, "op1": "-", "op2": "-", "result": -87}
{"question": "Solve: (150.19 / 57) - 130", "answer": "The result of (150.19 / 57) - 130 is -127.37", "a": 150.19, "b": 57, "c": 130, "op1": "/", "op2": "-", "result": -127.37}
{"question": "Solve: (58 + 91) + 47", "answer": "The result of (58 + 91) + 47 is 196", "a": 58, "b": 91, "c": 47, "op1": "+", "op2": "+", "result": 196}
{"question": "Solve: (127.96 - 163.9) + 180", "answer": "The result of (127.96 - 163.9) + 180 is 144.06", "a": 127.96, "b": 163.9, "c": 180, "op1": "-", "op2": "+", "result": 144.06}
{"question": "Solve: (131 / 172) - 118", "answer": "The result of (131 / 172) - 118 is -117.24", "a": 131, "b": 172, "c": 118, "op1": "/", "op2": "-", "result": -117.24}
{"question": "Solve: (147 - 157) * 6", "answer": "The result of (147 - 157) * 6 is -60", "a": 147, "b": 157, "c": 6, "op1": "-", "op2": "*", "result": -60}
{"question": "Solve: (161 * 14) + 78", "answer": "The result of (161 * 14) + 78 is 2332", "a": 161, "b": 14, "c": 78, "op1": "*", "op2": "+", "result": 2332}
{"question": "Solve: (189.31 - 77) + 22.04", "answer": "The result of (189.31 - 77) + 22.04 is 134.35", "a": 189.31, "b": 77, "c": 22.04, "op1": "-", "op2": "+", "result": 134.35}
{"question": "Solve: (45 + 185) * 159", "answer": "The result of (45 + 185) * 159 is 36570", "a": 45, "b": 185, "c": 159, "op1": "+", "op2": "*", "result": 36570}
{"question": "Solve: (124 + 18) * 163.74", "answer": "The result of (124 + 18) * 163.74 is 23251.08", "a": 124, "b": 18, "c": 163.74, "op1": "+", "op2": "*", "result": 23251.08}
{"question": "Solve: (25.43 / 15) - 176.41", "answer": "The result of (25.43 / 15) - 176.41 is -174.71", "a": 25.43, "b": 15, "c": 176.41, "op1": "/", "op2": "-", "result": -174.71}
{"question": "Solve: (29.34 - 46) + 43", "answer": "The result of (29.34 - 46) + 43 is 26.34", "a": 29.34, "b": 46, "c": 43, "op1": "-", "op2": "+", "result": 26.34}
{"question": "Solve: (147 - 113) + 128", "answer": "The result of (147 - 113) + 128 is 162", "a": 147, "b": 113, "c": 128, "op1": "-", "op2": "+", "result": 162}
{"question": "Solve: (100.33 * 45.37) * 124", "answer": "The result of (100.33 * 45.37) * 124 is 564444.54", "a": 100.33, "b": 45.37, "c": 124, "op1": "*", "op2": "*", "result": 564444.54}
{"question": "Solve: (40.61 * 39) + 12", "answer": "The result of (40.61 * 39) + 12 is 1595.79", "a": 40.61, "b": 39, "c": 12, "op1": "*", "op2": "+", "result": 1595.79}
{"question": "Solve: (121.68 - 85) - 32", "answer": "The result of (121.68 - 85) - 32 is 4.68", "a": 121.68, "b": 85, "c": 32, "op1": "-", "op2": "-", "result": 4.68}
{"question": "Solve: (169 * 125.46) - 141.6", "answer": "The result of (169 * 125.46) - 141.6 is 21061.14", "a": 169, "b": 125.46, "c": 141.6, "op1": "*", "op2": "-", "result": 21061.14}
{"question": "Solve: (52.75 - 178) / 153", "answer": "The result of (52.75 - 178) / 153 is -0.82", "a": 52.75, "b": 178, "c": 153, "op1": "-", "op2": "/", "result": -0.82}
{"question": "Solve: (112 - 84.14) + 17", "answer": "The result of (112 - 84.14) + 17 is 44.86", "a": 112, "b": 84.14, "c": 17, "op1": "-", "op2": "+", "result": 44.86}
{"question": "Solve: (55 - 113) * 46", "answer": "The result of (55 - 113) * 46 is -2668", "a": 55, "b": 113, "c": 46, "op1": "-", "op2": "*", "result": -2668}
{"question": "Solve: (10 / 36.61) + 90", "answer": "The result of (10 / 36.61) + 90 is 90.27", "a": 10, "b": 36.61, "c": 90, "op1": "/", "op2": "+", "result": 90.27}
{"question": "Solve: (14 * 45) * 160", "answer": "The result of (14 * 45) * 160 is 100800", "a": 14, "b": 45, "c": 160, "op1": "*", "op2": "*", "result": 100800}
{"question": "Solve: (198.67 + 88.62) + 47", "answer": "The result of (198.67 + 88.62) + 47 is 334.29", "a": 198.67, "b": 88.62, "c": 47, "op1": "+", "op2": "+", "result": 334.29}
{"question": "Solve: (113.66 / 27) / 193.64", "answer": "The result of (113.66 / 27) / 193.64 is 0.02", "a": 113.66, "b": 27, "c": 193.64, "op1": "/", "op2": "/", "result": 0.02}
{"question": "Solve: (180.97 + 168) + 2.73", "answer": "The result of (180.97 + 168) + 2.73 is 351.7", "a": 180.97, "b": 168, "c": 2.73, "op1": "+", "op2": "+", "result": 351.7}
{"question": "Solve: (82 - 49) / 164", "answer": "The result of (82 - 49) / 164 is 0.2", "a": 82, "b": 49, "c": 164, "op1": "-", "op2": "/", "result": 0.2}
{"question": "Solve: (97 + 156.94) + 155.22", "answer": "The result of (97 + 156.94) + 155.22 is 409.16", "a": 97, "b": 156.94, "c": 155.22, "op1": "+", "op2": "+", "result": 409.16}
{"question": "Solve: (143 + 160.52) * 85", "answer": "The result of (143 + 160.52) * 85 is 25799.2", "a": 143, "b": 160.52, "c": 85, "op1": "+", "op2": "*", "result": 25799.2}
{"question": "Solve: (10 * 20.51) - 101", "answer": "The result of (10 * 20.51) - 101 is 104.1", "a": 10, "b": 20.51, "c": 101, "op1": "*", "op2": "-", "result": 104.1}
{"question": "Solve: (141.2 - 72) - 29.49", "answer": "The result of (141.2 - 72) - 29.49 is 39.71", "a": 141.2, "b": 72, "c": 29.49, "op1": "-", "op2": "-", "result": 39.71}
{"question": "Solve: (187.6 + 67) * 122", "answer": "The result of (187.6 + 67) * 122 is 31061.2", "a": 187.6, "b": 67, "c": 122, "op1": "+", "op2": "*", "result": 31061.2}
{"question": "Solve: (115 * 176) - 16.1", "answer": "The result of (115 * 176) - 16.1 is 20223.9", "a": 115, "b": 176, "c": 16.1, "op1": "*", "op2": "-", "result": 20223.9}
{"question": "Solve: (111 + 93.1) + 6", "answer": "The result of (111 + 93.1) + 6 is 210.1", "a": 111, "b": 93.1, "c": 6, "op1": "+", "op2": "+", "result": 210.1}
{"question": "Solve: (111 * 62.48) - 115", "answer": "The result of (111 * 62.48) - 115 is 6820.28", "a": 111, "b": 62.48, "c": 115, "op1": "*", "op2": "-", "result": 6820.28}
{"question": "Solve: (103 - 86) - 105.23", "answer": "The result of (103 - 86) - 105.23 is -88.23", "a": 103, "b": 86, "c": 105.23, "op1": "-", "op2": "-", "result": -88.23}
{"question": "Solve: (103 * 154.61) - 5", "answer": "The result of (103 * 154.61) - 5 is 15919.83", "a": 103, "b": 154.61, "c": 5, "op1": "*", "op2": "-", "result": 15919.83}
{"question": "Solve: (92 - 194.87) - 155", "answer": "The result of (92 - 194.87) - 155 is -257.87", "a": 92, "b": 194.87, "c": 155, "op1": "-", "op2": "-", "result": -257.87}
{"question": "Solve: (197 - 189) + 106", "answer": "The result of (197 - 189) + 106 is 114", "a": 197, "b": 189, "c": 106, "op1": "-", "op2": "+", "result": 114}
{"question": "Solve: (53 + 180.95) - 67", "answer": "The result of (53 + 180.95) - 67 is 166.95", "a": 53, "b": 180.95, "c": 67, "op1": "+", "op2": "-", "result": 166.95}
{"question": "Solve: (88 - 97) + 83", "answer": "The result of (88 - 97) + 83 is 74", "a": 88, "b": 97, "c": 83, "op1": "-", "op2": "+", "result": 74}
{"question": "Solve: (195 * 77.13) - 174.18", "answer": "The result of (195 * 77.13) - 174.18 is 14866.17", "a": 195, "b": 77.13, "c": 174.18, "op1": "*", "op2": "-", "result": 14866.17}
{"question": "Solve: (136 + 168) / 83", "answer": "The result of (136 + 168) / 83 is 3.66", "a": 136, "b": 168, "c": 83, "op1": "+", "op2": "/", "result": 3.66}
{"question": "Solve: (11 / 168) + 175", "answer": "The result of (11 / 168) + 175 is 175.07", "a": 11, "b": 168, "c": 175, "op1": "/", "op2": "+", "result": 175.07}
{"question": "Solve: (57 * 55) + 116.01", "answer": "The result of (57 * 55) + 116.01 is 3251.01", "a": 57, "b": 55, "c": 116.01, "op1": "*", "op2": "+", "result": 3251.01}
{"question": "Solve: (39 - 112) + 174", "answer": "The result of (39 - 112) + 174 is 101", "a": 39, "b": 112, "c": 174, "op1": "-", "op2": "+", "result": 101}
{"question": "Solve: (58 - 48) - 13.15", "answer": "The result of (58 - 48) - 13.15 is -3.15", "a": 58, "b": 48, "c": 13.15, "op1": "-", "op2": "-", "result": -3.15}
{"question": "Solve: (70 * 134) - 129.59", "answer": "The result of (70 * 134) - 129.59 is 9250.41", "a": 70, "b": 134, "c": 129.59, "op1": "*", "op2": "-", "result": 9250.41}
{"question": "Solve: (104 - 65) - 20.67", "answer": "The result of (104 - 65) - 20.67 is 18.33", "a": 104, "b": 65, "c": 20.67, "op1": "-", "op2": "-", "result": 18.33}
{"question": "Solve: (13.75 - 93) / 36.67", "answer": "The result of (13.75 - 93) / 36.67 is -2.16", "a": 13.75, "b": 93, "c": 36.67, "op1": "-", "op2": "/", "result": -2.16}
{"question": "Solve: (34 / 111) + 159", "answer": "The result of (34 / 111) + 159 is 159.31", "a": 34, "b": 111, "c": 159, "op1": "/", "op2": "+", "result": 159.31}
{"question": "Solve: (197.67 * 138) * 122", "answer": "The result of (197.67 * 138) * 122 is 3327972.12", "a": 197.67, "b": 138, "c": 122, "op1": "*", "op2": "*", "result": 3327972.12}
{"question": "Solve: (31 / 38) * 16.71", "answer": "The result of (31 / 38) * 16.71 is 13.63", "a": 31, "b": 38, "c": 16.71, "op1": "/", "op2": "*", "result": 13.63}
{"question": "Solve: (67.81 * 31.06) - 62", "answer": "The result of (67.81 * 31.06) - 62 is 2044.18", "a": 67.81, "b": 31.06, "c": 62, "op1": "*", "op2": "-", "result": 2044.18}
{"question": "Solve: (132 + 9) + 196", "answer": "The result of (132 + 9) + 196 is 337", "a": 132, "b": 9, "c": 196, "op1": "+", "op2": "+", "result": 337}
{"question": "Solve: (19 - 90) - 143", "answer": "The result of (19 - 90) - 143 is -214", "a": 19, "b": 90, "c": 143, "op1": "-", "op2": "-", "result": -214}
{"question": "Solve: (187 + 180) * 181", "answer": "The result of (187 + 180) * 181 is 66427", "a": 187, "b": 180, "c": 181, "op1": "+", "op2": "*", "result": 66427}
{"question": "Solve: (124.11 * 137.22) + 80", "answer": "The result of (124.11 * 137.22) + 80 is 17110.37", "a": 124.11, "b": 137.22, "c": 80, "op1": "*", "op2": "+", "result": 17110.37}
{"question": "Solve: (183 - 65) + 149", "answer": "The result of (183 - 65) + 149 is 267", "a": 183, "b": 65, "c": 149, "op1": "-", "op2": "+", "result": 267}
{"question": "Solve: (87.43 * 67.77) - 94.12", "answer": "The result of (87.43 * 67.77) - 94.12 is 5831.01", "a": 87.43, "b": 67.77, "c": 94.12, "op1": "*", "op2": "-", "result": 5831.01}
{"question": "Solve: (181 * 35) + 44", "answer": "The result of (181 * 35) + 44 is 6379", "a": 181, "b": 35, "c": 44, "op1": "*", "op2": "+", "result": 6379}
{"question": "Solve: (53.84 * 70) - 5", "answer": "The result of (53.84 * 70) - 5 is 3763.8", "a": 53.84, "b": 70, "c": 5, "op1": "*", "op2": "-", "result": 3763.8}
{"question": "Solve: (96 - 64) - 67", "answer": "The result of (96 - 64) - 67 is -35", "a": 96, "b": 64, "c": 67, "op1": "-", "op2": "-", "result": -35}
{"question": "Solve: (160.15 - 192.55) + 28.93", "answer": "The result of (160.15 - 192.55) + 28.93 is -3.47", "a": 160.15, "b": 192.55, "c": 28.93, "op1": "-", "op2": "+", "result": -3.47}
{"question": "Solve: (35 * 1.09) * 116.77", "answer": "The result of (35 * 1.09) * 116.77 is 4454.78", "a": 35, "b": 1.09, "c": 116.77, "op1": "*", "op2": "*", "result": 4454.78}
{"question": "Solve: (62.27 * 30) * 12", "answer": "The result of (62.27 * 30) * 12 is 22417.2", "a": 62.27, "b": 30, "c": 12, "op1": "*", "op2": "*", "result": 22417.2}
{"question": "Solve: (121 * 106) - 43", "answer": "The result of (121 * 106) - 43 is 12783", "a": 121, "b": 106, "c": 43, "op1": "*", "op2": "-", "result": 12783}
{"question": "Solve: (174 - 22) * 41", "answer": "The result of (174 - 22) * 41 is 6232", "a": 174, "b": 22, "c": 41, "op1": "-", "op2": "*", "result": 6232}
{"question": "Solve: (77 / 166) * 78", "answer": "The result of (77 / 166) * 78 is 36.18", "a": 77, "b": 166, "c": 78, "op1": "/", "op2": "*", "result": 36.18}
{"question": "Solve: (78 + 193.36) - 182.37", "answer": "The result of (78 + 193.36) - 182.37 is 88.99", "a": 78, "b": 193.36, "c": 182.37, "op1": "+", "op2": "-", "result": 88.99}
{"question": "Solve: (19.79 + 174) - 92", "answer": "The result of (19.79 + 174) - 92 is 101.79", "a": 19.79, "b": 174, "c": 92, "op1": "+", "op2": "-", "result": 101.79}
{"question": "Solve: (6 / 182.37) + 151.7", "answer": "The result of (6 / 182.37) + 151.7 is 151.73", "a": 6, "b": 182.37, "c": 151.7, "op1": "/", "op2": "+", "result": 151.73}
{"question": "Solve: (161 - 166) - 153", "answer": "The result of (161 - 166) - 153 is -158", "a": 161, "b": 166, "c": 153, "op1": "-", "op2": "-", "result": -158}
{"question": "Solve: (124 * 72.19) / 169.84", "answer": "The result of (124 * 72.19) / 169.84 is 52.71", "a": 124, "b": 72.19, "c": 169.84, "op1": "*", "op2": "/", "result": 52.71}
{"question": "Solve: (132 * 126.99) * 158", "answer": "The result of (132 * 126.99) * 158 is 2648503.44", "a": 132, "b": 126.99, "c": 158, "op1": "*", "op2": "*", "result": 2648503.44}
{"question": "Solve: (177 * 77.99) / 130.64", "answer": "The result of (177 * 77.99) / 130.64 is 105.67", "a": 177, "b": 77.99, "c": 130.64, "op1": "*", "op2": "/", "result": 105.67}
{"question": "Solve: (35 - 73) + 6.06", "answer": "The result of (35 - 73) + 6.06 is -31.94", "a": 35, "b": 73, "c": 6.06, "op1": "-", "op2": "+", "result": -31.94}
{"question": "Solve: (34.51 - 22) * 184.57", "answer": "The result of (34.51 - 22) * 184.57 is 2308.97", "a": 34.51, "b": 22, "c": 184.57, "op1": "-", "op2": "*", "result": 2308.97}
{"question": "Solve: (6 * 27) / 26", "answer": "The result of (6 * 27) / 26 is 6.23", "a": 6, "b": 27, "c": 26, "op1": "*", "op2": "/", "result": 6.23}
{"question": "Solve: (72 + 117) + 51", "answer": "The result of (72 + 117) + 51 is 240", "a": 72, "b": 117, "c": 51, "op1": "+", "op2": "+", "result": 240}
{"question": "Solve: (198 * 48) * 166", "answer": "The result of (198 * 48) * 166 is 1577664", "a": 198, "b": 48, "c": 166, "op1": "*", "op2": "*", "result": 1577664}
{"question": "Solve: (104 + 60) + 12", "answer": "The result of (104 + 60) + 12 is 176", "a": 104, "b": 60, "c": 12, "op1": "+", "op2": "+", "result": 176}
{"question": "Solve: (8.13 / 148) + 149", "answer": "The result of (8.13 / 148) + 149 is 149.05", "a": 8.13, "b": 148, "c": 149, "op1": "/", "op2": "+", "result": 149.05}
{"question": "Solve: (111 + 15) / 61", "answer": "The result of (111 + 15) / 61 is 2.07", "a": 111, "b": 15, "c": 61, "op1": "+", "op2": "/", "result": 2.07}
{"question": "Solve: (1.44 / 188) + 61", "answer": "The result of (1.44 / 188) + 61 is 61.01", "a": 1.44, "b": 188, "c": 61, "op1": "/", "op2": "+", "result": 61.01}
{"question": "Solve: (150.01 - 149) + 199.82", "answer": "The result of (150.01 - 149) + 199.82 is 200.83", "a": 150.01, "b": 149, "c": 199.82, "op1": "-", "op2": "+", "result": 200.83}
{"question": "Solve: (191 + 77) / 139", "answer": "The result of (191 + 77) / 139 is 1.93", "a": 191, "b": 77, "c": 139, "op1": "+", "op2": "/", "result": 1.93}
{"question": "Solve: (111 / 134) - 95", "answer": "The result of (111 / 134) - 95 is -94.17", "a": 111, "b": 134, "c": 95, "op1": "/", "op2": "-", "result": -94.17}
{"question": "Solve: (153 + 63) + 145", "answer": "The result of (153 + 63) + 145 is 361", "a": 153, "b": 63, "c": 145, "op1": "+", "op2": "+", "result": 361}
{"question": "Solve: (90 + 1.42) / 73.38", "answer": "The result of (90 + 1.42) / 73.38 is 1.25", "a": 90, "b": 1.42, "c": 73.38, "op1": "+", "op2": "/", "result": 1.25}
{"question": "Solve: (43 + 21) + 54.87", "answer": "The result of (43 + 21) + 54.87 is 118.87", "a": 43, "b": 21, "c": 54.87, "op1": "+", "op2": "+", "result": 118.87}
{"question": "Solve: (152.09 + 60) + 37", "answer": "The result of (152.09 + 60) + 37 is 249.09", "a": 152.09, "b": 60, "c": 37, "op1": "+", "op2": "+", "result": 249.09}
{"question": "Solve: (136 - 115) + 195", "answer": "The result of (136 - 115) + 195 is 216", "a": 136, "b": 115, "c": 195, "op1": "-", "op2": "+", "result": 216}
{"question": "Solve: (64 + 21) * 135.73", "answer": "The result of (64 + 21) * 135.73 is 11537.05", "a": 64, "b": 21, "c": 135.73, "op1": "+", "op2": "*", "result": 11537.05}
{"question": "Solve: (165.07 + 98.6) + 57", "answer": "The result of (165.07 + 98.6) + 57 is 320.67", "a": 165.07, "b": 98.6, "c": 57, "op1": "+", "op2": "+", "result": 320.67}
{"question": "Solve: (57 + 6.75) - 176", "answer": "The result of (57 + 6.75) - 176 is -112.25", "a": 57, "b": 6.75, "c": 176, "op1": "+", "op2": "-", "result": -112.25}
{"question": "Solve: (144 + 169) / 66", "answer": "The result of (144 + 169) / 66 is 4.74", "a": 144, "b": 169, "c": 66, "op1": "+", "op2": "/", "result": 4.74}
{"question": "Solve: (166 * 60.45) + 50", "answer": "The result of (166 * 60.45) + 50 is 10084.7", "a": 166, "b": 60.45, "c": 50, "op1": "*", "op2": "+", "result": 10084.7}
{"question": "Solve: (168 + 193) - 186", "answer": "The result of (168 + 193) - 186 is 175", "a": 168, "b": 193, "c": 186, "op1": "+", "op2": "-", "result": 175}
{"question": "Solve: (16 - 107.39) + 22.43", "answer": "The result of (16 - 107.39) + 22.43 is -68.96", "a": 16, "b": 107.39, "c": 22.43, "op1": "-", "op2": "+", "result": -68.96}
{"question": "Solve: (16 - 119) + 49", "answer": "The result of (16 - 119) + 49 is -54", "a": 16, "b": 119, "c": 49, "op1": "-", "op2": "+", "result": -54}
{"question": "Solve: (176.87 * 8.44) - 189.87", "answer": "The result of (176.87 * 8.44) - 189.87 is 1302.91", "a": 176.87, "b": 8.44, "c": 189.87, "op1": "*", "op2": "-", "result": 1302.91}
{"question": "Solve: (85 * 108.16) / 113", "answer": "The result of (85 * 108.16) / 113 is 81.36", "a": 85, "b": 108.16, "c": 113, "op1": "*", "op2": "/", "result": 81.36}
{"question": "Solve: (160 - 118) + 154.21", "answer": "The result of (160 - 118) + 154.21 is 196.21", "a": 160, "b": 118, "c": 154.21, "op1": "-", "op2": "+", "result": 196.21}
{"question": "Solve: (43 + 49.33) - 80", "answer": "The result of (43 + 49.33) - 80 is 12.33", "a": 43, "b": 49.33, "c": 80, "op1": "+", "op2": "-", "result": 12.33}
{"question": "Solve: (151 * 12.95) * 177", "answer": "The result of (151 * 12.95) * 177 is 346114.65", "a": 151, "b": 12.95, "c": 177, "op1": "*", "op2": "*", "result": 346114.65}
{"question": "Solve: (100 * 187) - 192.5", "answer": "The result of (100 * 187) - 192.5 is 18507.5", "a": 100, "b": 187, "c": 192.5, "op1": "*", "op2": "-", "result": 18507.5}
{"question": "Solve: (28 / 182) / 147", "answer": "The result of (28 / 182) / 147 is 0.0", "a": 28, "b": 182, "c": 147, "op1": "/", "op2": "/", "result": 0.0}
{"question": "Solve: (62.44 - 51.86) - 184.12", "answer": "The result of (62.44 - 51.86) - 184.12 is -173.54", "a": 62.44, "b": 51.86, "c": 184.12, "op1": "-", "op2": "-", "result": -173.54}
{"question": "Solve: (192 * 184) + 4", "answer": "The result of (192 * 184) + 4 is 35332", "a": 192, "b": 184, "c": 4, "op1": "*", "op2": "+", "result": 35332}
{"question": "Solve: (34 * 71.1) - 24", "answer": "The result of (34 * 71.1) - 24 is 2393.4", "a": 34, "b": 71.1, "c": 24, "op1": "*", "op2": "-", "result": 2393.4}
{"question": "Solve: (143 - 125.03) * 66.75", "answer": "The result of (143 - 125.03) * 66.75 is 1199.5", "a": 143, "b": 125.03, "c": 66.75, "op1": "-", "op2": "*", "result": 1199.5}
{"question": "Solve: (53 - 126) + 93", "answer": "The result of (53 - 126) + 93 is 20", "a": 53, "b": 126, "c": 93, "op1": "-", "op2": "+", "result": 20}
{"question": "Solve: (24 - 103.17) * 125.72", "answer": "The result of (24 - 103.17) * 125.72 is -9953.25", "a": 24, "b": 103.17, "c": 125.72, "op1": "-", "op2": "*", "result": -9953.25}
{"question": "Solve: (145.32 + 183) + 136", "answer": "The result of (145.32 + 183) + 136 is 464.32", "a": 145.32, "b": 183, "c": 136, "op1": "+", "op2": "+", "result": 464.32}
{"question": "Solve: (14.08 * 182) + 119.14", "answer": "The result of (14.08 * 182) + 119.14 is 2681.7", "a": 14.08, "b": 182, "c": 119.14, "op1": "*", "op2": "+", "result": 2681.7}
{"question": "Solve: (74.9 - 31) / 67", "answer": "The result of (74.9 - 31) / 67 is 0.66", "a": 74.9, "b": 31, "c": 67, "op1": "-", "op2": "/", "result": 0.66}
{"question": "Solve: (37.74 / 189) * 106.52", "answer": "The result of (37.74 / 189) * 106.52 is 21.27", "a": 37.74, "b": 189, "c": 106.52, "op1": "/", "op2": "*", "result": 21.27}
{"question": "Solve: (175 + 167.37) + 6.55", "answer": "The result of (175 + 167.37) + 6.55 is 348.92", "a": 175, "b": 167.37, "c": 6.55, "op1": "+", "op2": "+", "result": 348.92}
{"question": "Solve: (173 / 27) - 102", "answer": "The result of (173 / 27) - 102 is -95.59", "a": 173, "b": 27, "c": 102, "op1": "/", "op2": "-", "result": -95.59}
{"question": "Solve: (175.81 + 90) - 1.78", "answer": "The result of (175.81 + 90) - 1.78 is 264.03", "a": 175.81, "b": 90, "c": 1.78, "op1": "+", "op2": "-", "result": 264.03}
{"question": "Solve: (183.32 - 70) - 64", "answer": "The result of (183.32 - 70) - 64 is 49.32", "a": 183.32, "b": 70, "c": 64, "op1": "-", "op2": "-", "result": 49.32}
{"question": "Solve: (102 + 79) * 17", "answer": "The result of (102 + 79) * 17 is 3077", "a": 102, "b": 79, "c": 17, "op1": "+", "op2": "*", "result": 3077}
{"question": "Solve: (45.17 + 12) + 12", "answer": "The result of (45.17 + 12) + 12 is 69.17", "a": 45.17, "b": 12, "c": 12, "op1": "+", "op2": "+", "result": 69.17}
{"question": "Solve: (144 * 89.95) + 46.72", "answer": "The result of (144 * 89.95) + 46.72 is 12999.52", "a": 144, "b": 89.95, "c": 46.72, "op1": "*", "op2": "+", "result": 12999.52}
{"question": "Solve: (156 + 100) * 93.56", "answer": "The result of (156 + 100) * 93.56 is 23951.36", "a": 156, "b": 100, "c": 93.56, "op1": "+", "op2": "*", "result": 23951.36}
{"question": "Solve: (23 + 144.02) + 83", "answer": "The result of (23 + 144.02) + 83 is 250.02", "a": 23, "b": 144.02, "c": 83, "op1": "+", "op2": "+", "result": 250.02}
{"question": "Solve: (84 * 177) + 70", "answer": "The result of (84 * 177) + 70 is 14938", "a": 84, "b": 177, "c": 70, "op1": "*", "op2": "+", "result": 14938}
{"question": "Solve: (84 - 112) + 8", "answer": "The result of (84 - 112) + 8 is -20", "a": 84, "b": 112, "c": 8, "op1": "-", "op2": "+", "result": -20}
{"question": "Solve: (145 - 119) - 106.03", "answer": "The result of (145 - 119) - 106.03 is -80.03", "a": 145, "b": 119, "c": 106.03, "op1": "-", "op2": "-", "result": -80.03}
{"question": "Solve: (164 - 173) * 114.1", "answer": "The result of (164 - 173) * 114.1 is -1026.9", "a": 164, "b": 173, "c": 114.1, "op1": "-", "op2": "*", "result": -1026.9}
{"question": "Solve: (33 - 93.42) * 93", "answer": "The result of (33 - 93.42) * 93 is -5619.06", "a": 33, "b": 93.42, "c": 93, "op1": "-", "op2": "*", "result": -5619.06}
{"question": "Solve: (164 / 180) * 144", "answer": "The result of (164 / 180) * 144 is 131.2", "a": 164, "b": 180, "c": 144, "op1": "/", "op2": "*", "result": 131.2}
{"question": "Solve: (30.93 - 191) - 129", "answer": "The result of (30.93 - 191) - 129 is -289.07", "a": 30.93, "b": 191, "c": 129, "op1": "-", "op2": "-", "result": -289.07}
{"question": "Solve: (25.45 - 181.23) * 122.27", "answer": "The result of (25.45 - 181.23) * 122.27 is -19047.22", "a": 25.45, "b": 181.23, "c": 122.27, "op1": "-", "op2": "*", "result": -19047.22}
{"question": "Solve: (71 / 183.73) + 136", "answer": "The result of (71 / 183.73) + 136 is 136.39", "a": 71, "b": 183.73, "c": 136, "op1": "/", "op2": "+", "result": 136.39}
{"question": "Solve: (12.93 + 170) + 63", "answer": "The result of (12.93 + 170) + 63 is 245.93", "a": 12.93, "b": 170, "c": 63, "op1": "+", "op2": "+", "result": 245.93}
{"question": "Solve: (141.09 + 28.88) * 134.06", "answer": "The result of (141.09 + 28.88) * 134.06 is 22786.18", "a": 141.09, "b": 28.88, "c": 134.06, "op1": "+", "op2": "*", "result": 22786.18}
{"question": "Solve: (182 - 193) + 69.06", "answer": "The result of (182 - 193) + 69.06 is 58.06", "a": 182, "b": 193, "c": 69.06, "op1": "-", "op2": "+", "result": 58.06}
{"question": "Solve: (28 - 190) / 86", "answer": "The result of (28 - 190) / 86 is -1.88", "a": 28, "b": 190, "c": 86, "op1": "-", "op2": "/", "result": -1.88}
{"question": "Solve: (52.57 / 184) * 44", "answer": "The result of (52.57 / 184) * 44 is 12.57", "a": 52.57, "b": 184, "c": 44, "op1": "/", "op2": "*", "result": 12.57}
{"question": "Solve: (2 * 15) + 19.37", "answer": "The result of (2 * 15) + 19.37 is 49.37", "a": 2, "b": 15, "c": 19.37, "op1": "*", "op2": "+", "result": 49.37}
{"question": "Solve: (169 + 155) - 62", "answer": "The result of (169 + 155) - 62 is 262", "a": 169, "b": 155, "c": 62, "op1": "+", "op2": "-", "result": 262}
{"question": "Solve: (87 - 176) / 156", "answer": "The result of (87 - 176) / 156 is -0.57", "a": 87, "b": 176, "c": 156, "op1": "-", "op2": "/", "result": -0.57}
{"question": "Solve: (78 * 7.93) * 186.29", "answer": "The result of (78 * 7.93) * 186.29 is 115227.82", "a": 78, "b": 7.93, "c": 186.29, "op1": "*", "op2": "*", "result": 115227.82}
{"question": "Solve: (185.32 - 161) * 65.6", "answer": "The result of (185.32 - 161) * 65.6 is 1595.39", "a": 185.32, "b": 161, "c": 65.6, "op1": "-", "op2": "*", "result": 1595.39}
{"question": "Solve: (58 * 103.49) / 42", "answer": "The result of (58 * 103.49) / 42 is 142.91", "a": 58, "b": 103.49, "c": 42, "op1": "*", "op2": "/", "result": 142.91}
{"question": "Solve: (150 * 134) * 150.01", "answer": "The result of (150 * 134) * 150.01 is 3015201.0", "a": 150, "b": 134, "c": 150.01, "op1": "*", "op2": "*", "result": 3015201.0}
{"question": "Solve: (194.43 + 31) * 16.26", "answer": "The result of (194.43 + 31) * 16.26 is 3665.49", "a": 194.43, "b": 31, "c": 16.26, "op1": "+", "op2": "*", "result": 3665.49}
{"question": "Solve: (96 - 182) - 151", "answer": "The result of (96 - 182) - 151 is -237", "a": 96, "b": 182, "c": 151, "op1": "-", "op2": "-", "result": -237}
{"question": "Solve: (109.63 * 59) * 170", "answer": "The result of (109.63 * 59) * 170 is 1099588.9", "a": 109.63, "b": 59, "c": 170, "op1": "*", "op2": "*", "result": 1099588.9}
{"question": "Solve: (103 + 6.49) * 169.77", "answer": "The result of (103 + 6.49) * 169.77 is 18588.12", "a": 103, "b": 6.49, "c": 169.77, "op1": "+", "op2": "*", "result": 18588.12}
{"question": "Solve: (30 + 60.35) / 133", "answer": "The result of (30 + 60.35) / 133 is 0.68", "a": 30, "b": 60.35, "c": 133, "op1": "+", "op2": "/", "result": 0.68}
{"question": "Solve: (61 + 50) - 97", "answer": "The result of (61 + 50) - 97 is 14", "a": 61, "b": 50, "c": 97, "op1": "+", "op2": "-", "result": 14}
{"question": "Solve: (18.51 - 68.18) / 37.08", "answer": "The result of (18.51 - 68.18) / 37.08 is -1.34", "a": 18.51, "b": 68.18, "c": 37.08, "op1": "-", "op2": "/", "result": -1.34}
{"question": "Solve: (13.45 * 9) - 144.16", "answer": "The result of (13.45 * 9) - 144.16 is -23.11", "a": 13.45, "b": 9, "c": 144.16, "op1": "*", "op2": "-", "result": -23.11}
{"question": "Solve: (150 + 70) + 34", "answer": "The result of (150 + 70) + 34 is 254", "a": 150, "b": 70, "c": 34, "op1": "+", "op2": "+", "result": 254}
{"question": "Solve: (162 + 20) * 97.14", "answer": "The result of (162 + 20) * 97.14 is 17679.48", "a": 162, "b": 20, "c": 97.14, "op1": "+", "op2": "*", "result": 17679.48}
{"question": "Solve: (147 - 156) / 197", "answer": "The result of (147 - 156) / 197 is -0.05", "a": 147, "b": 156, "c": 197, "op1": "-", "op2": "/", "result": -0.05}
{"question": "Solve: (13 + 199.77) - 141", "answer": "The result of (13 + 199.77) - 141 is 71.77", "a": 13, "b": 199.77, "c": 141, "op1": "+", "op2": "-", "result": 71.77}
{"question": "Solve: (120 + 113) / 157.06", "answer": "The result of (120 + 113) / 157.06 is 1.48", "a": 120, "b": 113, "c": 157.06, "op1": "+", "op2": "/", "result": 1.48}
{"question": "Solve: (41 * 183.33) * 124", "answer": "The result of (41 * 183.33) * 124 is 932049.72", "a": 41, "b": 183.33, "c": 124, "op1": "*", "op2": "*", "result": 932049.72}
{"question": "Solve: (64 / 47) - 152.31", "answer": "The result of (64 / 47) - 152.31 is -150.95", "a": 64, "b": 47, "c": 152.31, "op1": "/", "op2": "-", "result": -150.95}
{"question": "Solve: (142.98 * 199) - 112.92", "answer": "The result of (142.98 * 199) - 112.92 is 28340.1", "a": 142.98, "b": 199, "c": 112.92, "op1": "*", "op2": "-", "result": 28340.1}
{"question": "Solve: (96 * 195.63) + 121.33", "answer": "The result of (96 * 195.63) + 121.33 is 18901.81", "a": 96, "b": 195.63, "c": 121.33, "op1": "*", "op2": "+", "result": 18901.81}
{"question": "Solve: (10.34 * 84.9) + 4.35", "answer": "The result of (10.34 * 84.9) + 4.35 is 882.22", "a": 10.34, "b": 84.9, "c": 4.35, "op1": "*", "op2": "+", "result": 882.22}
{"question": "Solve: (135 * 112) * 87", "answer": "The result of (135 * 112) * 87 is 1315440", "a": 135, "b": 112, "c": 87, "op1": "*", "op2": "*", "result": 1315440}
{"question": "Solve: (109 - 58.57) - 7", "answer": "The result of (109 - 58.57) - 7 is 43.43", "a": 109, "b": 58.57, "c": 7, "op1": "-", "op2": "-", "result": 43.43}
{"question": "Solve: (198 + 58) - 200", "answer": "The result of (198 + 58) - 200 is 56", "a": 198, "b": 58, "c": 200, "op1": "+", "op2": "-", "result": 56}
{"question": "Solve: (191 - 172) - 84", "answer": "The result of (191 - 172) - 84 is -65", "a": 191, "b": 172, "c": 84, "op1": "-", "op2": "-", "result": -65}
{"question": "Solve: (93.59 * 69.57) + 168.42", "answer": "The result of (93.59 * 69.57) + 168.42 is 6679.48", "a": 93.59, "b": 69.57, "c": 168.42, "op1": "*", "op2": "+", "result": 6679.48}
{"question": "Solve: (75.87 / 75) * 144", "answer": "The result of (75.87 / 75) * 144 is 145.67", "a": 75.87, "b": 75, "c": 144, "op1": "/", "op2": "*", "result": 145.67}
{"question": "Solve: (60.97 * 145.29) * 87.19", "answer": "The result of (60.97 * 145.29) * 87.19 is 772357.91", "a": 60.97, "b": 145.29, "c": 87.19, "op1": "*", "op2": "*", "result": 772357.91}
{"question": "Solve: (174 - 64.59) - 110.67", "answer": "The result of (174 - 64.59) - 110.67 is -1.26", "a": 174, "b": 64.59, "c": 110.67, "op1": "-", "op2": "-", "result": -1.26}
{"question": "Solve: (193 - 71.7) * 52", "answer": "The result of (193 - 71.7) * 52 is 6307.6", "a": 193, "b": 71.7, "c": 52, "op1": "-", "op2": "*", "result": 6307.6}
{"question": "Solve: (28 + 69) + 7", "answer": "The result of (28 + 69) + 7 is 104", "a": 28, "b": 69, "c": 7, "op1": "+", "op2": "+", "result": 104}
{"question": "Solve: (119.3 + 21.79) * 110", "answer": "The result of (119.3 + 21.79) * 110 is 15519.9", "a": 119.3, "b": 21.79, "c": 110, "op1": "+", "op2": "*", "result": 15519.9}
{"question": "Solve: (57 / 177.05) - 31.45", "answer": "The result of (57 / 177.05) - 31.45 is -31.13", "a": 57, "b": 177.05, "c": 31.45, "op1": "/", "op2": "-", "result": -31.13}
{"question": "Solve: (63 * 48) + 157", "answer": "The result of (63 * 48) + 157 is 3181", "a": 63, "b": 48, "c": 157, "op1": "*", "op2": "+", "result": 3181}
{"question": "Solve: (56 - 113) * 101", "answer": "The result of (56 - 113) * 101 is -5757", "a": 56, "b": 113, "c": 101, "op1": "-", "op2": "*", "result": -5757}
{"question": "Solve: (50 - 30.71) - 139", "answer": "The result of (50 - 30.71) - 139 is -119.71", "a": 50, "b": 30.71, "c": 139, "op1": "-", "op2": "-", "result": -119.71}
{"question": "Solve: (17 - 96) * 37", "answer": "The result of (17 - 96) * 37 is -2923", "a": 17, "b": 96, "c": 37, "op1": "-", "op2": "*", "result": -2923}
{"question": "Solve: (119 + 29) - 61", "answer": "The result of (119 + 29) - 61 is 87", "a": 119, "b": 29, "c": 61, "op1": "+", "op2": "-", "result": 87}
{"question": "Solve: (127 - 94) / 143", "answer": "The result of (127 - 94) / 143 is 0.23", "a": 127, "b": 94, "c": 143, "op1": "-", "op2": "/", "result": 0.23}
{"question": "Solve: (104.84 * 129) - 149", "answer": "The result of (104.84 * 129) - 149 is 13375.36", "a": 104.84, "b": 129, "c": 149, "op1": "*", "op2": "-", "result": 13375.36}
{"question": "Solve: (166.55 - 38) - 112", "answer": "The result of (166.55 - 38) - 112 is 16.55", "a": 166.55, "b": 38, "c": 112, "op1": "-", "op2": "-", "result": 16.55}
{"question": "Solve: (199.44 - 19) - 14.14", "answer": "The result of (199.44 - 19) - 14.14 is 166.3", "a": 199.44, "b": 19, "c": 14.14, "op1": "-", "op2": "-", "result": 166.3}
{"question": "Solve: (117 - 79.87) / 181", "answer": "The result of (117 - 79.87) / 181 is 0.21", "a": 117, "b": 79.87, "c": 181, "op1": "-", "op2": "/", "result": 0.21}
{"question": "Solve: (64.97 * 23) + 184", "answer": "The result of (64.97 * 23) + 184 is 1678.31", "a": 64.97, "b": 23, "c": 184, "op1": "*", "op2": "+", "result": 1678.31}
{"question": "Solve: (121.26 - 149) - 3", "answer": "The result of (121.26 - 149) - 3 is -30.74", "a": 121.26, "b": 149, "c": 3, "op1": "-", "op2": "-", "result": -30.74}
{"question": "Solve: (14 + 124.43) - 34", "answer": "The result of (14 + 124.43) - 34 is 104.43", "a": 14, "b": 124.43, "c": 34, "op1": "+", "op2": "-", "result": 104.43}
{"question": "Solve: (159 + 161) * 110.74", "answer": "The result of (159 + 161) * 110.74 is 35436.8", "a": 159, "b": 161, "c": 110.74, "op1": "+", "op2": "*", "result": 35436.8}
{"question": "Solve: (183.86 * 76.16) * 55", "answer": "The result of (183.86 * 76.16) * 55 is 770152.77", "a": 183.86, "b": 76.16, "c": 55, "op1": "*", "op2": "*", "result": 770152.77}
{"question": "Solve: (77.05 / 59) / 174", "answer": "The result of (77.05 / 59) / 174 is 0.01", "a": 77.05, "b": 59, "c": 174, "op1": "/", "op2": "/", "result": 0.01}
{"question": "Solve: (145.5 - 105) - 151", "answer": "The result of (145.5 - 105) - 151 is -110.5", "a": 145.5, "b": 105, "c": 151, "op1": "-", "op2": "-", "result": -110.5}
{"question": "Solve: (85 / 61.46) * 76.51", "answer": "The result of (85 / 61.46) * 76.51 is 105.81", "a": 85, "b": 61.46, "c": 76.51, "op1": "/", "op2": "*", "result": 105.81}
{"question": "Solve: (114 * 77.02) + 60.4", "answer": "The result of (114 * 77.02) + 60.4 is 8840.68", "a": 114, "b": 77.02, "c": 60.4, "op1": "*", "op2": "+", "result": 8840.68}
{"question": "Solve: (153 + 47) + 67", "answer": "The result of (153 + 47) + 67 is 267", "a": 153, "b": 47, "c": 67, "op1": "+", "op2": "+", "result": 267}
{"question": "Solve: (42 / 164) + 4", "answer": "The result of (42 / 164) + 4 is 4.26", "a": 42, "b": 164, "c": 4, "op1": "/", "op2": "+", "result": 4.26}
{"question": "Solve: (169 * 63) + 110", "answer": "The result of (169 * 63) + 110 is 10757", "a": 169, "b": 63, "c": 110, "op1": "*", "op2": "+", "result": 10757}
{"question": "Solve: (166 * 83) * 164", "answer": "The result of (166 * 83) * 164 is 2259592", "a": 166, "b": 83, "c": 164, "op1": "*", "op2": "*", "result": 2259592}
{"question": "Solve: (108 + 40.29) - 104.17", "answer": "The result of (108 + 40.29) - 104.17 is 44.12", "a": 108, "b": 40.29, "c": 104.17, "op1": "+", "op2": "-", "result": 44.12}
{"question": "Solve: (172.27 + 59) * 22.34", "answer": "The result of (172.27 + 59) * 22.34 is 5166.57", "a": 172.27, "b": 59, "c": 22.34, "op1": "+", "op2": "*", "result": 5166.57}
{"question": "Solve: (21 / 46) / 2", "answer": "The result of (21 / 46) / 2 is 0.23", "a": 21, "b": 46, "c": 2, "op1": "/", "op2": "/", "result": 0.23}
{"question": "Solve: (40.56 * 74.58) * 48", "answer": "The result of (40.56 * 74.58) * 48 is 145198.31", "a": 40.56, "b": 74.58, "c": 48, "op1": "*", "op2": "*", "result": 145198.31}
{"question": "Solve: (160 - 20) - 197.21", "answer": "The result of (160 - 20) - 197.21 is -57.21", "a": 160, "b": 20, "c": 197.21, "op1": "-", "op2": "-", "result": -57.21}
{"question": "Solve: (85 * 40.03) * 112", "answer": "The result of (85 * 40.03) * 112 is 381085.6", "a": 85, "b": 40.03, "c": 112, "op1": "*", "op2": "*", "result": 381085.6}
{"question": "Solve: (89 + 102) - 61.96", "answer": "The result of (89 + 102) - 61.96 is 129.04", "a": 89, "b": 102, "c": 61.96, "op1": "+", "op2": "-", "result": 129.04}
{"question": "Solve: (104 * 9.19) + 16", "answer": "The result of (104 * 9.19) + 16 is 971.76", "a": 104, "b": 9.19, "c": 16, "op1": "*", "op2": "+", "result": 971.76}
{"question": "Solve: (122 + 158) / 144", "answer": "The result of (122 + 158) / 144 is 1.94", "a": 122, "b": 158, "c": 144, "op1": "+", "op2": "/", "result": 1.94}
{"question": "Solve: (188 - 102) * 46", "answer": "The result of (188 - 102) * 46 is 3956", "a": 188, "b": 102, "c": 46, "op1": "-", "op2": "*", "result": 3956}
{"question": "Solve: (124.16 + 81.78) * 152", "answer": "The result of (124.16 + 81.78) * 152 is 31302.88", "a": 124.16, "b": 81.78, "c": 152, "op1": "+", "op2": "*", "result": 31302.88}
{"question": "Solve: (176 + 86) - 175.59", "answer": "The result of (176 + 86) - 175.59 is 86.41", "a": 176, "b": 86, "c": 175.59, "op1": "+", "op2": "-", "result": 86.41}
{"question": "Solve: (134 - 66.57) * 115", "answer": "The result of (134 - 66.57) * 115 is 7754.45", "a": 134, "b": 66.57, "c": 115, "op1": "-", "op2": "*", "result": 7754.45}
{"question": "Solve: (40 * 30.74) + 48", "answer": "The result of (40 * 30.74) + 48 is 1277.6", "a": 40, "b": 30.74, "c": 48, "op1": "*", "op2": "+", "result": 1277.6}
{"question": "Solve: (159 + 40) - 81", "answer": "The result of (159 + 40) - 81 is 118", "a": 159, "b": 40, "c": 81, "op1": "+", "op2": "-", "result": 118}
{"question": "Solve: (61 * 163) - 198", "answer": "The result of (61 * 163) - 198 is 9745", "a": 61, "b": 163, "c": 198, "op1": "*", "op2": "-", "result": 9745}
{"question": "Solve: (17 + 47) - 14.92", "answer": "The result of (17 + 47) - 14.92 is 49.08", "a": 17, "b": 47, "c": 14.92, "op1": "+", "op2": "-", "result": 49.08}
{"question": "Solve: (41 / 183.82) / 111", "answer": "The result of (41 / 183.82) / 111 is 0.0", "a": 41, "b": 183.82, "c": 111, "op1": "/", "op2": "/", "result": 0.0}
{"question": "Solve: (164 - 44) - 66", "answer": "The result of (164 - 44) - 66 is 54", "a": 164, "b": 44, "c": 66, "op1": "-", "op2": "-", "result": 54}
{"question": "Solve: (22 / 142) * 187.31", "answer": "The result of (22 / 142) * 187.31 is 29.02", "a": 22, "b": 142, "c": 187.31, "op1": "/", "op2": "*", "result": 29.02}
{"question": "Solve: (62 + 159) + 117", "answer": "The result of (62 + 159) + 117 is 338", "a": 62, "b": 159, "c": 117, "op1": "+", "op2": "+", "result": 338}
{"question": "Solve: (70.42 - 32) + 65", "answer": "The result of (70.42 - 32) + 65 is 103.42", "a": 70.42, "b": 32, "c": 65, "op1": "-", "op2": "+", "result": 103.42}
{"question": "Solve: (134.7 * 25.04) * 75", "answer": "The result of (134.7 * 25.04) * 75 is 252966.6", "a": 134.7, "b": 25.04, "c": 75, "op1": "*", "op2": "*", "result": 252966.6}
{"question": "Solve: (131 + 185) * 36", "answer": "The result of (131 + 185) * 36 is 11376", "a": 131, "b": 185, "c": 36, "op1": "+", "op2": "*", "result": 11376}
{"question": "Solve: (177 / 121) * 163.84", "answer": "The result of (177 / 121) * 163.84 is 239.67", "a": 177, "b": 121, "c": 163.84, "op1": "/", "op2": "*", "result": 239.67}
{"question": "Solve: (35 / 32) - 88", "answer": "The result of (35 / 32) - 88 is -86.91", "a": 35, "b": 32, "c": 88, "op1": "/", "op2": "-", "result": -86.91}
{"question": "Solve: (196 + 13) - 144", "answer": "The result of (196 + 13) - 144 is 65", "a": 196, "b": 13, "c": 144, "op1": "+", "op2": "-", "result": 65}
{"question": "Solve: (155 + 121.69) - 85", "answer": "The result of (155 + 121.69) - 85 is 191.69", "a": 155, "b": 121.69, "c": 85, "op1": "+", "op2": "-", "result": 191.69}
{"question": "Solve: (10.97 * 94.58) + 110.33", "answer": "The result of (10.97 * 94.58) + 110.33 is 1147.87", "a": 10.97, "b": 94.58, "c": 110.33, "op1": "*", "op2": "+", "result": 1147.87}
{"question": "Solve: (66.44 / 129) - 163", "answer": "The result of (66.44 / 129) - 163 is -162.48", "a": 66.44, "b": 129, "c": 163, "op1": "/", "op2": "-", "result": -162.48}
{"question": "Solve: (67 - 143.4) + 38.15", "answer": "The result of (67 - 143.4) + 38.15 is -38.25", "a": 67, "b": 143.4, "c": 38.15, "op1": "-", "op2": "+", "result": -38.25}
{"question": "Solve: (142.22 * 158) * 169.96", "answer": "The result of (142.22 * 158) * 169.96 is 3819130.37", "a": 142.22, "b": 158, "c": 169.96, "op1": "*", "op2": "*", "result": 3819130.37}
{"question": "Solve: (190 / 196) - 118.91", "answer": "The result of (190 / 196) - 118.91 is -117.94", "a": 190, "b": 196, "c": 118.91, "op1": "/", "op2": "-", "result": -117.94}
{"question": "Solve: (23 - 116) - 139.66", "answer": "The result of (23 - 116) - 139.66 is -232.66", "a": 23, "b": 116, "c": 139.66, "op1": "-", "op2": "-", "result": -232.66}
{"question": "Solve: (185 / 26) / 12", "answer": "The result of (185 / 26) / 12 is 0.59", "a": 185, "b": 26, "c": 12, "op1": "/", "op2": "/", "result": 0.59}
{"question": "Solve: (103 + 52.43) - 3.78", "answer": "The result of (103 + 52.43) - 3.78 is 151.65", "a": 103, "b": 52.43, "c": 3.78, "op1": "+", "op2": "-", "result": 151.65}
{"question": "Solve: (174.31 * 92) - 78", "answer": "The result of (174.31 * 92) - 78 is 15958.52", "a": 174.31, "b": 92, "c": 78, "op1": "*", "op2": "-", "result": 15958.52}
{"question": "Solve: (159 + 115) * 98.52", "answer": "The result of (159 + 115) * 98.52 is 26994.48", "a": 159, "b": 115, "c": 98.52, "op1": "+", "op2": "*", "result": 26994.48}
{"question": "Solve: (129.37 - 187.46) * 86", "answer": "The result of (129.37 - 187.46) * 86 is -4995.74", "a": 129.37, "b": 187.46, "c": 86, "op1": "-", "op2": "*", "result": -4995.74}
{"question": "Solve: (130 + 152) - 88", "answer": "The result of (130 + 152) - 88 is 194", "a": 130, "b": 152, "c": 88, "op1": "+", "op2": "-", "result": 194}
{"question": "Solve: (36 + 59) + 17", "answer": "The result of (36 + 59) + 17 is 112", "a": 36, "b": 59, "c": 17, "op1": "+", "op2": "+", "result": 112}
{"question": "Solve: (15.56 + 192) + 61", "answer": "The result of (15.56 + 192) + 61 is 268.56", "a": 15.56, "b": 192, "c": 61, "op1": "+", "op2": "+", "result": 268.56}
{"question": "Solve: (144 + 72) * 89", "answer": "The result of (144 + 72) * 89 is 19224", "a": 144, "b": 72, "c": 89, "op1": "+", "op2": "*", "result": 19224}
{"question": "Solve: (30 / 37.3) + 80.57", "answer": "The result of (30 / 37.3) + 80.57 is 81.37", "a": 30, "b": 37.3, "c": 80.57, "op1": "/", "op2": "+", "result": 81.37}
{"question": "Solve: (80 - 39) / 82.56", "answer": "The result of (80 - 39) / 82.56 is 0.5", "a": 80, "b": 39, "c": 82.56, "op1": "-", "op2": "/", "result": 0.5}
{"question": "Solve: (81 * 134.59) - 10", "answer": "The result of (81 * 134.59) - 10 is 10891.79", "a": 81, "b": 134.59, "c": 10, "op1": "*", "op2": "-", "result": 10891.79}
{"question": "Solve: (42 * 68) + 36", "answer": "The result of (42 * 68) + 36 is 2892", "a": 42, "b": 68, "c": 36, "op1": "*", "op2": "+", "result": 2892}
{"question": "Solve: (90.95 + 177) / 194", "answer": "The result of (90.95 + 177) / 194 is 1.38", "a": 90.95, "b": 177, "c": 194, "op1": "+", "op2": "/", "result": 1.38}
{"question": "Solve: (34.3 + 122.12) - 49", "answer": "The result of (34.3 + 122.12) - 49 is 107.42", "a": 34.3, "b": 122.12, "c": 49, "op1": "+", "op2": "-", "result": 107.42}
{"question": "Solve: (81 + 124) - 164.29", "answer": "The result of (81 + 124) - 164.29 is 40.71", "a": 81, "b": 124, "c": 164.29, "op1": "+", "op2": "-", "result": 40.71}
{"question": "Solve: (130.27 + 77) * 18", "answer": "The result of (130.27 + 77) * 18 is 3730.86", "a": 130.27, "b": 77, "c": 18, "op1": "+", "op2": "*", "result": 3730.86}
{"question": "Solve: (164.61 / 19.39) * 166.83", "answer": "The result of (164.61 / 19.39) * 166.83 is 1416.29", "a": 164.61, "b": 19.39, "c": 166.83, "op1": "/", "op2": "*", "result": 1416.29}
{"question": "Solve: (143 - 25) + 36", "answer": "The result of (143 - 25) + 36 is 154", "a": 143, "b": 25, "c": 36, "op1": "-", "op2": "+", "result": 154}
{"question": "Solve: (34 - 150) * 32.78", "answer": "The result of (34 - 150) * 32.78 is -3802.48", "a": 34, "b": 150, "c": 32.78, "op1": "-", "op2": "*", "result": -3802.48}
{"question": "Solve: (148.63 * 108) - 79.94", "answer": "The result of (148.63 * 108) - 79.94 is 15972.1", "a": 148.63, "b": 108, "c": 79.94, "op1": "*", "op2": "-", "result": 15972.1}
{"question": "Solve: (20 - 18.83) * 153.42", "answer": "The result of (20 - 18.83) * 153.42 is 179.5", "a": 20, "b": 18.83, "c": 153.42, "op1": "-", "op2": "*", "result": 179.5}
{"question": "Solve: (41.04 - 45) - 188.82", "answer": "The result of (41.04 - 45) - 188.82 is -192.78", "a": 41.04, "b": 45, "c": 188.82, "op1": "-", "op2": "-", "result": -192.78}
{"question": "Solve: (23.9 + 32) + 3", "answer": "The result of (23.9 + 32) + 3 is 58.9", "a": 23.9, "b": 32, "c": 3, "op1": "+", "op2": "+", "result": 58.9}
{"question": "Solve: (35 - 69) / 129.6", "answer": "The result of (35 - 69) / 129.6 is -0.26", "a": 35, "b": 69, "c": 129.6, "op1": "-", "op2": "/", "result": -0.26}
{"question": "Solve: (104 - 149) * 80", "answer": "The result of (104 - 149) * 80 is -3600", "a": 104, "b": 149, "c": 80, "op1": "-", "op2": "*", "result": -3600}
{"question": "Solve: (83 / 169.31) + 70.75", "answer": "The result of (83 / 169.31) + 70.75 is 71.24", "a": 83, "b": 169.31, "c": 70.75, "op1": "/", "op2": "+", "result": 71.24}
{"question": "Solve: (172 - 101.16) - 54", "answer": "The result of (172 - 101.16) - 54 is 16.84", "a": 172, "b": 101.16, "c": 54, "op1": "-", "op2": "-", "result": 16.84}
{"question": "Solve: (142.32 - 34) * 41.92", "answer": "The result of (142.32 - 34) * 41.92 is 4540.77", "a": 142.32, "b": 34, "c": 41.92, "op1": "-", "op2": "*", "result": 4540.77}
{"question": "Solve: (60 - 133.79) / 168", "answer": "The result of (60 - 133.79) / 168 is -0.44", "a": 60, "b": 133.79, "c": 168, "op1": "-", "op2": "/", "result": -0.44}
{"question": "Solve: (112.93 * 181.63) - 42", "answer": "The result of (112.93 * 181.63) - 42 is 20469.48", "a": 112.93, "b": 181.63, "c": 42, "op1": "*", "op2": "-", "result": 20469.48}
{"question": "Solve: (118.71 + 31) * 27", "answer": "The result of (118.71 + 31) * 27 is 4042.17", "a": 118.71, "b": 31, "c": 27, "op1": "+", "op2": "*", "result": 4042.17}
{"question": "Solve: (120 - 116) - 134", "answer": "The result of (120 - 116) - 134 is -130", "a": 120, "b": 116, "c": 134, "op1": "-", "op2": "-", "result": -130}
{"question": "Solve: (17 * 143) * 148", "answer": "The result of (17 * 143) * 148 is 359788", "a": 17, "b": 143, "c": 148, "op1": "*", "op2": "*", "result": 359788}
{"question": "Solve: (65 * 37.45) * 45", "answer": "The result of (65 * 37.45) * 45 is 109541.25", "a": 65, "b": 37.45, "c": 45, "op1": "*", "op2": "*", "result": 109541.25}
{"question": "Solve: (70.46 * 171) - 42", "answer": "The result of (70.46 * 171) - 42 is 12006.66", "a": 70.46, "b": 171, "c": 42, "op1": "*", "op2": "-", "result": 12006.66}
{"question": "Solve: (37 * 188) * 193", "answer": "The result of (37 * 188) * 193 is 1342508", "a": 37, "b": 188, "c": 193, "op1": "*", "op2": "*", "result": 1342508}
{"question": "Solve: (49 - 148) + 160", "answer": "The result of (49 - 148) + 160 is 61", "a": 49, "b": 148, "c": 160, "op1": "-", "op2": "+", "result": 61}
{"question": "Solve: (122 + 117.22) - 167", "answer": "The result of (122 + 117.22) - 167 is 72.22", "a": 122, "b": 117.22, "c": 167, "op1": "+", "op2": "-", "result": 72.22}
{"question": "Solve: (117 - 140.22) - 173", "answer": "The result of (117 - 140.22) - 173 is -196.22", "a": 117, "b": 140.22, "c": 173, "op1": "-", "op2": "-", "result": -196.22}
{"question": "Solve: (190 - 71) - 194.72", "answer": "The result of (190 - 71) - 194.72 is -75.72", "a": 190, "b": 71, "c": 194.72, "op1": "-", "op2": "-", "result": -75.72}
{"question": "Solve: (178 + 4) * 160", "answer": "The result of (178 + 4) * 160 is 29120", "a": 178, "b": 4, "c": 160, "op1": "+", "op2": "*", "result": 29120}
{"question": "Solve: (21 - 24) - 68", "answer": "The result of (21 - 24) - 68 is -71", "a": 21, "b": 24, "c": 68, "op1": "-", "op2": "-", "result": -71}
{"question": "Solve: (105 + 159) * 130.29", "answer": "The result of (105 + 159) * 130.29 is 34396.56", "a": 105, "b": 159, "c": 130.29, "op1": "+", "op2": "*", "result": 34396.56}
{"question": "Solve: (122 + 88) * 53", "answer": "The result of (122 + 88) * 53 is 11130", "a": 122, "b": 88, "c": 53, "op1": "+", "op2": "*", "result": 11130}
{"question": "Solve: (126 * 111) + 173", "answer": "The result of (126 * 111) + 173 is 14159", "a": 126, "b": 111, "c": 173, "op1": "*", "op2": "+", "result": 14159}
{"question": "Solve: (114 + 159) * 23.29", "answer": "The result of (114 + 159) * 23.29 is 6358.17", "a": 114, "b": 159, "c": 23.29, "op1": "+", "op2": "*", "result": 6358.17}
{"question": "Solve: (191 + 53) + 83.95", "answer": "The result of (191 + 53) + 83.95 is 327.95", "a": 191, "b": 53, "c": 83.95, "op1": "+", "op2": "+", "result": 327.95}
{"question": "Solve: (97.69 * 187) * 125.0", "answer": "The result of (97.69 * 187) * 125.0 is 2283503.75", "a": 97.69, "b": 187, "c": 125.0, "op1": "*", "op2": "*", "result": 2283503.75}
{"question": "Solve: (98 - 67) / 115", "answer": "The result of (98 - 67) / 115 is 0.27", "a": 98, "b": 67, "c": 115, "op1": "-", "op2": "/", "result": 0.27}
{"question": "Solve: (124 / 33) / 171", "answer": "The result of (124 / 33) / 171 is 0.02", "a": 124, "b": 33, "c": 171, "op1": "/", "op2": "/", "result": 0.02}
{"question": "Solve: (171 + 156) + 90", "answer": "The result of (171 + 156) + 90 is 417", "a": 171, "b": 156, "c": 90, "op1": "+", "op2": "+", "result": 417}
{"question": "Solve: (146 / 17) * 62.32", "answer": "The result of (146 / 17) * 62.32 is 535.22", "a": 146, "b": 17, "c": 62.32, "op1": "/", "op2": "*", "result": 535.22}
{"question": "Solve: (93 * 126) - 133.44", "answer": "The result of (93 * 126) - 133.44 is 11584.56", "a": 93, "b": 126, "c": 133.44, "op1": "*", "op2": "-", "result": 11584.56}
{"question": "Solve: (176 * 20) - 128", "answer": "The result of (176 * 20) - 128 is 3392", "a": 176, "b": 20, "c": 128, "op1": "*", "op2": "-", "result": 3392}
{"question": "Solve: (178 / 116) + 193", "answer": "The result of (178 / 116) + 193 is 194.53", "a": 178, "b": 116, "c": 193, "op1": "/", "op2": "+", "result": 194.53}
{"question": "Solve: (73 - 142) + 172", "answer": "The result of (73 - 142) + 172 is 103", "a": 73, "b": 142, "c": 172, "op1": "-", "op2": "+", "result": 103}
{"question": "Solve: (125 / 107) * 26", "answer": "The result of (125 / 107) * 26 is 30.37", "a": 125, "b": 107, "c": 26, "op1": "/", "op2": "*", "result": 30.37}
{"question": "Solve: (75 - 59.29) + 3.26", "answer": "The result of (75 - 59.29) + 3.26 is 18.97", "a": 75, "b": 59.29, "c": 3.26, "op1": "-", "op2": "+", "result": 18.97}
{"question": "Solve: (62.29 + 32) + 128", "answer": "The result of (62.29 + 32) + 128 is 222.29", "a": 62.29, "b": 32, "c": 128, "op1": "+", "op2": "+", "result": 222.29}
{"question": "Solve: (2.75 * 114) * 81", "answer": "The result of (2.75 * 114) * 81 is 25393.5", "a": 2.75, "b": 114, "c": 81, "op1": "*", "op2": "*", "result": 25393.5}
{"question": "Solve: (3 - 62) / 164", "answer": "The result of (3 - 62) / 164 is -0.36", "a": 3, "b": 62, "c": 164, "op1": "-", "op2": "/", "result": -0.36}
{"question": "Solve: (72 * 138) * 199", "answer": "The result of (72 * 138) * 199 is 1977264", "a": 72, "b": 138, "c": 199, "op1": "*", "op2": "*", "result": 1977264}
{"question": "Solve: (104.42 + 82.04) * 135.18", "answer": "The result of (104.42 + 82.04) * 135.18 is 25205.66", "a": 104.42, "b": 82.04, "c": 135.18, "op1": "+", "op2": "*", "result": 25205.66}
{"question": "Solve: (35 * 89) / 54.93", "answer": "The result of (35 * 89) / 54.93 is 56.71", "a": 35, "b": 89, "c": 54.93, "op1": "*", "op2": "/", "result": 56.71}
{"question": "Solve: (192 + 136.76) * 7.06", "answer": "The result of (192 + 136.76) * 7.06 is 2321.05", "a": 192, "b": 136.76, "c": 7.06, "op1": "+", "op2": "*", "result": 2321.05}
{"question": "Solve: (53.03 + 94) + 83.03", "answer": "The result of (53.03 + 94) + 83.03 is 230.06", "a": 53.03, "b": 94, "c": 83.03, "op1": "+", "op2": "+", "result": 230.06}
{"question": "Solve: (5 - 190) + 153", "answer": "The result of (5 - 190) + 153 is -32", "a": 5, "b": 190, "c": 153, "op1": "-", "op2": "+", "result": -32}
{"question": "Solve: (112 * 156) - 131", "answer": "The result of (112 * 156) - 131 is 17341", "a": 112, "b": 156, "c": 131, "op1": "*", "op2": "-", "result": 17341}
{"question": "Solve: (87.45 + 17) - 109.88", "answer": "The result of (87.45 + 17) - 109.88 is -5.43", "a": 87.45, "b": 17, "c": 109.88, "op1": "+", "op2": "-", "result": -5.43}
{"question": "Solve: (113 + 68) - 160.66", "answer": "The result of (113 + 68) - 160.66 is 20.34", "a": 113, "b": 68, "c": 160.66, "op1": "+", "op2": "-", "result": 20.34}
{"question": "Solve: (76 + 19.0) - 179", "answer": "The result of (76 + 19.0) - 179 is -84.0", "a": 76, "b": 19.0, "c": 179, "op1": "+", "op2": "-", "result": -84.0}
{"question": "Solve: (61.67 + 58.65) * 78", "answer": "The result of (61.67 + 58.65) * 78 is 9384.96", "a": 61.67, "b": 58.65, "c": 78, "op1": "+", "op2": "*", "result": 9384.96}
{"question": "Solve: (181.19 * 98) - 131", "answer": "The result of (181.19 * 98) - 131 is 17625.62", "a": 181.19, "b": 98, "c": 131, "op1": "*", "op2": "-", "result": 17625.62}
{"question": "Solve: (183 * 145) + 141", "answer": "The result of (183 * 145) + 141 is 26676", "a": 183, "b": 145, "c": 141, "op1": "*", "op2": "+", "result": 26676}
{"question": "Solve: (4 * 185.9) / 41", "answer": "The result of (4 * 185.9) / 41 is 18.14", "a": 4, "b": 185.9, "c": 41, "op1": "*", "op2": "/", "result": 18.14}
{"question": "Solve: (150 - 44.68) - 177", "answer": "The result of (150 - 44.68) - 177 is -71.68", "a": 150, "b": 44.68, "c": 177, "op1": "-", "op2": "-", "result": -71.68}
{"question": "Solve: (198.42 - 155) * 47.13", "answer": "The result of (198.42 - 155) * 47.13 is 2046.38", "a": 198.42, "b": 155, "c": 47.13, "op1": "-", "op2": "*", "result": 2046.38}
{"question": "Solve: (44.19 - 52.11) * 18", "answer": "The result of (44.19 - 52.11) * 18 is -142.56", "a": 44.19, "b": 52.11, "c": 18, "op1": "-", "op2": "*", "result": -142.56}
{"question": "Solve: (38.27 - 105) - 164", "answer": "The result of (38.27 - 105) - 164 is -230.73", "a": 38.27, "b": 105, "c": 164, "op1": "-", "op2": "-", "result": -230.73}
{"question": "Solve: (147 / 62) / 58.45", "answer": "The result of (147 / 62) / 58.45 is 0.04", "a": 147, "b": 62, "c": 58.45, "op1": "/", "op2": "/", "result": 0.04}
{"question": "Solve: (179.74 / 129.7) + 79", "answer": "The result of (179.74 / 129.7) + 79 is 80.39", "a": 179.74, "b": 129.7, "c": 79, "op1": "/", "op2": "+", "result": 80.39}
{"question": "Solve: (131 * 37.92) + 128.72", "answer": "The result of (131 * 37.92) + 128.72 is 5096.24", "a": 131, "b": 37.92, "c": 128.72, "op1": "*", "op2": "+", "result": 5096.24}
{"question": "Solve: (189 - 184.89) * 103", "answer": "The result of (189 - 184.89) * 103 is 423.33", "a": 189, "b": 184.89, "c": 103, "op1": "-", "op2": "*", "result": 423.33}
{"question": "Solve: (85.56 / 89) / 138", "answer": "The result of (85.56 / 89) / 138 is 0.01", "a": 85.56, "b": 89, "c": 138, "op1": "/", "op2": "/", "result": 0.01}
{"question": "Solve: (128 + 122) - 121", "answer": "The result of (128 + 122) - 121 is 129", "a": 128, "b": 122, "c": 121, "op1": "+", "op2": "-", "result": 129}
{"question": "Solve: (33 / 63) + 122", "answer": "The result of (33 / 63) + 122 is 122.52", "a": 33, "b": 63, "c": 122, "op1": "/", "op2": "+", "result": 122.52}
{"question": "Solve: (96.65 / 96) + 150", "answer": "The result of (96.65 / 96) + 150 is 151.01", "a": 96.65, "b": 96, "c": 150, "op1": "/", "op2": "+", "result": 151.01}
{"question": "Solve: (65 - 194.32) + 14", "answer": "The result of (65 - 194.32) + 14 is -115.32", "a": 65, "b": 194.32, "c": 14, "op1": "-", "op2": "+", "result": -115.32}
{"question": "Solve: (88 + 155) - 182.2", "answer": "The result of (88 + 155) - 182.2 is 60.8", "a": 88, "b": 155, "c": 182.2, "op1": "+", "op2": "-", "result": 60.8}
{"question": "Solve: (126 * 88) + 93", "answer": "The result of (126 * 88) + 93 is 11181", "a": 126, "b": 88, "c": 93, "op1": "*", "op2": "+", "result": 11181}
{"question": "Solve: (110 - 87.15) + 75", "answer": "The result of (110 - 87.15) + 75 is 97.85", "a": 110, "b": 87.15, "c": 75, "op1": "-", "op2": "+", "result": 97.85}
{"question": "Solve: (114.95 / 136.53) + 143", "answer": "The result of (114.95 / 136.53) + 143 is 143.84", "a": 114.95, "b": 136.53, "c": 143, "op1": "/", "op2": "+", "result": 143.84}
{"question": "Solve: (68.15 * 189) * 41.09", "answer": "The result of (68.15 * 189) * 41.09 is 529253.58", "a": 68.15, "b": 189, "c": 41.09, "op1": "*", "op2": "*", "result": 529253.58}
{"question": "Solve: (110 * 186) / 41", "answer": "The result of (110 * 186) / 41 is 499.02", "a": 110, "b": 186, "c": 41, "op1": "*", "op2": "/", "result": 499.02}
{"question": "Solve: (15 + 100) + 172", "answer": "The result of (15 + 100) + 172 is 287", "a": 15, "b": 100, "c": 172, "op1": "+", "op2": "+", "result": 287}
{"question": "Solve: (25.5 - 151) / 113", "answer": "The result of (25.5 - 151) / 113 is -1.11", "a": 25.5, "b": 151, "c": 113, "op1": "-", "op2": "/", "result": -1.11}
{"question": "Solve: (61 * 69) * 11", "answer": "The result of (61 * 69) * 11 is 46299", "a": 61, "b": 69, "c": 11, "op1": "*", "op2": "*", "result": 46299}
{"question": "Solve: (54.92 * 86) * 168", "answer": "The result of (54.92 * 86) * 168 is 793484.16", "a": 54.92, "b": 86, "c": 168, "op1": "*", "op2": "*", "result": 793484.16}
{"question": "Solve: (115 * 77) + 63", "answer": "The result of (115 * 77) + 63 is 8918", "a": 115, "b": 77, "c": 63, "op1": "*", "op2": "+", "result": 8918}
{"question": "Solve: (58.61 - 189.98) - 188", "answer": "The result of (58.61 - 189.98) - 188 is -319.37", "a": 58.61, "b": 189.98, "c": 188, "op1": "-", "op2": "-", "result": -319.37}
{"question": "Solve: (134.98 / 189) + 191", "answer": "The result of (134.98 / 189) + 191 is 191.71", "a": 134.98, "b": 189, "c": 191, "op1": "/", "op2": "+", "result": 191.71}
{"question": "Solve: (155 - 147) * 69.29", "answer": "The result of (155 - 147) * 69.29 is 554.32", "a": 155, "b": 147, "c": 69.29, "op1": "-", "op2": "*", "result": 554.32}
{"question": "Solve: (10 * 91) / 185", "answer": "The result of (10 * 91) / 185 is 4.92", "a": 10, "b": 91, "c": 185, "op1": "*", "op2": "/", "result": 4.92}
{"question": "Solve: (97 - 200) + 170", "answer": "The result of (97 - 200) + 170 is 67", "a": 97, "b": 200, "c": 170, "op1": "-", "op2": "+", "result": 67}
{"question": "Solve: (167 - 108.18) + 93", "answer": "The result of (167 - 108.18) + 93 is 151.82", "a": 167, "b": 108.18, "c": 93, "op1": "-", "op2": "+", "result": 151.82}
{"question": "Solve: (64 - 127) + 60.7", "answer": "The result of (64 - 127) + 60.7 is -2.3", "a": 64, "b": 127, "c": 60.7, "op1": "-", "op2": "+", "result": -2.3}
{"question": "Solve: (116 * 200) * 171", "answer": "The result of (116 * 200) * 171 is 3967200", "a": 116, "b": 200, "c": 171, "op1": "*", "op2": "*", "result": 3967200}
{"question": "Solve: (182.14 - 173) / 153", "answer": "The result of (182.14 - 173) / 153 is 0.06", "a": 182.14, "b": 173, "c": 153, "op1": "-", "op2": "/", "result": 0.06}
{"question": "Solve: (61 - 9) + 89", "answer": "The result of (61 - 9) + 89 is 141", "a": 61, "b": 9, "c": 89, "op1": "-", "op2": "+", "result": 141}
{"question": "Solve: (13 * 83) / 29", "answer": "The result of (13 * 83) / 29 is 37.21", "a": 13, "b": 83, "c": 29, "op1": "*", "op2": "/", "result": 37.21}
{"question": "Solve: (58 / 29) / 194", "answer": "The result of (58 / 29) / 194 is 0.01", "a": 58, "b": 29, "c": 194, "op1": "/", "op2": "/", "result": 0.01}
{"question": "Solve: (137 - 22.6) + 53.78", "answer": "The result of (137 - 22.6) + 53.78 is 168.18", "a": 137, "b": 22.6, "c": 53.78, "op1": "-", "op2": "+", "result": 168.18}
{"question": "Solve: (4 - 10.39) * 135.76", "answer": "The result of (4 - 10.39) * 135.76 is -867.51", "a": 4, "b": 10.39, "c": 135.76, "op1": "-", "op2": "*", "result": -867.51}
{"question": "Solve: (83.09 / 122) + 118", "answer": "The result of (83.09 / 122) + 118 is 118.68", "a": 83.09, "b": 122, "c": 118, "op1": "/", "op2": "+", "result": 118.68}
{"question": "Solve: (77.85 + 155) - 175", "answer": "The result of (77.85 + 155) - 175 is 57.85", "a": 77.85, "b": 155, "c": 175, "op1": "+", "op2": "-", "result": 57.85}
{"question": "Solve: (53 + 24.61) * 142", "answer": "The result of (53 + 24.61) * 142 is 11020.62", "a": 53, "b": 24.61, "c": 142, "op1": "+", "op2": "*", "result": 11020.62}
{"question": "Solve: (190 / 137) - 54", "answer": "The result of (190 / 137) - 54 is -52.61", "a": 190, "b": 137, "c": 54, "op1": "/", "op2": "-", "result": -52.61}
{"question": "Solve: (130 * 24.0) + 137", "answer": "The result of (130 * 24.0) + 137 is 3257.0", "a": 130, "b": 24.0, "c": 137, "op1": "*", "op2": "+", "result": 3257.0}
{"question": "Solve: (48.72 - 123) * 171.74", "answer": "The result of (48.72 - 123) * 171.74 is -12756.85", "a": 48.72, "b": 123, "c": 171.74, "op1": "-", "op2": "*", "result": -12756.85}
{"question": "Solve: (72.33 / 151) - 91", "answer": "The result of (72.33 / 151) - 91 is -90.52", "a": 72.33, "b": 151, "c": 91, "op1": "/", "op2": "-", "result": -90.52}
{"question": "Solve: (91.36 * 4.19) * 46", "answer": "The result of (91.36 * 4.19) * 46 is 17608.73", "a": 91.36, "b": 4.19, "c": 46, "op1": "*", "op2": "*", "result": 17608.73}
{"question": "Solve: (169.68 + 174) / 137", "answer": "The result of (169.68 + 174) / 137 is 2.51", "a": 169.68, "b": 174, "c": 137, "op1": "+", "op2": "/", "result": 2.51}
{"question": "Solve: (136.25 + 75) + 146", "answer": "The result of (136.25 + 75) + 146 is 357.25", "a": 136.25, "b": 75, "c": 146, "op1": "+", "op2": "+", "result": 357.25}
{"question": "Solve: (119 * 69) * 2", "answer": "The result of (119 * 69) * 2 is 16422", "a": 119, "b": 69, "c": 2, "op1": "*", "op2": "*", "result": 16422}
{"question": "Solve: (151 + 86.13) * 7", "answer": "The result of (151 + 86.13) * 7 is 1659.91", "a": 151, "b": 86.13, "c": 7, "op1": "+", "op2": "*", "result": 1659.91}
{"question": "Solve: (190 - 93) + 9", "answer": "The result of (190 - 93) + 9 is 106", "a": 190, "b": 93, "c": 9, "op1": "-", "op2": "+", "result": 106}
{"question": "Solve: (92.05 * 162) / 16", "answer": "The result of (92.05 * 162) / 16 is 932.01", "a": 92.05, "b": 162, "c": 16, "op1": "*", "op2": "/", "result": 932.01}
{"question": "Solve: (84 - 136) * 169", "answer": "The result of (84 - 136) * 169 is -8788", "a": 84, "b": 136, "c": 169, "op1": "-", "op2": "*", "result": -8788}
{"question": "Solve: (137 - 153) * 152", "answer": "The result of (137 - 153) * 152 is -2432", "a": 137, "b": 153, "c": 152, "op1": "-", "op2": "*", "result": -2432}
{"question": "Solve: (140 / 48) + 74.73", "answer": "The result of (140 / 48) + 74.73 is 77.65", "a": 140, "b": 48, "c": 74.73, "op1": "/", "op2": "+", "result": 77.65}
{"question": "Solve: (32 / 165.64) + 89", "answer": "The result of (32 / 165.64) + 89 is 89.19", "a": 32, "b": 165.64, "c": 89, "op1": "/", "op2": "+", "result": 89.19}
{"question": "Solve: (128 + 191) * 34", "answer": "The result of (128 + 191) * 34 is 10846", "a": 128, "b": 191, "c": 34, "op1": "+", "op2": "*", "result": 10846}
{"question": "Solve: (132.35 / 200) - 185.71", "answer": "The result of (132.35 / 200) - 185.71 is -185.05", "a": 132.35, "b": 200, "c": 185.71, "op1": "/", "op2": "-", "result": -185.05}
{"question": "Solve: (97 + 125) + 182", "answer": "The result of (97 + 125) + 182 is 404", "a": 97, "b": 125, "c": 182, "op1": "+", "op2": "+", "result": 404}
{"question": "Solve: (56 * 114) + 18.33", "answer": "The result of (56 * 114) + 18.33 is 6402.33", "a": 56, "b": 114, "c": 18.33, "op1": "*", "op2": "+", "result": 6402.33}
{"question": "Solve: (102.03 * 167.57) * 79", "answer": "The result of (102.03 * 167.57) * 79 is 1350676.2", "a": 102.03, "b": 167.57, "c": 79, "op1": "*", "op2": "*", "result": 1350676.2}
{"question": "Solve: (184.67 + 51.59) - 142", "answer": "The result of (184.67 + 51.59) - 142 is 94.26", "a": 184.67, "b": 51.59, "c": 142, "op1": "+", "op2": "-", "result": 94.26}
{"question": "Solve: (84 + 1) * 34", "answer": "The result of (84 + 1) * 34 is 2890", "a": 84, "b": 1, "c": 34, "op1": "+", "op2": "*", "result": 2890}
{"question": "Solve: (164 + 140.18) - 39", "answer": "The result of (164 + 140.18) - 39 is 265.18", "a": 164, "b": 140.18, "c": 39, "op1": "+", "op2": "-", "result": 265.18}
{"question": "Solve: (109.89 + 55) / 114", "answer": "The result of (109.89 + 55) / 114 is 1.45", "a": 109.89, "b": 55, "c": 114, "op1": "+", "op2": "/", "result": 1.45}
{"question": "Solve: (196 * 5) + 116.79", "answer": "The result of (196 * 5) + 116.79 is 1096.79", "a": 196, "b": 5, "c": 116.79, "op1": "*", "op2": "+", "result": 1096.79}
{"question": "Solve: (87 + 29) / 58", "answer": "The result of (87 + 29) / 58 is 2.0", "a": 87, "b": 29, "c": 58, "op1": "+", "op2": "/", "result": 2.0}
{"question": "Solve: (77 - 198) + 66", "answer": "The result of (77 - 198) + 66 is -55", "a": 77, "b": 198, "c": 66, "op1": "-", "op2": "+", "result": -55}
{"question": "Solve: (108 + 198.68) + 197", "answer": "The result of (108 + 198.68) + 197 is 503.68", "a": 108, "b": 198.68, "c": 197, "op1": "+", "op2": "+", "result": 503.68}
{"question": "Solve: (176 + 146) / 14", "answer": "The result of (176 + 146) / 14 is 23.0", "a": 176, "b": 146, "c": 14, "op1": "+", "op2": "/", "result": 23.0}
{"question": "Solve: (23.97 / 60) * 188", "answer": "The result of (23.97 / 60) * 188 is 75.11", "a": 23.97, "b": 60, "c": 188, "op1": "/", "op2": "*", "result": 75.11}
{"question": "Solve: (198 + 56) + 137.63", "answer": "The result of (198 + 56) + 137.63 is 391.63", "a": 198, "b": 56, "c": 137.63, "op1": "+", "op2": "+", "result": 391.63}
{"question": "Solve: (27 + 63) + 16", "answer": "The result of (27 + 63) + 16 is 106", "a": 27, "b": 63, "c": 16, "op1": "+", "op2": "+", "result": 106}
{"question": "Solve: (10.17 + 26) + 79", "answer": "The result of (10.17 + 26) + 79 is 115.17", "a": 10.17, "b": 26, "c": 79, "op1": "+", "op2": "+", "result": 115.17}
{"question": "Solve: (101.84 + 1.72) * 192", "answer": "The result of (101.84 + 1.72) * 192 is 19883.52", "a": 101.84, "b": 1.72, "c": 192, "op1": "+", "op2": "*", "result": 19883.52}
{"question": "Solve: (60.21 + 192) - 134", "answer": "The result of (60.21 + 192) - 134 is 118.21", "a": 60.21, "b": 192, "c": 134, "op1": "+", "op2": "-", "result": 118.21}
{"question": "Solve: (180 - 148.59) + 130.13", "answer": "The result of (180 - 148.59) + 130.13 is 161.54", "a": 180, "b": 148.59, "c": 130.13, "op1": "-", "op2": "+", "result": 161.54}
{"question": "Solve: (189 * 37) - 47", "answer": "The result of (189 * 37) - 47 is 6946", "a": 189, "b": 37, "c": 47, "op1": "*", "op2": "-", "result": 6946}
{"question": "Solve: (122 + 63) - 61", "answer": "The result of (122 + 63) - 61 is 124", "a": 122, "b": 63, "c": 61, "op1": "+", "op2": "-", "result": 124}
{"question": "Solve: (57 - 187) / 135", "answer": "The result of (57 - 187) / 135 is -0.96", "a": 57, "b": 187, "c": 135, "op1": "-", "op2": "/", "result": -0.96}
{"question": "Solve: (102 * 90.64) * 107", "answer": "The result of (102 * 90.64) * 107 is 989244.96", "a": 102, "b": 90.64, "c": 107, "op1": "*", "op2": "*", "result": 989244.96}
{"question": "Solve: (178.56 - 135) - 30", "answer": "The result of (178.56 - 135) - 30 is 13.56", "a": 178.56, "b": 135, "c": 30, "op1": "-", "op2": "-", "result": 13.56}
{"question": "Solve: (34 - 166) / 69.13", "answer": "The result of (34 - 166) / 69.13 is -1.91", "a": 34, "b": 166, "c": 69.13, "op1": "-", "op2": "/", "result": -1.91}
{"question": "Solve: (133 - 32) + 66", "answer": "The result of (133 - 32) + 66 is 167", "a": 133, "b": 32, "c": 66, "op1": "-", "op2": "+", "result": 167}
{"question": "Solve: (140 + 58) / 168", "answer": "The result of (140 + 58) / 168 is 1.18", "a": 140, "b": 58, "c": 168, "op1": "+", "op2": "/", "result": 1.18}
{"question": "Solve: (111 + 152) * 124", "answer": "The result of (111 + 152) * 124 is 32612", "a": 111, "b": 152, "c": 124, "op1": "+", "op2": "*", "result": 32612}
{"question": "Solve: (88.89 - 187) - 55.19", "answer": "The result of (88.89 - 187) - 55.19 is -153.3", "a": 88.89, "b": 187, "c": 55.19, "op1": "-", "op2": "-", "result": -153.3}
{"question": "Solve: (146 - 72) * 92.3", "answer": "The result of (146 - 72) * 92.3 is 6830.2", "a": 146, "b": 72, "c": 92.3, "op1": "-", "op2": "*", "result": 6830.2}
{"question": "Solve: (85 * 98) + 167", "answer": "The result of (85 * 98) + 167 is 8497", "a": 85, "b": 98, "c": 167, "op1": "*", "op2": "+", "result": 8497}
{"question": "Solve: (44.61 + 42) - 179", "answer": "The result of (44.61 + 42) - 179 is -92.39", "a": 44.61, "b": 42, "c": 179, "op1": "+", "op2": "-", "result": -92.39}
{"question": "Solve: (199 * 108) * 124.24", "answer": "The result of (199 * 108) * 124.24 is 2670166.08", "a": 199, "b": 108, "c": 124.24, "op1": "*", "op2": "*", "result": 2670166.08}
{"question": "Solve: (182.68 + 110.65) - 27", "answer": "The result of (182.68 + 110.65) - 27 is 266.33", "a": 182.68, "b": 110.65, "c": 27, "op1": "+", "op2": "-", "result": 266.33}
{"question": "Solve: (113.83 / 37) + 141", "answer": "The result of (113.83 / 37) + 141 is 144.08", "a": 113.83, "b": 37, "c": 141, "op1": "/", "op2": "+", "result": 144.08}
{"question": "Solve: (176.65 / 88) + 191", "answer": "The result of (176.65 / 88) + 191 is 193.01", "a": 176.65, "b": 88, "c": 191, "op1": "/", "op2": "+", "result": 193.01}
{"question": "Solve: (91.52 + 153) - 84", "answer": "The result of (91.52 + 153) - 84 is 160.52", "a": 91.52, "b": 153, "c": 84, "op1": "+", "op2": "-", "result": 160.52}
{"question": "Solve: (75 + 191) - 26", "answer": "The result of (75 + 191) - 26 is 240", "a": 75, "b": 191, "c": 26, "op1": "+", "op2": "-", "result": 240}
{"question": "Solve: (178 - 32) * 174", "answer": "The result of (178 - 32) * 174 is 25404", "a": 178, "b": 32, "c": 174, "op1": "-", "op2": "*", "result": 25404}
{"question": "Solve: (114 + 73.37) + 65.25", "answer": "The result of (114 + 73.37) + 65.25 is 252.62", "a": 114, "b": 73.37, "c": 65.25, "op1": "+", "op2": "+", "result": 252.62}
{"question": "Solve: (112 + 11) * 127.82", "answer": "The result of (112 + 11) * 127.82 is 15721.86", "a": 112, "b": 11, "c": 127.82, "op1": "+", "op2": "*", "result": 15721.86}
{"question": "Solve: (2 + 38) + 72", "answer": "The result of (2 + 38) + 72 is 112", "a": 2, "b": 38, "c": 72, "op1": "+", "op2": "+", "result": 112}
{"question": "Solve: (153 + 157) - 62", "answer": "The result of (153 + 157) - 62 is 248", "a": 153, "b": 157, "c": 62, "op1": "+", "op2": "-", "result": 248}
{"question": "Solve: (97 - 70.85) - 100", "answer": "The result of (97 - 70.85) - 100 is -73.85", "a": 97, "b": 70.85, "c": 100, "op1": "-", "op2": "-", "result": -73.85}
{"question": "Solve: (135 - 55.45) / 93", "answer": "The result of (135 - 55.45) / 93 is 0.86", "a": 135, "b": 55.45, "c": 93, "op1": "-", "op2": "/", "result": 0.86}
{"question": "Solve: (117 / 8) * 146", "answer": "The result of (117 / 8) * 146 is 2135.25", "a": 117, "b": 8, "c": 146, "op1": "/", "op2": "*", "result": 2135.25}
{"question": "Solve: (84 - 180) + 74", "answer": "The result of (84 - 180) + 74 is -22", "a": 84, "b": 180, "c": 74, "op1": "-", "op2": "+", "result": -22}
{"question": "Solve: (64 * 140) * 147", "answer": "The result of (64 * 140) * 147 is 1317120", "a": 64, "b": 140, "c": 147, "op1": "*", "op2": "*", "result": 1317120}
{"question": "Solve: (111 - 184) - 36.34", "answer": "The result of (111 - 184) - 36.34 is -109.34", "a": 111, "b": 184, "c": 36.34, "op1": "-", "op2": "-", "result": -109.34}
{"question": "Solve: (189 * 59) - 18", "answer": "The result of (189 * 59) - 18 is 11133", "a": 189, "b": 59, "c": 18, "op1": "*", "op2": "-", "result": 11133}
{"question": "Solve: (82 - 26.15) * 154", "answer": "The result of (82 - 26.15) * 154 is 8600.9", "a": 82, "b": 26.15, "c": 154, "op1": "-", "op2": "*", "result": 8600.9}
{"question": "Solve: (3 / 63) - 102", "answer": "The result of (3 / 63) - 102 is -101.95", "a": 3, "b": 63, "c": 102, "op1": "/", "op2": "-", "result": -101.95}
{"question": "Solve: (123.32 + 14) * 80", "answer": "The result of (123.32 + 14) * 80 is 10985.6", "a": 123.32, "b": 14, "c": 80, "op1": "+", "op2": "*", "result": 10985.6}
{"question": "Solve: (119.85 - 101) / 65", "answer": "The result of (119.85 - 101) / 65 is 0.29", "a": 119.85, "b": 101, "c": 65, "op1": "-", "op2": "/", "result": 0.29}
{"question": "Solve: (60.68 + 72) - 18.53", "answer": "The result of (60.68 + 72) - 18.53 is 114.15", "a": 60.68, "b": 72, "c": 18.53, "op1": "+", "op2": "-", "result": 114.15}
{"question": "Solve: (83 - 77.25) * 29", "answer": "The result of (83 - 77.25) * 29 is 166.75", "a": 83, "b": 77.25, "c": 29, "op1": "-", "op2": "*", "result": 166.75}
{"question": "Solve: (137 + 24) - 60", "answer": "The result of (137 + 24) - 60 is 101", "a": 137, "b": 24, "c": 60, "op1": "+", "op2": "-", "result": 101}
{"question": "Solve: (159 * 97) / 66.52", "answer": "The result of (159 * 97) / 66.52 is 231.86", "a": 159, "b": 97, "c": 66.52, "op1": "*", "op2": "/", "result": 231.86}
{"question": "Solve: (16 - 40) - 73.37", "answer": "The result of (16 - 40) - 73.37 is -97.37", "a": 16, "b": 40, "c": 73.37, "op1": "-", "op2": "-", "result": -97.37}
{"question": "Solve: (93.02 / 101) - 72", "answer": "The result of (93.02 / 101) - 72 is -71.08", "a": 93.02, "b": 101, "c": 72, "op1": "/", "op2": "-", "result": -71.08}
{"question": "Solve: (142.38 - 166) + 120", "answer": "The result of (142.38 - 166) + 120 is 96.38", "a": 142.38, "b": 166, "c": 120, "op1": "-", "op2": "+", "result": 96.38}
{"question": "Solve: (114.86 - 130.31) / 42", "answer": "The result of (114.86 - 130.31) / 42 is -0.37", "a": 114.86, "b": 130.31, "c": 42, "op1": "-", "op2": "/", "result": -0.37}
{"question": "Solve: (49.99 - 118.43) - 175.12", "answer": "The result of (49.99 - 118.43) - 175.12 is -243.56", "a": 49.99, "b": 118.43, "c": 175.12, "op1": "-", "op2": "-", "result": -243.56}
{"question": "Solve: (125 * 107.85) - 189", "answer": "The result of (125 * 107.85) - 189 is 13292.25", "a": 125, "b": 107.85, "c": 189, "op1": "*", "op2": "-", "result": 13292.25}
{"question": "Solve: (104 + 155) * 157", "answer": "The result of (104 + 155) * 157 is 40663", "a": 104, "b": 155, "c": 157, "op1": "+", "op2": "*", "result": 40663}
{"question": "Solve: (173 - 43.66) - 111", "answer": "The result of (173 - 43.66) - 111 is 18.34", "a": 173, "b": 43.66, "c": 111, "op1": "-", "op2": "-", "result": 18.34}
{"question": "Solve: (105 / 190) / 98.43", "answer": "The result of (105 / 190) / 98.43 is 0.01", "a": 105, "b": 190, "c": 98.43, "op1": "/", "op2": "/", "result": 0.01}
{"question": "Solve: (188 / 106.03) - 147", "answer": "The result of (188 / 106.03) - 147 is -145.23", "a": 188, "b": 106.03, "c": 147, "op1": "/", "op2": "-", "result": -145.23}
{"question": "Solve: (1 / 34) * 79", "answer": "The result of (1 / 34) * 79 is 2.32", "a": 1, "b": 34, "c": 79, "op1": "/", "op2": "*", "result": 2.32}
{"question": "Solve: (33 - 121) + 82.11", "answer": "The result of (33 - 121) + 82.11 is -5.89", "a": 33, "b": 121, "c": 82.11, "op1": "-", "op2": "+", "result": -5.89}
{"question": "Solve: (102 - 141) + 79", "answer": "The result of (102 - 141) + 79 is 40", "a": 102, "b": 141, "c": 79, "op1": "-", "op2": "+", "result": 40}
{"question": "Solve: (29 / 117) - 153", "answer": "The result of (29 / 117) - 153 is -152.75", "a": 29, "b": 117, "c": 153, "op1": "/", "op2": "-", "result": -152.75}
{"question": "Solve: (183.3 + 153) * 111", "answer": "The result of (183.3 + 153) * 111 is 37329.3", "a": 183.3, "b": 153, "c": 111, "op1": "+", "op2": "*", "result": 37329.3}
{"question": "Solve: (91 + 134.01) - 173", "answer": "The result of (91 + 134.01) - 173 is 52.01", "a": 91, "b": 134.01, "c": 173, "op1": "+", "op2": "-", "result": 52.01}
{"question": "Solve: (66 / 18.97) / 70.93", "answer": "The result of (66 / 18.97) / 70.93 is 0.05", "a": 66, "b": 18.97, "c": 70.93, "op1": "/", "op2": "/", "result": 0.05}
{"question": "Solve: (85.49 - 179) - 181", "answer": "The result of (85.49 - 179) - 181 is -274.51", "a": 85.49, "b": 179, "c": 181, "op1": "-", "op2": "-", "result": -274.51}
{"question": "Solve: (139 * 27) + 161", "answer": "The result of (139 * 27) + 161 is 3914", "a": 139, "b": 27, "c": 161, "op1": "*", "op2": "+", "result": 3914}
{"question": "Solve: (33 + 150.68) - 118.02", "answer": "The result of (33 + 150.68) - 118.02 is 65.66", "a": 33, "b": 150.68, "c": 118.02, "op1": "+", "op2": "-", "result": 65.66}
{"question": "Solve: (161 / 50.23) - 48", "answer": "The result of (161 / 50.23) - 48 is -44.79", "a": 161, "b": 50.23, "c": 48, "op1": "/", "op2": "-", "result": -44.79}
{"question": "Solve: (141 + 5) / 109.18", "answer": "The result of (141 + 5) / 109.18 is 1.34", "a": 141, "b": 5, "c": 109.18, "op1": "+", "op2": "/", "result": 1.34}
{"question": "Solve: (29.97 + 197) + 155", "answer": "The result of (29.97 + 197) + 155 is 381.97", "a": 29.97, "b": 197, "c": 155, "op1": "+", "op2": "+", "result": 381.97}
{"question": "Solve: (123 - 149) / 105", "answer": "The result of (123 - 149) / 105 is -0.25", "a": 123, "b": 149, "c": 105, "op1": "-", "op2": "/", "result": -0.25}
{"question": "Solve: (93 + 31) + 50", "answer": "The result of (93 + 31) + 50 is 174", "a": 93, "b": 31, "c": 50, "op1": "+", "op2": "+", "result": 174}
{"question": "Solve: (41 + 82) - 133.85", "answer": "The result of (41 + 82) - 133.85 is -10.85", "a": 41, "b": 82, "c": 133.85, "op1": "+", "op2": "-", "result": -10.85}
{"question": "Solve: (113 * 41.1) / 134", "answer": "The result of (113 * 41.1) / 134 is 34.66", "a": 113, "b": 41.1, "c": 134, "op1": "*", "op2": "/", "result": 34.66}
{"question": "Solve: (21.8 - 111.63) + 71", "answer": "The result of (21.8 - 111.63) + 71 is -18.83", "a": 21.8, "b": 111.63, "c": 71, "op1": "-", "op2": "+", "result": -18.83}
{"question": "Solve: (110 - 63) - 30", "answer": "The result of (110 - 63) - 30 is 17", "a": 110, "b": 63, "c": 30, "op1": "-", "op2": "-", "result": 17}
{"question": "Solve: (46 - 166) + 1.62", "answer": "The result of (46 - 166) + 1.62 is -118.38", "a": 46, "b": 166, "c": 1.62, "op1": "-", "op2": "+", "result": -118.38}
{"question": "Solve: (66 - 177.8) * 44", "answer": "The result of (66 - 177.8) * 44 is -4919.2", "a": 66, "b": 177.8, "c": 44, "op1": "-", "op2": "*", "result": -4919.2}
{"question": "Solve: (118 - 1) + 23", "answer": "The result of (118 - 1) + 23 is 140", "a": 118, "b": 1, "c": 23, "op1": "-", "op2": "+", "result": 140}
{"question": "Solve: (105.48 / 93) / 150", "answer": "The result of (105.48 / 93) / 150 is 0.01", "a": 105.48, "b": 93, "c": 150, "op1": "/", "op2": "/", "result": 0.01}
{"question": "Solve: (52 - 82) * 46", "answer": "The result of (52 - 82) * 46 is -1380", "a": 52, "b": 82, "c": 46, "op1": "-", "op2": "*", "result": -1380}
{"question": "Solve: (22 / 52) - 2.09", "answer": "The result of (22 / 52) - 2.09 is -1.67", "a": 22, "b": 52, "c": 2.09, "op1": "/", "op2": "-", "result": -1.67}
{"question": "Solve: (104 + 191) * 173", "answer": "The result of (104 + 191) * 173 is 51035", "a": 104, "b": 191, "c": 173, "op1": "+", "op2": "*", "result": 51035}
{"question": "Solve: (181 + 81.29) - 21", "answer": "The result of (181 + 81.29) - 21 is 241.29", "a": 181, "b": 81.29, "c": 21, "op1": "+", "op2": "-", "result": 241.29}
{"question": "Solve: (48 + 49) / 93.03", "answer": "The result of (48 + 49) / 93.03 is 1.04", "a": 48, "b": 49, "c": 93.03, "op1": "+", "op2": "/", "result": 1.04}
{"question": "Solve: (47 / 50) + 153", "answer": "The result of (47 / 50) + 153 is 153.94", "a": 47, "b": 50, "c": 153, "op1": "/", "op2": "+", "result": 153.94}
{"question": "Solve: (189.73 + 71) + 76", "answer": "The result of (189.73 + 71) + 76 is 336.73", "a": 189.73, "b": 71, "c": 76, "op1": "+", "op2": "+", "result": 336.73}
{"question": "Solve: (108.21 - 90) - 139", "answer": "The result of (108.21 - 90) - 139 is -120.79", "a": 108.21, "b": 90, "c": 139, "op1": "-", "op2": "-", "result": -120.79}
{"question": "Solve: (59 * 14) + 80", "answer": "The result of (59 * 14) + 80 is 906", "a": 59, "b": 14, "c": 80, "op1": "*", "op2": "+", "result": 906}
{"question": "Solve: (100 - 119) + 68", "answer": "The result of (100 - 119) + 68 is 49", "a": 100, "b": 119, "c": 68, "op1": "-", "op2": "+", "result": 49}
{"question": "Solve: (104.42 + 91) / 177.33", "answer": "The result of (104.42 + 91) / 177.33 is 1.1", "a": 104.42, "b": 91, "c": 177.33, "op1": "+", "op2": "/", "result": 1.1}
{"question": "Solve: (47.67 - 163.6) + 44", "answer": "The result of (47.67 - 163.6) + 44 is -71.93", "a": 47.67, "b": 163.6, "c": 44, "op1": "-", "op2": "+", "result": -71.93}
{"question": "Solve: (84 - 178) * 50.52", "answer": "The result of (84 - 178) * 50.52 is -4748.88", "a": 84, "b": 178, "c": 50.52, "op1": "-", "op2": "*", "result": -4748.88}
{"question": "Solve: (54 / 4) * 142", "answer": "The result of (54 / 4) * 142 is 1917.0", "a": 54, "b": 4, "c": 142, "op1": "/", "op2": "*", "result": 1917.0}
{"question": "Solve: (185 + 190) + 8", "answer": "The result of (185 + 190) + 8 is 383", "a": 185, "b": 190, "c": 8, "op1": "+", "op2": "+", "result": 383}
{"question": "Solve: (42.13 - 154.87) + 178", "answer": "The result of (42.13 - 154.87) + 178 is 65.26", "a": 42.13, "b": 154.87, "c": 178, "op1": "-", "op2": "+", "result": 65.26}
{"question": "Solve: (69.72 + 138) * 178", "answer": "The result of (69.72 + 138) * 178 is 36974.16", "a": 69.72, "b": 138, "c": 178, "op1": "+", "op2": "*", "result": 36974.16}
{"question": "Solve: (127 * 161.49) - 141.64", "answer": "The result of (127 * 161.49) - 141.64 is 20367.59", "a": 127, "b": 161.49, "c": 141.64, "op1": "*", "op2": "-", "result": 20367.59}
{"question": "Solve: (182 + 8) - 137.19", "answer": "The result of (182 + 8) - 137.19 is 52.81", "a": 182, "b": 8, "c": 137.19, "op1": "+", "op2": "-", "result": 52.81}
{"question": "Solve: (187 * 199) - 101", "answer": "The result of (187 * 199) - 101 is 37112", "a": 187, "b": 199, "c": 101, "op1": "*", "op2": "-", "result": 37112}
{"question": "Solve: (51 / 70.98) + 60.83", "answer": "The result of (51 / 70.98) + 60.83 is 61.55", "a": 51, "b": 70.98, "c": 60.83, "op1": "/", "op2": "+", "result": 61.55}
{"question": "Solve: (66 * 2) - 30.22", "answer": "The result of (66 * 2) - 30.22 is 101.78", "a": 66, "b": 2, "c": 30.22, "op1": "*", "op2": "-", "result": 101.78}
{"question": "Solve: (136 - 31.46) + 200", "answer": "The result of (136 - 31.46) + 200 is 304.54", "a": 136, "b": 31.46, "c": 200, "op1": "-", "op2": "+", "result": 304.54}
{"question": "Solve: (140.09 + 27) - 171", "answer": "The result of (140.09 + 27) - 171 is -3.91", "a": 140.09, "b": 27, "c": 171, "op1": "+", "op2": "-", "result": -3.91}
{"question": "Solve: (80.54 / 65) + 59", "answer": "The result of (80.54 / 65) + 59 is 60.24", "a": 80.54, "b": 65, "c": 59, "op1": "/", "op2": "+", "result": 60.24}
{"question": "Solve: (94 - 20.65) / 183.76", "answer": "The result of (94 - 20.65) / 183.76 is 0.4", "a": 94, "b": 20.65, "c": 183.76, "op1": "-", "op2": "/", "result": 0.4}
{"question": "Solve: (26.02 - 79) * 177", "answer": "The result of (26.02 - 79) * 177 is -9377.46", "a": 26.02, "b": 79, "c": 177, "op1": "-", "op2": "*", "result": -9377.46}
{"question": "Solve: (27 * 109) * 107.75", "answer": "The result of (27 * 109) * 107.75 is 317108.25", "a": 27, "b": 109, "c": 107.75, "op1": "*", "op2": "*", "result": 317108.25}
{"question": "Solve: (112 * 147) - 95.45", "answer": "The result of (112 * 147) - 95.45 is 16368.55", "a": 112, "b": 147, "c": 95.45, "op1": "*", "op2": "-", "result": 16368.55}
{"question": "Solve: (77 + 57) * 47.72", "answer": "The result of (77 + 57) * 47.72 is 6394.48", "a": 77, "b": 57, "c": 47.72, "op1": "+", "op2": "*", "result": 6394.48}
{"question": "Solve: (52 - 72) - 29", "answer": "The result of (52 - 72) - 29 is -49", "a": 52, "b": 72, "c": 29, "op1": "-", "op2": "-", "result": -49}
{"question": "Solve: (36.99 - 170.9) / 96", "answer": "The result of (36.99 - 170.9) / 96 is -1.39", "a": 36.99, "b": 170.9, "c": 96, "op1": "-", "op2": "/", "result": -1.39}
{"question": "Solve: (152 + 83) / 159.31", "answer": "The result of (152 + 83) / 159.31 is 1.48", "a": 152, "b": 83, "c": 159.31, "op1": "+", "op2": "/", "result": 1.48}
{"question": "Solve: (190 / 53) + 112.57", "answer": "The result of (190 / 53) + 112.57 is 116.15", "a": 190, "b": 53, "c": 112.57, "op1": "/", "op2": "+", "result": 116.15}
{"question": "Solve: (65 + 192) + 94.09", "answer": "The result of (65 + 192) + 94.09 is 351.09", "a": 65, "b": 192, "c": 94.09, "op1": "+", "op2": "+", "result": 351.09}
{"question": "Solve: (31.23 * 197) + 59", "answer": "The result of (31.23 * 197) + 59 is 6211.31", "a": 31.23, "b": 197, "c": 59, "op1": "*", "op2": "+", "result": 6211.31}
{"question": "Solve: (64 + 182) + 117", "answer": "The result of (64 + 182) + 117 is 363", "a": 64, "b": 182, "c": 117, "op1": "+", "op2": "+", "result": 363}
{"question": "Solve: (32 + 47) - 67", "answer": "The result of (32 + 47) - 67 is 12", "a": 32, "b": 47, "c": 67, "op1": "+", "op2": "-", "result": 12}
{"question": "Solve: (99 * 26.93) * 143.38", "answer": "The result of (99 * 26.93) * 143.38 is 382261.12", "a": 99, "b": 26.93, "c": 143.38, "op1": "*", "op2": "*", "result": 382261.12}
{"question": "Solve: (193.99 / 190.74) + 124.86", "answer": "The result of (193.99 / 190.74) + 124.86 is 125.88", "a": 193.99, "b": 190.74, "c": 124.86, "op1": "/", "op2": "+", "result": 125.88}
{"question": "Solve: (195 / 72) - 12", "answer": "The result of (195 / 72) - 12 is -9.29", "a": 195, "b": 72, "c": 12, "op1": "/", "op2": "-", "result": -9.29}
{"question": "Solve: (1 + 101.17) / 151", "answer": "The result of (1 + 101.17) / 151 is 0.68", "a": 1, "b": 101.17, "c": 151, "op1": "+", "op2": "/", "result": 0.68}
{"question": "Solve: (117.44 - 50.34) + 125", "answer": "The result of (117.44 - 50.34) + 125 is 192.1", "a": 117.44, "b": 50.34, "c": 125, "op1": "-", "op2": "+", "result": 192.1}
{"question": "Solve: (122 * 94.12) + 162", "answer": "The result of (122 * 94.12) + 162 is 11644.64", "a": 122, "b": 94.12, "c": 162, "op1": "*", "op2": "+", "result": 11644.64}
{"question": "Solve: (46 - 85.91) * 135.28", "answer": "The result of (46 - 85.91) * 135.28 is -5399.02", "a": 46, "b": 85.91, "c": 135.28, "op1": "-", "op2": "*", "result": -5399.02}
{"question": "Solve: (35 / 93) + 90.54", "answer": "The result of (35 / 93) + 90.54 is 90.92", "a": 35, "b": 93, "c": 90.54, "op1": "/", "op2": "+", "result": 90.92}
{"question": "Solve: (78.53 / 68) + 52", "answer": "The result of (78.53 / 68) + 52 is 53.15", "a": 78.53, "b": 68, "c": 52, "op1": "/", "op2": "+", "result": 53.15}
{"question": "Solve: (28 * 47) - 118", "answer": "The result of (28 * 47) - 118 is 1198", "a": 28, "b": 47, "c": 118, "op1": "*", "op2": "-", "result": 1198}
{"question": "Solve: (186 / 66) * 15", "answer": "The result of (186 / 66) * 15 is 42.27", "a": 186, "b": 66, "c": 15, "op1": "/", "op2": "*", "result": 42.27}
{"question": "Solve: (114.06 - 64) * 39", "answer": "The result of (114.06 - 64) * 39 is 1952.34", "a": 114.06, "b": 64, "c": 39, "op1": "-", "op2": "*", "result": 1952.34}
{"question": "Solve: (166 * 36) + 3", "answer": "The result of (166 * 36) + 3 is 5979", "a": 166, "b": 36, "c": 3, "op1": "*", "op2": "+", "result": 5979}
{"question": "Solve: (62 + 142) - 56", "answer": "The result of (62 + 142) - 56 is 148", "a": 62, "b": 142, "c": 56, "op1": "+", "op2": "-", "result": 148}
{"question": "Solve: (146.31 * 123) * 56", "answer": "The result of (146.31 * 123) * 56 is 1007783.28", "a": 146.31, "b": 123, "c": 56, "op1": "*", "op2": "*", "result": 1007783.28}
{"question": "Solve: (87 / 181.54) - 24.35", "answer": "The result of (87 / 181.54) - 24.35 is -23.87", "a": 87, "b": 181.54, "c": 24.35, "op1": "/", "op2": "-", "result": -23.87}
{"question": "Solve: (50.37 + 107.17) + 192", "answer": "The result of (50.37 + 107.17) + 192 is 349.54", "a": 50.37, "b": 107.17, "c": 192, "op1": "+", "op2": "+", "result": 349.54}
{"question": "Solve: (74.13 - 2) * 66", "answer": "The result of (74.13 - 2) * 66 is 4760.58", "a": 74.13, "b": 2, "c": 66, "op1": "-", "op2": "*", "result": 4760.58}
{"question": "Solve: (120 + 5) * 68", "answer": "The result of (120 + 5) * 68 is 8500", "a": 120, "b": 5, "c": 68, "op1": "+", "op2": "*", "result": 8500}
{"question": "Solve: (41 * 96) - 146.62", "answer": "The result of (41 * 96) - 146.62 is 3789.38", "a": 41, "b": 96, "c": 146.62, "op1": "*", "op2": "-", "result": 3789.38}
{"question": "Solve: (82 / 125) / 17.37", "answer": "The result of (82 / 125) / 17.37 is 0.04", "a": 82, "b": 125, "c": 17.37, "op1": "/", "op2": "/", "result": 0.04}
{"question": "Solve: (31 - 156.34) - 40", "answer": "The result of (31 - 156.34) - 40 is -165.34", "a": 31, "b": 156.34, "c": 40, "op1": "-", "op2": "-", "result": -165.34}
{"question": "Solve: (153 * 67) * 71", "answer": "The result of (153 * 67) * 71 is 727821", "a": 153, "b": 67, "c": 71, "op1": "*", "op2": "*", "result": 727821}
{"question": "Solve: (55 - 136) - 116", "answer": "The result of (55 - 136) - 116 is -197", "a": 55, "b": 136, "c": 116, "op1": "-", "op2": "-", "result": -197}
{"question": "Solve: (89 + 62) * 65.72", "answer": "The result of (89 + 62) * 65.72 is 9923.72", "a": 89, "b": 62, "c": 65.72, "op1": "+", "op2": "*", "result": 9923.72}
{"question": "Solve: (147 - 133) + 76", "answer": "The result of (147 - 133) + 76 is 90", "a": 147, "b": 133, "c": 76, "op1": "-", "op2": "+", "result": 90}
{"question": "Solve: (167 + 68.76) / 6.51", "answer": "The result of (167 + 68.76) / 6.51 is 36.22", "a": 167, "b": 68.76, "c": 6.51, "op1": "+", "op2": "/", "result": 36.22}
{"question": "Solve: (32.97 * 117) + 122", "answer": "The result of (32.97 * 117) + 122 is 3979.49", "a": 32.97, "b": 117, "c": 122, "op1": "*", "op2": "+", "result": 3979.49}
{"question": "Solve: (67 - 84.33) - 26", "answer": "The result of (67 - 84.33) - 26 is -43.33", "a": 67, "b": 84.33, "c": 26, "op1": "-", "op2": "-", "result": -43.33}
{"question": "Solve: (67 + 176) / 152", "answer": "The result of (67 + 176) / 152 is 1.6", "a": 67, "b": 176, "c": 152, "op1": "+", "op2": "/", "result": 1.6}
{"question": "Solve: (77.37 + 142.49) / 5", "answer": "The result of (77.37 + 142.49) / 5 is 43.97", "a": 77.37, "b": 142.49, "c": 5, "op1": "+", "op2": "/", "result": 43.97}
{"question": "Solve: (61 + 121) + 34", "answer": "The result of (61 + 121) + 34 is 216", "a": 61, "b": 121, "c": 34, "op1": "+", "op2": "+", "result": 216}
{"question": "Solve: (71.07 - 13) + 17", "answer": "The result of (71.07 - 13) + 17 is 75.07", "a": 71.07, "b": 13, "c": 17, "op1": "-", "op2": "+", "result": 75.07}
{"question": "Solve: (13 + 6) * 121", "answer": "The result of (13 + 6) * 121 is 2299", "a": 13, "b": 6, "c": 121, "op1": "+", "op2": "*", "result": 2299}
{"question": "Solve: (15 * 175.55) * 3.57", "answer": "The result of (15 * 175.55) * 3.57 is 9400.7", "a": 15, "b": 175.55, "c": 3.57, "op1": "*", "op2": "*", "result": 9400.7}
{"question": "Solve: (125 * 130) + 120.74", "answer": "The result of (125 * 130) + 120.74 is 16370.74", "a": 125, "b": 130, "c": 120.74, "op1": "*", "op2": "+", "result": 16370.74}
{"question": "Solve: (64 * 117.26) - 147.24", "answer": "The result of (64 * 117.26) - 147.24 is 7357.4", "a": 64, "b": 117.26, "c": 147.24, "op1": "*", "op2": "-", "result": 7357.4}
{"question": "Solve: (187 - 169.62) - 187", "answer": "The result of (187 - 169.62) - 187 is -169.62", "a": 187, "b": 169.62, "c": 187, "op1": "-", "op2": "-", "result": -169.62}
{"question": "Solve: (71 + 173.8) * 7", "answer": "The result of (71 + 173.8) * 7 is 1713.6", "a": 71, "b": 173.8, "c": 7, "op1": "+", "op2": "*", "result": 1713.6}
{"question": "Solve: (13 + 179) - 142.87", "answer": "The result of (13 + 179) - 142.87 is 49.13", "a": 13, "b": 179, "c": 142.87, "op1": "+", "op2": "-", "result": 49.13}
{"question": "Solve: (143 + 141.44) / 103", "answer": "The result of (143 + 141.44) / 103 is 2.76", "a": 143, "b": 141.44, "c": 103, "op1": "+", "op2": "/", "result": 2.76}
{"question": "Solve: (18 - 168.87) / 38.62", "answer": "The result of (18 - 168.87) / 38.62 is -3.91", "a": 18, "b": 168.87, "c": 38.62, "op1": "-", "op2": "/", "result": -3.91}
{"question": "Solve: (197 - 32) - 136", "answer": "The result of (197 - 32) - 136 is 29", "a": 197, "b": 32, "c": 136, "op1": "-", "op2": "-", "result": 29}
{"question": "Solve: (126.0 / 161) / 11", "answer": "The result of (126.0 / 161) / 11 is 0.07", "a": 126.0, "b": 161, "c": 11, "op1": "/", "op2": "/", "result": 0.07}
{"question": "Solve: (191 + 103.99) * 165", "answer": "The result of (191 + 103.99) * 165 is 48673.35", "a": 191, "b": 103.99, "c": 165, "op1": "+", "op2": "*", "result": 48673.35}
{"question": "Solve: (162 + 128) - 79", "answer": "The result of (162 + 128) - 79 is 211", "a": 162, "b": 128, "c": 79, "op1": "+", "op2": "-", "result": 211}
{"question": "Solve: (73 * 49) * 159", "answer": "The result of (73 * 49) * 159 is 568743", "a": 73, "b": 49, "c": 159, "op1": "*", "op2": "*", "result": 568743}
{"question": "Solve: (102 + 77) - 68.02", "answer": "The result of (102 + 77) - 68.02 is 110.98", "a": 102, "b": 77, "c": 68.02, "op1": "+", "op2": "-", "result": 110.98}
{"question": "Solve: (95 + 95) - 156", "answer": "The result of (95 + 95) - 156 is 34", "a": 95, "b": 95, "c": 156, "op1": "+", "op2": "-", "result": 34}
{"question": "Solve: (136.92 + 148) - 70", "answer": "The result of (136.92 + 148) - 70 is 214.92", "a": 136.92, "b": 148, "c": 70, "op1": "+", "op2": "-", "result": 214.92}
{"question": "Solve: (58 / 154) - 184.84", "answer": "The result of (58 / 154) - 184.84 is -184.46", "a": 58, "b": 154, "c": 184.84, "op1": "/", "op2": "-", "result": -184.46}
{"question": "Solve: (114 - 59.6) * 55", "answer": "The result of (114 - 59.6) * 55 is 2992.0", "a": 114, "b": 59.6, "c": 55, "op1": "-", "op2": "*", "result": 2992.0}
{"question": "Solve: (162 * 41) + 51", "answer": "The result of (162 * 41) + 51 is 6693", "a": 162, "b": 41, "c": 51, "op1": "*", "op2": "+", "result": 6693}
{"question": "Solve: (3.43 + 181) + 106", "answer": "The result of (3.43 + 181) + 106 is 290.43", "a": 3.43, "b": 181, "c": 106, "op1": "+", "op2": "+", "result": 290.43}
{"question": "Solve: (58.71 / 166) * 64", "answer": "The result of (58.71 / 166) * 64 is 22.64", "a": 58.71, "b": 166, "c": 64, "op1": "/", "op2": "*", "result": 22.64}
{"question": "Solve: (149 + 7.29) / 44", "answer": "The result of (149 + 7.29) / 44 is 3.55", "a": 149, "b": 7.29, "c": 44, "op1": "+", "op2": "/", "result": 3.55}
{"question": "Solve: (140.58 + 76) / 142", "answer": "The result of (140.58 + 76) / 142 is 1.53", "a": 140.58, "b": 76, "c": 142, "op1": "+", "op2": "/", "result": 1.53}
{"question": "Solve: (113 + 105.29) / 43", "answer": "The result of (113 + 105.29) / 43 is 5.08", "a": 113, "b": 105.29, "c": 43, "op1": "+", "op2": "/", "result": 5.08}
{"question": "Solve: (114 * 163) - 1", "answer": "The result of (114 * 163) - 1 is 18581", "a": 114, "b": 163, "c": 1, "op1": "*", "op2": "-", "result": 18581}
{"question": "Solve: (106.47 * 197) - 142", "answer": "The result of (106.47 * 197) - 142 is 20832.59", "a": 106.47, "b": 197, "c": 142, "op1": "*", "op2": "-", "result": 20832.59}
{"question": "Solve: (89.03 + 163.38) / 151", "answer": "The result of (89.03 + 163.38) / 151 is 1.67", "a": 89.03, "b": 163.38, "c": 151, "op1": "+", "op2": "/", "result": 1.67}
{"question": "Solve: (37 - 176) - 139", "answer": "The result of (37 - 176) - 139 is -278", "a": 37, "b": 176, "c": 139, "op1": "-", "op2": "-", "result": -278}
{"question": "Solve: (32 - 13) + 143.62", "answer": "The result of (32 - 13) + 143.62 is 162.62", "a": 32, "b": 13, "c": 143.62, "op1": "-", "op2": "+", "result": 162.62}
{"question": "Solve: (52.17 / 152) - 21.97", "answer": "The result of (52.17 / 152) - 21.97 is -21.63", "a": 52.17, "b": 152, "c": 21.97, "op1": "/", "op2": "-", "result": -21.63}
{"question": "Solve: (117 / 149.02) / 172.21", "answer": "The result of (117 / 149.02) / 172.21 is 0.0", "a": 117, "b": 149.02, "c": 172.21, "op1": "/", "op2": "/", "result": 0.0}
{"question": "Solve: (135 * 73.74) * 177", "answer": "The result of (135 * 73.74) * 177 is 1762017.3", "a": 135, "b": 73.74, "c": 177, "op1": "*", "op2": "*", "result": 1762017.3}
{"question": "Solve: (5.14 + 159) * 18", "answer": "The result of (5.14 + 159) * 18 is 2954.52", "a": 5.14, "b": 159, "c": 18, "op1": "+", "op2": "*", "result": 2954.52}
{"question": "Solve: (23 - 176) - 42", "answer": "The result of (23 - 176) - 42 is -195", "a": 23, "b": 176, "c": 42, "op1": "-", "op2": "-", "result": -195}
{"question": "Solve: (153 * 178) + 5", "answer": "The result of (153 * 178) + 5 is 27239", "a": 153, "b": 178, "c": 5, "op1": "*", "op2": "+", "result": 27239}
{"question": "Solve: (66 / 148) / 30.6", "answer": "The result of (66 / 148) / 30.6 is 0.01", "a": 66, "b": 148, "c": 30.6, "op1": "/", "op2": "/", "result": 0.01}
{"question": "Solve: (50 + 148) - 72.68", "answer": "The result of (50 + 148) - 72.68 is 125.32", "a": 50, "b": 148, "c": 72.68, "op1": "+", "op2": "-", "result": 125.32}
{"question": "Solve: (196.6 - 33.4) - 24.78", "answer": "The result of (196.6 - 33.4) - 24.78 is 138.42", "a": 196.6, "b": 33.4, "c": 24.78, "op1": "-", "op2": "-", "result": 138.42}
{"question": "Solve: (64.04 + 114.33) + 32", "answer": "The result of (64.04 + 114.33) + 32 is 210.37", "a": 64.04, "b": 114.33, "c": 32, "op1": "+", "op2": "+", "result": 210.37}
{"question": "Solve: (128 + 167) + 24", "answer": "The result of (128 + 167) + 24 is 319", "a": 128, "b": 167, "c": 24, "op1": "+", "op2": "+", "result": 319}
{"question": "Solve: (105 / 129) + 189.39", "answer": "The result of (105 / 129) + 189.39 is 190.2", "a": 105, "b": 129, "c": 189.39, "op1": "/", "op2": "+", "result": 190.2}
{"question": "Solve: (21 * 190) - 83.43", "answer": "The result of (21 * 190) - 83.43 is 3906.57", "a": 21, "b": 190, "c": 83.43, "op1": "*", "op2": "-", "result": 3906.57}
{"question": "Solve: (170 + 133) / 11", "answer": "The result of (170 + 133) / 11 is 27.55", "a": 170, "b": 133, "c": 11, "op1": "+", "op2": "/", "result": 27.55}
{"question": "Solve: (160 + 80) + 91", "answer": "The result of (160 + 80) + 91 is 331", "a": 160, "b": 80, "c": 91, "op1": "+", "op2": "+", "result": 331}
{"question": "Solve: (67.36 / 25.53) + 170", "answer": "The result of (67.36 / 25.53) + 170 is 172.64", "a": 67.36, "b": 25.53, "c": 170, "op1": "/", "op2": "+", "result": 172.64}
{"question": "Solve: (13 + 111.45) / 191", "answer": "The result of (13 + 111.45) / 191 is 0.65", "a": 13, "b": 111.45, "c": 191, "op1": "+", "op2": "/", "result": 0.65}
{"question": "Solve: (192.91 - 40) + 130", "answer": "The result of (192.91 - 40) + 130 is 282.91", "a": 192.91, "b": 40, "c": 130, "op1": "-", "op2": "+", "result": 282.91}
{"question": "Solve: (164.25 + 170) * 102.0", "answer": "The result of (164.25 + 170) * 102.0 is 34093.5", "a": 164.25, "b": 170, "c": 102.0, "op1": "+", "op2": "*", "result": 34093.5}
{"question": "Solve: (195 / 12.85) / 107", "answer": "The result of (195 / 12.85) / 107 is 0.14", "a": 195, "b": 12.85, "c": 107, "op1": "/", "op2": "/", "result": 0.14}
{"question": "Solve: (41 + 125.15) + 184", "answer": "The result of (41 + 125.15) + 184 is 350.15", "a": 41, "b": 125.15, "c": 184, "op1": "+", "op2": "+", "result": 350.15}
{"question": "Solve: (126 + 5.95) + 145.49", "answer": "The result of (126 + 5.95) + 145.49 is 277.44", "a": 126, "b": 5.95, "c": 145.49, "op1": "+", "op2": "+", "result": 277.44}
{"question": "Solve: (14 + 92) - 48", "answer": "The result of (14 + 92) - 48 is 58", "a": 14, "b": 92, "c": 48, "op1": "+", "op2": "-", "result": 58}
{"question": "Solve: (145 * 23) * 174.61", "answer": "The result of (145 * 23) * 174.61 is 582324.35", "a": 145, "b": 23, "c": 174.61, "op1": "*", "op2": "*", "result": 582324.35}
{"question": "Solve: (100.84 * 8) - 96.12", "answer": "The result of (100.84 * 8) - 96.12 is 710.6", "a": 100.84, "b": 8, "c": 96.12, "op1": "*", "op2": "-", "result": 710.6}
{"question": "Solve: (145 + 98) + 110.06", "answer": "The result of (145 + 98) + 110.06 is 353.06", "a": 145, "b": 98, "c": 110.06, "op1": "+", "op2": "+", "result": 353.06}
{"question": "Solve: (163 + 105.77) + 139", "answer": "The result of (163 + 105.77) + 139 is 407.77", "a": 163, "b": 105.77, "c": 139, "op1": "+", "op2": "+", "result": 407.77}
{"question": "Solve: (28 - 3.77) / 75.51", "answer": "The result of (28 - 3.77) / 75.51 is 0.32", "a": 28, "b": 3.77, "c": 75.51, "op1": "-", "op2": "/", "result": 0.32}
{"question": "Solve: (69.36 * 100) * 63", "answer": "The result of (69.36 * 100) * 63 is 436968.0", "a": 69.36, "b": 100, "c": 63, "op1": "*", "op2": "*", "result": 436968.0}
{"question": "Solve: (188.42 * 34) - 178.19", "answer": "The result of (188.42 * 34) - 178.19 is 6228.09", "a": 188.42, "b": 34, "c": 178.19, "op1": "*", "op2": "-", "result": 6228.09}
{"question": "Solve: (47 + 72.49) / 58", "answer": "The result of (47 + 72.49) / 58 is 2.06", "a": 47, "b": 72.49, "c": 58, "op1": "+", "op2": "/", "result": 2.06}
{"question": "Solve: (145 - 134) - 74", "answer": "The result of (145 - 134) - 74 is -63", "a": 145, "b": 134, "c": 74, "op1": "-", "op2": "-", "result": -63}
{"question": "Solve: (5 / 180.61) - 148.32", "answer": "The result of (5 / 180.61) - 148.32 is -148.29", "a": 5, "b": 180.61, "c": 148.32, "op1": "/", "op2": "-", "result": -148.29}
{"question": "Solve: (158 + 133.62) / 145", "answer": "The result of (158 + 133.62) / 145 is 2.01", "a": 158, "b": 133.62, "c": 145, "op1": "+", "op2": "/", "result": 2.01}
{"question": "Solve: (1 / 16.63) + 145", "answer": "The result of (1 / 16.63) + 145 is 145.06", "a": 1, "b": 16.63, "c": 145, "op1": "/", "op2": "+", "result": 145.06}
{"question": "Solve: (199 - 76) + 110.02", "answer": "The result of (199 - 76) + 110.02 is 233.02", "a": 199, "b": 76, "c": 110.02, "op1": "-", "op2": "+", "result": 233.02}
{"question": "Solve: (95 - 160.18) - 194", "answer": "The result of (95 - 160.18) - 194 is -259.18", "a": 95, "b": 160.18, "c": 194, "op1": "-", "op2": "-", "result": -259.18}
{"question": "Solve: (16 * 46) * 127", "answer": "The result of (16 * 46) * 127 is 93472", "a": 16, "b": 46, "c": 127, "op1": "*", "op2": "*", "result": 93472}
{"question": "Solve: (8 - 181) + 57", "answer": "The result of (8 - 181) + 57 is -116", "a": 8, "b": 181, "c": 57, "op1": "-", "op2": "+", "result": -116}
{"question": "Solve: (140.78 / 78) + 155", "answer": "The result of (140.78 / 78) + 155 is 156.8", "a": 140.78, "b": 78, "c": 155, "op1": "/", "op2": "+", "result": 156.8}
{"question": "Solve: (132 + 34) - 119", "answer": "The result of (132 + 34) - 119 is 47", "a": 132, "b": 34, "c": 119, "op1": "+", "op2": "-", "result": 47}
{"question": "Solve: (175 + 163) + 44", "answer": "The result of (175 + 163) + 44 is 382", "a": 175, "b": 163, "c": 44, "op1": "+", "op2": "+", "result": 382}
{"question": "Solve: (177 / 47.51) - 172", "answer": "The result of (177 / 47.51) - 172 is -168.27", "a": 177, "b": 47.51, "c": 172, "op1": "/", "op2": "-", "result": -168.27}
{"question": "Solve: (171.31 + 195) - 88", "answer": "The result of (171.31 + 195) - 88 is 278.31", "a": 171.31, "b": 195, "c": 88, "op1": "+", "op2": "-", "result": 278.31}
{"question": "Solve: (9 - 74) + 188", "answer": "The result of (9 - 74) + 188 is 123", "a": 9, "b": 74, "c": 188, "op1": "-", "op2": "+", "result": 123}
{"question": "Solve: (84 / 41) - 40.29", "answer": "The result of (84 / 41) - 40.29 is -38.24", "a": 84, "b": 41, "c": 40.29, "op1": "/", "op2": "-", "result": -38.24}
{"question": "Solve: (163 + 140.28) / 112.6", "answer": "The result of (163 + 140.28) / 112.6 is 2.69", "a": 163, "b": 140.28, "c": 112.6, "op1": "+", "op2": "/", "result": 2.69}
{"question": "Solve: (42.65 - 5) / 149", "answer": "The result of (42.65 - 5) / 149 is 0.25", "a": 42.65, "b": 5, "c": 149, "op1": "-", "op2": "/", "result": 0.25}
{"question": "Solve: (3 + 125) - 158", "answer": "The result of (3 + 125) - 158 is -30", "a": 3, "b": 125, "c": 158, "op1": "+", "op2": "-", "result": -30}
{"question": "Solve: (163 - 36) / 58", "answer": "The result of (163 - 36) / 58 is 2.19", "a": 163, "b": 36, "c": 58, "op1": "-", "op2": "/", "result": 2.19}
{"question": "Solve: (198 / 2) + 118", "answer": "The result of (198 / 2) + 118 is 217.0", "a": 198, "b": 2, "c": 118, "op1": "/", "op2": "+", "result": 217.0}
{"question": "Solve: (57 + 180) - 4.91", "answer": "The result of (57 + 180) - 4.91 is 232.09", "a": 57, "b": 180, "c": 4.91, "op1": "+", "op2": "-", "result": 232.09}
{"question": "Solve: (150 + 80) + 112", "answer": "The result of (150 + 80) + 112 is 342", "a": 150, "b": 80, "c": 112, "op1": "+", "op2": "+", "result": 342}
{"question": "Solve: (198.69 * 161) - 191", "answer": "The result of (198.69 * 161) - 191 is 31798.09", "a": 198.69, "b": 161, "c": 191, "op1": "*", "op2": "-", "result": 31798.09}
{"question": "Solve: (106 + 191) - 170", "answer": "The result of (106 + 191) - 170 is 127", "a": 106, "b": 191, "c": 170, "op1": "+", "op2": "-", "result": 127}
{"question": "Solve: (182 - 100) * 110", "answer": "The result of (182 - 100) * 110 is 9020", "a": 182, "b": 100, "c": 110, "op1": "-", "op2": "*", "result": 9020}
{"question": "Solve: (85.89 - 166) * 24", "answer": "The result of (85.89 - 166) * 24 is -1922.64", "a": 85.89, "b": 166, "c": 24, "op1": "-", "op2": "*", "result": -1922.64}
{"question": "Solve: (99.96 * 130) * 13.98", "answer": "The result of (99.96 * 130) * 13.98 is 181667.3", "a": 99.96, "b": 130, "c": 13.98, "op1": "*", "op2": "*", "result": 181667.3}
{"question": "Solve: (48.27 + 131) * 96", "answer": "The result of (48.27 + 131) * 96 is 17209.92", "a": 48.27, "b": 131, "c": 96, "op1": "+", "op2": "*", "result": 17209.92}
{"question": "Solve: (181 - 98.09) + 107", "answer": "The result of (181 - 98.09) + 107 is 189.91", "a": 181, "b": 98.09, "c": 107, "op1": "-", "op2": "+", "result": 189.91}
{"question": "Solve: (92.74 / 46) - 191", "answer": "The result of (92.74 / 46) - 191 is -188.98", "a": 92.74, "b": 46, "c": 191, "op1": "/", "op2": "-", "result": -188.98}
{"question": "Solve: (133.05 / 23) - 135", "answer": "The result of (133.05 / 23) - 135 is -129.22", "a": 133.05, "b": 23, "c": 135, "op1": "/", "op2": "-", "result": -129.22}
{"question": "Solve: (133 * 67) - 133.44", "answer": "The result of (133 * 67) - 133.44 is 8777.56", "a": 133, "b": 67, "c": 133.44, "op1": "*", "op2": "-", "result": 8777.56}
{"question": "Solve: (120.37 / 10) * 15", "answer": "The result of (120.37 / 10) * 15 is 180.56", "a": 120.37, "b": 10, "c": 15, "op1": "/", "op2": "*", "result": 180.56}
{"question": "Solve: (26 - 109.1) * 191", "answer": "The result of (26 - 109.1) * 191 is -15872.1", "a": 26, "b": 109.1, "c": 191, "op1": "-", "op2": "*", "result": -15872.1}
{"question": "Solve: (8 + 164.74) * 163", "answer": "The result of (8 + 164.74) * 163 is 28156.62", "a": 8, "b": 164.74, "c": 163, "op1": "+", "op2": "*", "result": 28156.62}
{"question": "Solve: (143 * 51) + 27", "answer": "The result of (143 * 51) + 27 is 7320", "a": 143, "b": 51, "c": 27, "op1": "*", "op2": "+", "result": 7320}
{"question": "Solve: (45 - 92) + 6.0", "answer": "The result of (45 - 92) + 6.0 is -41.0", "a": 45, "b": 92, "c": 6.0, "op1": "-", "op2": "+", "result": -41.0}
{"question": "Solve: (43 - 1) / 8", "answer": "The result of (43 - 1) / 8 is 5.25", "a": 43, "b": 1, "c": 8, "op1": "-", "op2": "/", "result": 5.25}
{"question": "Solve: (104 + 199) - 49", "answer": "The result of (104 + 199) - 49 is 254", "a": 104, "b": 199, "c": 49, "op1": "+", "op2": "-", "result": 254}
{"question": "Solve: (59 - 122) / 127", "answer": "The result of (59 - 122) / 127 is -0.5", "a": 59, "b": 122, "c": 127, "op1": "-", "op2": "/", "result": -0.5}
{"question": "Solve: (67 * 3) * 88", "answer": "The result of (67 * 3) * 88 is 17688", "a": 67, "b": 3, "c": 88, "op1": "*", "op2": "*", "result": 17688}
{"question": "Solve: (180.0 + 137) * 28", "answer": "The result of (180.0 + 137) * 28 is 8876.0", "a": 180.0, "b": 137, "c": 28, "op1": "+", "op2": "*", "result": 8876.0}
{"question": "Solve: (133 * 96.8) - 171", "answer": "The result of (133 * 96.8) - 171 is 12703.4", "a": 133, "b": 96.8, "c": 171, "op1": "*", "op2": "-", "result": 12703.4}
{"question": "Solve: (60.36 / 12) + 137", "answer": "The result of (60.36 / 12) + 137 is 142.03", "a": 60.36, "b": 12, "c": 137, "op1": "/", "op2": "+", "result": 142.03}
{"question": "Solve: (53.05 * 14) + 132.71", "answer": "The result of (53.05 * 14) + 132.71 is 875.41", "a": 53.05, "b": 14, "c": 132.71, "op1": "*", "op2": "+", "result": 875.41}
{"question": "Solve: (194 / 37) + 185.87", "answer": "The result of (194 / 37) + 185.87 is 191.11", "a": 194, "b": 37, "c": 185.87, "op1": "/", "op2": "+", "result": 191.11}
{"question": "Solve: (88 * 50) + 34", "answer": "The result of (88 * 50) + 34 is 4434", "a": 88, "b": 50, "c": 34, "op1": "*", "op2": "+", "result": 4434}
{"question": "Solve: (5 - 54.85) + 126", "answer": "The result of (5 - 54.85) + 126 is 76.15", "a": 5, "b": 54.85, "c": 126, "op1": "-", "op2": "+", "result": 76.15}
{"question": "Solve: (53 * 120) - 93", "answer": "The result of (53 * 120) - 93 is 6267", "a": 53, "b": 120, "c": 93, "op1": "*", "op2": "-", "result": 6267}
{"question": "Solve: (65 - 99.84) + 58.22", "answer": "The result of (65 - 99.84) + 58.22 is 23.38", "a": 65, "b": 99.84, "c": 58.22, "op1": "-", "op2": "+", "result": 23.38}
{"question": "Solve: (42.72 - 66) - 193", "answer": "The result of (42.72 - 66) - 193 is -216.28", "a": 42.72, "b": 66, "c": 193, "op1": "-", "op2": "-", "result": -216.28}
{"question": "Solve: (184 - 10) * 66.78", "answer": "The result of (184 - 10) * 66.78 is 11619.72", "a": 184, "b": 10, "c": 66.78, "op1": "-", "op2": "*", "result": 11619.72}
{"question": "Solve: (68 + 105) * 169", "answer": "The result of (68 + 105) * 169 is 29237", "a": 68, "b": 105, "c": 169, "op1": "+", "op2": "*", "result": 29237}
{"question": "Solve: (174.7 * 65) + 118", "answer": "The result of (174.7 * 65) + 118 is 11473.5", "a": 174.7, "b": 65, "c": 118, "op1": "*", "op2": "+", "result": 11473.5}
{"question": "Solve: (72 + 56) - 71.21", "answer": "The result of (72 + 56) - 71.21 is 56.79", "a": 72, "b": 56, "c": 71.21, "op1": "+", "op2": "-", "result": 56.79}
{"question": "Solve: (186 + 71) - 62", "answer": "The result of (186 + 71) - 62 is 195", "a": 186, "b": 71, "c": 62, "op1": "+", "op2": "-", "result": 195}
{"question": "Solve: (23 + 140.04) - 34", "answer": "The result of (23 + 140.04) - 34 is 129.04", "a": 23, "b": 140.04, "c": 34, "op1": "+", "op2": "-", "result": 129.04}
{"question": "Solve: (18.97 + 83) - 67", "answer": "The result of (18.97 + 83) - 67 is 34.97", "a": 18.97, "b": 83, "c": 67, "op1": "+", "op2": "-", "result": 34.97}
{"question": "Solve: (194.3 + 124) - 44", "answer": "The result of (194.3 + 124) - 44 is 274.3", "a": 194.3, "b": 124, "c": 44, "op1": "+", "op2": "-", "result": 274.3}
{"question": "Solve: (56.23 * 5) / 142", "answer": "The result of (56.23 * 5) / 142 is 1.98", "a": 56.23, "b": 5, "c": 142, "op1": "*", "op2": "/", "result": 1.98}
{"question": "Solve: (124 + 166.08) * 20", "answer": "The result of (124 + 166.08) * 20 is 5801.6", "a": 124, "b": 166.08, "c": 20, "op1": "+", "op2": "*", "result": 5801.6}
{"question": "Solve: (50.58 - 29.08) + 30.67", "answer": "The result of (50.58 - 29.08) + 30.67 is 52.17", "a": 50.58, "b": 29.08, "c": 30.67, "op1": "-", "op2": "+", "result": 52.17}
{"question": "Solve: (47 * 26) - 137", "answer": "The result of (47 * 26) - 137 is 1085", "a": 47, "b": 26, "c": 137, "op1": "*", "op2": "-", "result": 1085}
{"question": "Solve: (116 / 13.67) / 127", "answer": "The result of (116 / 13.67) / 127 is 0.07", "a": 116, "b": 13.67, "c": 127, "op1": "/", "op2": "/", "result": 0.07}
{"question": "Solve: (8 + 35) + 46.65", "answer": "The result of (8 + 35) + 46.65 is 89.65", "a": 8, "b": 35, "c": 46.65, "op1": "+", "op2": "+", "result": 89.65}
{"question": "Solve: (22 * 134) / 103.71", "answer": "The result of (22 * 134) / 103.71 is 28.43", "a": 22, "b": 134, "c": 103.71, "op1": "*", "op2": "/", "result": 28.43}
{"question": "Solve: (51 + 36) - 28.9", "answer": "The result of (51 + 36) - 28.9 is 58.1", "a": 51, "b": 36, "c": 28.9, "op1": "+", "op2": "-", "result": 58.1}
{"question": "Solve: (114 * 111) - 26", "answer": "The result of (114 * 111) - 26 is 12628", "a": 114, "b": 111, "c": 26, "op1": "*", "op2": "-", "result": 12628}
{"question": "Solve: (51 * 38.5) - 156", "answer": "The result of (51 * 38.5) - 156 is 1807.5", "a": 51, "b": 38.5, "c": 156, "op1": "*", "op2": "-", "result": 1807.5}
{"question": "Solve: (112 * 117) - 64.61", "answer": "The result of (112 * 117) - 64.61 is 13039.39", "a": 112, "b": 117, "c": 64.61, "op1": "*", "op2": "-", "result": 13039.39}
{"question": "Solve: (104 - 113.75) + 143.66", "answer": "The result of (104 - 113.75) + 143.66 is 133.91", "a": 104, "b": 113.75, "c": 143.66, "op1": "-", "op2": "+", "result": 133.91}
{"question": "Solve: (43 + 117.06) / 87", "answer": "The result of (43 + 117.06) / 87 is 1.84", "a": 43, "b": 117.06, "c": 87, "op1": "+", "op2": "/", "result": 1.84}
{"question": "Solve: (135 + 186) / 60", "answer": "The result of (135 + 186) / 60 is 5.35", "a": 135, "b": 186, "c": 60, "op1": "+", "op2": "/", "result": 5.35}
{"question": "Solve: (86 - 161) * 36", "answer": "The result of (86 - 161) * 36 is -2700", "a": 86, "b": 161, "c": 36, "op1": "-", "op2": "*", "result": -2700}
{"question": "Solve: (58 + 64) * 59", "answer": "The result of (58 + 64) * 59 is 7198", "a": 58, "b": 64, "c": 59, "op1": "+", "op2": "*", "result": 7198}
{"question": "Solve: (59.57 + 98) - 59", "answer": "The result of (59.57 + 98) - 59 is 98.57", "a": 59.57, "b": 98, "c": 59, "op1": "+", "op2": "-", "result": 98.57}
{"question": "Solve: (184 * 181) - 81.11", "answer": "The result of (184 * 181) - 81.11 is 33222.89", "a": 184, "b": 181, "c": 81.11, "op1": "*", "op2": "-", "result": 33222.89}
{"question": "Solve: (59 + 194) * 133.32", "answer": "The result of (59 + 194) * 133.32 is 33729.96", "a": 59, "b": 194, "c": 133.32, "op1": "+", "op2": "*", "result": 33729.96}
{"question": "Solve: (38 * 76.5) + 111.8", "answer": "The result of (38 * 76.5) + 111.8 is 3018.8", "a": 38, "b": 76.5, "c": 111.8, "op1": "*", "op2": "+", "result": 3018.8}
{"question": "Solve: (73.51 - 12) / 24.96", "answer": "The result of (73.51 - 12) / 24.96 is 2.46", "a": 73.51, "b": 12, "c": 24.96, "op1": "-", "op2": "/", "result": 2.46}
{"question": "Solve: (12.55 - 1.81) + 177", "answer": "The result of (12.55 - 1.81) + 177 is 187.74", "a": 12.55, "b": 1.81, "c": 177, "op1": "-", "op2": "+", "result": 187.74}
{"question": "Solve: (63 * 100.05) * 165", "answer": "The result of (63 * 100.05) * 165 is 1040019.75", "a": 63, "b": 100.05, "c": 165, "op1": "*", "op2": "*", "result": 1040019.75}
{"question": "Solve: (82 * 188.66) / 136", "answer": "The result of (82 * 188.66) / 136 is 113.75", "a": 82, "b": 188.66, "c": 136, "op1": "*", "op2": "/", "result": 113.75}
{"question": "Solve: (8.21 * 42) / 21", "answer": "The result of (8.21 * 42) / 21 is 16.42", "a": 8.21, "b": 42, "c": 21, "op1": "*", "op2": "/", "result": 16.42}
{"question": "Solve: (97.59 - 78) * 132", "answer": "The result of (97.59 - 78) * 132 is 2585.88", "a": 97.59, "b": 78, "c": 132, "op1": "-", "op2": "*", "result": 2585.88}
{"question": "Solve: (115 - 86) / 6", "answer": "The result of (115 - 86) / 6 is 4.83", "a": 115, "b": 86, "c": 6, "op1": "-", "op2": "/", "result": 4.83}
{"question": "Solve: (1.07 * 9) - 77", "answer": "The result of (1.07 * 9) - 77 is -67.37", "a": 1.07, "b": 9, "c": 77, "op1": "*", "op2": "-", "result": -67.37}
{"question": "Solve: (173 * 159.62) / 142", "answer": "The result of (173 * 159.62) / 142 is 194.47", "a": 173, "b": 159.62, "c": 142, "op1": "*", "op2": "/", "result": 194.47}
{"question": "Solve: (196.67 + 5) * 33", "answer": "The result of (196.67 + 5) * 33 is 6655.11", "a": 196.67, "b": 5, "c": 33, "op1": "+", "op2": "*", "result": 6655.11}
{"question": "Solve: (61.07 + 102) / 147", "answer": "The result of (61.07 + 102) / 147 is 1.11", "a": 61.07, "b": 102, "c": 147, "op1": "+", "op2": "/", "result": 1.11}
{"question": "Solve: (85 - 191) - 114", "answer": "The result of (85 - 191) - 114 is -220", "a": 85, "b": 191, "c": 114, "op1": "-", "op2": "-", "result": -220}
{"question": "Solve: (111.72 + 134.95) + 177", "answer": "The result of (111.72 + 134.95) + 177 is 423.67", "a": 111.72, "b": 134.95, "c": 177, "op1": "+", "op2": "+", "result": 423.67}
{"question": "Solve: (104.95 - 90.67) / 151.46", "answer": "The result of (104.95 - 90.67) / 151.46 is 0.09", "a": 104.95, "b": 90.67, "c": 151.46, "op1": "-", "op2": "/", "result": 0.09}
{"question": "Solve: (196 * 68) + 4", "answer": "The result of (196 * 68) + 4 is 13332", "a": 196, "b": 68, "c": 4, "op1": "*", "op2": "+", "result": 13332}
{"question": "Solve: (123 + 128) - 37.09", "answer": "The result of (123 + 128) - 37.09 is 213.91", "a": 123, "b": 128, "c": 37.09, "op1": "+", "op2": "-", "result": 213.91}
{"question": "Solve: (163 * 11) - 110.49", "answer": "The result of (163 * 11) - 110.49 is 1682.51", "a": 163, "b": 11, "c": 110.49, "op1": "*", "op2": "-", "result": 1682.51}
{"question": "Solve: (67 * 194) + 9", "answer": "The result of (67 * 194) + 9 is 13007", "a": 67, "b": 194, "c": 9, "op1": "*", "op2": "+", "result": 13007}
{"question": "Solve: (86.02 + 110.92) - 90", "answer": "The result of (86.02 + 110.92) - 90 is 106.94", "a": 86.02, "b": 110.92, "c": 90, "op1": "+", "op2": "-", "result": 106.94}
{"question": "Solve: (44 - 182) - 124", "answer": "The result of (44 - 182) - 124 is -262", "a": 44, "b": 182, "c": 124, "op1": "-", "op2": "-", "result": -262}
{"question": "Solve: (191.15 + 114) + 150.91", "answer": "The result of (191.15 + 114) + 150.91 is 456.06", "a": 191.15, "b": 114, "c": 150.91, "op1": "+", "op2": "+", "result": 456.06}
{"question": "Solve: (163 - 90) + 144.3", "answer": "The result of (163 - 90) + 144.3 is 217.3", "a": 163, "b": 90, "c": 144.3, "op1": "-", "op2": "+", "result": 217.3}
{"question": "Solve: (123.62 + 162.12) / 119", "answer": "The result of (123.62 + 162.12) / 119 is 2.4", "a": 123.62, "b": 162.12, "c": 119, "op1": "+", "op2": "/", "result": 2.4}
{"question": "Solve: (121 + 104) - 85", "answer": "The result of (121 + 104) - 85 is 140", "a": 121, "b": 104, "c": 85, "op1": "+", "op2": "-", "result": 140}
{"question": "Solve: (95 - 88.18) * 75", "answer": "The result of (95 - 88.18) * 75 is 511.5", "a": 95, "b": 88.18, "c": 75, "op1": "-", "op2": "*", "result": 511.5}
{"question": "Solve: (73 - 55.74) - 142.31", "answer": "The result of (73 - 55.74) - 142.31 is -125.05", "a": 73, "b": 55.74, "c": 142.31, "op1": "-", "op2": "-", "result": -125.05}
{"question": "Solve: (142.59 - 139) - 67.59", "answer": "The result of (142.59 - 139) - 67.59 is -64.0", "a": 142.59, "b": 139, "c": 67.59, "op1": "-", "op2": "-", "result": -64.0}
{"question": "Solve: (56 - 89) - 1.8", "answer": "The result of (56 - 89) - 1.8 is -34.8", "a": 56, "b": 89, "c": 1.8, "op1": "-", "op2": "-", "result": -34.8}
{"question": "Solve: (162.18 * 149) - 114.8", "answer": "The result of (162.18 * 149) - 114.8 is 24050.02", "a": 162.18, "b": 149, "c": 114.8, "op1": "*", "op2": "-", "result": 24050.02}
{"question": "Solve: (196.21 + 12.93) + 22", "answer": "The result of (196.21 + 12.93) + 22 is 231.14", "a": 196.21, "b": 12.93, "c": 22, "op1": "+", "op2": "+", "result": 231.14}
{"question": "Solve: (169 - 161) + 44", "answer": "The result of (169 - 161) + 44 is 52", "a": 169, "b": 161, "c": 44, "op1": "-", "op2": "+", "result": 52}
{"question": "Solve: (141 + 126) + 115", "answer": "The result of (141 + 126) + 115 is 382", "a": 141, "b": 126, "c": 115, "op1": "+", "op2": "+", "result": 382}
{"question": "Solve: (127 + 184) / 133.11", "answer": "The result of (127 + 184) / 133.11 is 2.34", "a": 127, "b": 184, "c": 133.11, "op1": "+", "op2": "/", "result": 2.34}
{"question": "Solve: (101 + 123.72) * 125", "answer": "The result of (101 + 123.72) * 125 is 28090.0", "a": 101, "b": 123.72, "c": 125, "op1": "+", "op2": "*", "result": 28090.0}
{"question": "Solve: (51 / 135.38) * 15", "answer": "The result of (51 / 135.38) * 15 is 5.65", "a": 51, "b": 135.38, "c": 15, "op1": "/", "op2": "*", "result": 5.65}
{"question": "Solve: (98 + 46.74) + 4.64", "answer": "The result of (98 + 46.74) + 4.64 is 149.38", "a": 98, "b": 46.74, "c": 4.64, "op1": "+", "op2": "+", "result": 149.38}
{"question": "Solve: (121 - 113.72) - 83", "answer": "The result of (121 - 113.72) - 83 is -75.72", "a": 121, "b": 113.72, "c": 83, "op1": "-", "op2": "-", "result": -75.72}
{"question": "Solve: (139 - 66) * 22", "answer": "The result of (139 - 66) * 22 is 1606", "a": 139, "b": 66, "c": 22, "op1": "-", "op2": "*", "result": 1606}
{"question": "Solve: (117 + 36.2) / 89", "answer": "The result of (117 + 36.2) / 89 is 1.72", "a": 117, "b": 36.2, "c": 89, "op1": "+", "op2": "/", "result": 1.72}
{"question": "Solve: (51 - 124.18) / 145", "answer": "The result of (51 - 124.18) / 145 is -0.5", "a": 51, "b": 124.18, "c": 145, "op1": "-", "op2": "/", "result": -0.5}
{"question": "Solve: (93 - 141) - 21.45", "answer": "The result of (93 - 141) - 21.45 is -69.45", "a": 93, "b": 141, "c": 21.45, "op1": "-", "op2": "-", "result": -69.45}
{"question": "Solve: (196 * 3.58) * 77", "answer": "The result of (196 * 3.58) * 77 is 54029.36", "a": 196, "b": 3.58, "c": 77, "op1": "*", "op2": "*", "result": 54029.36}
{"question": "Solve: (138 + 9) - 176.67", "answer": "The result of (138 + 9) - 176.67 is -29.67", "a": 138, "b": 9, "c": 176.67, "op1": "+", "op2": "-", "result": -29.67}
{"question": "Solve: (4.67 + 86) + 37", "answer": "The result of (4.67 + 86) + 37 is 127.67", "a": 4.67, "b": 86, "c": 37, "op1": "+", "op2": "+", "result": 127.67}
{"question": "Solve: (137 + 159.97) * 102", "answer": "The result of (137 + 159.97) * 102 is 30290.94", "a": 137, "b": 159.97, "c": 102, "op1": "+", "op2": "*", "result": 30290.94}
{"question": "Solve: (182 / 114) + 178.16", "answer": "The result of (182 / 114) + 178.16 is 179.76", "a": 182, "b": 114, "c": 178.16, "op1": "/", "op2": "+", "result": 179.76}
{"question": "Solve: (59 + 70) - 176", "answer": "The result of (59 + 70) - 176 is -47", "a": 59, "b": 70, "c": 176, "op1": "+", "op2": "-", "result": -47}
{"question": "Solve: (197 + 86) + 189.07", "answer": "The result of (197 + 86) + 189.07 is 472.07", "a": 197, "b": 86, "c": 189.07, "op1": "+", "op2": "+", "result": 472.07}
{"question": "Solve: (168 * 72) * 58", "answer": "The result of (168 * 72) * 58 is 701568", "a": 168, "b": 72, "c": 58, "op1": "*", "op2": "*", "result": 701568}
{"question": "Solve: (10 - 143) / 26.13", "answer": "The result of (10 - 143) / 26.13 is -5.09", "a": 10, "b": 143, "c": 26.13, "op1": "-", "op2": "/", "result": -5.09}
{"question": "Solve: (74 * 83) - 59.41", "answer": "The result of (74 * 83) - 59.41 is 6082.59", "a": 74, "b": 83, "c": 59.41, "op1": "*", "op2": "-", "result": 6082.59}
{"question": "Solve: (109.41 - 69) - 109", "answer": "The result of (109.41 - 69) - 109 is -68.59", "a": 109.41, "b": 69, "c": 109, "op1": "-", "op2": "-", "result": -68.59}
{"question": "Solve: (20 - 62.35) - 108", "answer": "The result of (20 - 62.35) - 108 is -150.35", "a": 20, "b": 62.35, "c": 108, "op1": "-", "op2": "-", "result": -150.35}
{"question": "Solve: (24 / 17.19) + 79", "answer": "The result of (24 / 17.19) + 79 is 80.4", "a": 24, "b": 17.19, "c": 79, "op1": "/", "op2": "+", "result": 80.4}
{"question": "Solve: (113 / 66.23) / 77", "answer": "The result of (113 / 66.23) / 77 is 0.02", "a": 113, "b": 66.23, "c": 77, "op1": "/", "op2": "/", "result": 0.02}
{"question": "Solve: (199 - 81) / 170.21", "answer": "The result of (199 - 81) / 170.21 is 0.69", "a": 199, "b": 81, "c": 170.21, "op1": "-", "op2": "/", "result": 0.69}
{"question": "Solve: (99 * 109) - 122.85", "answer": "The result of (99 * 109) - 122.85 is 10668.15", "a": 99, "b": 109, "c": 122.85, "op1": "*", "op2": "-", "result": 10668.15}
{"question": "Solve: (4 - 32) * 83", "answer": "The result of (4 - 32) * 83 is -2324", "a": 4, "b": 32, "c": 83, "op1": "-", "op2": "*", "result": -2324}
{"question": "Solve: (114.43 / 157) + 149", "answer": "The result of (114.43 / 157) + 149 is 149.73", "a": 114.43, "b": 157, "c": 149, "op1": "/", "op2": "+", "result": 149.73}
{"question": "Solve: (197 * 75) - 117.47", "answer": "The result of (197 * 75) - 117.47 is 14657.53", "a": 197, "b": 75, "c": 117.47, "op1": "*", "op2": "-", "result": 14657.53}
{"question": "Solve: (187 + 186) + 30", "answer": "The result of (187 + 186) + 30 is 403", "a": 187, "b": 186, "c": 30, "op1": "+", "op2": "+", "result": 403}
{"question": "Solve: (196.36 * 76) + 45", "answer": "The result of (196.36 * 76) + 45 is 14968.36", "a": 196.36, "b": 76, "c": 45, "op1": "*", "op2": "+", "result": 14968.36}
{"question": "Solve: (2 - 66.85) / 58.7", "answer": "The result of (2 - 66.85) / 58.7 is -1.1", "a": 2, "b": 66.85, "c": 58.7, "op1": "-", "op2": "/", "result": -1.1}
{"question": "Solve: (183.15 - 151) + 133.88", "answer": "The result of (183.15 - 151) + 133.88 is 166.03", "a": 183.15, "b": 151, "c": 133.88, "op1": "-", "op2": "+", "result": 166.03}
{"question": "Solve: (196 + 80.97) + 108", "answer": "The result of (196 + 80.97) + 108 is 384.97", "a": 196, "b": 80.97, "c": 108, "op1": "+", "op2": "+", "result": 384.97}
{"question": "Solve: (152.29 + 61) + 151", "answer": "The result of (152.29 + 61) + 151 is 364.29", "a": 152.29, "b": 61, "c": 151, "op1": "+", "op2": "+", "result": 364.29}
{"question": "Solve: (143 - 41) - 10.98", "answer": "The result of (143 - 41) - 10.98 is 91.02", "a": 143, "b": 41, "c": 10.98, "op1": "-", "op2": "-", "result": 91.02}
{"question": "Solve: (63.96 + 109) / 57.58", "answer": "The result of (63.96 + 109) / 57.58 is 3.0", "a": 63.96, "b": 109, "c": 57.58, "op1": "+", "op2": "/", "result": 3.0}
{"question": "Solve: (22 / 24.15) * 169.24", "answer": "The result of (22 / 24.15) * 169.24 is 154.17", "a": 22, "b": 24.15, "c": 169.24, "op1": "/", "op2": "*", "result": 154.17}
{"question": "Solve: (55.33 + 57) + 64", "answer": "The result of (55.33 + 57) + 64 is 176.33", "a": 55.33, "b": 57, "c": 64, "op1": "+", "op2": "+", "result": 176.33}
{"question": "Solve: (5 - 169) / 168.16", "answer": "The result of (5 - 169) / 168.16 is -0.98", "a": 5, "b": 169, "c": 168.16, "op1": "-", "op2": "/", "result": -0.98}
{"question": "Solve: (162 * 47) * 127", "answer": "The result of (162 * 47) * 127 is 966978", "a": 162, "b": 47, "c": 127, "op1": "*", "op2": "*", "result": 966978}
{"question": "Solve: (93 - 102.29) + 100", "answer": "The result of (93 - 102.29) + 100 is 90.71", "a": 93, "b": 102.29, "c": 100, "op1": "-", "op2": "+", "result": 90.71}
{"question": "Solve: (57 - 167.71) - 133", "answer": "The result of (57 - 167.71) - 133 is -243.71", "a": 57, "b": 167.71, "c": 133, "op1": "-", "op2": "-", "result": -243.71}
{"question": "Solve: (47 * 194) / 199.95", "answer": "The result of (47 * 194) / 199.95 is 45.6", "a": 47, "b": 194, "c": 199.95, "op1": "*", "op2": "/", "result": 45.6}
{"question": "Solve: (151 * 86) + 167", "answer": "The result of (151 * 86) + 167 is 13153", "a": 151, "b": 86, "c": 167, "op1": "*", "op2": "+", "result": 13153}
{"question": "Solve: (11 * 132) * 19", "answer": "The result of (11 * 132) * 19 is 27588", "a": 11, "b": 132, "c": 19, "op1": "*", "op2": "*", "result": 27588}
{"question": "Solve: (157 * 81) / 109", "answer": "The result of (157 * 81) / 109 is 116.67", "a": 157, "b": 81, "c": 109, "op1": "*", "op2": "/", "result": 116.67}
{"question": "Solve: (40 + 20) + 129", "answer": "The result of (40 + 20) + 129 is 189", "a": 40, "b": 20, "c": 129, "op1": "+", "op2": "+", "result": 189}
{"question": "Solve: (99 + 45) / 6", "answer": "The result of (99 + 45) / 6 is 24.0", "a": 99, "b": 45, "c": 6, "op1": "+", "op2": "/", "result": 24.0}
{"question": "Solve: (49.31 - 104) - 46", "answer": "The result of (49.31 - 104) - 46 is -100.69", "a": 49.31, "b": 104, "c": 46, "op1": "-", "op2": "-", "result": -100.69}
{"question": "Solve: (171.1 + 53.66) - 93", "answer": "The result of (171.1 + 53.66) - 93 is 131.76", "a": 171.1, "b": 53.66, "c": 93, "op1": "+", "op2": "-", "result": 131.76}
{"question": "Solve: (96.11 + 115) * 17", "answer": "The result of (96.11 + 115) * 17 is 3588.87", "a": 96.11, "b": 115, "c": 17, "op1": "+", "op2": "*", "result": 3588.87}
{"question": "Solve: (170 + 54.21) / 168", "answer": "The result of (170 + 54.21) / 168 is 1.33", "a": 170, "b": 54.21, "c": 168, "op1": "+", "op2": "/", "result": 1.33}
{"question": "Solve: (194 * 50) / 192.46", "answer": "The result of (194 * 50) / 192.46 is 50.4", "a": 194, "b": 50, "c": 192.46, "op1": "*", "op2": "/", "result": 50.4}
{"question": "Solve: (2 + 161.06) - 61", "answer": "The result of (2 + 161.06) - 61 is 102.06", "a": 2, "b": 161.06, "c": 61, "op1": "+", "op2": "-", "result": 102.06}
{"question": "Solve: (176.07 + 177) * 179", "answer": "The result of (176.07 + 177) * 179 is 63199.53", "a": 176.07, "b": 177, "c": 179, "op1": "+", "op2": "*", "result": 63199.53}
{"question": "Solve: (48 * 148.61) - 172", "answer": "The result of (48 * 148.61) - 172 is 6961.28", "a": 48, "b": 148.61, "c": 172, "op1": "*", "op2": "-", "result": 6961.28}
{"question": "Solve: (10 + 96) + 90.75", "answer": "The result of (10 + 96) + 90.75 is 196.75", "a": 10, "b": 96, "c": 90.75, "op1": "+", "op2": "+", "result": 196.75}
{"question": "Solve: (158 + 90) * 164", "answer": "The result of (158 + 90) * 164 is 40672", "a": 158, "b": 90, "c": 164, "op1": "+", "op2": "*", "result": 40672}
{"question": "Solve: (190 - 115) * 138.43", "answer": "The result of (190 - 115) * 138.43 is 10382.25", "a": 190, "b": 115, "c": 138.43, "op1": "-", "op2": "*", "result": 10382.25}
{"question": "Solve: (39.62 + 12) * 13", "answer": "The result of (39.62 + 12) * 13 is 671.06", "a": 39.62, "b": 12, "c": 13, "op1": "+", "op2": "*", "result": 671.06}
{"question": "Solve: (143 + 47) - 142.38", "answer": "The result of (143 + 47) - 142.38 is 47.62", "a": 143, "b": 47, "c": 142.38, "op1": "+", "op2": "-", "result": 47.62}
{"question": "Solve: (172 + 35) + 155", "answer": "The result of (172 + 35) + 155 is 362", "a": 172, "b": 35, "c": 155, "op1": "+", "op2": "+", "result": 362}
{"question": "Solve: (162 / 177) * 155", "answer": "The result of (162 / 177) * 155 is 141.86", "a": 162, "b": 177, "c": 155, "op1": "/", "op2": "*", "result": 141.86}
{"question": "Solve: (22 + 168) - 66", "answer": "The result of (22 + 168) - 66 is 124", "a": 22, "b": 168, "c": 66, "op1": "+", "op2": "-", "result": 124}
{"question": "Solve: (6 * 150.19) - 28.64", "answer": "The result of (6 * 150.19) - 28.64 is 872.5", "a": 6, "b": 150.19, "c": 28.64, "op1": "*", "op2": "-", "result": 872.5}
{"question": "Solve: (199.94 * 166.69) * 115", "answer": "The result of (199.94 * 166.69) * 115 is 3832719.84", "a": 199.94, "b": 166.69, "c": 115, "op1": "*", "op2": "*", "result": 3832719.84}
{"question": "Solve: (121.63 - 142.92) - 196.58", "answer": "The result of (121.63 - 142.92) - 196.58 is -217.87", "a": 121.63, "b": 142.92, "c": 196.58, "op1": "-", "op2": "-", "result": -217.87}
{"question": "Solve: (105.0 + 137.53) * 106", "answer": "The result of (105.0 + 137.53) * 106 is 25708.18", "a": 105.0, "b": 137.53, "c": 106, "op1": "+", "op2": "*", "result": 25708.18}
{"question": "Solve: (167 + 75) + 59", "answer": "The result of (167 + 75) + 59 is 301", "a": 167, "b": 75, "c": 59, "op1": "+", "op2": "+", "result": 301}
{"question": "Solve: (78 - 170) - 19.8", "answer": "The result of (78 - 170) - 19.8 is -111.8", "a": 78, "b": 170, "c": 19.8, "op1": "-", "op2": "-", "result": -111.8}
{"question": "Solve: (170.51 * 9) - 177", "answer": "The result of (170.51 * 9) - 177 is 1357.59", "a": 170.51, "b": 9, "c": 177, "op1": "*", "op2": "-", "result": 1357.59}
{"question": "Solve: (162.93 + 90.56) / 62", "answer": "The result of (162.93 + 90.56) / 62 is 4.09", "a": 162.93, "b": 90.56, "c": 62, "op1": "+", "op2": "/", "result": 4.09}
{"question": "Solve: (118 + 161) - 146", "answer": "The result of (118 + 161) - 146 is 133", "a": 118, "b": 161, "c": 146, "op1": "+", "op2": "-", "result": 133}
{"question": "Solve: (135.42 + 149.7) * 2", "answer": "The result of (135.42 + 149.7) * 2 is 570.24", "a": 135.42, "b": 149.7, "c": 2, "op1": "+", "op2": "*", "result": 570.24}
{"question": "Solve: (58 + 199) * 174", "answer": "The result of (58 + 199) * 174 is 44718", "a": 58, "b": 199, "c": 174, "op1": "+", "op2": "*", "result": 44718}
{"question": "Solve: (187 - 192) + 115.2", "answer": "The result of (187 - 192) + 115.2 is 110.2", "a": 187, "b": 192, "c": 115.2, "op1": "-", "op2": "+", "result": 110.2}
{"question": "Solve: (50 * 7) * 154", "answer": "The result of (50 * 7) * 154 is 53900", "a": 50, "b": 7, "c": 154, "op1": "*", "op2": "*", "result": 53900}
{"question": "Solve: (60 + 108.75) * 98", "answer": "The result of (60 + 108.75) * 98 is 16537.5", "a": 60, "b": 108.75, "c": 98, "op1": "+", "op2": "*", "result": 16537.5}
{"question": "Solve: (179 * 136) + 165", "answer": "The result of (179 * 136) + 165 is 24509", "a": 179, "b": 136, "c": 165, "op1": "*", "op2": "+", "result": 24509}
{"question": "Solve: (134 * 158.23) - 159", "answer": "The result of (134 * 158.23) - 159 is 21043.82", "a": 134, "b": 158.23, "c": 159, "op1": "*", "op2": "-", "result": 21043.82}
{"question": "Solve: (165 - 17) * 186", "answer": "The result of (165 - 17) * 186 is 27528", "a": 165, "b": 17, "c": 186, "op1": "-", "op2": "*", "result": 27528}
{"question": "Solve: (181 + 93) + 193.33", "answer": "The result of (181 + 93) + 193.33 is 467.33", "a": 181, "b": 93, "c": 193.33, "op1": "+", "op2": "+", "result": 467.33}
{"question": "Solve: (50 - 198.02) - 89", "answer": "The result of (50 - 198.02) - 89 is -237.02", "a": 50, "b": 198.02, "c": 89, "op1": "-", "op2": "-", "result": -237.02}
{"question": "Solve: (29.25 / 12) - 196.94", "answer": "The result of (29.25 / 12) - 196.94 is -194.5", "a": 29.25, "b": 12, "c": 196.94, "op1": "/", "op2": "-", "result": -194.5}
{"question": "Solve: (79 + 19) / 97", "answer": "The result of (79 + 19) / 97 is 1.01", "a": 79, "b": 19, "c": 97, "op1": "+", "op2": "/", "result": 1.01}
{"question": "Solve: (6 + 82) * 28.32", "answer": "The result of (6 + 82) * 28.32 is 2492.16", "a": 6, "b": 82, "c": 28.32, "op1": "+", "op2": "*", "result": 2492.16}
{"question": "Solve: (26.14 * 118) * 183.72", "answer": "The result of (26.14 * 118) * 183.72 is 566688.01", "a": 26.14, "b": 118, "c": 183.72, "op1": "*", "op2": "*", "result": 566688.01}
{"question": "Solve: (38 + 87.55) / 71.73", "answer": "The result of (38 + 87.55) / 71.73 is 1.75", "a": 38, "b": 87.55, "c": 71.73, "op1": "+", "op2": "/", "result": 1.75}
{"question": "Solve: (48.42 / 122) * 20", "answer": "The result of (48.42 / 122) * 20 is 7.94", "a": 48.42, "b": 122, "c": 20, "op1": "/", "op2": "*", "result": 7.94}
{"question": "Solve: (156 * 120) + 188", "answer": "The result of (156 * 120) + 188 is 18908", "a": 156, "b": 120, "c": 188, "op1": "*", "op2": "+", "result": 18908}
{"question": "Solve: (151.92 * 51) - 44.63", "answer": "The result of (151.92 * 51) - 44.63 is 7703.29", "a": 151.92, "b": 51, "c": 44.63, "op1": "*", "op2": "-", "result": 7703.29}
{"question": "Solve: (188 + 30) - 21", "answer": "The result of (188 + 30) - 21 is 197", "a": 188, "b": 30, "c": 21, "op1": "+", "op2": "-", "result": 197}
{"question": "Solve: (166 + 161) + 170", "answer": "The result of (166 + 161) + 170 is 497", "a": 166, "b": 161, "c": 170, "op1": "+", "op2": "+", "result": 497}
{"question": "Solve: (68.64 * 33) * 75", "answer": "The result of (68.64 * 33) * 75 is 169884.0", "a": 68.64, "b": 33, "c": 75, "op1": "*", "op2": "*", "result": 169884.0}
{"question": "Solve: (9 / 71) * 154", "answer": "The result of (9 / 71) * 154 is 19.52", "a": 9, "b": 71, "c": 154, "op1": "/", "op2": "*", "result": 19.52}
{"question": "Solve: (160 * 45) - 91", "answer": "The result of (160 * 45) - 91 is 7109", "a": 160, "b": 45, "c": 91, "op1": "*", "op2": "-", "result": 7109}
{"question": "Solve: (126 / 116.33) / 67.3", "answer": "The result of (126 / 116.33) / 67.3 is 0.02", "a": 126, "b": 116.33, "c": 67.3, "op1": "/", "op2": "/", "result": 0.02}
{"question": "Solve: (119 * 171) - 156", "answer": "The result of (119 * 171) - 156 is 20193", "a": 119, "b": 171, "c": 156, "op1": "*", "op2": "-", "result": 20193}
{"question": "Solve: (103 - 7) * 144", "answer": "The result of (103 - 7) * 144 is 13824", "a": 103, "b": 7, "c": 144, "op1": "-", "op2": "*", "result": 13824}
{"question": "Solve: (30 / 63) / 186", "answer": "The result of (30 / 63) / 186 is 0.0", "a": 30, "b": 63, "c": 186, "op1": "/", "op2": "/", "result": 0.0}
{"question": "Solve: (188 + 160.65) * 101", "answer": "The result of (188 + 160.65) * 101 is 35213.65", "a": 188, "b": 160.65, "c": 101, "op1": "+", "op2": "*", "result": 35213.65}
{"question": "Solve: (19 / 166) - 89", "answer": "The result of (19 / 166) - 89 is -88.89", "a": 19, "b": 166, "c": 89, "op1": "/", "op2": "-", "result": -88.89}
{"question": "Solve: (6.19 + 151.63) - 144", "answer": "The result of (6.19 + 151.63) - 144 is 13.82", "a": 6.19, "b": 151.63, "c": 144, "op1": "+", "op2": "-", "result": 13.82}
{"question": "Solve: (122 + 198) * 88", "answer": "The result of (122 + 198) * 88 is 28160", "a": 122, "b": 198, "c": 88, "op1": "+", "op2": "*", "result": 28160}
{"question": "Solve: (46.95 + 92) * 112", "answer": "The result of (46.95 + 92) * 112 is 15562.4", "a": 46.95, "b": 92, "c": 112, "op1": "+", "op2": "*", "result": 15562.4}
{"question": "Solve: (59 + 78.33) + 28.36", "answer": "The result of (59 + 78.33) + 28.36 is 165.69", "a": 59, "b": 78.33, "c": 28.36, "op1": "+", "op2": "+", "result": 165.69}
{"question": "Solve: (37 - 74) - 140", "answer": "The result of (37 - 74) - 140 is -177", "a": 37, "b": 74, "c": 140, "op1": "-", "op2": "-", "result": -177}
{"question": "Solve: (140 * 185) * 121.55", "answer": "The result of (140 * 185) * 121.55 is 3148145.0", "a": 140, "b": 185, "c": 121.55, "op1": "*", "op2": "*", "result": 3148145.0}
{"question": "Solve: (143 + 156.59) * 74.56", "answer": "The result of (143 + 156.59) * 74.56 is 22337.43", "a": 143, "b": 156.59, "c": 74.56, "op1": "+", "op2": "*", "result": 22337.43}
{"question": "Solve: (125.71 - 186) - 8", "answer": "The result of (125.71 - 186) - 8 is -68.29", "a": 125.71, "b": 186, "c": 8, "op1": "-", "op2": "-", "result": -68.29}
{"question": "Solve: (197 - 78) / 51.79", "answer": "The result of (197 - 78) / 51.79 is 2.3", "a": 197, "b": 78, "c": 51.79, "op1": "-", "op2": "/", "result": 2.3}
{"question": "Solve: (129 + 146) - 191", "answer": "The result of (129 + 146) - 191 is 84", "a": 129, "b": 146, "c": 191, "op1": "+", "op2": "-", "result": 84}
{"question": "Solve: (78 + 164) * 73", "answer": "The result of (78 + 164) * 73 is 17666", "a": 78, "b": 164, "c": 73, "op1": "+", "op2": "*", "result": 17666}
{"question": "Solve: (81 + 6.89) + 172", "answer": "The result of (81 + 6.89) + 172 is 259.89", "a": 81, "b": 6.89, "c": 172, "op1": "+", "op2": "+", "result": 259.89}
{"question": "Solve: (182 * 154) * 12.16", "answer": "The result of (182 * 154) * 12.16 is 340820.48", "a": 182, "b": 154, "c": 12.16, "op1": "*", "op2": "*", "result": 340820.48}
{"question": "Solve: (20.18 - 156) + 180", "answer": "The result of (20.18 - 156) + 180 is 44.18", "a": 20.18, "b": 156, "c": 180, "op1": "-", "op2": "+", "result": 44.18}
{"question": "Solve: (175 - 144) + 10", "answer": "The result of (175 - 144) + 10 is 41", "a": 175, "b": 144, "c": 10, "op1": "-", "op2": "+", "result": 41}
{"question": "Solve: (50 * 117) - 23", "answer": "The result of (50 * 117) - 23 is 5827", "a": 50, "b": 117, "c": 23, "op1": "*", "op2": "-", "result": 5827}
{"question": "Solve: (96.32 - 27) * 79", "answer": "The result of (96.32 - 27) * 79 is 5476.28", "a": 96.32, "b": 27, "c": 79, "op1": "-", "op2": "*", "result": 5476.28}
{"question": "Solve: (109 * 144.85) * 107", "answer": "The result of (109 * 144.85) * 107 is 1689385.55", "a": 109, "b": 144.85, "c": 107, "op1": "*", "op2": "*", "result": 1689385.55}
{"question": "Solve: (106.21 * 162) * 27", "answer": "The result of (106.21 * 162) * 27 is 464562.54", "a": 106.21, "b": 162, "c": 27, "op1": "*", "op2": "*", "result": 464562.54}
{"question": "Solve: (154 + 134) * 88", "answer": "The result of (154 + 134) * 88 is 25344", "a": 154, "b": 134, "c": 88, "op1": "+", "op2": "*", "result": 25344}
{"question": "Solve: (37 - 173) / 120", "answer": "The result of (37 - 173) / 120 is -1.13", "a": 37, "b": 173, "c": 120, "op1": "-", "op2": "/", "result": -1.13}
{"question": "Solve: (137.03 - 159) + 190.68", "answer": "The result of (137.03 - 159) + 190.68 is 168.71", "a": 137.03, "b": 159, "c": 190.68, "op1": "-", "op2": "+", "result": 168.71}
{"question": "Solve: (166 + 199.28) * 90", "answer": "The result of (166 + 199.28) * 90 is 32875.2", "a": 166, "b": 199.28, "c": 90, "op1": "+", "op2": "*", "result": 32875.2}
{"question": "Solve: (125 - 4) + 29", "answer": "The result of (125 - 4) + 29 is 150", "a": 125, "b": 4, "c": 29, "op1": "-", "op2": "+", "result": 150}
{"question": "Solve: (167 - 68.83) / 138", "answer": "The result of (167 - 68.83) / 138 is 0.71", "a": 167, "b": 68.83, "c": 138, "op1": "-", "op2": "/", "result": 0.71}
{"question": "Solve: (105 + 187) - 157", "answer": "The result of (105 + 187) - 157 is 135", "a": 105, "b": 187, "c": 157, "op1": "+", "op2": "-", "result": 135}
{"question": "Solve: (165 + 159.34) + 12.25", "answer": "The result of (165 + 159.34) + 12.25 is 336.59", "a": 165, "b": 159.34, "c": 12.25, "op1": "+", "op2": "+", "result": 336.59}
{"question": "Solve: (76 * 9) + 153.12", "answer": "The result of (76 * 9) + 153.12 is 837.12", "a": 76, "b": 9, "c": 153.12, "op1": "*", "op2": "+", "result": 837.12}
{"question": "Solve: (199 + 155.46) + 52", "answer": "The result of (199 + 155.46) + 52 is 406.46", "a": 199, "b": 155.46, "c": 52, "op1": "+", "op2": "+", "result": 406.46}
{"question": "Solve: (9 - 159.99) + 135", "answer": "The result of (9 - 159.99) + 135 is -15.99", "a": 9, "b": 159.99, "c": 135, "op1": "-", "op2": "+", "result": -15.99}
{"question": "Solve: (151.67 - 122) + 59", "answer": "The result of (151.67 - 122) + 59 is 88.67", "a": 151.67, "b": 122, "c": 59, "op1": "-", "op2": "+", "result": 88.67}
{"question": "Solve: (147 + 39.02) / 18", "answer": "The result of (147 + 39.02) / 18 is 10.33", "a": 147, "b": 39.02, "c": 18, "op1": "+", "op2": "/", "result": 10.33}
{"question": "Solve: (124 * 100) * 53", "answer": "The result of (124 * 100) * 53 is 657200", "a": 124, "b": 100, "c": 53, "op1": "*", "op2": "*", "result": 657200}
{"question": "Solve: (101 + 53) + 153", "answer": "The result of (101 + 53) + 153 is 307", "a": 101, "b": 53, "c": 153, "op1": "+", "op2": "+", "result": 307}
{"question": "Solve: (14 + 154) - 173.96", "answer": "The result of (14 + 154) - 173.96 is -5.96", "a": 14, "b": 154, "c": 173.96, "op1": "+", "op2": "-", "result": -5.96}
{"question": "Solve: (133 + 86.5) + 49", "answer": "The result of (133 + 86.5) + 49 is 268.5", "a": 133, "b": 86.5, "c": 49, "op1": "+", "op2": "+", "result": 268.5}
{"question": "Solve: (43 * 46) + 22.9", "answer": "The result of (43 * 46) + 22.9 is 2000.9", "a": 43, "b": 46, "c": 22.9, "op1": "*", "op2": "+", "result": 2000.9}
{"question": "Solve: (129 - 127) * 46.53", "answer": "The result of (129 - 127) * 46.53 is 93.06", "a": 129, "b": 127, "c": 46.53, "op1": "-", "op2": "*", "result": 93.06}
{"question": "Solve: (133 + 51) - 166", "answer": "The result of (133 + 51) - 166 is 18", "a": 133, "b": 51, "c": 166, "op1": "+", "op2": "-", "result": 18}
{"question": "Solve: (70.18 - 165) / 159", "answer": "The result of (70.18 - 165) / 159 is -0.6", "a": 70.18, "b": 165, "c": 159, "op1": "-", "op2": "/", "result": -0.6}
{"question": "Solve: (109 / 99) + 110", "answer": "The result of (109 / 99) + 110 is 111.1", "a": 109, "b": 99, "c": 110, "op1": "/", "op2": "+", "result": 111.1}
{"question": "Solve: (57 - 50) - 18.95", "answer": "The result of (57 - 50) - 18.95 is -11.95", "a": 57, "b": 50, "c": 18.95, "op1": "-", "op2": "-", "result": -11.95}
{"question": "Solve: (197 * 113.79) / 56", "answer": "The result of (197 * 113.79) / 56 is 400.3", "a": 197, "b": 113.79, "c": 56, "op1": "*", "op2": "/", "result": 400.3}
{"question": "Solve: (149 - 187) - 171", "answer": "The result of (149 - 187) - 171 is -209", "a": 149, "b": 187, "c": 171, "op1": "-", "op2": "-", "result": -209}
{"question": "Solve: (127 + 74) + 70", "answer": "The result of (127 + 74) + 70 is 271", "a": 127, "b": 74, "c": 70, "op1": "+", "op2": "+", "result": 271}
{"question": "Solve: (42 / 162.74) - 99", "answer": "The result of (42 / 162.74) - 99 is -98.74", "a": 42, "b": 162.74, "c": 99, "op1": "/", "op2": "-", "result": -98.74}
{"question": "Solve: (80 - 57) * 190", "answer": "The result of (80 - 57) * 190 is 4370", "a": 80, "b": 57, "c": 190, "op1": "-", "op2": "*", "result": 4370}
{"question": "Solve: (61 + 177) - 89.18", "answer": "The result of (61 + 177) - 89.18 is 148.82", "a": 61, "b": 177, "c": 89.18, "op1": "+", "op2": "-", "result": 148.82}
{"question": "Solve: (133.8 / 167) + 185", "answer": "The result of (133.8 / 167) + 185 is 185.8", "a": 133.8, "b": 167, "c": 185, "op1": "/", "op2": "+", "result": 185.8}
{"question": "Solve: (16 - 87) * 31", "answer": "The result of (16 - 87) * 31 is -2201", "a": 16, "b": 87, "c": 31, "op1": "-", "op2": "*", "result": -2201}
{"question": "Solve: (151 + 5) * 162", "answer": "The result of (151 + 5) * 162 is 25272", "a": 151, "b": 5, "c": 162, "op1": "+", "op2": "*", "result": 25272}
{"question": "Solve: (191 - 119.59) + 180.29", "answer": "The result of (191 - 119.59) + 180.29 is 251.7", "a": 191, "b": 119.59, "c": 180.29, "op1": "-", "op2": "+", "result": 251.7}
{"question": "Solve: (13 - 42) + 11", "answer": "The result of (13 - 42) + 11 is -18", "a": 13, "b": 42, "c": 11, "op1": "-", "op2": "+", "result": -18}
{"question": "Solve: (97 + 12.6) * 32.27", "answer": "The result of (97 + 12.6) * 32.27 is 3536.79", "a": 97, "b": 12.6, "c": 32.27, "op1": "+", "op2": "*", "result": 3536.79}
{"question": "Solve: (153 + 150) + 124", "answer": "The result of (153 + 150) + 124 is 427", "a": 153, "b": 150, "c": 124, "op1": "+", "op2": "+", "result": 427}
{"question": "Solve: (104.79 + 112) + 91", "answer": "The result of (104.79 + 112) + 91 is 307.79", "a": 104.79, "b": 112, "c": 91, "op1": "+", "op2": "+", "result": 307.79}
{"question": "Solve: (104 + 99) - 74", "answer": "The result of (104 + 99) - 74 is 129", "a": 104, "b": 99, "c": 74, "op1": "+", "op2": "-", "result": 129}
{"question": "Solve: (192 - 88) * 55", "answer": "The result of (192 - 88) * 55 is 5720", "a": 192, "b": 88, "c": 55, "op1": "-", "op2": "*", "result": 5720}
{"question": "Solve: (39 * 114) + 34", "answer": "The result of (39 * 114) + 34 is 4480", "a": 39, "b": 114, "c": 34, "op1": "*", "op2": "+", "result": 4480}
{"question": "Solve: (192 * 107.72) - 159", "answer": "The result of (192 * 107.72) - 159 is 20523.24", "a": 192, "b": 107.72, "c": 159, "op1": "*", "op2": "-", "result": 20523.24}
{"question": "Solve: (9.13 + 68.41) - 112", "answer": "The result of (9.13 + 68.41) - 112 is -34.46", "a": 9.13, "b": 68.41, "c": 112, "op1": "+", "op2": "-", "result": -34.46}
{"question": "Solve: (180.79 + 76) / 27", "answer": "The result of (180.79 + 76) / 27 is 9.51", "a": 180.79, "b": 76, "c": 27, "op1": "+", "op2": "/", "result": 9.51}
{"question": "Solve: (4.22 - 23) + 110", "answer": "The result of (4.22 - 23) + 110 is 91.22", "a": 4.22, "b": 23, "c": 110, "op1": "-", "op2": "+", "result": 91.22}
{"question": "Solve: (9 + 191) + 76", "answer": "The result of (9 + 191) + 76 is 276", "a": 9, "b": 191, "c": 76, "op1": "+", "op2": "+", "result": 276}
{"question": "Solve: (75 / 176) * 183.57", "answer": "The result of (75 / 176) * 183.57 is 78.23", "a": 75, "b": 176, "c": 183.57, "op1": "/", "op2": "*", "result": 78.23}
{"question": "Solve: (101.34 * 1.14) - 26.82", "answer": "The result of (101.34 * 1.14) - 26.82 is 88.71", "a": 101.34, "b": 1.14, "c": 26.82, "op1": "*", "op2": "-", "result": 88.71}
{"question": "Solve: (174 + 144.54) - 189.07", "answer": "The result of (174 + 144.54) - 189.07 is 129.47", "a": 174, "b": 144.54, "c": 189.07, "op1": "+", "op2": "-", "result": 129.47}
{"question": "Solve: (91 * 81) * 3", "answer": "The result of (91 * 81) * 3 is 22113", "a": 91, "b": 81, "c": 3, "op1": "*", "op2": "*", "result": 22113}
{"question": "Solve: (28 - 192.08) - 36", "answer": "The result of (28 - 192.08) - 36 is -200.08", "a": 28, "b": 192.08, "c": 36, "op1": "-", "op2": "-", "result": -200.08}
{"question": "Solve: (121 - 127) - 31.17", "answer": "The result of (121 - 127) - 31.17 is -37.17", "a": 121, "b": 127, "c": 31.17, "op1": "-", "op2": "-", "result": -37.17}
{"question": "Solve: (172.31 - 158) - 125", "answer": "The result of (172.31 - 158) - 125 is -110.69", "a": 172.31, "b": 158, "c": 125, "op1": "-", "op2": "-", "result": -110.69}
{"question": "Solve: (146 - 19) / 160.91", "answer": "The result of (146 - 19) / 160.91 is 0.79", "a": 146, "b": 19, "c": 160.91, "op1": "-", "op2": "/", "result": 0.79}
{"question": "Solve: (92.92 + 127) / 174", "answer": "The result of (92.92 + 127) / 174 is 1.26", "a": 92.92, "b": 127, "c": 174, "op1": "+", "op2": "/", "result": 1.26}
{"question": "Solve: (70 + 66) - 138.04", "answer": "The result of (70 + 66) - 138.04 is -2.04", "a": 70, "b": 66, "c": 138.04, "op1": "+", "op2": "-", "result": -2.04}
{"question": "Solve: (95 * 139.77) + 184", "answer": "The result of (95 * 139.77) + 184 is 13462.15", "a": 95, "b": 139.77, "c": 184, "op1": "*", "op2": "+", "result": 13462.15}
{"question": "Solve: (158 * 54) + 105", "answer": "The result of (158 * 54) + 105 is 8637", "a": 158, "b": 54, "c": 105, "op1": "*", "op2": "+", "result": 8637}
{"question": "Solve: (84 - 62.27) * 67", "answer": "The result of (84 - 62.27) * 67 is 1455.91", "a": 84, "b": 62.27, "c": 67, "op1": "-", "op2": "*", "result": 1455.91}
{"question": "Solve: (175 / 21) - 154", "answer": "The result of (175 / 21) - 154 is -145.67", "a": 175, "b": 21, "c": 154, "op1": "/", "op2": "-", "result": -145.67}
{"question": "Solve: (68 + 18.78) + 160.83", "answer": "The result of (68 + 18.78) + 160.83 is 247.61", "a": 68, "b": 18.78, "c": 160.83, "op1": "+", "op2": "+", "result": 247.61}
{"question": "Solve: (6 + 194) / 28", "answer": "The result of (6 + 194) / 28 is 7.14", "a": 6, "b": 194, "c": 28, "op1": "+", "op2": "/", "result": 7.14}
{"question": "Solve: (122 + 141.94) + 142", "answer": "The result of (122 + 141.94) + 142 is 405.94", "a": 122, "b": 141.94, "c": 142, "op1": "+", "op2": "+", "result": 405.94}
{"question": "Solve: (106.74 / 174) - 153.11", "answer": "The result of (106.74 / 174) - 153.11 is -152.5", "a": 106.74, "b": 174, "c": 153.11, "op1": "/", "op2": "-", "result": -152.5}
{"question": "Solve: (126.65 * 168) / 67", "answer": "The result of (126.65 * 168) / 67 is 317.57", "a": 126.65, "b": 168, "c": 67, "op1": "*", "op2": "/", "result": 317.57}
{"question": "Solve: (129 / 132.08) * 87", "answer": "The result of (129 / 132.08) * 87 is 84.97", "a": 129, "b": 132.08, "c": 87, "op1": "/", "op2": "*", "result": 84.97}
{"question": "Solve: (131 + 21) / 163", "answer": "The result of (131 + 21) / 163 is 0.93", "a": 131, "b": 21, "c": 163, "op1": "+", "op2": "/", "result": 0.93}
{"question": "Solve: (72.29 / 185.24) - 93", "answer": "The result of (72.29 / 185.24) - 93 is -92.61", "a": 72.29, "b": 185.24, "c": 93, "op1": "/", "op2": "-", "result": -92.61}
{"question": "Solve: (1 * 63) * 20", "answer": "The result of (1 * 63) * 20 is 1260", "a": 1, "b": 63, "c": 20, "op1": "*", "op2": "*", "result": 1260}
{"question": "Solve: (100.28 + 122) + 186", "answer": "The result of (100.28 + 122) + 186 is 408.28", "a": 100.28, "b": 122, "c": 186, "op1": "+", "op2": "+", "result": 408.28}
{"question": "Solve: (143.29 - 44) - 33", "answer": "The result of (143.29 - 44) - 33 is 66.29", "a": 143.29, "b": 44, "c": 33, "op1": "-", "op2": "-", "result": 66.29}
{"question": "Solve: (68 * 66) * 161", "answer": "The result of (68 * 66) * 161 is 722568", "a": 68, "b": 66, "c": 161, "op1": "*", "op2": "*", "result": 722568}
{"question": "Solve: (180.63 - 57) + 112.46", "answer": "The result of (180.63 - 57) + 112.46 is 236.09", "a": 180.63, "b": 57, "c": 112.46, "op1": "-", "op2": "+", "result": 236.09}
{"question": "Solve: (27.59 * 160.5) / 23.96", "answer": "The result of (27.59 * 160.5) / 23.96 is 184.82", "a": 27.59, "b": 160.5, "c": 23.96, "op1": "*", "op2": "/", "result": 184.82}
{"question": "Solve: (84 * 153) / 5.69", "answer": "The result of (84 * 153) / 5.69 is 2258.7", "a": 84, "b": 153, "c": 5.69, "op1": "*", "op2": "/", "result": 2258.7}
{"question": "Solve: (193 / 93) - 85", "answer": "The result of (193 / 93) - 85 is -82.92", "a": 193, "b": 93, "c": 85, "op1": "/", "op2": "-", "result": -82.92}
{"question": "Solve: (5 - 116.01) / 187.69", "answer": "The result of (5 - 116.01) / 187.69 is -0.59", "a": 5, "b": 116.01, "c": 187.69, "op1": "-", "op2": "/", "result": -0.59}
{"question": "Solve: (20 / 24.94) - 16", "answer": "The result of (20 / 24.94) - 16 is -15.2", "a": 20, "b": 24.94, "c": 16, "op1": "/", "op2": "-", "result": -15.2}
{"question": "Solve: (164 * 124.66) + 190", "answer": "The result of (164 * 124.66) + 190 is 20634.24", "a": 164, "b": 124.66, "c": 190, "op1": "*", "op2": "+", "result": 20634.24}
{"question": "Solve: (153.06 - 48) * 178", "answer": "The result of (153.06 - 48) * 178 is 18700.68", "a": 153.06, "b": 48, "c": 178, "op1": "-", "op2": "*", "result": 18700.68}
{"question": "Solve: (6 + 198) - 138", "answer": "The result of (6 + 198) - 138 is 66", "a": 6, "b": 198, "c": 138, "op1": "+", "op2": "-", "result": 66}
{"question": "Solve: (129.77 / 52.16) * 6", "answer": "The result of (129.77 / 52.16) * 6 is 14.93", "a": 129.77, "b": 52.16, "c": 6, "op1": "/", "op2": "*", "result": 14.93}
{"question": "Solve: (56 / 12) + 156.18", "answer": "The result of (56 / 12) + 156.18 is 160.85", "a": 56, "b": 12, "c": 156.18, "op1": "/", "op2": "+", "result": 160.85}
{"question": "Solve: (77 - 32) + 37", "answer": "The result of (77 - 32) + 37 is 82", "a": 77, "b": 32, "c": 37, "op1": "-", "op2": "+", "result": 82}
{"question": "Solve: (197.71 - 63) / 96", "answer": "The result of (197.71 - 63) / 96 is 1.4", "a": 197.71, "b": 63, "c": 96, "op1": "-", "op2": "/", "result": 1.4}
{"question": "Solve: (173 / 135.1) / 187.28", "answer": "The result of (173 / 135.1) / 187.28 is 0.01", "a": 173, "b": 135.1, "c": 187.28, "op1": "/", "op2": "/", "result": 0.01}
{"question": "Solve: (105 - 29.07) * 105", "answer": "The result of (105 - 29.07) * 105 is 7972.65", "a": 105, "b": 29.07, "c": 105, "op1": "-", "op2": "*", "result": 7972.65}
{"question": "Solve: (60 - 4) * 168", "answer": "The result of (60 - 4) * 168 is 9408", "a": 60, "b": 4, "c": 168, "op1": "-", "op2": "*", "result": 9408}
{"question": "Solve: (183 - 84) - 66", "answer": "The result of (183 - 84) - 66 is 33", "a": 183, "b": 84, "c": 66, "op1": "-", "op2": "-", "result": 33}
{"question": "Solve: (155 + 20.76) / 31.13", "answer": "The result of (155 + 20.76) / 31.13 is 5.65", "a": 155, "b": 20.76, "c": 31.13, "op1": "+", "op2": "/", "result": 5.65}
{"question": "Solve: (37 - 144.3) / 199", "answer": "The result of (37 - 144.3) / 199 is -0.54", "a": 37, "b": 144.3, "c": 199, "op1": "-", "op2": "/", "result": -0.54}
{"question": "Solve: (141 * 63.2) + 166.13", "answer": "The result of (141 * 63.2) + 166.13 is 9077.33", "a": 141, "b": 63.2, "c": 166.13, "op1": "*", "op2": "+", "result": 9077.33}
{"question": "Solve: (183 * 146) - 11.92", "answer": "The result of (183 * 146) - 11.92 is 26706.08", "a": 183, "b": 146, "c": 11.92, "op1": "*", "op2": "-", "result": 26706.08}
{"question": "Solve: (196 - 61) - 82.01", "answer": "The result of (196 - 61) - 82.01 is 52.99", "a": 196, "b": 61, "c": 82.01, "op1": "-", "op2": "-", "result": 52.99}
{"question": "Solve: (70.71 * 135) * 146", "answer": "The result of (70.71 * 135) * 146 is 1393694.1", "a": 70.71, "b": 135, "c": 146, "op1": "*", "op2": "*", "result": 1393694.1}
{"question": "Solve: (117 / 15) / 192", "answer": "The result of (117 / 15) / 192 is 0.04", "a": 117, "b": 15, "c": 192, "op1": "/", "op2": "/", "result": 0.04}
{"question": "Solve: (126 + 186.51) + 127", "answer": "The result of (126 + 186.51) + 127 is 439.51", "a": 126, "b": 186.51, "c": 127, "op1": "+", "op2": "+", "result": 439.51}
{"question": "Solve: (144.79 - 199) + 57", "answer": "The result of (144.79 - 199) + 57 is 2.79", "a": 144.79, "b": 199, "c": 57, "op1": "-", "op2": "+", "result": 2.79}
{"question": "Solve: (114 - 164) / 38", "answer": "The result of (114 - 164) / 38 is -1.32", "a": 114, "b": 164, "c": 38, "op1": "-", "op2": "/", "result": -1.32}
{"question": "Solve: (138.21 + 84.91) - 117", "answer": "The result of (138.21 + 84.91) - 117 is 106.12", "a": 138.21, "b": 84.91, "c": 117, "op1": "+", "op2": "-", "result": 106.12}
{"question": "Solve: (123 + 47) - 49", "answer": "The result of (123 + 47) - 49 is 121", "a": 123, "b": 47, "c": 49, "op1": "+", "op2": "-", "result": 121}
{"question": "Solve: (2 * 73) - 118", "answer": "The result of (2 * 73) - 118 is 28", "a": 2, "b": 73, "c": 118, "op1": "*", "op2": "-", "result": 28}
{"question": "Solve: (89 + 8.53) - 111", "answer": "The result of (89 + 8.53) - 111 is -13.47", "a": 89, "b": 8.53, "c": 111, "op1": "+", "op2": "-", "result": -13.47}
{"question": "Solve: (49.83 + 62.7) * 148", "answer": "The result of (49.83 + 62.7) * 148 is 16654.44", "a": 49.83, "b": 62.7, "c": 148, "op1": "+", "op2": "*", "result": 16654.44}
{"question": "Solve: (186 * 47) / 109", "answer": "The result of (186 * 47) / 109 is 80.2", "a": 186, "b": 47, "c": 109, "op1": "*", "op2": "/", "result": 80.2}
{"question": "Solve: (94 - 116) - 148", "answer": "The result of (94 - 116) - 148 is -170", "a": 94, "b": 116, "c": 148, "op1": "-", "op2": "-", "result": -170}
{"question": "Solve: (149.5 + 10) + 8", "answer": "The result of (149.5 + 10) + 8 is 167.5", "a": 149.5, "b": 10, "c": 8, "op1": "+", "op2": "+", "result": 167.5}
{"question": "Solve: (29 - 183) - 87.95", "answer": "The result of (29 - 183) - 87.95 is -241.95", "a": 29, "b": 183, "c": 87.95, "op1": "-", "op2": "-", "result": -241.95}
{"question": "Solve: (178.46 + 3.02) - 145.16", "answer": "The result of (178.46 + 3.02) - 145.16 is 36.32", "a": 178.46, "b": 3.02, "c": 145.16, "op1": "+", "op2": "-", "result": 36.32}
{"question": "Solve: (15 - 105) - 137.91", "answer": "The result of (15 - 105) - 137.91 is -227.91", "a": 15, "b": 105, "c": 137.91, "op1": "-", "op2": "-", "result": -227.91}
{"question": "Solve: (88 / 52) - 37", "answer": "The result of (88 / 52) - 37 is -35.31", "a": 88, "b": 52, "c": 37, "op1": "/", "op2": "-", "result": -35.31}
{"question": "Solve: (197.3 - 1) - 197", "answer": "The result of (197.3 - 1) - 197 is -0.7", "a": 197.3, "b": 1, "c": 197, "op1": "-", "op2": "-", "result": -0.7}
{"question": "Solve: (119.44 - 93) * 126", "answer": "The result of (119.44 - 93) * 126 is 3331.44", "a": 119.44, "b": 93, "c": 126, "op1": "-", "op2": "*", "result": 3331.44}
{"question": "Solve: (57 * 164) + 35", "answer": "The result of (57 * 164) + 35 is 9383", "a": 57, "b": 164, "c": 35, "op1": "*", "op2": "+", "result": 9383}
{"question": "Solve: (131 - 59) / 188", "answer": "The result of (131 - 59) / 188 is 0.38", "a": 131, "b": 59, "c": 188, "op1": "-", "op2": "/", "result": 0.38}
{"question": "Solve: (33.95 / 129.98) + 110", "answer": "The result of (33.95 / 129.98) + 110 is 110.26", "a": 33.95, "b": 129.98, "c": 110, "op1": "/", "op2": "+", "result": 110.26}
{"question": "Solve: (72 + 99) * 25", "answer": "The result of (72 + 99) * 25 is 4275", "a": 72, "b": 99, "c": 25, "op1": "+", "op2": "*", "result": 4275}
{"question": "Solve: (72.25 - 176) + 50.89", "answer": "The result of (72.25 - 176) + 50.89 is -52.86", "a": 72.25, "b": 176, "c": 50.89, "op1": "-", "op2": "+", "result": -52.86}
{"question": "Solve: (21 - 169) / 188", "answer": "The result of (21 - 169) / 188 is -0.79", "a": 21, "b": 169, "c": 188, "op1": "-", "op2": "/", "result": -0.79}
{"question": "Solve: (55 / 143) + 139", "answer": "The result of (55 / 143) + 139 is 139.38", "a": 55, "b": 143, "c": 139, "op1": "/", "op2": "+", "result": 139.38}
{"question": "Solve: (38.22 / 70) * 166.86", "answer": "The result of (38.22 / 70) * 166.86 is 91.11", "a": 38.22, "b": 70, "c": 166.86, "op1": "/", "op2": "*", "result": 91.11}
{"question": "Solve: (70.58 - 71) * 139", "answer": "The result of (70.58 - 71) * 139 is -58.38", "a": 70.58, "b": 71, "c": 139, "op1": "-", "op2": "*", "result": -58.38}
{"question": "Solve: (124.55 - 2) + 95.03", "answer": "The result of (124.55 - 2) + 95.03 is 217.58", "a": 124.55, "b": 2, "c": 95.03, "op1": "-", "op2": "+", "result": 217.58}
{"question": "Solve: (178 + 173) * 96.02", "answer": "The result of (178 + 173) * 96.02 is 33703.02", "a": 178, "b": 173, "c": 96.02, "op1": "+", "op2": "*", "result": 33703.02}
{"question": "Solve: (190.12 * 186) * 162.37", "answer": "The result of (190.12 * 186) * 162.37 is 5741779.9", "a": 190.12, "b": 186, "c": 162.37, "op1": "*", "op2": "*", "result": 5741779.9}
{"question": "Solve: (124 * 8.38) - 15", "answer": "The result of (124 * 8.38) - 15 is 1024.12", "a": 124, "b": 8.38, "c": 15, "op1": "*", "op2": "-", "result": 1024.12}
{"question": "Solve: (168 * 78.91) * 195", "answer": "The result of (168 * 78.91) * 195 is 2585091.6", "a": 168, "b": 78.91, "c": 195, "op1": "*", "op2": "*", "result": 2585091.6}
{"question": "Solve: (9.28 + 137) + 139", "answer": "The result of (9.28 + 137) + 139 is 285.28", "a": 9.28, "b": 137, "c": 139, "op1": "+", "op2": "+", "result": 285.28}
{"question": "Solve: (73 / 8) * 164", "answer": "The result of (73 / 8) * 164 is 1496.5", "a": 73, "b": 8, "c": 164, "op1": "/", "op2": "*", "result": 1496.5}
{"question": "Solve: (189.48 + 142) + 157", "answer": "The result of (189.48 + 142) + 157 is 488.48", "a": 189.48, "b": 142, "c": 157, "op1": "+", "op2": "+", "result": 488.48}
{"question": "Solve: (166.97 - 86) / 101", "answer": "The result of (166.97 - 86) / 101 is 0.8", "a": 166.97, "b": 86, "c": 101, "op1": "-", "op2": "/", "result": 0.8}
{"question": "Solve: (184 / 44.08) - 134", "answer": "The result of (184 / 44.08) - 134 is -129.83", "a": 184, "b": 44.08, "c": 134, "op1": "/", "op2": "-", "result": -129.83}
{"question": "Solve: (1 + 88.87) - 17", "answer": "The result of (1 + 88.87) - 17 is 72.87", "a": 1, "b": 88.87, "c": 17, "op1": "+", "op2": "-", "result": 72.87}
{"question": "Solve: (4 + 102) - 63", "answer": "The result of (4 + 102) - 63 is 43", "a": 4, "b": 102, "c": 63, "op1": "+", "op2": "-", "result": 43}
{"question": "Solve: (105 / 123) / 179", "answer": "The result of (105 / 123) / 179 is 0.0", "a": 105, "b": 123, "c": 179, "op1": "/", "op2": "/", "result": 0.0}
{"question": "Solve: (150 + 81.97) / 100", "answer": "The result of (150 + 81.97) / 100 is 2.32", "a": 150, "b": 81.97, "c": 100, "op1": "+", "op2": "/", "result": 2.32}
{"question": "Solve: (109 - 187.31) - 154", "answer": "The result of (109 - 187.31) - 154 is -232.31", "a": 109, "b": 187.31, "c": 154, "op1": "-", "op2": "-", "result": -232.31}
{"question": "Solve: (121 - 200) + 104", "answer": "The result of (121 - 200) + 104 is 25", "a": 121, "b": 200, "c": 104, "op1": "-", "op2": "+", "result": 25}
{"question": "Solve: (67 - 149.36) - 178", "answer": "The result of (67 - 149.36) - 178 is -260.36", "a": 67, "b": 149.36, "c": 178, "op1": "-", "op2": "-", "result": -260.36}
{"question": "Solve: (89 - 131) - 127", "answer": "The result of (89 - 131) - 127 is -169", "a": 89, "b": 131, "c": 127, "op1": "-", "op2": "-", "result": -169}
{"question": "Solve: (97 - 138) + 103", "answer": "The result of (97 - 138) + 103 is 62", "a": 97, "b": 138, "c": 103, "op1": "-", "op2": "+", "result": 62}
{"question": "Solve: (60 + 175) - 126.04", "answer": "The result of (60 + 175) - 126.04 is 108.96", "a": 60, "b": 175, "c": 126.04, "op1": "+", "op2": "-", "result": 108.96}
{"question": "Solve: (49 - 151) + 167", "answer": "The result of (49 - 151) + 167 is 65", "a": 49, "b": 151, "c": 167, "op1": "-", "op2": "+", "result": 65}
{"question": "Solve: (105 - 82) * 143", "answer": "The result of (105 - 82) * 143 is 3289", "a": 105, "b": 82, "c": 143, "op1": "-", "op2": "*", "result": 3289}
{"question": "Solve: (73 / 24) - 85.32", "answer": "The result of (73 / 24) - 85.32 is -82.28", "a": 73, "b": 24, "c": 85.32, "op1": "/", "op2": "-", "result": -82.28}
{"question": "Solve: (111 + 1) + 112", "answer": "The result of (111 + 1) + 112 is 224", "a": 111, "b": 1, "c": 112, "op1": "+", "op2": "+", "result": 224}
{"question": "Solve: (88 + 102) + 91", "answer": "The result of (88 + 102) + 91 is 281", "a": 88, "b": 102, "c": 91, "op1": "+", "op2": "+", "result": 281}
{"question": "Solve: (120.37 * 76) + 127", "answer": "The result of (120.37 * 76) + 127 is 9275.12", "a": 120.37, "b": 76, "c": 127, "op1": "*", "op2": "+", "result": 9275.12}
{"question": "Solve: (130 - 195) - 161", "answer": "The result of (130 - 195) - 161 is -226", "a": 130, "b": 195, "c": 161, "op1": "-", "op2": "-", "result": -226}
{"question": "Solve: (61.27 / 160) - 119", "answer": "The result of (61.27 / 160) - 119 is -118.62", "a": 61.27, "b": 160, "c": 119, "op1": "/", "op2": "-", "result": -118.62}
{"question": "Solve: (81 - 19) / 183.59", "answer": "The result of (81 - 19) / 183.59 is 0.34", "a": 81, "b": 19, "c": 183.59, "op1": "-", "op2": "/", "result": 0.34}
{"question": "Solve: (52.78 * 11) + 1", "answer": "The result of (52.78 * 11) + 1 is 581.58", "a": 52.78, "b": 11, "c": 1, "op1": "*", "op2": "+", "result": 581.58}
{"question": "Solve: (8 / 45.03) + 114.97", "answer": "The result of (8 / 45.03) + 114.97 is 115.15", "a": 8, "b": 45.03, "c": 114.97, "op1": "/", "op2": "+", "result": 115.15}
{"question": "Solve: (116.05 / 171) * 91", "answer": "The result of (116.05 / 171) * 91 is 61.76", "a": 116.05, "b": 171, "c": 91, "op1": "/", "op2": "*", "result": 61.76}
{"question": "Solve: (199 - 68) + 162", "answer": "The result of (199 - 68) + 162 is 293", "a": 199, "b": 68, "c": 162, "op1": "-", "op2": "+", "result": 293}
{"question": "Solve: (126 * 42.55) + 163", "answer": "The result of (126 * 42.55) + 163 is 5524.3", "a": 126, "b": 42.55, "c": 163, "op1": "*", "op2": "+", "result": 5524.3}
{"question": "Solve: (120 * 145) + 90", "answer": "The result of (120 * 145) + 90 is 17490", "a": 120, "b": 145, "c": 90, "op1": "*", "op2": "+", "result": 17490}
{"question": "Solve: (172 * 170) - 8", "answer": "The result of (172 * 170) - 8 is 29232", "a": 172, "b": 170, "c": 8, "op1": "*", "op2": "-", "result": 29232}
{"question": "Solve: (109.93 + 123.3) + 49", "answer": "The result of (109.93 + 123.3) + 49 is 282.23", "a": 109.93, "b": 123.3, "c": 49, "op1": "+", "op2": "+", "result": 282.23}
{"question": "Solve: (114 - 134) * 106", "answer": "The result of (114 - 134) * 106 is -2120", "a": 114, "b": 134, "c": 106, "op1": "-", "op2": "*", "result": -2120}
{"question": "Solve: (87 - 147) - 26", "answer": "The result of (87 - 147) - 26 is -86", "a": 87, "b": 147, "c": 26, "op1": "-", "op2": "-", "result": -86}
{"question": "Solve: (78 - 131) * 99.65", "answer": "The result of (78 - 131) * 99.65 is -5281.45", "a": 78, "b": 131, "c": 99.65, "op1": "-", "op2": "*", "result": -5281.45}
{"question": "Solve: (187 / 90) * 149", "answer": "The result of (187 / 90) * 149 is 309.59", "a": 187, "b": 90, "c": 149, "op1": "/", "op2": "*", "result": 309.59}
{"question": "Solve: (36 + 143) + 157.69", "answer": "The result of (36 + 143) + 157.69 is 336.69", "a": 36, "b": 143, "c": 157.69, "op1": "+", "op2": "+", "result": 336.69}
{"question": "Solve: (55 / 138) * 193", "answer": "The result of (55 / 138) * 193 is 76.92", "a": 55, "b": 138, "c": 193, "op1": "/", "op2": "*", "result": 76.92}
{"question": "Solve: (118.58 - 28) / 93", "answer": "The result of (118.58 - 28) / 93 is 0.97", "a": 118.58, "b": 28, "c": 93, "op1": "-", "op2": "/", "result": 0.97}
{"question": "Solve: (107 + 165) + 97.3", "answer": "The result of (107 + 165) + 97.3 is 369.3", "a": 107, "b": 165, "c": 97.3, "op1": "+", "op2": "+", "result": 369.3}
{"question": "Solve: (193 + 61) * 99", "answer": "The result of (193 + 61) * 99 is 25146", "a": 193, "b": 61, "c": 99, "op1": "+", "op2": "*", "result": 25146}
{"question": "Solve: (185 - 186) + 23", "answer": "The result of (185 - 186) + 23 is 22", "a": 185, "b": 186, "c": 23, "op1": "-", "op2": "+", "result": 22}
{"question": "Solve: (97 + 13) + 50", "answer": "The result of (97 + 13) + 50 is 160", "a": 97, "b": 13, "c": 50, "op1": "+", "op2": "+", "result": 160}
{"question": "Solve: (74.0 - 105) - 108", "answer": "The result of (74.0 - 105) - 108 is -139.0", "a": 74.0, "b": 105, "c": 108, "op1": "-", "op2": "-", "result": -139.0}
{"question": "Solve: (12.6 - 54.7) / 150", "answer": "The result of (12.6 - 54.7) / 150 is -0.28", "a": 12.6, "b": 54.7, "c": 150, "op1": "-", "op2": "/", "result": -0.28}
{"question": "Solve: (10 + 80) + 179.95", "answer": "The result of (10 + 80) + 179.95 is 269.95", "a": 10, "b": 80, "c": 179.95, "op1": "+", "op2": "+", "result": 269.95}
{"question": "Solve: (109 / 56.56) - 192.49", "answer": "The result of (109 / 56.56) - 192.49 is -190.56", "a": 109, "b": 56.56, "c": 192.49, "op1": "/", "op2": "-", "result": -190.56}
{"question": "Solve: (178.82 / 99) - 177.49", "answer": "The result of (178.82 / 99) - 177.49 is -175.68", "a": 178.82, "b": 99, "c": 177.49, "op1": "/", "op2": "-", "result": -175.68}
{"question": "Solve: (16 + 195) * 96", "answer": "The result of (16 + 195) * 96 is 20256", "a": 16, "b": 195, "c": 96, "op1": "+", "op2": "*", "result": 20256}
{"question": "Solve: (107 - 135.15) + 38", "answer": "The result of (107 - 135.15) + 38 is 9.85", "a": 107, "b": 135.15, "c": 38, "op1": "-", "op2": "+", "result": 9.85}
{"question": "Solve: (13 + 187) + 9", "answer": "The result of (13 + 187) + 9 is 209", "a": 13, "b": 187, "c": 9, "op1": "+", "op2": "+", "result": 209}
{"question": "Solve: (95 - 151.63) * 79", "answer": "The result of (95 - 151.63) * 79 is -4473.77", "a": 95, "b": 151.63, "c": 79, "op1": "-", "op2": "*", "result": -4473.77}
{"question": "Solve: (120 + 143.75) * 130", "answer": "The result of (120 + 143.75) * 130 is 34287.5", "a": 120, "b": 143.75, "c": 130, "op1": "+", "op2": "*", "result": 34287.5}
{"question": "Solve: (164 + 126.93) + 135", "answer": "The result of (164 + 126.93) + 135 is 425.93", "a": 164, "b": 126.93, "c": 135, "op1": "+", "op2": "+", "result": 425.93}
{"question": "Solve: (116 - 155) - 140", "answer": "The result of (116 - 155) - 140 is -179", "a": 116, "b": 155, "c": 140, "op1": "-", "op2": "-", "result": -179}
{"question": "Solve: (127 / 164) - 140", "answer": "The result of (127 / 164) - 140 is -139.23", "a": 127, "b": 164, "c": 140, "op1": "/", "op2": "-", "result": -139.23}
{"question": "Solve: (19.94 - 38) + 19", "answer": "The result of (19.94 - 38) + 19 is 0.94", "a": 19.94, "b": 38, "c": 19, "op1": "-", "op2": "+", "result": 0.94}
{"question": "Solve: (86 + 27) - 174", "answer": "The result of (86 + 27) - 174 is -61", "a": 86, "b": 27, "c": 174, "op1": "+", "op2": "-", "result": -61}
{"question": "Solve: (54 + 38) + 160", "answer": "The result of (54 + 38) + 160 is 252", "a": 54, "b": 38, "c": 160, "op1": "+", "op2": "+", "result": 252}
{"question": "Solve: (185 - 78.47) * 195.31", "answer": "The result of (185 - 78.47) * 195.31 is 20806.37", "a": 185, "b": 78.47, "c": 195.31, "op1": "-", "op2": "*", "result": 20806.37}
{"question": "Solve: (28 / 134) + 148", "answer": "The result of (28 / 134) + 148 is 148.21", "a": 28, "b": 134, "c": 148, "op1": "/", "op2": "+", "result": 148.21}
{"question": "Solve: (70 - 25.95) + 195", "answer": "The result of (70 - 25.95) + 195 is 239.05", "a": 70, "b": 25.95, "c": 195, "op1": "-", "op2": "+", "result": 239.05}
{"question": "Solve: (177 + 150) + 77", "answer": "The result of (177 + 150) + 77 is 404", "a": 177, "b": 150, "c": 77, "op1": "+", "op2": "+", "result": 404}
{"question": "Solve: (187 / 92.65) * 77", "answer": "The result of (187 / 92.65) * 77 is 155.41", "a": 187, "b": 92.65, "c": 77, "op1": "/", "op2": "*", "result": 155.41}
{"question": "Solve: (100.4 / 68) * 117.47", "answer": "The result of (100.4 / 68) * 117.47 is 173.44", "a": 100.4, "b": 68, "c": 117.47, "op1": "/", "op2": "*", "result": 173.44}
{"question": "Solve: (14.43 - 117) * 77", "answer": "The result of (14.43 - 117) * 77 is -7897.89", "a": 14.43, "b": 117, "c": 77, "op1": "-", "op2": "*", "result": -7897.89}
{"question": "Solve: (127 / 159.57) - 91.21", "answer": "The result of (127 / 159.57) - 91.21 is -90.41", "a": 127, "b": 159.57, "c": 91.21, "op1": "/", "op2": "-", "result": -90.41}
{"question": "Solve: (198 / 191.17) / 45", "answer": "The result of (198 / 191.17) / 45 is 0.02", "a": 198, "b": 191.17, "c": 45, "op1": "/", "op2": "/", "result": 0.02}
{"question": "Solve: (13 + 85) - 76", "answer": "The result of (13 + 85) - 76 is 22", "a": 13, "b": 85, "c": 76, "op1": "+", "op2": "-", "result": 22}
{"question": "Solve: (166 * 16.73) * 175.92", "answer": "The result of (166 * 16.73) * 175.92 is 488561.51", "a": 166, "b": 16.73, "c": 175.92, "op1": "*", "op2": "*", "result": 488561.51}
{"question": "Solve: (169 - 90.28) - 196", "answer": "The result of (169 - 90.28) - 196 is -117.28", "a": 169, "b": 90.28, "c": 196, "op1": "-", "op2": "-", "result": -117.28}
{"question": "Solve: (37.31 - 70.9) * 181", "answer": "The result of (37.31 - 70.9) * 181 is -6079.79", "a": 37.31, "b": 70.9, "c": 181, "op1": "-", "op2": "*", "result": -6079.79}
{"question": "Solve: (191.78 + 7) + 142", "answer": "The result of (191.78 + 7) + 142 is 340.78", "a": 191.78, "b": 7, "c": 142, "op1": "+", "op2": "+", "result": 340.78}
{"question": "Solve: (27 / 160.46) - 193", "answer": "The result of (27 / 160.46) - 193 is -192.83", "a": 27, "b": 160.46, "c": 193, "op1": "/", "op2": "-", "result": -192.83}
{"question": "Solve: (64 * 106.62) - 86.65", "answer": "The result of (64 * 106.62) - 86.65 is 6737.03", "a": 64, "b": 106.62, "c": 86.65, "op1": "*", "op2": "-", "result": 6737.03}
{"question": "Solve: (172.09 + 171) - 103", "answer": "The result of (172.09 + 171) - 103 is 240.09", "a": 172.09, "b": 171, "c": 103, "op1": "+", "op2": "-", "result": 240.09}
{"question": "Solve: (118 + 155.63) * 104", "answer": "The result of (118 + 155.63) * 104 is 28457.52", "a": 118, "b": 155.63, "c": 104, "op1": "+", "op2": "*", "result": 28457.52}
{"question": "Solve: (93 * 66) + 45", "answer": "The result of (93 * 66) + 45 is 6183", "a": 93, "b": 66, "c": 45, "op1": "*", "op2": "+", "result": 6183}
{"question": "Solve: (75 - 162.27) / 67", "answer": "The result of (75 - 162.27) / 67 is -1.3", "a": 75, "b": 162.27, "c": 67, "op1": "-", "op2": "/", "result": -1.3}
{"question": "Solve: (190 * 136) / 192.23", "answer": "The result of (190 * 136) / 192.23 is 134.42", "a": 190, "b": 136, "c": 192.23, "op1": "*", "op2": "/", "result": 134.42}
{"question": "Solve: (58 - 163) + 89", "answer": "The result of (58 - 163) + 89 is -16", "a": 58, "b": 163, "c": 89, "op1": "-", "op2": "+", "result": -16}
{"question": "Solve: (35.57 + 68) + 77.83", "answer": "The result of (35.57 + 68) + 77.83 is 181.4", "a": 35.57, "b": 68, "c": 77.83, "op1": "+", "op2": "+", "result": 181.4}
{"question": "Solve: (125.41 + 10) + 118", "answer": "The result of (125.41 + 10) + 118 is 253.41", "a": 125.41, "b": 10, "c": 118, "op1": "+", "op2": "+", "result": 253.41}
{"question": "Solve: (45 / 175) * 20", "answer": "The result of (45 / 175) * 20 is 5.14", "a": 45, "b": 175, "c": 20, "op1": "/", "op2": "*", "result": 5.14}
{"question": "Solve: (56.38 + 80) - 120", "answer": "The result of (56.38 + 80) - 120 is 16.38", "a": 56.38, "b": 80, "c": 120, "op1": "+", "op2": "-", "result": 16.38}
{"question": "Solve: (13 / 153) / 35", "answer": "The result of (13 / 153) / 35 is 0.0", "a": 13, "b": 153, "c": 35, "op1": "/", "op2": "/", "result": 0.0}
{"question": "Solve: (51.15 + 164) + 194", "answer": "The result of (51.15 + 164) + 194 is 409.15", "a": 51.15, "b": 164, "c": 194, "op1": "+", "op2": "+", "result": 409.15}
{"question": "Solve: (13 - 107.91) * 16.34", "answer": "The result of (13 - 107.91) * 16.34 is -1550.83", "a": 13, "b": 107.91, "c": 16.34, "op1": "-", "op2": "*", "result": -1550.83}
{"question": "Solve: (12 * 115.32) - 128.41", "answer": "The result of (12 * 115.32) - 128.41 is 1255.43", "a": 12, "b": 115.32, "c": 128.41, "op1": "*", "op2": "-", "result": 1255.43}
{"question": "Solve: (21 / 71.74) * 63", "answer": "The result of (21 / 71.74) * 63 is 18.44", "a": 21, "b": 71.74, "c": 63, "op1": "/", "op2": "*", "result": 18.44}
{"question": "Solve: (57 * 35) - 15.99", "answer": "The result of (57 * 35) - 15.99 is 1979.01", "a": 57, "b": 35, "c": 15.99, "op1": "*", "op2": "-", "result": 1979.01}
{"question": "Solve: (62 + 16.02) * 145.36", "answer": "The result of (62 + 16.02) * 145.36 is 11340.99", "a": 62, "b": 16.02, "c": 145.36, "op1": "+", "op2": "*", "result": 11340.99}
{"question": "Solve: (2.04 - 2.44) + 90.1", "answer": "The result of (2.04 - 2.44) + 90.1 is 89.7", "a": 2.04, "b": 2.44, "c": 90.1, "op1": "-", "op2": "+", "result": 89.7}
{"question": "Solve: (76.85 / 195.07) + 13.84", "answer": "The result of (76.85 / 195.07) + 13.84 is 14.23", "a": 76.85, "b": 195.07, "c": 13.84, "op1": "/", "op2": "+", "result": 14.23}
{"question": "Solve: (2 - 125.24) + 108", "answer": "The result of (2 - 125.24) + 108 is -15.24", "a": 2, "b": 125.24, "c": 108, "op1": "-", "op2": "+", "result": -15.24}
{"question": "Solve: (33 + 137) - 18", "answer": "The result of (33 + 137) - 18 is 152", "a": 33, "b": 137, "c": 18, "op1": "+", "op2": "-", "result": 152}
{"question": "Solve: (94 - 113.97) * 169", "answer": "The result of (94 - 113.97) * 169 is -3374.93", "a": 94, "b": 113.97, "c": 169, "op1": "-", "op2": "*", "result": -3374.93}
{"question": "Solve: (125 - 45) * 88.81", "answer": "The result of (125 - 45) * 88.81 is 7104.8", "a": 125, "b": 45, "c": 88.81, "op1": "-", "op2": "*", "result": 7104.8}
{"question": "Solve: (146 - 61) * 191", "answer": "The result of (146 - 61) * 191 is 16235", "a": 146, "b": 61, "c": 191, "op1": "-", "op2": "*", "result": 16235}
{"question": "Solve: (194 * 187) - 7.11", "answer": "The result of (194 * 187) - 7.11 is 36270.89", "a": 194, "b": 187, "c": 7.11, "op1": "*", "op2": "-", "result": 36270.89}
{"question": "Solve: (23 * 172) * 2", "answer": "The result of (23 * 172) * 2 is 7912", "a": 23, "b": 172, "c": 2, "op1": "*", "op2": "*", "result": 7912}
{"question": "Solve: (24 - 20) - 14", "answer": "The result of (24 - 20) - 14 is -10", "a": 24, "b": 20, "c": 14, "op1": "-", "op2": "-", "result": -10}
{"question": "Solve: (21 / 46.59) + 78", "answer": "The result of (21 / 46.59) + 78 is 78.45", "a": 21, "b": 46.59, "c": 78, "op1": "/", "op2": "+", "result": 78.45}
{"question": "Solve: (78.11 + 36.66) - 17", "answer": "The result of (78.11 + 36.66) - 17 is 97.77", "a": 78.11, "b": 36.66, "c": 17, "op1": "+", "op2": "-", "result": 97.77}
{"question": "Solve: (142.53 + 56) * 161.69", "answer": "The result of (142.53 + 56) * 161.69 is 32100.32", "a": 142.53, "b": 56, "c": 161.69, "op1": "+", "op2": "*", "result": 32100.32}
{"question": "Solve: (131 - 185.0) + 180", "answer": "The result of (131 - 185.0) + 180 is 126.0", "a": 131, "b": 185.0, "c": 180, "op1": "-", "op2": "+", "result": 126.0}
{"question": "Solve: (42 + 131.06) + 191", "answer": "The result of (42 + 131.06) + 191 is 364.06", "a": 42, "b": 131.06, "c": 191, "op1": "+", "op2": "+", "result": 364.06}
{"question": "Solve: (48.37 * 14) + 21", "answer": "The result of (48.37 * 14) + 21 is 698.18", "a": 48.37, "b": 14, "c": 21, "op1": "*", "op2": "+", "result": 698.18}
{"question": "Solve: (8 * 198) - 85.52", "answer": "The result of (8 * 198) - 85.52 is 1498.48", "a": 8, "b": 198, "c": 85.52, "op1": "*", "op2": "-", "result": 1498.48}
{"question": "Solve: (182.8 + 73.0) + 83.19", "answer": "The result of (182.8 + 73.0) + 83.19 is 338.99", "a": 182.8, "b": 73.0, "c": 83.19, "op1": "+", "op2": "+", "result": 338.99}
{"question": "Solve: (135.78 - 181.57) - 147", "answer": "The result of (135.78 - 181.57) - 147 is -192.79", "a": 135.78, "b": 181.57, "c": 147, "op1": "-", "op2": "-", "result": -192.79}
{"question": "Solve: (63 / 77.68) - 129", "answer": "The result of (63 / 77.68) - 129 is -128.19", "a": 63, "b": 77.68, "c": 129, "op1": "/", "op2": "-", "result": -128.19}
{"question": "Solve: (61 / 122) + 3", "answer": "The result of (61 / 122) + 3 is 3.5", "a": 61, "b": 122, "c": 3, "op1": "/", "op2": "+", "result": 3.5}
{"question": "Solve: (44.3 + 19) + 38.52", "answer": "The result of (44.3 + 19) + 38.52 is 101.82", "a": 44.3, "b": 19, "c": 38.52, "op1": "+", "op2": "+", "result": 101.82}
{"question": "Solve: (152 / 169.04) - 100", "answer": "The result of (152 / 169.04) - 100 is -99.1", "a": 152, "b": 169.04, "c": 100, "op1": "/", "op2": "-", "result": -99.1}
{"question": "Solve: (40.01 * 194.23) / 157", "answer": "The result of (40.01 * 194.23) / 157 is 49.5", "a": 40.01, "b": 194.23, "c": 157, "op1": "*", "op2": "/", "result": 49.5}
{"question": "Solve: (172 * 70) / 168", "answer": "The result of (172 * 70) / 168 is 71.67", "a": 172, "b": 70, "c": 168, "op1": "*", "op2": "/", "result": 71.67}
{"question": "Solve: (18 + 83.33) - 63", "answer": "The result of (18 + 83.33) - 63 is 38.33", "a": 18, "b": 83.33, "c": 63, "op1": "+", "op2": "-", "result": 38.33}
{"question": "Solve: (54.75 - 188) * 111", "answer": "The result of (54.75 - 188) * 111 is -14790.75", "a": 54.75, "b": 188, "c": 111, "op1": "-", "op2": "*", "result": -14790.75}
{"question": "Solve: (149 - 131.3) - 159.52", "answer": "The result of (149 - 131.3) - 159.52 is -141.82", "a": 149, "b": 131.3, "c": 159.52, "op1": "-", "op2": "-", "result": -141.82}
{"question": "Solve: (93 / 19.1) * 78.55", "answer": "The result of (93 / 19.1) * 78.55 is 382.47", "a": 93, "b": 19.1, "c": 78.55, "op1": "/", "op2": "*", "result": 382.47}
{"question": "Solve: (135 - 48) / 132", "answer": "The result of (135 - 48) / 132 is 0.66", "a": 135, "b": 48, "c": 132, "op1": "-", "op2": "/", "result": 0.66}
{"question": "Solve: (34 + 61.25) - 62", "answer": "The result of (34 + 61.25) - 62 is 33.25", "a": 34, "b": 61.25, "c": 62, "op1": "+", "op2": "-", "result": 33.25}
{"question": "Solve: (148.89 + 45) + 51", "answer": "The result of (148.89 + 45) + 51 is 244.89", "a": 148.89, "b": 45, "c": 51, "op1": "+", "op2": "+", "result": 244.89}
{"question": "Solve: (148 + 137) + 99.64", "answer": "The result of (148 + 137) + 99.64 is 384.64", "a": 148, "b": 137, "c": 99.64, "op1": "+", "op2": "+", "result": 384.64}
{"question": "Solve: (113 + 13) + 84", "answer": "The result of (113 + 13) + 84 is 210", "a": 113, "b": 13, "c": 84, "op1": "+", "op2": "+", "result": 210}
{"question": "Solve: (125.95 + 142) - 108", "answer": "The result of (125.95 + 142) - 108 is 159.95", "a": 125.95, "b": 142, "c": 108, "op1": "+", "op2": "-", "result": 159.95}
{"question": "Solve: (182.64 - 43) * 5", "answer": "The result of (182.64 - 43) * 5 is 698.2", "a": 182.64, "b": 43, "c": 5, "op1": "-", "op2": "*", "result": 698.2}
{"question": "Solve: (20 / 26.0) * 11", "answer": "The result of (20 / 26.0) * 11 is 8.46", "a": 20, "b": 26.0, "c": 11, "op1": "/", "op2": "*", "result": 8.46}
{"question": "Solve: (46 * 59) + 1", "answer": "The result of (46 * 59) + 1 is 2715", "a": 46, "b": 59, "c": 1, "op1": "*", "op2": "+", "result": 2715}
{"question": "Solve: (5.1 + 153) - 167", "answer": "The result of (5.1 + 153) - 167 is -8.9", "a": 5.1, "b": 153, "c": 167, "op1": "+", "op2": "-", "result": -8.9}
{"question": "Solve: (165.97 * 38.97) * 53", "answer": "The result of (165.97 * 38.97) * 53 is 342796.1", "a": 165.97, "b": 38.97, "c": 53, "op1": "*", "op2": "*", "result": 342796.1}
{"question": "Solve: (101.27 * 8.87) / 121", "answer": "The result of (101.27 * 8.87) / 121 is 7.42", "a": 101.27, "b": 8.87, "c": 121, "op1": "*", "op2": "/", "result": 7.42}
{"question": "Solve: (73 + 27) - 138", "answer": "The result of (73 + 27) - 138 is -38", "a": 73, "b": 27, "c": 138, "op1": "+", "op2": "-", "result": -38}
{"question": "Solve: (148 + 85) + 92.67", "answer": "The result of (148 + 85) + 92.67 is 325.67", "a": 148, "b": 85, "c": 92.67, "op1": "+", "op2": "+", "result": 325.67}
{"question": "Solve: (191 + 148.14) - 52", "answer": "The result of (191 + 148.14) - 52 is 287.14", "a": 191, "b": 148.14, "c": 52, "op1": "+", "op2": "-", "result": 287.14}
{"question": "Solve: (141 * 181) * 12.17", "answer": "The result of (141 * 181) * 12.17 is 310590.57", "a": 141, "b": 181, "c": 12.17, "op1": "*", "op2": "*", "result": 310590.57}
{"question": "Solve: (39 * 12.63) * 158", "answer": "The result of (39 * 12.63) * 158 is 77826.06", "a": 39, "b": 12.63, "c": 158, "op1": "*", "op2": "*", "result": 77826.06}
{"question": "Solve: (148 * 200) + 46", "answer": "The result of (148 * 200) + 46 is 29646", "a": 148, "b": 200, "c": 46, "op1": "*", "op2": "+", "result": 29646}
{"question": "Solve: (198.17 - 154.13) * 160", "answer": "The result of (198.17 - 154.13) * 160 is 7046.4", "a": 198.17, "b": 154.13, "c": 160, "op1": "-", "op2": "*", "result": 7046.4}
{"question": "Solve: (181 / 126) + 83", "answer": "The result of (181 / 126) + 83 is 84.44", "a": 181, "b": 126, "c": 83, "op1": "/", "op2": "+", "result": 84.44}
{"question": "Solve: (191 / 147) * 122", "answer": "The result of (191 / 147) * 122 is 158.52", "a": 191, "b": 147, "c": 122, "op1": "/", "op2": "*", "result": 158.52}
{"question": "Solve: (150 - 92) - 6", "answer": "The result of (150 - 92) - 6 is 52", "a": 150, "b": 92, "c": 6, "op1": "-", "op2": "-", "result": 52}
{"question": "Solve: (34.31 * 108) + 91", "answer": "The result of (34.31 * 108) + 91 is 3796.48", "a": 34.31, "b": 108, "c": 91, "op1": "*", "op2": "+", "result": 3796.48}
{"question": "Solve: (191 / 62) + 183", "answer": "The result of (191 / 62) + 183 is 186.08", "a": 191, "b": 62, "c": 183, "op1": "/", "op2": "+", "result": 186.08}
{"question": "Solve: (22 + 146.13) * 137", "answer": "The result of (22 + 146.13) * 137 is 23033.81", "a": 22, "b": 146.13, "c": 137, "op1": "+", "op2": "*", "result": 23033.81}
{"question": "Solve: (105.59 - 154) * 5", "answer": "The result of (105.59 - 154) * 5 is -242.05", "a": 105.59, "b": 154, "c": 5, "op1": "-", "op2": "*", "result": -242.05}
{"question": "Solve: (99.23 * 87.98) + 163.99", "answer": "The result of (99.23 * 87.98) + 163.99 is 8894.25", "a": 99.23, "b": 87.98, "c": 163.99, "op1": "*", "op2": "+", "result": 8894.25}
{"question": "Solve: (105 - 133) / 141", "answer": "The result of (105 - 133) / 141 is -0.2", "a": 105, "b": 133, "c": 141, "op1": "-", "op2": "/", "result": -0.2}
{"question": "Solve: (114.6 - 10.18) - 53.59", "answer": "The result of (114.6 - 10.18) - 53.59 is 50.83", "a": 114.6, "b": 10.18, "c": 53.59, "op1": "-", "op2": "-", "result": 50.83}
{"question": "Solve: (94.4 - 59.18) / 17", "answer": "The result of (94.4 - 59.18) / 17 is 2.07", "a": 94.4, "b": 59.18, "c": 17, "op1": "-", "op2": "/", "result": 2.07}
{"question": "Solve: (7 - 164.45) - 55", "answer": "The result of (7 - 164.45) - 55 is -212.45", "a": 7, "b": 164.45, "c": 55, "op1": "-", "op2": "-", "result": -212.45}
{"question": "Solve: (188 - 128) - 49", "answer": "The result of (188 - 128) - 49 is 11", "a": 188, "b": 128, "c": 49, "op1": "-", "op2": "-", "result": 11}
{"question": "Solve: (81.35 + 168.79) - 101", "answer": "The result of (81.35 + 168.79) - 101 is 149.14", "a": 81.35, "b": 168.79, "c": 101, "op1": "+", "op2": "-", "result": 149.14}
{"question": "Solve: (106 * 155) + 4.62", "answer": "The result of (106 * 155) + 4.62 is 16434.62", "a": 106, "b": 155, "c": 4.62, "op1": "*", "op2": "+", "result": 16434.62}
{"question": "Solve: (55 - 72) - 13.61", "answer": "The result of (55 - 72) - 13.61 is -30.61", "a": 55, "b": 72, "c": 13.61, "op1": "-", "op2": "-", "result": -30.61}
{"question": "Solve: (55 * 196) + 60.92", "answer": "The result of (55 * 196) + 60.92 is 10840.92", "a": 55, "b": 196, "c": 60.92, "op1": "*", "op2": "+", "result": 10840.92}
{"question": "Solve: (90.13 * 14) / 172", "answer": "The result of (90.13 * 14) / 172 is 7.34", "a": 90.13, "b": 14, "c": 172, "op1": "*", "op2": "/", "result": 7.34}
{"question": "Solve: (133 * 112.76) * 48.16", "answer": "The result of (133 * 112.76) * 48.16 is 722259.37", "a": 133, "b": 112.76, "c": 48.16, "op1": "*", "op2": "*", "result": 722259.37}
{"question": "Solve: (88 * 93) + 148", "answer": "The result of (88 * 93) + 148 is 8332", "a": 88, "b": 93, "c": 148, "op1": "*", "op2": "+", "result": 8332}
{"question": "Solve: (32 - 196) * 191", "answer": "The result of (32 - 196) * 191 is -31324", "a": 32, "b": 196, "c": 191, "op1": "-", "op2": "*", "result": -31324}
{"question": "Solve: (39 * 102.84) / 11", "answer": "The result of (39 * 102.84) / 11 is 364.61", "a": 39, "b": 102.84, "c": 11, "op1": "*", "op2": "/", "result": 364.61}
{"question": "Solve: (5 + 120) / 189.56", "answer": "The result of (5 + 120) / 189.56 is 0.66", "a": 5, "b": 120, "c": 189.56, "op1": "+", "op2": "/", "result": 0.66}
{"question": "Solve: (15 * 100.5) + 81.23", "answer": "The result of (15 * 100.5) + 81.23 is 1588.73", "a": 15, "b": 100.5, "c": 81.23, "op1": "*", "op2": "+", "result": 1588.73}
{"question": "Solve: (28 - 179) + 4", "answer": "The result of (28 - 179) + 4 is -147", "a": 28, "b": 179, "c": 4, "op1": "-", "op2": "+", "result": -147}
{"question": "Solve: (91.18 - 89) + 126.53", "answer": "The result of (91.18 - 89) + 126.53 is 128.71", "a": 91.18, "b": 89, "c": 126.53, "op1": "-", "op2": "+", "result": 128.71}
{"question": "Solve: (3 - 63) + 49.53", "answer": "The result of (3 - 63) + 49.53 is -10.47", "a": 3, "b": 63, "c": 49.53, "op1": "-", "op2": "+", "result": -10.47}
{"question": "Solve: (126.82 * 23.12) - 112", "answer": "The result of (126.82 * 23.12) - 112 is 2820.08", "a": 126.82, "b": 23.12, "c": 112, "op1": "*", "op2": "-", "result": 2820.08}
{"question": "Solve: (74 / 156) + 71.25", "answer": "The result of (74 / 156) + 71.25 is 71.72", "a": 74, "b": 156, "c": 71.25, "op1": "/", "op2": "+", "result": 71.72}
{"question": "Solve: (59 - 7) + 69", "answer": "The result of (59 - 7) + 69 is 121", "a": 59, "b": 7, "c": 69, "op1": "-", "op2": "+", "result": 121}
{"question": "Solve: (89.97 - 62) - 52.82", "answer": "The result of (89.97 - 62) - 52.82 is -24.85", "a": 89.97, "b": 62, "c": 52.82, "op1": "-", "op2": "-", "result": -24.85}
{"question": "Solve: (150.47 * 153.25) + 167", "answer": "The result of (150.47 * 153.25) + 167 is 23226.53", "a": 150.47, "b": 153.25, "c": 167, "op1": "*", "op2": "+", "result": 23226.53}
{"question": "Solve: (3.46 - 35) + 49", "answer": "The result of (3.46 - 35) + 49 is 17.46", "a": 3.46, "b": 35, "c": 49, "op1": "-", "op2": "+", "result": 17.46}
{"question": "Solve: (190 / 104) * 71", "answer": "The result of (190 / 104) * 71 is 129.71", "a": 190, "b": 104, "c": 71, "op1": "/", "op2": "*", "result": 129.71}
{"question": "Solve: (10.34 * 139) * 188", "answer": "The result of (10.34 * 139) * 188 is 270204.88", "a": 10.34, "b": 139, "c": 188, "op1": "*", "op2": "*", "result": 270204.88}
{"question": "Solve: (29 - 165) / 167", "answer": "The result of (29 - 165) / 167 is -0.81", "a": 29, "b": 165, "c": 167, "op1": "-", "op2": "/", "result": -0.81}
{"question": "Solve: (81.15 + 138) - 9", "answer": "The result of (81.15 + 138) - 9 is 210.15", "a": 81.15, "b": 138, "c": 9, "op1": "+", "op2": "-", "result": 210.15}
{"question": "Solve: (151 - 108) * 166", "answer": "The result of (151 - 108) * 166 is 7138", "a": 151, "b": 108, "c": 166, "op1": "-", "op2": "*", "result": 7138}
{"question": "Solve: (156 * 4.06) - 156", "answer": "The result of (156 * 4.06) - 156 is 477.36", "a": 156, "b": 4.06, "c": 156, "op1": "*", "op2": "-", "result": 477.36}
{"question": "Solve: (136.99 + 106.18) - 79", "answer": "The result of (136.99 + 106.18) - 79 is 164.17", "a": 136.99, "b": 106.18, "c": 79, "op1": "+", "op2": "-", "result": 164.17}
{"question": "Solve: (92.2 - 123.08) * 26", "answer": "The result of (92.2 - 123.08) * 26 is -802.88", "a": 92.2, "b": 123.08, "c": 26, "op1": "-", "op2": "*", "result": -802.88}
{"question": "Solve: (93 - 92.63) - 116.1", "answer": "The result of (93 - 92.63) - 116.1 is -115.73", "a": 93, "b": 92.63, "c": 116.1, "op1": "-", "op2": "-", "result": -115.73}
{"question": "Solve: (146.25 + 194.23) - 36", "answer": "The result of (146.25 + 194.23) - 36 is 304.48", "a": 146.25, "b": 194.23, "c": 36, "op1": "+", "op2": "-", "result": 304.48}
{"question": "Solve: (127.81 * 198) * 57", "answer": "The result of (127.81 * 198) * 57 is 1442463.66", "a": 127.81, "b": 198, "c": 57, "op1": "*", "op2": "*", "result": 1442463.66}
{"question": "Solve: (137 + 85) - 71.7", "answer": "The result of (137 + 85) - 71.7 is 150.3", "a": 137, "b": 85, "c": 71.7, "op1": "+", "op2": "-", "result": 150.3}
{"question": "Solve: (81 * 147) * 199", "answer": "The result of (81 * 147) * 199 is 2369493", "a": 81, "b": 147, "c": 199, "op1": "*", "op2": "*", "result": 2369493}
{"question": "Solve: (155 + 32.84) / 149", "answer": "The result of (155 + 32.84) / 149 is 1.26", "a": 155, "b": 32.84, "c": 149, "op1": "+", "op2": "/", "result": 1.26}
{"question": "Solve: (63 - 128) - 162.61", "answer": "The result of (63 - 128) - 162.61 is -227.61", "a": 63, "b": 128, "c": 162.61, "op1": "-", "op2": "-", "result": -227.61}
{"question": "Solve: (154 / 87) * 161", "answer": "The result of (154 / 87) * 161 is 284.99", "a": 154, "b": 87, "c": 161, "op1": "/", "op2": "*", "result": 284.99}
{"question": "Solve: (114.27 * 126) + 181.14", "answer": "The result of (114.27 * 126) + 181.14 is 14579.16", "a": 114.27, "b": 126, "c": 181.14, "op1": "*", "op2": "+", "result": 14579.16}
{"question": "Solve: (82 * 198) * 10", "answer": "The result of (82 * 198) * 10 is 162360", "a": 82, "b": 198, "c": 10, "op1": "*", "op2": "*", "result": 162360}
{"question": "Solve: (146.76 * 136) + 197", "answer": "The result of (146.76 * 136) + 197 is 20156.36", "a": 146.76, "b": 136, "c": 197, "op1": "*", "op2": "+", "result": 20156.36}
{"question": "Solve: (58 - 73) - 179", "answer": "The result of (58 - 73) - 179 is -194", "a": 58, "b": 73, "c": 179, "op1": "-", "op2": "-", "result": -194}
{"question": "Solve: (145 - 15.02) / 22", "answer": "The result of (145 - 15.02) / 22 is 5.91", "a": 145, "b": 15.02, "c": 22, "op1": "-", "op2": "/", "result": 5.91}
{"question": "Solve: (162 * 119) + 103", "answer": "The result of (162 * 119) + 103 is 19381", "a": 162, "b": 119, "c": 103, "op1": "*", "op2": "+", "result": 19381}
{"question": "Solve: (163.59 * 140) * 121.92", "answer": "The result of (163.59 * 140) * 121.92 is 2792284.99", "a": 163.59, "b": 140, "c": 121.92, "op1": "*", "op2": "*", "result": 2792284.99}
{"question": "Solve: (188.41 + 188) + 22.99", "answer": "The result of (188.41 + 188) + 22.99 is 399.4", "a": 188.41, "b": 188, "c": 22.99, "op1": "+", "op2": "+", "result": 399.4}
{"question": "Solve: (14 + 137.64) * 67", "answer": "The result of (14 + 137.64) * 67 is 10159.88", "a": 14, "b": 137.64, "c": 67, "op1": "+", "op2": "*", "result": 10159.88}
{"question": "Solve: (143.71 + 98) - 186", "answer": "The result of (143.71 + 98) - 186 is 55.71", "a": 143.71, "b": 98, "c": 186, "op1": "+", "op2": "-", "result": 55.71}
{"question": "Solve: (77.32 + 57.89) - 179.91", "answer": "The result of (77.32 + 57.89) - 179.91 is -44.7", "a": 77.32, "b": 57.89, "c": 179.91, "op1": "+", "op2": "-", "result": -44.7}
{"question": "Solve: (195 - 85) * 97.1", "answer": "The result of (195 - 85) * 97.1 is 10681.0", "a": 195, "b": 85, "c": 97.1, "op1": "-", "op2": "*", "result": 10681.0}
{"question": "Solve: (184.74 + 72) - 15", "answer": "The result of (184.74 + 72) - 15 is 241.74", "a": 184.74, "b": 72, "c": 15, "op1": "+", "op2": "-", "result": 241.74}
{"question": "Solve: (195.12 - 38) * 13.69", "answer": "The result of (195.12 - 38) * 13.69 is 2150.97", "a": 195.12, "b": 38, "c": 13.69, "op1": "-", "op2": "*", "result": 2150.97}
{"question": "Solve: (198 - 66) + 168.82", "answer": "The result of (198 - 66) + 168.82 is 300.82", "a": 198, "b": 66, "c": 168.82, "op1": "-", "op2": "+", "result": 300.82}
{"question": "Solve: (74.86 * 172) - 23", "answer": "The result of (74.86 * 172) - 23 is 12852.92", "a": 74.86, "b": 172, "c": 23, "op1": "*", "op2": "-", "result": 12852.92}
{"question": "Solve: (140.75 - 150.86) + 155.0", "answer": "The result of (140.75 - 150.86) + 155.0 is 144.89", "a": 140.75, "b": 150.86, "c": 155.0, "op1": "-", "op2": "+", "result": 144.89}
{"question": "Solve: (89 - 151) - 79", "answer": "The result of (89 - 151) - 79 is -141", "a": 89, "b": 151, "c": 79, "op1": "-", "op2": "-", "result": -141}
{"question": "Solve: (139 * 161) + 176", "answer": "The result of (139 * 161) + 176 is 22555", "a": 139, "b": 161, "c": 176, "op1": "*", "op2": "+", "result": 22555}
{"question": "Solve: (12 * 56.89) + 84", "answer": "The result of (12 * 56.89) + 84 is 766.68", "a": 12, "b": 56.89, "c": 84, "op1": "*", "op2": "+", "result": 766.68}
{"question": "Solve: (200 / 10) * 42.03", "answer": "The result of (200 / 10) * 42.03 is 840.6", "a": 200, "b": 10, "c": 42.03, "op1": "/", "op2": "*", "result": 840.6}
{"question": "Solve: (186 / 11.28) - 166.06", "answer": "The result of (186 / 11.28) - 166.06 is -149.57", "a": 186, "b": 11.28, "c": 166.06, "op1": "/", "op2": "-", "result": -149.57}
{"question": "Solve: (27.79 / 157) - 119", "answer": "The result of (27.79 / 157) - 119 is -118.82", "a": 27.79, "b": 157, "c": 119, "op1": "/", "op2": "-", "result": -118.82}
{"question": "Solve: (140 + 56) * 154", "answer": "The result of (140 + 56) * 154 is 30184", "a": 140, "b": 56, "c": 154, "op1": "+", "op2": "*", "result": 30184}
{"question": "Solve: (75 / 28) * 46", "answer": "The result of (75 / 28) * 46 is 123.21", "a": 75, "b": 28, "c": 46, "op1": "/", "op2": "*", "result": 123.21}
{"question": "Solve: (13.17 + 139.74) + 72.7", "answer": "The result of (13.17 + 139.74) + 72.7 is 225.61", "a": 13.17, "b": 139.74, "c": 72.7, "op1": "+", "op2": "+", "result": 225.61}
{"question": "Solve: (61.42 * 8) - 133", "answer": "The result of (61.42 * 8) - 133 is 358.36", "a": 61.42, "b": 8, "c": 133, "op1": "*", "op2": "-", "result": 358.36}
{"question": "Solve: (146 * 89) * 189.8", "answer": "The result of (146 * 89) * 189.8 is 2466261.2", "a": 146, "b": 89, "c": 189.8, "op1": "*", "op2": "*", "result": 2466261.2}
{"question": "Solve: (3 * 195) - 186", "answer": "The result of (3 * 195) - 186 is 399", "a": 3, "b": 195, "c": 186, "op1": "*", "op2": "-", "result": 399}
{"question": "Solve: (78 - 159.19) - 75", "answer": "The result of (78 - 159.19) - 75 is -156.19", "a": 78, "b": 159.19, "c": 75, "op1": "-", "op2": "-", "result": -156.19}
{"question": "Solve: (74.7 + 53) - 20", "answer": "The result of (74.7 + 53) - 20 is 107.7", "a": 74.7, "b": 53, "c": 20, "op1": "+", "op2": "-", "result": 107.7}
{"question": "Solve: (16 / 42) / 25", "answer": "The result of (16 / 42) / 25 is 0.02", "a": 16, "b": 42, "c": 25, "op1": "/", "op2": "/", "result": 0.02}
{"question": "Solve: (85 * 66.36) - 96.37", "answer": "The result of (85 * 66.36) - 96.37 is 5544.23", "a": 85, "b": 66.36, "c": 96.37, "op1": "*", "op2": "-", "result": 5544.23}
{"question": "Solve: (104.63 / 156) - 77", "answer": "The result of (104.63 / 156) - 77 is -76.33", "a": 104.63, "b": 156, "c": 77, "op1": "/", "op2": "-", "result": -76.33}
{"question": "Solve: (2 / 87) - 148", "answer": "The result of (2 / 87) - 148 is -147.98", "a": 2, "b": 87, "c": 148, "op1": "/", "op2": "-", "result": -147.98}
{"question": "Solve: (99 / 69.79) - 106.64", "answer": "The result of (99 / 69.79) - 106.64 is -105.22", "a": 99, "b": 69.79, "c": 106.64, "op1": "/", "op2": "-", "result": -105.22}
{"question": "Solve: (38 * 113) + 62", "answer": "The result of (38 * 113) + 62 is 4356", "a": 38, "b": 113, "c": 62, "op1": "*", "op2": "+", "result": 4356}
{"question": "Solve: (185 + 188) * 151", "answer": "The result of (185 + 188) * 151 is 56323", "a": 185, "b": 188, "c": 151, "op1": "+", "op2": "*", "result": 56323}
{"question": "Solve: (60 - 18) * 28", "answer": "The result of (60 - 18) * 28 is 1176", "a": 60, "b": 18, "c": 28, "op1": "-", "op2": "*", "result": 1176}
{"question": "Solve: (25 * 1) * 112", "answer": "The result of (25 * 1) * 112 is 2800", "a": 25, "b": 1, "c": 112, "op1": "*", "op2": "*", "result": 2800}
{"question": "Solve: (24 * 48) - 134", "answer": "The result of (24 * 48) - 134 is 1018", "a": 24, "b": 48, "c": 134, "op1": "*", "op2": "-", "result": 1018}
{"question": "Solve: (118 - 164) / 18.49", "answer": "The result of (118 - 164) / 18.49 is -2.49", "a": 118, "b": 164, "c": 18.49, "op1": "-", "op2": "/", "result": -2.49}
{"question": "Solve: (137.8 - 52) - 183.9", "answer": "The result of (137.8 - 52) - 183.9 is -98.1", "a": 137.8, "b": 52, "c": 183.9, "op1": "-", "op2": "-", "result": -98.1}
{"question": "Solve: (19 - 3) * 31.16", "answer": "The result of (19 - 3) * 31.16 is 498.56", "a": 19, "b": 3, "c": 31.16, "op1": "-", "op2": "*", "result": 498.56}
{"question": "Solve: (145.22 - 9) - 4.96", "answer": "The result of (145.22 - 9) - 4.96 is 131.26", "a": 145.22, "b": 9, "c": 4.96, "op1": "-", "op2": "-", "result": 131.26}
{"question": "Solve: (31 * 103.53) - 172", "answer": "The result of (31 * 103.53) - 172 is 3037.43", "a": 31, "b": 103.53, "c": 172, "op1": "*", "op2": "-", "result": 3037.43}
{"question": "Solve: (15 - 189.3) - 92", "answer": "The result of (15 - 189.3) - 92 is -266.3", "a": 15, "b": 189.3, "c": 92, "op1": "-", "op2": "-", "result": -266.3}
{"question": "Solve: (129 - 72.68) - 151.27", "answer": "The result of (129 - 72.68) - 151.27 is -94.95", "a": 129, "b": 72.68, "c": 151.27, "op1": "-", "op2": "-", "result": -94.95}
{"question": "Solve: (65 - 74) * 99", "answer": "The result of (65 - 74) * 99 is -891", "a": 65, "b": 74, "c": 99, "op1": "-", "op2": "*", "result": -891}
{"question": "Solve: (49 - 158) - 80.41", "answer": "The result of (49 - 158) - 80.41 is -189.41", "a": 49, "b": 158, "c": 80.41, "op1": "-", "op2": "-", "result": -189.41}
{"question": "Solve: (40.45 / 176) - 175", "answer": "The result of (40.45 / 176) - 175 is -174.77", "a": 40.45, "b": 176, "c": 175, "op1": "/", "op2": "-", "result": -174.77}
{"question": "Solve: (93 / 28.94) / 11.38", "answer": "The result of (93 / 28.94) / 11.38 is 0.28", "a": 93, "b": 28.94, "c": 11.38, "op1": "/", "op2": "/", "result": 0.28}
{"question": "Solve: (83 * 148) * 10", "answer": "The result of (83 * 148) * 10 is 122840", "a": 83, "b": 148, "c": 10, "op1": "*", "op2": "*", "result": 122840}
{"question": "Solve: (3 - 42.4) + 105.94", "answer": "The result of (3 - 42.4) + 105.94 is 66.54", "a": 3, "b": 42.4, "c": 105.94, "op1": "-", "op2": "+", "result": 66.54}
{"question": "Solve: (158.95 - 64) * 15.15", "answer": "The result of (158.95 - 64) * 15.15 is 1438.49", "a": 158.95, "b": 64, "c": 15.15, "op1": "-", "op2": "*", "result": 1438.49}
{"question": "Solve: (163 / 144) - 31.26", "answer": "The result of (163 / 144) - 31.26 is -30.13", "a": 163, "b": 144, "c": 31.26, "op1": "/", "op2": "-", "result": -30.13}
{"question": "Solve: (177 * 198.48) + 147", "answer": "The result of (177 * 198.48) + 147 is 35277.96", "a": 177, "b": 198.48, "c": 147, "op1": "*", "op2": "+", "result": 35277.96}
{"question": "Solve: (127 * 199) - 82", "answer": "The result of (127 * 199) - 82 is 25191", "a": 127, "b": 199, "c": 82, "op1": "*", "op2": "-", "result": 25191}
{"question": "Solve: (16 - 158) - 117", "answer": "The result of (16 - 158) - 117 is -259", "a": 16, "b": 158, "c": 117, "op1": "-", "op2": "-", "result": -259}
{"question": "Solve: (49 * 149.12) * 42.3", "answer": "The result of (49 * 149.12) * 42.3 is 309081.02", "a": 49, "b": 149.12, "c": 42.3, "op1": "*", "op2": "*", "result": 309081.02}
{"question": "Solve: (49.13 * 90.27) * 55", "answer": "The result of (49.13 * 90.27) * 55 is 243923.08", "a": 49.13, "b": 90.27, "c": 55, "op1": "*", "op2": "*", "result": 243923.08}
{"question": "Solve: (36 * 143) - 92", "answer": "The result of (36 * 143) - 92 is 5056", "a": 36, "b": 143, "c": 92, "op1": "*", "op2": "-", "result": 5056}
{"question": "Solve: (130.17 - 57) + 192.94", "answer": "The result of (130.17 - 57) + 192.94 is 266.11", "a": 130.17, "b": 57, "c": 192.94, "op1": "-", "op2": "+", "result": 266.11}
{"question": "Solve: (89 / 158.9) + 9.07", "answer": "The result of (89 / 158.9) + 9.07 is 9.63", "a": 89, "b": 158.9, "c": 9.07, "op1": "/", "op2": "+", "result": 9.63}
{"question": "Solve: (155.82 + 61) + 30", "answer": "The result of (155.82 + 61) + 30 is 246.82", "a": 155.82, "b": 61, "c": 30, "op1": "+", "op2": "+", "result": 246.82}
{"question": "Solve: (181 - 21) - 160.99", "answer": "The result of (181 - 21) - 160.99 is -0.99", "a": 181, "b": 21, "c": 160.99, "op1": "-", "op2": "-", "result": -0.99}
{"question": "Solve: (149 + 9) * 156", "answer": "The result of (149 + 9) * 156 is 24648", "a": 149, "b": 9, "c": 156, "op1": "+", "op2": "*", "result": 24648}
{"question": "Solve: (30 * 110.11) + 23", "answer": "The result of (30 * 110.11) + 23 is 3326.3", "a": 30, "b": 110.11, "c": 23, "op1": "*", "op2": "+", "result": 3326.3}
{"question": "Solve: (36 + 180) - 16", "answer": "The result of (36 + 180) - 16 is 200", "a": 36, "b": 180, "c": 16, "op1": "+", "op2": "-", "result": 200}
{"question": "Solve: (121 + 46) - 97.58", "answer": "The result of (121 + 46) - 97.58 is 69.42", "a": 121, "b": 46, "c": 97.58, "op1": "+", "op2": "-", "result": 69.42}
{"question": "Solve: (62 * 166) + 178", "answer": "The result of (62 * 166) + 178 is 10470", "a": 62, "b": 166, "c": 178, "op1": "*", "op2": "+", "result": 10470}
{"question": "Solve: (56 + 84) / 78", "answer": "The result of (56 + 84) / 78 is 1.79", "a": 56, "b": 84, "c": 78, "op1": "+", "op2": "/", "result": 1.79}
{"question": "Solve: (114.2 - 97) * 56.77", "answer": "The result of (114.2 - 97) * 56.77 is 976.44", "a": 114.2, "b": 97, "c": 56.77, "op1": "-", "op2": "*", "result": 976.44}
{"question": "Solve: (19.57 - 114.02) + 21", "answer": "The result of (19.57 - 114.02) + 21 is -73.45", "a": 19.57, "b": 114.02, "c": 21, "op1": "-", "op2": "+", "result": -73.45}
{"question": "Solve: (135 / 3) * 77.71", "answer": "The result of (135 / 3) * 77.71 is 3496.95", "a": 135, "b": 3, "c": 77.71, "op1": "/", "op2": "*", "result": 3496.95}
{"question": "Solve: (89.33 - 86) + 76", "answer": "The result of (89.33 - 86) + 76 is 79.33", "a": 89.33, "b": 86, "c": 76, "op1": "-", "op2": "+", "result": 79.33}
{"question": "Solve: (159 - 174) / 113", "answer": "The result of (159 - 174) / 113 is -0.13", "a": 159, "b": 174, "c": 113, "op1": "-", "op2": "/", "result": -0.13}
{"question": "Solve: (125 * 137) + 191", "answer": "The result of (125 * 137) + 191 is 17316", "a": 125, "b": 137, "c": 191, "op1": "*", "op2": "+", "result": 17316}
{"question": "Solve: (85 + 119) - 124.67", "answer": "The result of (85 + 119) - 124.67 is 79.33", "a": 85, "b": 119, "c": 124.67, "op1": "+", "op2": "-", "result": 79.33}
{"question": "Solve: (86 / 133) / 111", "answer": "The result of (86 / 133) / 111 is 0.01", "a": 86, "b": 133, "c": 111, "op1": "/", "op2": "/", "result": 0.01}
{"question": "Solve: (156.36 / 188) + 133.82", "answer": "The result of (156.36 / 188) + 133.82 is 134.65", "a": 156.36, "b": 188, "c": 133.82, "op1": "/", "op2": "+", "result": 134.65}
{"question": "Solve: (74 + 60) * 109.89", "answer": "The result of (74 + 60) * 109.89 is 14725.26", "a": 74, "b": 60, "c": 109.89, "op1": "+", "op2": "*", "result": 14725.26}
{"question": "Solve: (33.81 * 28) * 80.24", "answer": "The result of (33.81 * 28) * 80.24 is 75961.6", "a": 33.81, "b": 28, "c": 80.24, "op1": "*", "op2": "*", "result": 75961.6}
{"question": "Solve: (190 - 65.09) * 135", "answer": "The result of (190 - 65.09) * 135 is 16862.85", "a": 190, "b": 65.09, "c": 135, "op1": "-", "op2": "*", "result": 16862.85}
{"question": "Solve: (38 - 146.56) + 103", "answer": "The result of (38 - 146.56) + 103 is -5.56", "a": 38, "b": 146.56, "c": 103, "op1": "-", "op2": "+", "result": -5.56}
{"question": "Solve: (182.47 - 17) + 3", "answer": "The result of (182.47 - 17) + 3 is 168.47", "a": 182.47, "b": 17, "c": 3, "op1": "-", "op2": "+", "result": 168.47}
{"question": "Solve: (101.18 * 73.46) + 17", "answer": "The result of (101.18 * 73.46) + 17 is 7449.68", "a": 101.18, "b": 73.46, "c": 17, "op1": "*", "op2": "+", "result": 7449.68}
{"question": "Solve: (37.83 + 46) + 77.66", "answer": "The result of (37.83 + 46) + 77.66 is 161.49", "a": 37.83, "b": 46, "c": 77.66, "op1": "+", "op2": "+", "result": 161.49}
{"question": "Solve: (167 - 158) + 78.42", "answer": "The result of (167 - 158) + 78.42 is 87.42", "a": 167, "b": 158, "c": 78.42, "op1": "-", "op2": "+", "result": 87.42}
{"question": "Solve: (175 + 124) / 11", "answer": "The result of (175 + 124) / 11 is 27.18", "a": 175, "b": 124, "c": 11, "op1": "+", "op2": "/", "result": 27.18}
{"question": "Solve: (5.46 + 200) / 102", "answer": "The result of (5.46 + 200) / 102 is 2.01", "a": 5.46, "b": 200, "c": 102, "op1": "+", "op2": "/", "result": 2.01}
{"question": "Solve: (106 * 149) - 1", "answer": "The result of (106 * 149) - 1 is 15793", "a": 106, "b": 149, "c": 1, "op1": "*", "op2": "-", "result": 15793}
{"question": "Solve: (191 * 146.09) / 101.61", "answer": "The result of (191 * 146.09) / 101.61 is 274.61", "a": 191, "b": 146.09, "c": 101.61, "op1": "*", "op2": "/", "result": 274.61}
{"question": "Solve: (82.12 * 71) / 32", "answer": "The result of (82.12 * 71) / 32 is 182.2", "a": 82.12, "b": 71, "c": 32, "op1": "*", "op2": "/", "result": 182.2}
{"question": "Solve: (66 - 130) * 118", "answer": "The result of (66 - 130) * 118 is -7552", "a": 66, "b": 130, "c": 118, "op1": "-", "op2": "*", "result": -7552}
{"question": "Solve: (193 + 26.17) / 13", "answer": "The result of (193 + 26.17) / 13 is 16.86", "a": 193, "b": 26.17, "c": 13, "op1": "+", "op2": "/", "result": 16.86}
{"question": "Solve: (42 + 42.9) * 67.64", "answer": "The result of (42 + 42.9) * 67.64 is 5742.64", "a": 42, "b": 42.9, "c": 67.64, "op1": "+", "op2": "*", "result": 5742.64}
{"question": "Solve: (192 + 155.41) - 66", "answer": "The result of (192 + 155.41) - 66 is 281.41", "a": 192, "b": 155.41, "c": 66, "op1": "+", "op2": "-", "result": 281.41}
{"question": "Solve: (78 - 76) + 37", "answer": "The result of (78 - 76) + 37 is 39", "a": 78, "b": 76, "c": 37, "op1": "-", "op2": "+", "result": 39}
{"question": "Solve: (179 - 100) * 140.97", "answer": "The result of (179 - 100) * 140.97 is 11136.63", "a": 179, "b": 100, "c": 140.97, "op1": "-", "op2": "*", "result": 11136.63}
{"question": "Solve: (72.8 + 173) - 197", "answer": "The result of (72.8 + 173) - 197 is 48.8", "a": 72.8, "b": 173, "c": 197, "op1": "+", "op2": "-", "result": 48.8}
{"question": "Solve: (38 + 100) / 120", "answer": "The result of (38 + 100) / 120 is 1.15", "a": 38, "b": 100, "c": 120, "op1": "+", "op2": "/", "result": 1.15}
{"question": "Solve: (134 * 8) + 156", "answer": "The result of (134 * 8) + 156 is 1228", "a": 134, "b": 8, "c": 156, "op1": "*", "op2": "+", "result": 1228}
{"question": "Solve: (112.42 + 82) / 2.11", "answer": "The result of (112.42 + 82) / 2.11 is 92.14", "a": 112.42, "b": 82, "c": 2.11, "op1": "+", "op2": "/", "result": 92.14}
{"question": "Solve: (172.43 + 55.37) * 78.15", "answer": "The result of (172.43 + 55.37) * 78.15 is 17802.57", "a": 172.43, "b": 55.37, "c": 78.15, "op1": "+", "op2": "*", "result": 17802.57}
{"question": "Solve: (40 - 97) * 27", "answer": "The result of (40 - 97) * 27 is -1539", "a": 40, "b": 97, "c": 27, "op1": "-", "op2": "*", "result": -1539}
{"question": "Solve: (50 / 100.03) * 26", "answer": "The result of (50 / 100.03) * 26 is 13.0", "a": 50, "b": 100.03, "c": 26, "op1": "/", "op2": "*", "result": 13.0}
{"question": "Solve: (121.74 / 50.13) + 133", "answer": "The result of (121.74 / 50.13) + 133 is 135.43", "a": 121.74, "b": 50.13, "c": 133, "op1": "/", "op2": "+", "result": 135.43}
{"question": "Solve: (144 - 1) - 42.67", "answer": "The result of (144 - 1) - 42.67 is 100.33", "a": 144, "b": 1, "c": 42.67, "op1": "-", "op2": "-", "result": 100.33}
{"question": "Solve: (117.37 - 126) - 82", "answer": "The result of (117.37 - 126) - 82 is -90.63", "a": 117.37, "b": 126, "c": 82, "op1": "-", "op2": "-", "result": -90.63}
{"question": "Solve: (124.79 - 83) * 64", "answer": "The result of (124.79 - 83) * 64 is 2674.56", "a": 124.79, "b": 83, "c": 64, "op1": "-", "op2": "*", "result": 2674.56}
{"question": "Solve: (46 + 123.87) * 104", "answer": "The result of (46 + 123.87) * 104 is 17666.48", "a": 46, "b": 123.87, "c": 104, "op1": "+", "op2": "*", "result": 17666.48}
{"question": "Solve: (84 * 197) + 3", "answer": "The result of (84 * 197) + 3 is 16551", "a": 84, "b": 197, "c": 3, "op1": "*", "op2": "+", "result": 16551}
{"question": "Solve: (80 - 182) * 103", "answer": "The result of (80 - 182) * 103 is -10506", "a": 80, "b": 182, "c": 103, "op1": "-", "op2": "*", "result": -10506}
{"question": "Solve: (11 - 157) * 183", "answer": "The result of (11 - 157) * 183 is -26718", "a": 11, "b": 157, "c": 183, "op1": "-", "op2": "*", "result": -26718}
{"question": "Solve: (120.91 / 53) + 124.19", "answer": "The result of (120.91 / 53) + 124.19 is 126.47", "a": 120.91, "b": 53, "c": 124.19, "op1": "/", "op2": "+", "result": 126.47}
{"question": "Solve: (96 - 155.21) + 58.85", "answer": "The result of (96 - 155.21) + 58.85 is -0.36", "a": 96, "b": 155.21, "c": 58.85, "op1": "-", "op2": "+", "result": -0.36}
{"question": "Solve: (100 * 87) + 35", "answer": "The result of (100 * 87) + 35 is 8735", "a": 100, "b": 87, "c": 35, "op1": "*", "op2": "+", "result": 8735}
{"question": "Solve: (26 * 100) - 143.52", "answer": "The result of (26 * 100) - 143.52 is 2456.48", "a": 26, "b": 100, "c": 143.52, "op1": "*", "op2": "-", "result": 2456.48}
{"question": "Solve: (89.95 - 154) + 77", "answer": "The result of (89.95 - 154) + 77 is 12.95", "a": 89.95, "b": 154, "c": 77, "op1": "-", "op2": "+", "result": 12.95}
{"question": "Solve: (42 * 191) - 10.13", "answer": "The result of (42 * 191) - 10.13 is 8011.87", "a": 42, "b": 191, "c": 10.13, "op1": "*", "op2": "-", "result": 8011.87}
{"question": "Solve: (186 - 191.88) * 1.25", "answer": "The result of (186 - 191.88) * 1.25 is -7.35", "a": 186, "b": 191.88, "c": 1.25, "op1": "-", "op2": "*", "result": -7.35}
{"question": "Solve: (149 / 143) + 123", "answer": "The result of (149 / 143) + 123 is 124.04", "a": 149, "b": 143, "c": 123, "op1": "/", "op2": "+", "result": 124.04}
{"question": "Solve: (149.07 * 159.21) - 94.47", "answer": "The result of (149.07 * 159.21) - 94.47 is 23638.96", "a": 149.07, "b": 159.21, "c": 94.47, "op1": "*", "op2": "-", "result": 23638.96}
{"question": "Solve: (183 - 23) - 184", "answer": "The result of (183 - 23) - 184 is -24", "a": 183, "b": 23, "c": 184, "op1": "-", "op2": "-", "result": -24}
{"question": "Solve: (19 - 4) * 153.3", "answer": "The result of (19 - 4) * 153.3 is 2299.5", "a": 19, "b": 4, "c": 153.3, "op1": "-", "op2": "*", "result": 2299.5}
{"question": "Solve: (106 + 2) + 49", "answer": "The result of (106 + 2) + 49 is 157", "a": 106, "b": 2, "c": 49, "op1": "+", "op2": "+", "result": 157}
{"question": "Solve: (89.49 + 111) + 185", "answer": "The result of (89.49 + 111) + 185 is 385.49", "a": 89.49, "b": 111, "c": 185, "op1": "+", "op2": "+", "result": 385.49}
{"question": "Solve: (138 - 117) + 11.46", "answer": "The result of (138 - 117) + 11.46 is 32.46", "a": 138, "b": 117, "c": 11.46, "op1": "-", "op2": "+", "result": 32.46}
{"question": "Solve: (115 / 166.38) * 166", "answer": "The result of (115 / 166.38) * 166 is 114.74", "a": 115, "b": 166.38, "c": 166, "op1": "/", "op2": "*", "result": 114.74}
{"question": "Solve: (7.2 + 105) + 158", "answer": "The result of (7.2 + 105) + 158 is 270.2", "a": 7.2, "b": 105, "c": 158, "op1": "+", "op2": "+", "result": 270.2}
{"question": "Solve: (59 * 148) * 111.05", "answer": "The result of (59 * 148) * 111.05 is 969688.6", "a": 59, "b": 148, "c": 111.05, "op1": "*", "op2": "*", "result": 969688.6}
{"question": "Solve: (105 - 123) - 40", "answer": "The result of (105 - 123) - 40 is -58", "a": 105, "b": 123, "c": 40, "op1": "-", "op2": "-", "result": -58}
{"question": "Solve: (24.64 / 182) - 128", "answer": "The result of (24.64 / 182) - 128 is -127.86", "a": 24.64, "b": 182, "c": 128, "op1": "/", "op2": "-", "result": -127.86}
{"question": "Solve: (106 - 75) + 70", "answer": "The result of (106 - 75) + 70 is 101", "a": 106, "b": 75, "c": 70, "op1": "-", "op2": "+", "result": 101}
{"question": "Solve: (171 * 28) * 58", "answer": "The result of (171 * 28) * 58 is 277704", "a": 171, "b": 28, "c": 58, "op1": "*", "op2": "*", "result": 277704}
{"question": "Solve: (61 + 65) * 142", "answer": "The result of (61 + 65) * 142 is 17892", "a": 61, "b": 65, "c": 142, "op1": "+", "op2": "*", "result": 17892}
{"question": "Solve: (183 - 181) + 171", "answer": "The result of (183 - 181) + 171 is 173", "a": 183, "b": 181, "c": 171, "op1": "-", "op2": "+", "result": 173}
{"question": "Solve: (137 + 136) + 78", "answer": "The result of (137 + 136) + 78 is 351", "a": 137, "b": 136, "c": 78, "op1": "+", "op2": "+", "result": 351}
{"question": "Solve: (184.22 - 182.73) - 29.66", "answer": "The result of (184.22 - 182.73) - 29.66 is -28.17", "a": 184.22, "b": 182.73, "c": 29.66, "op1": "-", "op2": "-", "result": -28.17}
{"question": "Solve: (18 * 56) - 12", "answer": "The result of (18 * 56) - 12 is 996", "a": 18, "b": 56, "c": 12, "op1": "*", "op2": "-", "result": 996}
{"question": "Solve: (58 + 106) - 33.97", "answer": "The result of (58 + 106) - 33.97 is 130.03", "a": 58, "b": 106, "c": 33.97, "op1": "+", "op2": "-", "result": 130.03}
{"question": "Solve: (188 - 135.19) + 33.38", "answer": "The result of (188 - 135.19) + 33.38 is 86.19", "a": 188, "b": 135.19, "c": 33.38, "op1": "-", "op2": "+", "result": 86.19}
{"question": "Solve: (69.4 * 27) * 199.72", "answer": "The result of (69.4 * 27) * 199.72 is 374235.34", "a": 69.4, "b": 27, "c": 199.72, "op1": "*", "op2": "*", "result": 374235.34}
{"question": "Solve: (24 + 99) + 102.71", "answer": "The result of (24 + 99) + 102.71 is 225.71", "a": 24, "b": 99, "c": 102.71, "op1": "+", "op2": "+", "result": 225.71}
{"question": "Solve: (92 + 151.45) - 174", "answer": "The result of (92 + 151.45) - 174 is 69.45", "a": 92, "b": 151.45, "c": 174, "op1": "+", "op2": "-", "result": 69.45}
{"question": "Solve: (2 - 112) + 151", "answer": "The result of (2 - 112) + 151 is 41", "a": 2, "b": 112, "c": 151, "op1": "-", "op2": "+", "result": 41}
{"question": "Solve: (28 / 164.77) * 114", "answer": "The result of (28 / 164.77) * 114 is 19.37", "a": 28, "b": 164.77, "c": 114, "op1": "/", "op2": "*", "result": 19.37}
{"question": "Solve: (134 / 94.33) - 27", "answer": "The result of (134 / 94.33) - 27 is -25.58", "a": 134, "b": 94.33, "c": 27, "op1": "/", "op2": "-", "result": -25.58}
{"question": "Solve: (94 - 100.97) - 31", "answer": "The result of (94 - 100.97) - 31 is -37.97", "a": 94, "b": 100.97, "c": 31, "op1": "-", "op2": "-", "result": -37.97}
{"question": "Solve: (4 / 106.63) * 49.98", "answer": "The result of (4 / 106.63) * 49.98 is 1.87", "a": 4, "b": 106.63, "c": 49.98, "op1": "/", "op2": "*", "result": 1.87}
{"question": "Solve: (185 - 105) - 65", "answer": "The result of (185 - 105) - 65 is 15", "a": 185, "b": 105, "c": 65, "op1": "-", "op2": "-", "result": 15}
{"question": "Solve: (96 + 103) * 56", "answer": "The result of (96 + 103) * 56 is 11144", "a": 96, "b": 103, "c": 56, "op1": "+", "op2": "*", "result": 11144}
{"question": "Solve: (22 * 128) - 182", "answer": "The result of (22 * 128) - 182 is 2634", "a": 22, "b": 128, "c": 182, "op1": "*", "op2": "-", "result": 2634}
{"question": "Solve: (44 + 94.83) + 98.69", "answer": "The result of (44 + 94.83) + 98.69 is 237.52", "a": 44, "b": 94.83, "c": 98.69, "op1": "+", "op2": "+", "result": 237.52}
{"question": "Solve: (12 - 47.97) + 59", "answer": "The result of (12 - 47.97) + 59 is 23.03", "a": 12, "b": 47.97, "c": 59, "op1": "-", "op2": "+", "result": 23.03}
{"question": "Solve: (92 + 98) * 96", "answer": "The result of (92 + 98) * 96 is 18240", "a": 92, "b": 98, "c": 96, "op1": "+", "op2": "*", "result": 18240}
{"question": "Solve: (90 * 67.97) + 149", "answer": "The result of (90 * 67.97) + 149 is 6266.3", "a": 90, "b": 67.97, "c": 149, "op1": "*", "op2": "+", "result": 6266.3}
{"question": "Solve: (103.58 * 94.84) * 167", "answer": "The result of (103.58 * 94.84) * 167 is 1640529.04", "a": 103.58, "b": 94.84, "c": 167, "op1": "*", "op2": "*", "result": 1640529.04}
{"question": "Solve: (85 + 24) - 125", "answer": "The result of (85 + 24) - 125 is -16", "a": 85, "b": 24, "c": 125, "op1": "+", "op2": "-", "result": -16}
{"question": "Solve: (42 * 197) * 127", "answer": "The result of (42 * 197) * 127 is 1050798", "a": 42, "b": 197, "c": 127, "op1": "*", "op2": "*", "result": 1050798}
{"question": "Solve: (20.18 - 166) / 174", "answer": "The result of (20.18 - 166) / 174 is -0.84", "a": 20.18, "b": 166, "c": 174, "op1": "-", "op2": "/", "result": -0.84}
{"question": "Solve: (70 + 148) - 53.66", "answer": "The result of (70 + 148) - 53.66 is 164.34", "a": 70, "b": 148, "c": 53.66, "op1": "+", "op2": "-", "result": 164.34}
{"question": "Solve: (14 + 101.83) - 171.49", "answer": "The result of (14 + 101.83) - 171.49 is -55.66", "a": 14, "b": 101.83, "c": 171.49, "op1": "+", "op2": "-", "result": -55.66}
{"question": "Solve: (53 / 191) / 154.31", "answer": "The result of (53 / 191) / 154.31 is 0.0", "a": 53, "b": 191, "c": 154.31, "op1": "/", "op2": "/", "result": 0.0}
{"question": "Solve: (69 / 20.67) - 6", "answer": "The result of (69 / 20.67) - 6 is -2.66", "a": 69, "b": 20.67, "c": 6, "op1": "/", "op2": "-", "result": -2.66}
{"question": "Solve: (199 + 1) - 106.84", "answer": "The result of (199 + 1) - 106.84 is 93.16", "a": 199, "b": 1, "c": 106.84, "op1": "+", "op2": "-", "result": 93.16}
{"question": "Solve: (18 / 107) - 16", "answer": "The result of (18 / 107) - 16 is -15.83", "a": 18, "b": 107, "c": 16, "op1": "/", "op2": "-", "result": -15.83}
{"question": "Solve: (68 + 15) * 104", "answer": "The result of (68 + 15) * 104 is 8632", "a": 68, "b": 15, "c": 104, "op1": "+", "op2": "*", "result": 8632}
{"question": "Solve: (10 + 77) * 121", "answer": "The result of (10 + 77) * 121 is 10527", "a": 10, "b": 77, "c": 121, "op1": "+", "op2": "*", "result": 10527}
{"question": "Solve: (192 - 79) + 192", "answer": "The result of (192 - 79) + 192 is 305", "a": 192, "b": 79, "c": 192, "op1": "-", "op2": "+", "result": 305}
{"question": "Solve: (55.08 * 183.69) * 168", "answer": "The result of (55.08 * 183.69) * 168 is 1699764.39", "a": 55.08, "b": 183.69, "c": 168, "op1": "*", "op2": "*", "result": 1699764.39}
{"question": "Solve: (120.58 * 195) * 159", "answer": "The result of (120.58 * 195) * 159 is 3738582.9", "a": 120.58, "b": 195, "c": 159, "op1": "*", "op2": "*", "result": 3738582.9}
{"question": "Solve: (72 / 153.76) + 79", "answer": "The result of (72 / 153.76) + 79 is 79.47", "a": 72, "b": 153.76, "c": 79, "op1": "/", "op2": "+", "result": 79.47}
{"question": "Solve: (33 / 52) * 102", "answer": "The result of (33 / 52) * 102 is 64.73", "a": 33, "b": 52, "c": 102, "op1": "/", "op2": "*", "result": 64.73}
{"question": "Solve: (133 + 106) - 12", "answer": "The result of (133 + 106) - 12 is 227", "a": 133, "b": 106, "c": 12, "op1": "+", "op2": "-", "result": 227}
{"question": "Solve: (96 * 127) + 100", "answer": "The result of (96 * 127) + 100 is 12292", "a": 96, "b": 127, "c": 100, "op1": "*", "op2": "+", "result": 12292}
{"question": "Solve: (42 - 83) + 147.55", "answer": "The result of (42 - 83) + 147.55 is 106.55", "a": 42, "b": 83, "c": 147.55, "op1": "-", "op2": "+", "result": 106.55}
{"question": "Solve: (162 + 112) * 177", "answer": "The result of (162 + 112) * 177 is 48498", "a": 162, "b": 112, "c": 177, "op1": "+", "op2": "*", "result": 48498}
{"question": "Solve: (56 + 115) / 94", "answer": "The result of (56 + 115) / 94 is 1.82", "a": 56, "b": 115, "c": 94, "op1": "+", "op2": "/", "result": 1.82}
{"question": "Solve: (54 + 111) + 163", "answer": "The result of (54 + 111) + 163 is 328", "a": 54, "b": 111, "c": 163, "op1": "+", "op2": "+", "result": 328}
{"question": "Solve: (109 / 149) * 17", "answer": "The result of (109 / 149) * 17 is 12.44", "a": 109, "b": 149, "c": 17, "op1": "/", "op2": "*", "result": 12.44}
{"question": "Solve: (200 - 1.9) * 6", "answer": "The result of (200 - 1.9) * 6 is 1188.6", "a": 200, "b": 1.9, "c": 6, "op1": "-", "op2": "*", "result": 1188.6}
{"question": "Solve: (121 + 48.08) - 120", "answer": "The result of (121 + 48.08) - 120 is 49.08", "a": 121, "b": 48.08, "c": 120, "op1": "+", "op2": "-", "result": 49.08}
{"question": "Solve: (152.03 - 156) * 84.42", "answer": "The result of (152.03 - 156) * 84.42 is -335.15", "a": 152.03, "b": 156, "c": 84.42, "op1": "-", "op2": "*", "result": -335.15}
{"question": "Solve: (157 + 80) + 58", "answer": "The result of (157 + 80) + 58 is 295", "a": 157, "b": 80, "c": 58, "op1": "+", "op2": "+", "result": 295}
{"question": "Solve: (148 - 79) - 72", "answer": "The result of (148 - 79) - 72 is -3", "a": 148, "b": 79, "c": 72, "op1": "-", "op2": "-", "result": -3}
{"question": "Solve: (54 / 77) + 118", "answer": "The result of (54 / 77) + 118 is 118.7", "a": 54, "b": 77, "c": 118, "op1": "/", "op2": "+", "result": 118.7}
{"question": "Solve: (167.59 - 196) - 164", "answer": "The result of (167.59 - 196) - 164 is -192.41", "a": 167.59, "b": 196, "c": 164, "op1": "-", "op2": "-", "result": -192.41}
{"question": "Solve: (160 - 169.75) + 33", "answer": "The result of (160 - 169.75) + 33 is 23.25", "a": 160, "b": 169.75, "c": 33, "op1": "-", "op2": "+", "result": 23.25}
{"question": "Solve: (97.72 * 188.04) - 159", "answer": "The result of (97.72 * 188.04) - 159 is 18216.27", "a": 97.72, "b": 188.04, "c": 159, "op1": "*", "op2": "-", "result": 18216.27}
{"question": "Solve: (98 / 1) * 36", "answer": "The result of (98 / 1) * 36 is 3528.0", "a": 98, "b": 1, "c": 36, "op1": "/", "op2": "*", "result": 3528.0}
{"question": "Solve: (87 / 177) * 122", "answer": "The result of (87 / 177) * 122 is 59.97", "a": 87, "b": 177, "c": 122, "op1": "/", "op2": "*", "result": 59.97}
{"question": "Solve: (22 + 139) - 42.31", "answer": "The result of (22 + 139) - 42.31 is 118.69", "a": 22, "b": 139, "c": 42.31, "op1": "+", "op2": "-", "result": 118.69}
{"question": "Solve: (50 + 25.06) + 79", "answer": "The result of (50 + 25.06) + 79 is 154.06", "a": 50, "b": 25.06, "c": 79, "op1": "+", "op2": "+", "result": 154.06}
{"question": "Solve: (163 * 199.99) - 113", "answer": "The result of (163 * 199.99) - 113 is 32485.37", "a": 163, "b": 199.99, "c": 113, "op1": "*", "op2": "-", "result": 32485.37}
{"question": "Solve: (142 / 128) / 153", "answer": "The result of (142 / 128) / 153 is 0.01", "a": 142, "b": 128, "c": 153, "op1": "/", "op2": "/", "result": 0.01}
{"question": "Solve: (46.34 * 179) * 77.28", "answer": "The result of (46.34 * 179) * 77.28 is 641026.78", "a": 46.34, "b": 179, "c": 77.28, "op1": "*", "op2": "*", "result": 641026.78}
{"question": "Solve: (115 - 164) + 95", "answer": "The result of (115 - 164) + 95 is 46", "a": 115, "b": 164, "c": 95, "op1": "-", "op2": "+", "result": 46}
{"question": "Solve: (199 + 60.95) / 99.19", "answer": "The result of (199 + 60.95) / 99.19 is 2.62", "a": 199, "b": 60.95, "c": 99.19, "op1": "+", "op2": "/", "result": 2.62}
{"question": "Solve: (8 + 69.75) * 91", "answer": "The result of (8 + 69.75) * 91 is 7075.25", "a": 8, "b": 69.75, "c": 91, "op1": "+", "op2": "*", "result": 7075.25}
{"question": "Solve: (148.99 + 180) + 138", "answer": "The result of (148.99 + 180) + 138 is 466.99", "a": 148.99, "b": 180, "c": 138, "op1": "+", "op2": "+", "result": 466.99}
{"question": "Solve: (165.73 + 182) * 129", "answer": "The result of (165.73 + 182) * 129 is 44857.17", "a": 165.73, "b": 182, "c": 129, "op1": "+", "op2": "*", "result": 44857.17}
{"question": "Solve: (174 + 18.24) * 69", "answer": "The result of (174 + 18.24) * 69 is 13264.56", "a": 174, "b": 18.24, "c": 69, "op1": "+", "op2": "*", "result": 13264.56}
{"question": "Solve: (188 / 37) * 46", "answer": "The result of (188 / 37) * 46 is 233.73", "a": 188, "b": 37, "c": 46, "op1": "/", "op2": "*", "result": 233.73}
{"question": "Solve: (37 * 192.39) + 180.76", "answer": "The result of (37 * 192.39) + 180.76 is 7299.19", "a": 37, "b": 192.39, "c": 180.76, "op1": "*", "op2": "+", "result": 7299.19}
{"question": "Solve: (105.24 + 62) * 122.03", "answer": "The result of (105.24 + 62) * 122.03 is 20408.3", "a": 105.24, "b": 62, "c": 122.03, "op1": "+", "op2": "*", "result": 20408.3}
{"question": "Solve: (192.79 * 156.11) + 34.59", "answer": "The result of (192.79 * 156.11) + 34.59 is 30131.04", "a": 192.79, "b": 156.11, "c": 34.59, "op1": "*", "op2": "+", "result": 30131.04}
{"question": "Solve: (41 + 93.66) * 193", "answer": "The result of (41 + 93.66) * 193 is 25989.38", "a": 41, "b": 93.66, "c": 193, "op1": "+", "op2": "*", "result": 25989.38}
{"question": "Solve: (61 * 165) + 129", "answer": "The result of (61 * 165) + 129 is 10194", "a": 61, "b": 165, "c": 129, "op1": "*", "op2": "+", "result": 10194}
{"question": "Solve: (196.94 / 45) * 78", "answer": "The result of (196.94 / 45) * 78 is 341.36", "a": 196.94, "b": 45, "c": 78, "op1": "/", "op2": "*", "result": 341.36}
{"question": "Solve: (184 * 146) - 4.83", "answer": "The result of (184 * 146) - 4.83 is 26859.17", "a": 184, "b": 146, "c": 4.83, "op1": "*", "op2": "-", "result": 26859.17}
{"question": "Solve: (33.27 * 168) - 64", "answer": "The result of (33.27 * 168) - 64 is 5525.36", "a": 33.27, "b": 168, "c": 64, "op1": "*", "op2": "-", "result": 5525.36}
{"question": "Solve: (68 / 101.43) - 90.75", "answer": "The result of (68 / 101.43) - 90.75 is -90.08", "a": 68, "b": 101.43, "c": 90.75, "op1": "/", "op2": "-", "result": -90.08}
{"question": "Solve: (100.92 + 117.76) + 35", "answer": "The result of (100.92 + 117.76) + 35 is 253.68", "a": 100.92, "b": 117.76, "c": 35, "op1": "+", "op2": "+", "result": 253.68}
{"question": "Solve: (10 / 89) / 16.69", "answer": "The result of (10 / 89) / 16.69 is 0.01", "a": 10, "b": 89, "c": 16.69, "op1": "/", "op2": "/", "result": 0.01}
{"question": "Solve: (102 / 48.36) / 163", "answer": "The result of (102 / 48.36) / 163 is 0.01", "a": 102, "b": 48.36, "c": 163, "op1": "/", "op2": "/", "result": 0.01}
{"question": "Solve: (25 + 20) * 165", "answer": "The result of (25 + 20) * 165 is 7425", "a": 25, "b": 20, "c": 165, "op1": "+", "op2": "*", "result": 7425}
{"question": "Solve: (126.19 / 167) * 190", "answer": "The result of (126.19 / 167) * 190 is 143.57", "a": 126.19, "b": 167, "c": 190, "op1": "/", "op2": "*", "result": 143.57}
{"question": "Solve: (151.09 * 173) - 21", "answer": "The result of (151.09 * 173) - 21 is 26117.57", "a": 151.09, "b": 173, "c": 21, "op1": "*", "op2": "-", "result": 26117.57}
{"question": "Solve: (139 - 79) * 46.75", "answer": "The result of (139 - 79) * 46.75 is 2805.0", "a": 139, "b": 79, "c": 46.75, "op1": "-", "op2": "*", "result": 2805.0}
{"question": "Solve: (199 + 172) - 127.98", "answer": "The result of (199 + 172) - 127.98 is 243.02", "a": 199, "b": 172, "c": 127.98, "op1": "+", "op2": "-", "result": 243.02}
{"question": "Solve: (46 + 28.83) - 81", "answer": "The result of (46 + 28.83) - 81 is -6.17", "a": 46, "b": 28.83, "c": 81, "op1": "+", "op2": "-", "result": -6.17}
{"question": "Solve: (12 - 102) - 3", "answer": "The result of (12 - 102) - 3 is -93", "a": 12, "b": 102, "c": 3, "op1": "-", "op2": "-", "result": -93}
{"question": "Solve: (48 - 45.76) - 155.38", "answer": "The result of (48 - 45.76) - 155.38 is -153.14", "a": 48, "b": 45.76, "c": 155.38, "op1": "-", "op2": "-", "result": -153.14}
{"question": "Solve: (111 / 150.73) - 54", "answer": "The result of (111 / 150.73) - 54 is -53.26", "a": 111, "b": 150.73, "c": 54, "op1": "/", "op2": "-", "result": -53.26}
{"question": "Solve: (123 / 121.91) + 105", "answer": "The result of (123 / 121.91) + 105 is 106.01", "a": 123, "b": 121.91, "c": 105, "op1": "/", "op2": "+", "result": 106.01}
{"question": "Solve: (166.13 - 5) / 6", "answer": "The result of (166.13 - 5) / 6 is 26.86", "a": 166.13, "b": 5, "c": 6, "op1": "-", "op2": "/", "result": 26.86}
{"question": "Solve: (101.35 / 15) / 138", "answer": "The result of (101.35 / 15) / 138 is 0.05", "a": 101.35, "b": 15, "c": 138, "op1": "/", "op2": "/", "result": 0.05}
{"question": "Solve: (134.62 / 4) + 114", "answer": "The result of (134.62 / 4) + 114 is 147.66", "a": 134.62, "b": 4, "c": 114, "op1": "/", "op2": "+", "result": 147.66}
{"question": "Solve: (88.76 + 161) - 152", "answer": "The result of (88.76 + 161) - 152 is 97.76", "a": 88.76, "b": 161, "c": 152, "op1": "+", "op2": "-", "result": 97.76}
{"question": "Solve: (92 * 99.08) + 6", "answer": "The result of (92 * 99.08) + 6 is 9121.36", "a": 92, "b": 99.08, "c": 6, "op1": "*", "op2": "+", "result": 9121.36}
{"question": "Solve: (123 * 159) + 115.85", "answer": "The result of (123 * 159) + 115.85 is 19672.85", "a": 123, "b": 159, "c": 115.85, "op1": "*", "op2": "+", "result": 19672.85}
{"question": "Solve: (88 / 80) + 38.63", "answer": "The result of (88 / 80) + 38.63 is 39.73", "a": 88, "b": 80, "c": 38.63, "op1": "/", "op2": "+", "result": 39.73}
{"question": "Solve: (13 + 86) * 166", "answer": "The result of (13 + 86) * 166 is 16434", "a": 13, "b": 86, "c": 166, "op1": "+", "op2": "*", "result": 16434}
{"question": "Solve: (33 - 47.57) * 191", "answer": "The result of (33 - 47.57) * 191 is -2782.87", "a": 33, "b": 47.57, "c": 191, "op1": "-", "op2": "*", "result": -2782.87}
{"question": "Solve: (173 / 143.0) + 155", "answer": "The result of (173 / 143.0) + 155 is 156.21", "a": 173, "b": 143.0, "c": 155, "op1": "/", "op2": "+", "result": 156.21}
{"question": "Solve: (10 * 165) / 193", "answer": "The result of (10 * 165) / 193 is 8.55", "a": 10, "b": 165, "c": 193, "op1": "*", "op2": "/", "result": 8.55}
{"question": "Solve: (52 + 102) - 50", "answer": "The result of (52 + 102) - 50 is 104", "a": 52, "b": 102, "c": 50, "op1": "+", "op2": "-", "result": 104}
{"question": "Solve: (162.31 * 74.33) - 50.16", "answer": "The result of (162.31 * 74.33) - 50.16 is 12014.34", "a": 162.31, "b": 74.33, "c": 50.16, "op1": "*", "op2": "-", "result": 12014.34}
{"question": "Solve: (49 - 177) - 126", "answer": "The result of (49 - 177) - 126 is -254", "a": 49, "b": 177, "c": 126, "op1": "-", "op2": "-", "result": -254}
{"question": "Solve: (49 * 120) * 26", "answer": "The result of (49 * 120) * 26 is 152880", "a": 49, "b": 120, "c": 26, "op1": "*", "op2": "*", "result": 152880}
{"question": "Solve: (127 / 172) - 197.78", "answer": "The result of (127 / 172) - 197.78 is -197.04", "a": 127, "b": 172, "c": 197.78, "op1": "/", "op2": "-", "result": -197.04}
{"question": "Solve: (25.5 + 140.57) - 95", "answer": "The result of (25.5 + 140.57) - 95 is 71.07", "a": 25.5, "b": 140.57, "c": 95, "op1": "+", "op2": "-", "result": 71.07}
{"question": "Solve: (44 - 50) - 68.75", "answer": "The result of (44 - 50) - 68.75 is -74.75", "a": 44, "b": 50, "c": 68.75, "op1": "-", "op2": "-", "result": -74.75}
{"question": "Solve: (46 * 157) + 31", "answer": "The result of (46 * 157) + 31 is 7253", "a": 46, "b": 157, "c": 31, "op1": "*", "op2": "+", "result": 7253}
{"question": "Solve: (196 * 174) * 25", "answer": "The result of (196 * 174) * 25 is 852600", "a": 196, "b": 174, "c": 25, "op1": "*", "op2": "*", "result": 852600}
{"question": "Solve: (142.64 * 7) - 82.17", "answer": "The result of (142.64 * 7) - 82.17 is 916.31", "a": 142.64, "b": 7, "c": 82.17, "op1": "*", "op2": "-", "result": 916.31}
{"question": "Solve: (112 + 177) * 66", "answer": "The result of (112 + 177) * 66 is 19074", "a": 112, "b": 177, "c": 66, "op1": "+", "op2": "*", "result": 19074}
{"question": "Solve: (88.81 - 161.52) * 181", "answer": "The result of (88.81 - 161.52) * 181 is -13160.51", "a": 88.81, "b": 161.52, "c": 181, "op1": "-", "op2": "*", "result": -13160.51}
{"question": "Solve: (45.29 * 48.68) + 41.94", "answer": "The result of (45.29 * 48.68) + 41.94 is 2246.66", "a": 45.29, "b": 48.68, "c": 41.94, "op1": "*", "op2": "+", "result": 2246.66}
{"question": "Solve: (116.06 * 145.67) + 153", "answer": "The result of (116.06 * 145.67) + 153 is 17059.46", "a": 116.06, "b": 145.67, "c": 153, "op1": "*", "op2": "+", "result": 17059.46}
{"question": "Solve: (81 / 66) * 166.98", "answer": "The result of (81 / 66) * 166.98 is 204.93", "a": 81, "b": 66, "c": 166.98, "op1": "/", "op2": "*", "result": 204.93}
{"question": "Solve: (54.27 * 51) * 33", "answer": "The result of (54.27 * 51) * 33 is 91336.41", "a": 54.27, "b": 51, "c": 33, "op1": "*", "op2": "*", "result": 91336.41}
{"question": "Solve: (69 + 78) * 82.14", "answer": "The result of (69 + 78) * 82.14 is 12074.58", "a": 69, "b": 78, "c": 82.14, "op1": "+", "op2": "*", "result": 12074.58}
{"question": "Solve: (190 + 174) + 189", "answer": "The result of (190 + 174) + 189 is 553", "a": 190, "b": 174, "c": 189, "op1": "+", "op2": "+", "result": 553}
{"question": "Solve: (51 - 89.45) - 19", "answer": "The result of (51 - 89.45) - 19 is -57.45", "a": 51, "b": 89.45, "c": 19, "op1": "-", "op2": "-", "result": -57.45}
{"question": "Solve: (120 + 77) - 16", "answer": "The result of (120 + 77) - 16 is 181", "a": 120, "b": 77, "c": 16, "op1": "+", "op2": "-", "result": 181}
{"question": "Solve: (33 + 148) + 61", "answer": "The result of (33 + 148) + 61 is 242", "a": 33, "b": 148, "c": 61, "op1": "+", "op2": "+", "result": 242}
{"question": "Solve: (18.77 / 2) + 50", "answer": "The result of (18.77 / 2) + 50 is 59.38", "a": 18.77, "b": 2, "c": 50, "op1": "/", "op2": "+", "result": 59.38}
{"question": "Solve: (113 + 52.83) - 57", "answer": "The result of (113 + 52.83) - 57 is 108.83", "a": 113, "b": 52.83, "c": 57, "op1": "+", "op2": "-", "result": 108.83}
{"question": "Solve: (45 + 103) + 9", "answer": "The result of (45 + 103) + 9 is 157", "a": 45, "b": 103, "c": 9, "op1": "+", "op2": "+", "result": 157}
{"question": "Solve: (47 / 5) - 187", "answer": "The result of (47 / 5) - 187 is -177.6", "a": 47, "b": 5, "c": 187, "op1": "/", "op2": "-", "result": -177.6}
{"question": "Solve: (154 - 44) / 142", "answer": "The result of (154 - 44) / 142 is 0.77", "a": 154, "b": 44, "c": 142, "op1": "-", "op2": "/", "result": 0.77}
{"question": "Solve: (87.49 * 12) * 97", "answer": "The result of (87.49 * 12) * 97 is 101838.36", "a": 87.49, "b": 12, "c": 97, "op1": "*", "op2": "*", "result": 101838.36}
{"question": "Solve: (80 - 156) - 133.9", "answer": "The result of (80 - 156) - 133.9 is -209.9", "a": 80, "b": 156, "c": 133.9, "op1": "-", "op2": "-", "result": -209.9}
{"question": "Solve: (7.32 + 138) + 120", "answer": "The result of (7.32 + 138) + 120 is 265.32", "a": 7.32, "b": 138, "c": 120, "op1": "+", "op2": "+", "result": 265.32}
{"question": "Solve: (102 + 99) - 143", "answer": "The result of (102 + 99) - 143 is 58", "a": 102, "b": 99, "c": 143, "op1": "+", "op2": "-", "result": 58}
{"question": "Solve: (68 - 15) * 176.78", "answer": "The result of (68 - 15) * 176.78 is 9369.34", "a": 68, "b": 15, "c": 176.78, "op1": "-", "op2": "*", "result": 9369.34}
{"question": "Solve: (37 * 73.6) + 186.85", "answer": "The result of (37 * 73.6) + 186.85 is 2910.05", "a": 37, "b": 73.6, "c": 186.85, "op1": "*", "op2": "+", "result": 2910.05}
{"question": "Solve: (98 / 54) - 82.76", "answer": "The result of (98 / 54) - 82.76 is -80.95", "a": 98, "b": 54, "c": 82.76, "op1": "/", "op2": "-", "result": -80.95}
{"question": "Solve: (178 - 119) * 169", "answer": "The result of (178 - 119) * 169 is 9971", "a": 178, "b": 119, "c": 169, "op1": "-", "op2": "*", "result": 9971}
{"question": "Solve: (1 + 144.03) - 140", "answer": "The result of (1 + 144.03) - 140 is 5.03", "a": 1, "b": 144.03, "c": 140, "op1": "+", "op2": "-", "result": 5.03}
{"question": "Solve: (172 + 60.6) / 9.33", "answer": "The result of (172 + 60.6) / 9.33 is 24.93", "a": 172, "b": 60.6, "c": 9.33, "op1": "+", "op2": "/", "result": 24.93}
{"question": "Solve: (144.61 - 11.86) + 194.0", "answer": "The result of (144.61 - 11.86) + 194.0 is 326.75", "a": 144.61, "b": 11.86, "c": 194.0, "op1": "-", "op2": "+", "result": 326.75}
{"question": "Solve: (171.41 + 26) + 148", "answer": "The result of (171.41 + 26) + 148 is 345.41", "a": 171.41, "b": 26, "c": 148, "op1": "+", "op2": "+", "result": 345.41}
{"question": "Solve: (25 - 141) / 78.55", "answer": "The result of (25 - 141) / 78.55 is -1.48", "a": 25, "b": 141, "c": 78.55, "op1": "-", "op2": "/", "result": -1.48}
{"question": "Solve: (169 / 71) + 30", "answer": "The result of (169 / 71) + 30 is 32.38", "a": 169, "b": 71, "c": 30, "op1": "/", "op2": "+", "result": 32.38}
{"question": "Solve: (130.82 - 114) - 144.44", "answer": "The result of (130.82 - 114) - 144.44 is -127.62", "a": 130.82, "b": 114, "c": 144.44, "op1": "-", "op2": "-", "result": -127.62}
{"question": "Solve: (160 - 137) * 165", "answer": "The result of (160 - 137) * 165 is 3795", "a": 160, "b": 137, "c": 165, "op1": "-", "op2": "*", "result": 3795}
{"question": "Solve: (62 + 99) - 44.51", "answer": "The result of (62 + 99) - 44.51 is 116.49", "a": 62, "b": 99, "c": 44.51, "op1": "+", "op2": "-", "result": 116.49}
{"question": "Solve: (103 + 194) / 12", "answer": "The result of (103 + 194) / 12 is 24.75", "a": 103, "b": 194, "c": 12, "op1": "+", "op2": "/", "result": 24.75}
{"question": "Solve: (7.49 + 133.41) / 62", "answer": "The result of (7.49 + 133.41) / 62 is 2.27", "a": 7.49, "b": 133.41, "c": 62, "op1": "+", "op2": "/", "result": 2.27}
{"question": "Solve: (100.35 - 20) / 109.24", "answer": "The result of (100.35 - 20) / 109.24 is 0.74", "a": 100.35, "b": 20, "c": 109.24, "op1": "-", "op2": "/", "result": 0.74}
{"question": "Solve: (176 * 196.37) * 46", "answer": "The result of (176 * 196.37) * 46 is 1589811.52", "a": 176, "b": 196.37, "c": 46, "op1": "*", "op2": "*", "result": 1589811.52}
{"question": "Solve: (61 * 175.78) + 102.84", "answer": "The result of (61 * 175.78) + 102.84 is 10825.42", "a": 61, "b": 175.78, "c": 102.84, "op1": "*", "op2": "+", "result": 10825.42}
{"question": "Solve: (12.61 + 169.65) / 143.57", "answer": "The result of (12.61 + 169.65) / 143.57 is 1.27", "a": 12.61, "b": 169.65, "c": 143.57, "op1": "+", "op2": "/", "result": 1.27}
{"question": "Solve: (12 / 134.73) - 166", "answer": "The result of (12 / 134.73) - 166 is -165.91", "a": 12, "b": 134.73, "c": 166, "op1": "/", "op2": "-", "result": -165.91}
{"question": "Solve: (150 + 132.59) - 179", "answer": "The result of (150 + 132.59) - 179 is 103.59", "a": 150, "b": 132.59, "c": 179, "op1": "+", "op2": "-", "result": 103.59}
{"question": "Solve: (23.49 * 1) + 19", "answer": "The result of (23.49 * 1) + 19 is 42.49", "a": 23.49, "b": 1, "c": 19, "op1": "*", "op2": "+", "result": 42.49}
{"question": "Solve: (153 / 121) * 175", "answer": "The result of (153 / 121) * 175 is 221.28", "a": 153, "b": 121, "c": 175, "op1": "/", "op2": "*", "result": 221.28}
{"question": "Solve: (36 * 136) + 17", "answer": "The result of (36 * 136) + 17 is 4913", "a": 36, "b": 136, "c": 17, "op1": "*", "op2": "+", "result": 4913}
{"question": "Solve: (164 + 107) / 17", "answer": "The result of (164 + 107) / 17 is 15.94", "a": 164, "b": 107, "c": 17, "op1": "+", "op2": "/", "result": 15.94}
{"question": "Solve: (121 - 167) / 101", "answer": "The result of (121 - 167) / 101 is -0.46", "a": 121, "b": 167, "c": 101, "op1": "-", "op2": "/", "result": -0.46}
{"question": "Solve: (127.36 - 41) / 60", "answer": "The result of (127.36 - 41) / 60 is 1.44", "a": 127.36, "b": 41, "c": 60, "op1": "-", "op2": "/", "result": 1.44}
{"question": "Solve: (53.19 + 31) - 48.07", "answer": "The result of (53.19 + 31) - 48.07 is 36.12", "a": 53.19, "b": 31, "c": 48.07, "op1": "+", "op2": "-", "result": 36.12}
{"question": "Solve: (185 * 71.98) + 173", "answer": "The result of (185 * 71.98) + 173 is 13489.3", "a": 185, "b": 71.98, "c": 173, "op1": "*", "op2": "+", "result": 13489.3}
{"question": "Solve: (126 - 59) - 89", "answer": "The result of (126 - 59) - 89 is -22", "a": 126, "b": 59, "c": 89, "op1": "-", "op2": "-", "result": -22}
{"question": "Solve: (3 * 99) - 90", "answer": "The result of (3 * 99) - 90 is 207", "a": 3, "b": 99, "c": 90, "op1": "*", "op2": "-", "result": 207}
{"question": "Solve: (4.23 - 106) - 146.07", "answer": "The result of (4.23 - 106) - 146.07 is -247.84", "a": 4.23, "b": 106, "c": 146.07, "op1": "-", "op2": "-", "result": -247.84}
{"question": "Solve: (187 - 46) + 175.2", "answer": "The result of (187 - 46) + 175.2 is 316.2", "a": 187, "b": 46, "c": 175.2, "op1": "-", "op2": "+", "result": 316.2}
{"question": "Solve: (158 + 139) - 129", "answer": "The result of (158 + 139) - 129 is 168", "a": 158, "b": 139, "c": 129, "op1": "+", "op2": "-", "result": 168}
{"question": "Solve: (189.42 + 80.65) + 90", "answer": "The result of (189.42 + 80.65) + 90 is 360.07", "a": 189.42, "b": 80.65, "c": 90, "op1": "+", "op2": "+", "result": 360.07}
{"question": "Solve: (155 - 160) * 160.91", "answer": "The result of (155 - 160) * 160.91 is -804.55", "a": 155, "b": 160, "c": 160.91, "op1": "-", "op2": "*", "result": -804.55}
{"question": "Solve: (163.14 + 102) + 137.75", "answer": "The result of (163.14 + 102) + 137.75 is 402.89", "a": 163.14, "b": 102, "c": 137.75, "op1": "+", "op2": "+", "result": 402.89}
{"question": "Solve: (114 / 24) * 191", "answer": "The result of (114 / 24) * 191 is 907.25", "a": 114, "b": 24, "c": 191, "op1": "/", "op2": "*", "result": 907.25}
{"question": "Solve: (174 - 184.03) + 181", "answer": "The result of (174 - 184.03) + 181 is 170.97", "a": 174, "b": 184.03, "c": 181, "op1": "-", "op2": "+", "result": 170.97}
{"question": "Solve: (20 / 101) + 15", "answer": "The result of (20 / 101) + 15 is 15.2", "a": 20, "b": 101, "c": 15, "op1": "/", "op2": "+", "result": 15.2}
{"question": "Solve: (76 * 68) - 86", "answer": "The result of (76 * 68) - 86 is 5082", "a": 76, "b": 68, "c": 86, "op1": "*", "op2": "-", "result": 5082}
{"question": "Solve: (90 + 188) + 69.71", "answer": "The result of (90 + 188) + 69.71 is 347.71", "a": 90, "b": 188, "c": 69.71, "op1": "+", "op2": "+", "result": 347.71}
{"question": "Solve: (60 + 195.1) + 72", "answer": "The result of (60 + 195.1) + 72 is 327.1", "a": 60, "b": 195.1, "c": 72, "op1": "+", "op2": "+", "result": 327.1}
{"question": "Solve: (181 / 198.18) * 83", "answer": "The result of (181 / 198.18) * 83 is 75.8", "a": 181, "b": 198.18, "c": 83, "op1": "/", "op2": "*", "result": 75.8}
{"question": "Solve: (148 + 113) * 95", "answer": "The result of (148 + 113) * 95 is 24795", "a": 148, "b": 113, "c": 95, "op1": "+", "op2": "*", "result": 24795}
{"question": "Solve: (99 - 1.61) - 97", "answer": "The result of (99 - 1.61) - 97 is 0.39", "a": 99, "b": 1.61, "c": 97, "op1": "-", "op2": "-", "result": 0.39}
{"question": "Solve: (82 + 195) + 28", "answer": "The result of (82 + 195) + 28 is 305", "a": 82, "b": 195, "c": 28, "op1": "+", "op2": "+", "result": 305}
{"question": "Solve: (111 / 101) + 63", "answer": "The result of (111 / 101) + 63 is 64.1", "a": 111, "b": 101, "c": 63, "op1": "/", "op2": "+", "result": 64.1}
{"question": "Solve: (108 * 5) - 45.82", "answer": "The result of (108 * 5) - 45.82 is 494.18", "a": 108, "b": 5, "c": 45.82, "op1": "*", "op2": "-", "result": 494.18}
{"question": "Solve: (190.99 * 172.63) + 152", "answer": "The result of (190.99 * 172.63) + 152 is 33122.6", "a": 190.99, "b": 172.63, "c": 152, "op1": "*", "op2": "+", "result": 33122.6}
{"question": "Solve: (19 + 25) * 56.73", "answer": "The result of (19 + 25) * 56.73 is 2496.12", "a": 19, "b": 25, "c": 56.73, "op1": "+", "op2": "*", "result": 2496.12}
{"question": "Solve: (81.44 - 121) + 4", "answer": "The result of (81.44 - 121) + 4 is -35.56", "a": 81.44, "b": 121, "c": 4, "op1": "-", "op2": "+", "result": -35.56}
{"question": "Solve: (170 - 62.92) + 9.23", "answer": "The result of (170 - 62.92) + 9.23 is 116.31", "a": 170, "b": 62.92, "c": 9.23, "op1": "-", "op2": "+", "result": 116.31}
{"question": "Solve: (141.4 * 35) / 194.98", "answer": "The result of (141.4 * 35) / 194.98 is 25.38", "a": 141.4, "b": 35, "c": 194.98, "op1": "*", "op2": "/", "result": 25.38}
{"question": "Solve: (150 * 170) * 154.14", "answer": "The result of (150 * 170) * 154.14 is 3930570.0", "a": 150, "b": 170, "c": 154.14, "op1": "*", "op2": "*", "result": 3930570.0}
{"question": "Solve: (179.09 - 146.01) + 102", "answer": "The result of (179.09 - 146.01) + 102 is 135.08", "a": 179.09, "b": 146.01, "c": 102, "op1": "-", "op2": "+", "result": 135.08}
{"question": "Solve: (169.34 - 5) - 60.14", "answer": "The result of (169.34 - 5) - 60.14 is 104.2", "a": 169.34, "b": 5, "c": 60.14, "op1": "-", "op2": "-", "result": 104.2}
{"question": "Solve: (43 / 186.74) - 181", "answer": "The result of (43 / 186.74) - 181 is -180.77", "a": 43, "b": 186.74, "c": 181, "op1": "/", "op2": "-", "result": -180.77}
{"question": "Solve: (34.89 * 8.25) * 171", "answer": "The result of (34.89 * 8.25) * 171 is 49221.07", "a": 34.89, "b": 8.25, "c": 171, "op1": "*", "op2": "*", "result": 49221.07}
{"question": "Solve: (135.23 - 79) * 167.26", "answer": "The result of (135.23 - 79) * 167.26 is 9405.03", "a": 135.23, "b": 79, "c": 167.26, "op1": "-", "op2": "*", "result": 9405.03}
{"question": "Solve: (92 - 122) * 104", "answer": "The result of (92 - 122) * 104 is -3120", "a": 92, "b": 122, "c": 104, "op1": "-", "op2": "*", "result": -3120}
{"question": "Solve: (194 + 156.8) + 108", "answer": "The result of (194 + 156.8) + 108 is 458.8", "a": 194, "b": 156.8, "c": 108, "op1": "+", "op2": "+", "result": 458.8}
{"question": "Solve: (170.67 + 28.63) - 169.01", "answer": "The result of (170.67 + 28.63) - 169.01 is 30.29", "a": 170.67, "b": 28.63, "c": 169.01, "op1": "+", "op2": "-", "result": 30.29}
{"question": "Solve: (143 - 21.71) / 88", "answer": "The result of (143 - 21.71) / 88 is 1.38", "a": 143, "b": 21.71, "c": 88, "op1": "-", "op2": "/", "result": 1.38}
{"question": "Solve: (108 * 92.38) - 183.45", "answer": "The result of (108 * 92.38) - 183.45 is 9793.59", "a": 108, "b": 92.38, "c": 183.45, "op1": "*", "op2": "-", "result": 9793.59}
{"question": "Solve: (179 + 169) * 5.67", "answer": "The result of (179 + 169) * 5.67 is 1973.16", "a": 179, "b": 169, "c": 5.67, "op1": "+", "op2": "*", "result": 1973.16}
{"question": "Solve: (86 * 90) * 92.97", "answer": "The result of (86 * 90) * 92.97 is 719587.8", "a": 86, "b": 90, "c": 92.97, "op1": "*", "op2": "*", "result": 719587.8}
{"question": "Solve: (147.15 * 108.27) * 161", "answer": "The result of (147.15 * 108.27) * 161 is 2565040.81", "a": 147.15, "b": 108.27, "c": 161, "op1": "*", "op2": "*", "result": 2565040.81}
{"question": "Solve: (130.62 + 99) + 7", "answer": "The result of (130.62 + 99) + 7 is 236.62", "a": 130.62, "b": 99, "c": 7, "op1": "+", "op2": "+", "result": 236.62}
{"question": "Solve: (177.33 + 194) * 132", "answer": "The result of (177.33 + 194) * 132 is 49015.56", "a": 177.33, "b": 194, "c": 132, "op1": "+", "op2": "*", "result": 49015.56}
{"question": "Solve: (150 - 157.13) - 27", "answer": "The result of (150 - 157.13) - 27 is -34.13", "a": 150, "b": 157.13, "c": 27, "op1": "-", "op2": "-", "result": -34.13}
{"question": "Solve: (85.04 * 25.54) * 175.4", "answer": "The result of (85.04 * 25.54) * 175.4 is 380955.05", "a": 85.04, "b": 25.54, "c": 175.4, "op1": "*", "op2": "*", "result": 380955.05}
{"question": "Solve: (102 + 81.18) * 69", "answer": "The result of (102 + 81.18) * 69 is 12639.42", "a": 102, "b": 81.18, "c": 69, "op1": "+", "op2": "*", "result": 12639.42}
{"question": "Solve: (106 / 9.8) + 44", "answer": "The result of (106 / 9.8) + 44 is 54.82", "a": 106, "b": 9.8, "c": 44, "op1": "/", "op2": "+", "result": 54.82}
{"question": "Solve: (17 / 173) + 172", "answer": "The result of (17 / 173) + 172 is 172.1", "a": 17, "b": 173, "c": 172, "op1": "/", "op2": "+", "result": 172.1}
{"question": "Solve: (141 + 84) + 118", "answer": "The result of (141 + 84) + 118 is 343", "a": 141, "b": 84, "c": 118, "op1": "+", "op2": "+", "result": 343}
{"question": "Solve: (45.22 + 61.14) + 134.93", "answer": "The result of (45.22 + 61.14) + 134.93 is 241.29", "a": 45.22, "b": 61.14, "c": 134.93, "op1": "+", "op2": "+", "result": 241.29}
{"question": "Solve: (85 / 136.33) + 73.61", "answer": "The result of (85 / 136.33) + 73.61 is 74.23", "a": 85, "b": 136.33, "c": 73.61, "op1": "/", "op2": "+", "result": 74.23}
{"question": "Solve: (120 * 172) - 53", "answer": "The result of (120 * 172) - 53 is 20587", "a": 120, "b": 172, "c": 53, "op1": "*", "op2": "-", "result": 20587}
{"question": "Solve: (77.71 + 21) - 134", "answer": "The result of (77.71 + 21) - 134 is -35.29", "a": 77.71, "b": 21, "c": 134, "op1": "+", "op2": "-", "result": -35.29}
{"question": "Solve: (123.91 - 41.49) * 154.65", "answer": "The result of (123.91 - 41.49) * 154.65 is 12746.25", "a": 123.91, "b": 41.49, "c": 154.65, "op1": "-", "op2": "*", "result": 12746.25}
{"question": "Solve: (188 * 94) - 147.66", "answer": "The result of (188 * 94) - 147.66 is 17524.34", "a": 188, "b": 94, "c": 147.66, "op1": "*", "op2": "-", "result": 17524.34}
{"question": "Solve: (129.7 - 146) - 79", "answer": "The result of (129.7 - 146) - 79 is -95.3", "a": 129.7, "b": 146, "c": 79, "op1": "-", "op2": "-", "result": -95.3}
{"question": "Solve: (41 - 32) + 44", "answer": "The result of (41 - 32) + 44 is 53", "a": 41, "b": 32, "c": 44, "op1": "-", "op2": "+", "result": 53}
{"question": "Solve: (91 * 76.23) - 45.93", "answer": "The result of (91 * 76.23) - 45.93 is 6891.0", "a": 91, "b": 76.23, "c": 45.93, "op1": "*", "op2": "-", "result": 6891.0}
{"question": "Solve: (179.92 * 19.93) - 103", "answer": "The result of (179.92 * 19.93) - 103 is 3482.81", "a": 179.92, "b": 19.93, "c": 103, "op1": "*", "op2": "-", "result": 3482.81}
{"question": "Solve: (171 - 171) - 96", "answer": "The result of (171 - 171) - 96 is -96", "a": 171, "b": 171, "c": 96, "op1": "-", "op2": "-", "result": -96}
{"question": "Solve: (183 + 58.67) * 192", "answer": "The result of (183 + 58.67) * 192 is 46400.64", "a": 183, "b": 58.67, "c": 192, "op1": "+", "op2": "*", "result": 46400.64}
{"question": "Solve: (46.68 / 9.92) - 182", "answer": "The result of (46.68 / 9.92) - 182 is -177.29", "a": 46.68, "b": 9.92, "c": 182, "op1": "/", "op2": "-", "result": -177.29}
{"question": "Solve: (48 + 149) * 181", "answer": "The result of (48 + 149) * 181 is 35657", "a": 48, "b": 149, "c": 181, "op1": "+", "op2": "*", "result": 35657}
{"question": "Solve: (46 - 159) + 63.68", "answer": "The result of (46 - 159) + 63.68 is -49.32", "a": 46, "b": 159, "c": 63.68, "op1": "-", "op2": "+", "result": -49.32}
{"question": "Solve: (171.72 + 110) + 93", "answer": "The result of (171.72 + 110) + 93 is 374.72", "a": 171.72, "b": 110, "c": 93, "op1": "+", "op2": "+", "result": 374.72}
{"question": "Solve: (16 / 47) - 76", "answer": "The result of (16 / 47) - 76 is -75.66", "a": 16, "b": 47, "c": 76, "op1": "/", "op2": "-", "result": -75.66}
{"question": "Solve: (85.28 * 193) - 59", "answer": "The result of (85.28 * 193) - 59 is 16400.04", "a": 85.28, "b": 193, "c": 59, "op1": "*", "op2": "-", "result": 16400.04}
{"question": "Solve: (79 - 75) + 139", "answer": "The result of (79 - 75) + 139 is 143", "a": 79, "b": 75, "c": 139, "op1": "-", "op2": "+", "result": 143}
{"question": "Solve: (173 / 174) - 143", "answer": "The result of (173 / 174) - 143 is -142.01", "a": 173, "b": 174, "c": 143, "op1": "/", "op2": "-", "result": -142.01}
{"question": "Solve: (14.53 - 138) / 11.64", "answer": "The result of (14.53 - 138) / 11.64 is -10.61", "a": 14.53, "b": 138, "c": 11.64, "op1": "-", "op2": "/", "result": -10.61}
{"question": "Solve: (45 - 155.81) * 74", "answer": "The result of (45 - 155.81) * 74 is -8199.94", "a": 45, "b": 155.81, "c": 74, "op1": "-", "op2": "*", "result": -8199.94}
{"question": "Solve: (117 * 164.83) / 5", "answer": "The result of (117 * 164.83) / 5 is 3857.02", "a": 117, "b": 164.83, "c": 5, "op1": "*", "op2": "/", "result": 3857.02}
{"question": "Solve: (35 - 55) - 185", "answer": "The result of (35 - 55) - 185 is -205", "a": 35, "b": 55, "c": 185, "op1": "-", "op2": "-", "result": -205}
{"question": "Solve: (7 - 103) - 88.37", "answer": "The result of (7 - 103) - 88.37 is -184.37", "a": 7, "b": 103, "c": 88.37, "op1": "-", "op2": "-", "result": -184.37}
{"question": "Solve: (146.41 + 152.43) - 118", "answer": "The result of (146.41 + 152.43) - 118 is 180.84", "a": 146.41, "b": 152.43, "c": 118, "op1": "+", "op2": "-", "result": 180.84}
{"question": "Solve: (141.47 - 181) - 185", "answer": "The result of (141.47 - 181) - 185 is -224.53", "a": 141.47, "b": 181, "c": 185, "op1": "-", "op2": "-", "result": -224.53}
{"question": "Solve: (141.69 / 104) + 171", "answer": "The result of (141.69 / 104) + 171 is 172.36", "a": 141.69, "b": 104, "c": 171, "op1": "/", "op2": "+", "result": 172.36}
{"question": "Solve: (30 / 32) * 168", "answer": "The result of (30 / 32) * 168 is 157.5", "a": 30, "b": 32, "c": 168, "op1": "/", "op2": "*", "result": 157.5}
{"question": "Solve: (159 - 118.82) * 144.34", "answer": "The result of (159 - 118.82) * 144.34 is 5799.58", "a": 159, "b": 118.82, "c": 144.34, "op1": "-", "op2": "*", "result": 5799.58}
{"question": "Solve: (37 * 16) - 50.09", "answer": "The result of (37 * 16) - 50.09 is 541.91", "a": 37, "b": 16, "c": 50.09, "op1": "*", "op2": "-", "result": 541.91}
{"question": "Solve: (169 + 134) / 103.16", "answer": "The result of (169 + 134) / 103.16 is 2.94", "a": 169, "b": 134, "c": 103.16, "op1": "+", "op2": "/", "result": 2.94}
{"question": "Solve: (63 * 2) * 107.6", "answer": "The result of (63 * 2) * 107.6 is 13557.6", "a": 63, "b": 2, "c": 107.6, "op1": "*", "op2": "*", "result": 13557.6}
{"question": "Solve: (125.95 + 172.36) - 193", "answer": "The result of (125.95 + 172.36) - 193 is 105.31", "a": 125.95, "b": 172.36, "c": 193, "op1": "+", "op2": "-", "result": 105.31}
{"question": "Solve: (86 + 69) + 100", "answer": "The result of (86 + 69) + 100 is 255", "a": 86, "b": 69, "c": 100, "op1": "+", "op2": "+", "result": 255}
{"question": "Solve: (105 * 175) - 156.75", "answer": "The result of (105 * 175) - 156.75 is 18218.25", "a": 105, "b": 175, "c": 156.75, "op1": "*", "op2": "-", "result": 18218.25}
{"question": "Solve: (159 + 127) * 72.52", "answer": "The result of (159 + 127) * 72.52 is 20740.72", "a": 159, "b": 127, "c": 72.52, "op1": "+", "op2": "*", "result": 20740.72}
{"question": "Solve: (37.72 - 119) - 107.47", "answer": "The result of (37.72 - 119) - 107.47 is -188.75", "a": 37.72, "b": 119, "c": 107.47, "op1": "-", "op2": "-", "result": -188.75}
{"question": "Solve: (2 + 88) + 171", "answer": "The result of (2 + 88) + 171 is 261", "a": 2, "b": 88, "c": 171, "op1": "+", "op2": "+", "result": 261}
{"question": "Solve: (26.88 - 153.86) - 68", "answer": "The result of (26.88 - 153.86) - 68 is -194.98", "a": 26.88, "b": 153.86, "c": 68, "op1": "-", "op2": "-", "result": -194.98}
{"question": "Solve: (177 * 99.58) * 159", "answer": "The result of (177 * 99.58) * 159 is 2802479.94", "a": 177, "b": 99.58, "c": 159, "op1": "*", "op2": "*", "result": 2802479.94}
{"question": "Solve: (62 * 59.79) / 183", "answer": "The result of (62 * 59.79) / 183 is 20.26", "a": 62, "b": 59.79, "c": 183, "op1": "*", "op2": "/", "result": 20.26}
{"question": "Solve: (141 * 129) / 169", "answer": "The result of (141 * 129) / 169 is 107.63", "a": 141, "b": 129, "c": 169, "op1": "*", "op2": "/", "result": 107.63}
{"question": "Solve: (24.01 - 91) / 183.3", "answer": "The result of (24.01 - 91) / 183.3 is -0.37", "a": 24.01, "b": 91, "c": 183.3, "op1": "-", "op2": "/", "result": -0.37}
{"question": "Solve: (40 * 88) - 36", "answer": "The result of (40 * 88) - 36 is 3484", "a": 40, "b": 88, "c": 36, "op1": "*", "op2": "-", "result": 3484}
{"question": "Solve: (151 - 171) / 87.64", "answer": "The result of (151 - 171) / 87.64 is -0.23", "a": 151, "b": 171, "c": 87.64, "op1": "-", "op2": "/", "result": -0.23}
{"question": "Solve: (23 - 35) - 82", "answer": "The result of (23 - 35) - 82 is -94", "a": 23, "b": 35, "c": 82, "op1": "-", "op2": "-", "result": -94}
{"question": "Solve: (46 / 21) + 173", "answer": "The result of (46 / 21) + 173 is 175.19", "a": 46, "b": 21, "c": 173, "op1": "/", "op2": "+", "result": 175.19}
{"question": "Solve: (125 * 148.99) + 137", "answer": "The result of (125 * 148.99) + 137 is 18760.75", "a": 125, "b": 148.99, "c": 137, "op1": "*", "op2": "+", "result": 18760.75}
{"question": "Solve: (103.4 + 187.36) - 189", "answer": "The result of (103.4 + 187.36) - 189 is 101.76", "a": 103.4, "b": 187.36, "c": 189, "op1": "+", "op2": "-", "result": 101.76}
{"question": "Solve: (6 - 28) + 106", "answer": "The result of (6 - 28) + 106 is 84", "a": 6, "b": 28, "c": 106, "op1": "-", "op2": "+", "result": 84}
{"question": "Solve: (61 / 67.35) / 30", "answer": "The result of (61 / 67.35) / 30 is 0.03", "a": 61, "b": 67.35, "c": 30, "op1": "/", "op2": "/", "result": 0.03}
{"question": "Solve: (167 + 160) + 34", "answer": "The result of (167 + 160) + 34 is 361", "a": 167, "b": 160, "c": 34, "op1": "+", "op2": "+", "result": 361}
{"question": "Solve: (154 / 165) + 173", "answer": "The result of (154 / 165) + 173 is 173.93", "a": 154, "b": 165, "c": 173, "op1": "/", "op2": "+", "result": 173.93}
{"question": "Solve: (79 * 5) + 75.36", "answer": "The result of (79 * 5) + 75.36 is 470.36", "a": 79, "b": 5, "c": 75.36, "op1": "*", "op2": "+", "result": 470.36}
{"question": "Solve: (7.21 / 179) * 18.3", "answer": "The result of (7.21 / 179) * 18.3 is 0.74", "a": 7.21, "b": 179, "c": 18.3, "op1": "/", "op2": "*", "result": 0.74}
{"question": "Solve: (80 - 190) * 52", "answer": "The result of (80 - 190) * 52 is -5720", "a": 80, "b": 190, "c": 52, "op1": "-", "op2": "*", "result": -5720}
{"question": "Solve: (26 - 156.59) * 179", "answer": "The result of (26 - 156.59) * 179 is -23375.61", "a": 26, "b": 156.59, "c": 179, "op1": "-", "op2": "*", "result": -23375.61}
{"question": "Solve: (99 * 120.85) * 179", "answer": "The result of (99 * 120.85) * 179 is 2141582.85", "a": 99, "b": 120.85, "c": 179, "op1": "*", "op2": "*", "result": 2141582.85}
{"question": "Solve: (142 - 33.92) - 149.12", "answer": "The result of (142 - 33.92) - 149.12 is -41.04", "a": 142, "b": 33.92, "c": 149.12, "op1": "-", "op2": "-", "result": -41.04}
{"question": "Solve: (65 + 82) + 97", "answer": "The result of (65 + 82) + 97 is 244", "a": 65, "b": 82, "c": 97, "op1": "+", "op2": "+", "result": 244}
{"question": "Solve: (89 + 31) + 152", "answer": "The result of (89 + 31) + 152 is 272", "a": 89, "b": 31, "c": 152, "op1": "+", "op2": "+", "result": 272}
{"question": "Solve: (151 - 38.58) + 3", "answer": "The result of (151 - 38.58) + 3 is 115.42", "a": 151, "b": 38.58, "c": 3, "op1": "-", "op2": "+", "result": 115.42}
{"question": "Solve: (182 / 96) + 74.84", "answer": "The result of (182 / 96) + 74.84 is 76.74", "a": 182, "b": 96, "c": 74.84, "op1": "/", "op2": "+", "result": 76.74}
{"question": "Solve: (131 - 30) - 176", "answer": "The result of (131 - 30) - 176 is -75", "a": 131, "b": 30, "c": 176, "op1": "-", "op2": "-", "result": -75}
{"question": "Solve: (148 - 93.75) * 42", "answer": "The result of (148 - 93.75) * 42 is 2278.5", "a": 148, "b": 93.75, "c": 42, "op1": "-", "op2": "*", "result": 2278.5}
{"question": "Solve: (51 * 43) - 180.77", "answer": "The result of (51 * 43) - 180.77 is 2012.23", "a": 51, "b": 43, "c": 180.77, "op1": "*", "op2": "-", "result": 2012.23}
{"question": "Solve: (165 * 171) * 51", "answer": "The result of (165 * 171) * 51 is 1438965", "a": 165, "b": 171, "c": 51, "op1": "*", "op2": "*", "result": 1438965}
{"question": "Solve: (50 - 110) + 148.15", "answer": "The result of (50 - 110) + 148.15 is 88.15", "a": 50, "b": 110, "c": 148.15, "op1": "-", "op2": "+", "result": 88.15}
{"question": "Solve: (27.48 + 183.49) - 27", "answer": "The result of (27.48 + 183.49) - 27 is 183.97", "a": 27.48, "b": 183.49, "c": 27, "op1": "+", "op2": "-", "result": 183.97}
{"question": "Solve: (173 * 177) + 74", "answer": "The result of (173 * 177) + 74 is 30695", "a": 173, "b": 177, "c": 74, "op1": "*", "op2": "+", "result": 30695}
{"question": "Solve: (96 / 189) * 146.08", "answer": "The result of (96 / 189) * 146.08 is 74.2", "a": 96, "b": 189, "c": 146.08, "op1": "/", "op2": "*", "result": 74.2}
{"question": "Solve: (146 + 122.57) * 195", "answer": "The result of (146 + 122.57) * 195 is 52371.15", "a": 146, "b": 122.57, "c": 195, "op1": "+", "op2": "*", "result": 52371.15}
{"question": "Solve: (142 / 190) * 145", "answer": "The result of (142 / 190) * 145 is 108.37", "a": 142, "b": 190, "c": 145, "op1": "/", "op2": "*", "result": 108.37}
{"question": "Solve: (177.76 + 177.11) + 195", "answer": "The result of (177.76 + 177.11) + 195 is 549.87", "a": 177.76, "b": 177.11, "c": 195, "op1": "+", "op2": "+", "result": 549.87}
{"question": "Solve: (189 + 17) * 77", "answer": "The result of (189 + 17) * 77 is 15862", "a": 189, "b": 17, "c": 77, "op1": "+", "op2": "*", "result": 15862}
{"question": "Solve: (80 - 161) + 32", "answer": "The result of (80 - 161) + 32 is -49", "a": 80, "b": 161, "c": 32, "op1": "-", "op2": "+", "result": -49}
{"question": "Solve: (174 - 199.5) + 159", "answer": "The result of (174 - 199.5) + 159 is 133.5", "a": 174, "b": 199.5, "c": 159, "op1": "-", "op2": "+", "result": 133.5}
{"question": "Solve: (190.39 / 180) / 62", "answer": "The result of (190.39 / 180) / 62 is 0.02", "a": 190.39, "b": 180, "c": 62, "op1": "/", "op2": "/", "result": 0.02}
{"question": "Solve: (38.03 * 192.57) - 31.22", "answer": "The result of (38.03 * 192.57) - 31.22 is 7292.22", "a": 38.03, "b": 192.57, "c": 31.22, "op1": "*", "op2": "-", "result": 7292.22}
{"question": "Solve: (187 + 179) + 93", "answer": "The result of (187 + 179) + 93 is 459", "a": 187, "b": 179, "c": 93, "op1": "+", "op2": "+", "result": 459}
{"question": "Solve: (190 + 15) + 139", "answer": "The result of (190 + 15) + 139 is 344", "a": 190, "b": 15, "c": 139, "op1": "+", "op2": "+", "result": 344}
{"question": "Solve: (142 - 110.35) * 35", "answer": "The result of (142 - 110.35) * 35 is 1107.75", "a": 142, "b": 110.35, "c": 35, "op1": "-", "op2": "*", "result": 1107.75}
{"question": "Solve: (20 / 123) / 28.35", "answer": "The result of (20 / 123) / 28.35 is 0.01", "a": 20, "b": 123, "c": 28.35, "op1": "/", "op2": "/", "result": 0.01}
{"question": "Solve: (77 - 81) * 156", "answer": "The result of (77 - 81) * 156 is -624", "a": 77, "b": 81, "c": 156, "op1": "-", "op2": "*", "result": -624}
{"question": "Solve: (56 + 4) + 165", "answer": "The result of (56 + 4) + 165 is 225", "a": 56, "b": 4, "c": 165, "op1": "+", "op2": "+", "result": 225}
{"question": "Solve: (175 / 92) * 177.53", "answer": "The result of (175 / 92) * 177.53 is 337.69", "a": 175, "b": 92, "c": 177.53, "op1": "/", "op2": "*", "result": 337.69}
{"question": "Solve: (50.68 - 195.34) - 123", "answer": "The result of (50.68 - 195.34) - 123 is -267.66", "a": 50.68, "b": 195.34, "c": 123, "op1": "-", "op2": "-", "result": -267.66}
{"question": "Solve: (175 + 191) + 70.53", "answer": "The result of (175 + 191) + 70.53 is 436.53", "a": 175, "b": 191, "c": 70.53, "op1": "+", "op2": "+", "result": 436.53}
{"question": "Solve: (162 - 34) / 146", "answer": "The result of (162 - 34) / 146 is 0.88", "a": 162, "b": 34, "c": 146, "op1": "-", "op2": "/", "result": 0.88}
{"question": "Solve: (185 * 74.98) * 108", "answer": "The result of (185 * 74.98) * 108 is 1498100.4", "a": 185, "b": 74.98, "c": 108, "op1": "*", "op2": "*", "result": 1498100.4}
{"question": "Solve: (158 + 158) * 154", "answer": "The result of (158 + 158) * 154 is 48664", "a": 158, "b": 158, "c": 154, "op1": "+", "op2": "*", "result": 48664}
{"question": "Solve: (176 / 68.42) * 66", "answer": "The result of (176 / 68.42) * 66 is 169.77", "a": 176, "b": 68.42, "c": 66, "op1": "/", "op2": "*", "result": 169.77}
{"question": "Solve: (142.24 + 47) + 183", "answer": "The result of (142.24 + 47) + 183 is 372.24", "a": 142.24, "b": 47, "c": 183, "op1": "+", "op2": "+", "result": 372.24}
{"question": "Solve: (173.12 / 66.78) - 166", "answer": "The result of (173.12 / 66.78) - 166 is -163.41", "a": 173.12, "b": 66.78, "c": 166, "op1": "/", "op2": "-", "result": -163.41}
{"question": "Solve: (160 - 72) + 125", "answer": "The result of (160 - 72) + 125 is 213", "a": 160, "b": 72, "c": 125, "op1": "-", "op2": "+", "result": 213}
{"question": "Solve: (188 + 187.9) + 144", "answer": "The result of (188 + 187.9) + 144 is 519.9", "a": 188, "b": 187.9, "c": 144, "op1": "+", "op2": "+", "result": 519.9}
{"question": "Solve: (36 / 187.31) + 114.37", "answer": "The result of (36 / 187.31) + 114.37 is 114.56", "a": 36, "b": 187.31, "c": 114.37, "op1": "/", "op2": "+", "result": 114.56}
{"question": "Solve: (194 * 47) + 16", "answer": "The result of (194 * 47) + 16 is 9134", "a": 194, "b": 47, "c": 16, "op1": "*", "op2": "+", "result": 9134}
{"question": "Solve: (96 + 97) - 4", "answer": "The result of (96 + 97) - 4 is 189", "a": 96, "b": 97, "c": 4, "op1": "+", "op2": "-", "result": 189}
{"question": "Solve: (188.2 - 65.71) - 132", "answer": "The result of (188.2 - 65.71) - 132 is -9.51", "a": 188.2, "b": 65.71, "c": 132, "op1": "-", "op2": "-", "result": -9.51}
{"question": "Solve: (46.32 - 79) + 78.13", "answer": "The result of (46.32 - 79) + 78.13 is 45.45", "a": 46.32, "b": 79, "c": 78.13, "op1": "-", "op2": "+", "result": 45.45}
{"question": "Solve: (144 + 101) - 75", "answer": "The result of (144 + 101) - 75 is 170", "a": 144, "b": 101, "c": 75, "op1": "+", "op2": "-", "result": 170}
{"question": "Solve: (146.1 * 151.66) - 173.02", "answer": "The result of (146.1 * 151.66) - 173.02 is 21984.51", "a": 146.1, "b": 151.66, "c": 173.02, "op1": "*", "op2": "-", "result": 21984.51}
{"question": "Solve: (2.35 + 123.24) * 79", "answer": "The result of (2.35 + 123.24) * 79 is 9921.61", "a": 2.35, "b": 123.24, "c": 79, "op1": "+", "op2": "*", "result": 9921.61}
{"question": "Solve: (102.58 - 47) * 83", "answer": "The result of (102.58 - 47) * 83 is 4613.14", "a": 102.58, "b": 47, "c": 83, "op1": "-", "op2": "*", "result": 4613.14}
{"question": "Solve: (167 + 113) - 94.82", "answer": "The result of (167 + 113) - 94.82 is 185.18", "a": 167, "b": 113, "c": 94.82, "op1": "+", "op2": "-", "result": 185.18}
{"question": "Solve: (131 * 45) + 27", "answer": "The result of (131 * 45) + 27 is 5922", "a": 131, "b": 45, "c": 27, "op1": "*", "op2": "+", "result": 5922}
{"question": "Solve: (145.08 / 123) + 128", "answer": "The result of (145.08 / 123) + 128 is 129.18", "a": 145.08, "b": 123, "c": 128, "op1": "/", "op2": "+", "result": 129.18}
{"question": "Solve: (143 + 3.08) - 187", "answer": "The result of (143 + 3.08) - 187 is -40.92", "a": 143, "b": 3.08, "c": 187, "op1": "+", "op2": "-", "result": -40.92}
{"question": "Solve: (172 - 23) + 198", "answer": "The result of (172 - 23) + 198 is 347", "a": 172, "b": 23, "c": 198, "op1": "-", "op2": "+", "result": 347}
{"question": "Solve: (49 * 165.3) - 158.48", "answer": "The result of (49 * 165.3) - 158.48 is 7941.22", "a": 49, "b": 165.3, "c": 158.48, "op1": "*", "op2": "-", "result": 7941.22}
{"question": "Solve: (181.87 * 18.58) - 171.96", "answer": "The result of (181.87 * 18.58) - 171.96 is 3207.18", "a": 181.87, "b": 18.58, "c": 171.96, "op1": "*", "op2": "-", "result": 3207.18}
{"question": "Solve: (192 + 103) + 85.14", "answer": "The result of (192 + 103) + 85.14 is 380.14", "a": 192, "b": 103, "c": 85.14, "op1": "+", "op2": "+", "result": 380.14}
{"question": "Solve: (34 + 199.1) * 125", "answer": "The result of (34 + 199.1) * 125 is 29137.5", "a": 34, "b": 199.1, "c": 125, "op1": "+", "op2": "*", "result": 29137.5}
{"question": "Solve: (186 + 58.96) + 94.11", "answer": "The result of (186 + 58.96) + 94.11 is 339.07", "a": 186, "b": 58.96, "c": 94.11, "op1": "+", "op2": "+", "result": 339.07}
{"question": "Solve: (15.57 * 88) * 39", "answer": "The result of (15.57 * 88) * 39 is 53436.24", "a": 15.57, "b": 88, "c": 39, "op1": "*", "op2": "*", "result": 53436.24}
{"question": "Solve: (30 + 138) + 172", "answer": "The result of (30 + 138) + 172 is 340", "a": 30, "b": 138, "c": 172, "op1": "+", "op2": "+", "result": 340}
{"question": "Solve: (145 - 113) - 18.78", "answer": "The result of (145 - 113) - 18.78 is 13.22", "a": 145, "b": 113, "c": 18.78, "op1": "-", "op2": "-", "result": 13.22}
{"question": "Solve: (120 / 2) * 175.91", "answer": "The result of (120 / 2) * 175.91 is 10554.6", "a": 120, "b": 2, "c": 175.91, "op1": "/", "op2": "*", "result": 10554.6}
{"question": "Solve: (58 / 136) / 144", "answer": "The result of (58 / 136) / 144 is 0.0", "a": 58, "b": 136, "c": 144, "op1": "/", "op2": "/", "result": 0.0}
{"question": "Solve: (180 + 179) + 52", "answer": "The result of (180 + 179) + 52 is 411", "a": 180, "b": 179, "c": 52, "op1": "+", "op2": "+", "result": 411}
{"question": "Solve: (66 * 169.22) / 94.54", "answer": "The result of (66 * 169.22) / 94.54 is 118.14", "a": 66, "b": 169.22, "c": 94.54, "op1": "*", "op2": "/", "result": 118.14}
{"question": "Solve: (105 - 167) - 116.19", "answer": "The result of (105 - 167) - 116.19 is -178.19", "a": 105, "b": 167, "c": 116.19, "op1": "-", "op2": "-", "result": -178.19}
{"question": "Solve: (165 * 54.56) + 42", "answer": "The result of (165 * 54.56) + 42 is 9044.4", "a": 165, "b": 54.56, "c": 42, "op1": "*", "op2": "+", "result": 9044.4}
{"question": "Solve: (109 - 26.61) - 104", "answer": "The result of (109 - 26.61) - 104 is -21.61", "a": 109, "b": 26.61, "c": 104, "op1": "-", "op2": "-", "result": -21.61}
{"question": "Solve: (39 / 85) + 187", "answer": "The result of (39 / 85) + 187 is 187.46", "a": 39, "b": 85, "c": 187, "op1": "/", "op2": "+", "result": 187.46}
{"question": "Solve: (188 - 152) / 14", "answer": "The result of (188 - 152) / 14 is 2.57", "a": 188, "b": 152, "c": 14, "op1": "-", "op2": "/", "result": 2.57}
{"question": "Solve: (184 * 197.38) * 64", "answer": "The result of (184 * 197.38) * 64 is 2324346.88", "a": 184, "b": 197.38, "c": 64, "op1": "*", "op2": "*", "result": 2324346.88}
{"question": "Solve: (184.67 / 178) / 188.67", "answer": "The result of (184.67 / 178) / 188.67 is 0.01", "a": 184.67, "b": 178, "c": 188.67, "op1": "/", "op2": "/", "result": 0.01}
{"question": "Solve: (119 / 81) * 162", "answer": "The result of (119 / 81) * 162 is 238.0", "a": 119, "b": 81, "c": 162, "op1": "/", "op2": "*", "result": 238.0}
{"question": "Solve: (180 * 152) * 93.44", "answer": "The result of (180 * 152) * 93.44 is 2556518.4", "a": 180, "b": 152, "c": 93.44, "op1": "*", "op2": "*", "result": 2556518.4}
{"question": "Solve: (127 - 48) - 86.19", "answer": "The result of (127 - 48) - 86.19 is -7.19", "a": 127, "b": 48, "c": 86.19, "op1": "-", "op2": "-", "result": -7.19}
{"question": "Solve: (15 - 68) + 186", "answer": "The result of (15 - 68) + 186 is 133", "a": 15, "b": 68, "c": 186, "op1": "-", "op2": "+", "result": 133}
{"question": "Solve: (193.51 / 37) - 199", "answer": "The result of (193.51 / 37) - 199 is -193.77", "a": 193.51, "b": 37, "c": 199, "op1": "/", "op2": "-", "result": -193.77}
{"question": "Solve: (32 - 37) + 52.51", "answer": "The result of (32 - 37) + 52.51 is 47.51", "a": 32, "b": 37, "c": 52.51, "op1": "-", "op2": "+", "result": 47.51}
{"question": "Solve: (22 * 186) - 164.27", "answer": "The result of (22 * 186) - 164.27 is 3927.73", "a": 22, "b": 186, "c": 164.27, "op1": "*", "op2": "-", "result": 3927.73}
{"question": "Solve: (157.88 + 175) - 81.49", "answer": "The result of (157.88 + 175) - 81.49 is 251.39", "a": 157.88, "b": 175, "c": 81.49, "op1": "+", "op2": "-", "result": 251.39}
{"question": "Solve: (59.8 * 20.38) / 188", "answer": "The result of (59.8 * 20.38) / 188 is 6.48", "a": 59.8, "b": 20.38, "c": 188, "op1": "*", "op2": "/", "result": 6.48}
{"question": "Solve: (103.31 - 152) - 128", "answer": "The result of (103.31 - 152) - 128 is -176.69", "a": 103.31, "b": 152, "c": 128, "op1": "-", "op2": "-", "result": -176.69}
{"question": "Solve: (8 / 102) / 20.84", "answer": "The result of (8 / 102) / 20.84 is 0.0", "a": 8, "b": 102, "c": 20.84, "op1": "/", "op2": "/", "result": 0.0}
{"question": "Solve: (138 * 168) + 150.19", "answer": "The result of (138 * 168) + 150.19 is 23334.19", "a": 138, "b": 168, "c": 150.19, "op1": "*", "op2": "+", "result": 23334.19}
{"question": "Solve: (67.36 + 35.59) / 63", "answer": "The result of (67.36 + 35.59) / 63 is 1.63", "a": 67.36, "b": 35.59, "c": 63, "op1": "+", "op2": "/", "result": 1.63}
{"question": "Solve: (102.95 + 94) / 122", "answer": "The result of (102.95 + 94) / 122 is 1.61", "a": 102.95, "b": 94, "c": 122, "op1": "+", "op2": "/", "result": 1.61}
{"question": "Solve: (188.71 - 113.54) * 136.99", "answer": "The result of (188.71 - 113.54) * 136.99 is 10297.54", "a": 188.71, "b": 113.54, "c": 136.99, "op1": "-", "op2": "*", "result": 10297.54}
{"question": "Solve: (97.19 * 2) * 154", "answer": "The result of (97.19 * 2) * 154 is 29934.52", "a": 97.19, "b": 2, "c": 154, "op1": "*", "op2": "*", "result": 29934.52}
{"question": "Solve: (54 + 67) * 178.77", "answer": "The result of (54 + 67) * 178.77 is 21631.17", "a": 54, "b": 67, "c": 178.77, "op1": "+", "op2": "*", "result": 21631.17}
{"question": "Solve: (165.27 * 91) - 138.6", "answer": "The result of (165.27 * 91) - 138.6 is 14900.97", "a": 165.27, "b": 91, "c": 138.6, "op1": "*", "op2": "-", "result": 14900.97}
{"question": "Solve: (21 / 156) + 125", "answer": "The result of (21 / 156) + 125 is 125.13", "a": 21, "b": 156, "c": 125, "op1": "/", "op2": "+", "result": 125.13}
{"question": "Solve: (27 - 176) + 47.51", "answer": "The result of (27 - 176) + 47.51 is -101.49", "a": 27, "b": 176, "c": 47.51, "op1": "-", "op2": "+", "result": -101.49}
{"question": "Solve: (148.3 + 95.06) - 179.82", "answer": "The result of (148.3 + 95.06) - 179.82 is 63.54", "a": 148.3, "b": 95.06, "c": 179.82, "op1": "+", "op2": "-", "result": 63.54}
{"question": "Solve: (166 + 153.27) * 141", "answer": "The result of (166 + 153.27) * 141 is 45017.07", "a": 166, "b": 153.27, "c": 141, "op1": "+", "op2": "*", "result": 45017.07}
{"question": "Solve: (187 * 122) + 33.88", "answer": "The result of (187 * 122) + 33.88 is 22847.88", "a": 187, "b": 122, "c": 33.88, "op1": "*", "op2": "+", "result": 22847.88}
{"question": "Solve: (179.26 - 185.25) + 185.88", "answer": "The result of (179.26 - 185.25) + 185.88 is 179.89", "a": 179.26, "b": 185.25, "c": 185.88, "op1": "-", "op2": "+", "result": 179.89}
{"question": "Solve: (88 * 125.12) * 189", "answer": "The result of (88 * 125.12) * 189 is 2080995.84", "a": 88, "b": 125.12, "c": 189, "op1": "*", "op2": "*", "result": 2080995.84}
{"question": "Solve: (197 + 15.83) - 41.39", "answer": "The result of (197 + 15.83) - 41.39 is 171.44", "a": 197, "b": 15.83, "c": 41.39, "op1": "+", "op2": "-", "result": 171.44}
{"question": "Solve: (76.32 / 86) * 78", "answer": "The result of (76.32 / 86) * 78 is 69.22", "a": 76.32, "b": 86, "c": 78, "op1": "/", "op2": "*", "result": 69.22}
{"question": "Solve: (86 * 78) + 84", "answer": "The result of (86 * 78) + 84 is 6792", "a": 86, "b": 78, "c": 84, "op1": "*", "op2": "+", "result": 6792}
{"question": "Solve: (8 * 106) + 28", "answer": "The result of (8 * 106) + 28 is 876", "a": 8, "b": 106, "c": 28, "op1": "*", "op2": "+", "result": 876}
{"question": "Solve: (85 / 39) * 122", "answer": "The result of (85 / 39) * 122 is 265.9", "a": 85, "b": 39, "c": 122, "op1": "/", "op2": "*", "result": 265.9}
{"question": "Solve: (66.91 / 127.28) * 127.95", "answer": "The result of (66.91 / 127.28) * 127.95 is 67.26", "a": 66.91, "b": 127.28, "c": 127.95, "op1": "/", "op2": "*", "result": 67.26}
{"question": "Solve: (135 / 56) * 171", "answer": "The result of (135 / 56) * 171 is 412.23", "a": 135, "b": 56, "c": 171, "op1": "/", "op2": "*", "result": 412.23}
{"question": "Solve: (65 * 181) / 54", "answer": "The result of (65 * 181) / 54 is 217.87", "a": 65, "b": 181, "c": 54, "op1": "*", "op2": "/", "result": 217.87}
{"question": "Solve: (87 + 188.33) + 126.4", "answer": "The result of (87 + 188.33) + 126.4 is 401.73", "a": 87, "b": 188.33, "c": 126.4, "op1": "+", "op2": "+", "result": 401.73}
{"question": "Solve: (5 + 134.23) - 98", "answer": "The result of (5 + 134.23) - 98 is 41.23", "a": 5, "b": 134.23, "c": 98, "op1": "+", "op2": "-", "result": 41.23}
{"question": "Solve: (24 * 142.68) / 159", "answer": "The result of (24 * 142.68) / 159 is 21.54", "a": 24, "b": 142.68, "c": 159, "op1": "*", "op2": "/", "result": 21.54}
{"question": "Solve: (188 + 75.42) / 144", "answer": "The result of (188 + 75.42) / 144 is 1.83", "a": 188, "b": 75.42, "c": 144, "op1": "+", "op2": "/", "result": 1.83}
{"question": "Solve: (46 / 32.2) * 76", "answer": "The result of (46 / 32.2) * 76 is 108.57", "a": 46, "b": 32.2, "c": 76, "op1": "/", "op2": "*", "result": 108.57}
{"question": "Solve: (111.13 / 81) - 133", "answer": "The result of (111.13 / 81) - 133 is -131.63", "a": 111.13, "b": 81, "c": 133, "op1": "/", "op2": "-", "result": -131.63}
{"question": "Solve: (85.31 - 111) + 154", "answer": "The result of (85.31 - 111) + 154 is 128.31", "a": 85.31, "b": 111, "c": 154, "op1": "-", "op2": "+", "result": 128.31}
{"question": "Solve: (73 - 100.1) / 168", "answer": "The result of (73 - 100.1) / 168 is -0.16", "a": 73, "b": 100.1, "c": 168, "op1": "-", "op2": "/", "result": -0.16}
{"question": "Solve: (9 + 78) / 66.43", "answer": "The result of (9 + 78) / 66.43 is 1.31", "a": 9, "b": 78, "c": 66.43, "op1": "+", "op2": "/", "result": 1.31}
{"question": "Solve: (5 / 168.47) * 169", "answer": "The result of (5 / 168.47) * 169 is 5.02", "a": 5, "b": 168.47, "c": 169, "op1": "/", "op2": "*", "result": 5.02}
{"question": "Solve: (34.0 / 69) / 145", "answer": "The result of (34.0 / 69) / 145 is 0.0", "a": 34.0, "b": 69, "c": 145, "op1": "/", "op2": "/", "result": 0.0}
{"question": "Solve: (48 / 125) - 7.87", "answer": "The result of (48 / 125) - 7.87 is -7.49", "a": 48, "b": 125, "c": 7.87, "op1": "/", "op2": "-", "result": -7.49}
{"question": "Solve: (134.48 + 117) - 47.91", "answer": "The result of (134.48 + 117) - 47.91 is 203.57", "a": 134.48, "b": 117, "c": 47.91, "op1": "+", "op2": "-", "result": 203.57}
{"question": "Solve: (87 / 68.56) + 119", "answer": "The result of (87 / 68.56) + 119 is 120.27", "a": 87, "b": 68.56, "c": 119, "op1": "/", "op2": "+", "result": 120.27}
{"question": "Solve: (64 * 176.22) + 162", "answer": "The result of (64 * 176.22) + 162 is 11440.08", "a": 64, "b": 176.22, "c": 162, "op1": "*", "op2": "+", "result": 11440.08}
{"question": "Solve: (147 - 57.53) + 5.44", "answer": "The result of (147 - 57.53) + 5.44 is 94.91", "a": 147, "b": 57.53, "c": 5.44, "op1": "-", "op2": "+", "result": 94.91}
{"question": "Solve: (98 - 33) / 166", "answer": "The result of (98 - 33) / 166 is 0.39", "a": 98, "b": 33, "c": 166, "op1": "-", "op2": "/", "result": 0.39}
{"question": "Solve: (121 - 13.04) + 31", "answer": "The result of (121 - 13.04) + 31 is 138.96", "a": 121, "b": 13.04, "c": 31, "op1": "-", "op2": "+", "result": 138.96}
{"question": "Solve: (152 + 195) / 46.9", "answer": "The result of (152 + 195) / 46.9 is 7.4", "a": 152, "b": 195, "c": 46.9, "op1": "+", "op2": "/", "result": 7.4}
{"question": "Solve: (130 + 130.21) * 141.99", "answer": "The result of (130 + 130.21) * 141.99 is 36947.22", "a": 130, "b": 130.21, "c": 141.99, "op1": "+", "op2": "*", "result": 36947.22}
{"question": "Solve: (2 - 131.79) + 199", "answer": "The result of (2 - 131.79) + 199 is 69.21", "a": 2, "b": 131.79, "c": 199, "op1": "-", "op2": "+", "result": 69.21}
{"question": "Solve: (176.63 + 99) * 1", "answer": "The result of (176.63 + 99) * 1 is 275.63", "a": 176.63, "b": 99, "c": 1, "op1": "+", "op2": "*", "result": 275.63}
{"question": "Solve: (73 + 153) / 39.63", "answer": "The result of (73 + 153) / 39.63 is 5.7", "a": 73, "b": 153, "c": 39.63, "op1": "+", "op2": "/", "result": 5.7}
{"question": "Solve: (75 + 33) * 15", "answer": "The result of (75 + 33) * 15 is 1620", "a": 75, "b": 33, "c": 15, "op1": "+", "op2": "*", "result": 1620}
{"question": "Solve: (175 - 87) - 152", "answer": "The result of (175 - 87) - 152 is -64", "a": 175, "b": 87, "c": 152, "op1": "-", "op2": "-", "result": -64}
{"question": "Solve: (112 * 169) * 59", "answer": "The result of (112 * 169) * 59 is 1116752", "a": 112, "b": 169, "c": 59, "op1": "*", "op2": "*", "result": 1116752}
{"question": "Solve: (129 * 49) / 30", "answer": "The result of (129 * 49) / 30 is 210.7", "a": 129, "b": 49, "c": 30, "op1": "*", "op2": "/", "result": 210.7}
{"question": "Solve: (72 - 32) * 34", "answer": "The result of (72 - 32) * 34 is 1360", "a": 72, "b": 32, "c": 34, "op1": "-", "op2": "*", "result": 1360}
{"question": "Solve: (53 + 54) + 160", "answer": "The result of (53 + 54) + 160 is 267", "a": 53, "b": 54, "c": 160, "op1": "+", "op2": "+", "result": 267}
{"question": "Solve: (116 + 92.21) * 107", "answer": "The result of (116 + 92.21) * 107 is 22278.47", "a": 116, "b": 92.21, "c": 107, "op1": "+", "op2": "*", "result": 22278.47}
{"question": "Solve: (199 + 164.53) - 109", "answer": "The result of (199 + 164.53) - 109 is 254.53", "a": 199, "b": 164.53, "c": 109, "op1": "+", "op2": "-", "result": 254.53}
{"question": "Solve: (65 * 20.01) / 36", "answer": "The result of (65 * 20.01) / 36 is 36.13", "a": 65, "b": 20.01, "c": 36, "op1": "*", "op2": "/", "result": 36.13}
{"question": "Solve: (26 * 168) + 174.67", "answer": "The result of (26 * 168) + 174.67 is 4542.67", "a": 26, "b": 168, "c": 174.67, "op1": "*", "op2": "+", "result": 4542.67}
{"question": "Solve: (91 - 70) / 100", "answer": "The result of (91 - 70) / 100 is 0.21", "a": 91, "b": 70, "c": 100, "op1": "-", "op2": "/", "result": 0.21}
{"question": "Solve: (22 * 127) - 89.85", "answer": "The result of (22 * 127) - 89.85 is 2704.15", "a": 22, "b": 127, "c": 89.85, "op1": "*", "op2": "-", "result": 2704.15}
{"question": "Solve: (163 - 89) / 121", "answer": "The result of (163 - 89) / 121 is 0.61", "a": 163, "b": 89, "c": 121, "op1": "-", "op2": "/", "result": 0.61}
{"question": "Solve: (61 * 28) - 108", "answer": "The result of (61 * 28) - 108 is 1600", "a": 61, "b": 28, "c": 108, "op1": "*", "op2": "-", "result": 1600}
{"question": "Solve: (1.01 * 100.63) * 199", "answer": "The result of (1.01 * 100.63) * 199 is 20225.62", "a": 1.01, "b": 100.63, "c": 199, "op1": "*", "op2": "*", "result": 20225.62}
{"question": "Solve: (69.42 * 124) / 122.91", "answer": "The result of (69.42 * 124) / 122.91 is 70.04", "a": 69.42, "b": 124, "c": 122.91, "op1": "*", "op2": "/", "result": 70.04}
{"question": "Solve: (156 * 110) + 102.07", "answer": "The result of (156 * 110) + 102.07 is 17262.07", "a": 156, "b": 110, "c": 102.07, "op1": "*", "op2": "+", "result": 17262.07}
{"question": "Solve: (60 + 60) / 129", "answer": "The result of (60 + 60) / 129 is 0.93", "a": 60, "b": 60, "c": 129, "op1": "+", "op2": "/", "result": 0.93}
{"question": "Solve: (95 + 93) * 183", "answer": "The result of (95 + 93) * 183 is 34404", "a": 95, "b": 93, "c": 183, "op1": "+", "op2": "*", "result": 34404}
{"question": "Solve: (37 - 72) + 70", "answer": "The result of (37 - 72) + 70 is 35", "a": 37, "b": 72, "c": 70, "op1": "-", "op2": "+", "result": 35}
{"question": "Solve: (14 - 194.46) + 58", "answer": "The result of (14 - 194.46) + 58 is -122.46", "a": 14, "b": 194.46, "c": 58, "op1": "-", "op2": "+", "result": -122.46}
{"question": "Solve: (144.69 - 110.07) + 68", "answer": "The result of (144.69 - 110.07) + 68 is 102.62", "a": 144.69, "b": 110.07, "c": 68, "op1": "-", "op2": "+", "result": 102.62}
{"question": "Solve: (73.31 * 165.45) - 200", "answer": "The result of (73.31 * 165.45) - 200 is 11929.14", "a": 73.31, "b": 165.45, "c": 200, "op1": "*", "op2": "-", "result": 11929.14}
{"question": "Solve: (154.37 + 111) * 79", "answer": "The result of (154.37 + 111) * 79 is 20964.23", "a": 154.37, "b": 111, "c": 79, "op1": "+", "op2": "*", "result": 20964.23}
{"question": "Solve: (169 + 174) + 51", "answer": "The result of (169 + 174) + 51 is 394", "a": 169, "b": 174, "c": 51, "op1": "+", "op2": "+", "result": 394}
{"question": "Solve: (190 * 130) - 194.61", "answer": "The result of (190 * 130) - 194.61 is 24505.39", "a": 190, "b": 130, "c": 194.61, "op1": "*", "op2": "-", "result": 24505.39}
{"question": "Solve: (89 * 170) + 54", "answer": "The result of (89 * 170) + 54 is 15184", "a": 89, "b": 170, "c": 54, "op1": "*", "op2": "+", "result": 15184}
{"question": "Solve: (76 - 12) * 76.41", "answer": "The result of (76 - 12) * 76.41 is 4890.24", "a": 76, "b": 12, "c": 76.41, "op1": "-", "op2": "*", "result": 4890.24}
{"question": "Solve: (1 + 92) + 90.49", "answer": "The result of (1 + 92) + 90.49 is 183.49", "a": 1, "b": 92, "c": 90.49, "op1": "+", "op2": "+", "result": 183.49}
{"question": "Solve: (26.92 * 20.52) - 13", "answer": "The result of (26.92 * 20.52) - 13 is 539.4", "a": 26.92, "b": 20.52, "c": 13, "op1": "*", "op2": "-", "result": 539.4}
{"question": "Solve: (104 - 48) - 150", "answer": "The result of (104 - 48) - 150 is -94", "a": 104, "b": 48, "c": 150, "op1": "-", "op2": "-", "result": -94}
{"question": "Solve: (70 + 149) - 162", "answer": "The result of (70 + 149) - 162 is 57", "a": 70, "b": 149, "c": 162, "op1": "+", "op2": "-", "result": 57}
{"question": "Solve: (172.75 * 54) * 60.79", "answer": "The result of (172.75 * 54) * 60.79 is 567079.52", "a": 172.75, "b": 54, "c": 60.79, "op1": "*", "op2": "*", "result": 567079.52}
{"question": "Solve: (177 - 149) / 144.97", "answer": "The result of (177 - 149) / 144.97 is 0.19", "a": 177, "b": 149, "c": 144.97, "op1": "-", "op2": "/", "result": 0.19}
{"question": "Solve: (44.27 / 127) - 140", "answer": "The result of (44.27 / 127) - 140 is -139.65", "a": 44.27, "b": 127, "c": 140, "op1": "/", "op2": "-", "result": -139.65}
{"question": "Solve: (116 / 131) / 135", "answer": "The result of (116 / 131) / 135 is 0.01", "a": 116, "b": 131, "c": 135, "op1": "/", "op2": "/", "result": 0.01}
{"question": "Solve: (127.32 - 47) * 125", "answer": "The result of (127.32 - 47) * 125 is 10040.0", "a": 127.32, "b": 47, "c": 125, "op1": "-", "op2": "*", "result": 10040.0}
{"question": "Solve: (116 * 133) * 41", "answer": "The result of (116 * 133) * 41 is 632548", "a": 116, "b": 133, "c": 41, "op1": "*", "op2": "*", "result": 632548}
{"question": "Solve: (43 + 191.07) - 134", "answer": "The result of (43 + 191.07) - 134 is 100.07", "a": 43, "b": 191.07, "c": 134, "op1": "+", "op2": "-", "result": 100.07}
{"question": "Solve: (67.37 * 61) / 86.62", "answer": "The result of (67.37 * 61) / 86.62 is 47.44", "a": 67.37, "b": 61, "c": 86.62, "op1": "*", "op2": "/", "result": 47.44}
{"question": "Solve: (155 / 17) - 27.67", "answer": "The result of (155 / 17) - 27.67 is -18.55", "a": 155, "b": 17, "c": 27.67, "op1": "/", "op2": "-", "result": -18.55}
{"question": "Solve: (162 * 98) - 71", "answer": "The result of (162 * 98) - 71 is 15805", "a": 162, "b": 98, "c": 71, "op1": "*", "op2": "-", "result": 15805}
{"question": "Solve: (54 + 27) - 10", "answer": "The result of (54 + 27) - 10 is 71", "a": 54, "b": 27, "c": 10, "op1": "+", "op2": "-", "result": 71}
{"question": "Solve: (121 + 117.22) - 56", "answer": "The result of (121 + 117.22) - 56 is 182.22", "a": 121, "b": 117.22, "c": 56, "op1": "+", "op2": "-", "result": 182.22}
{"question": "Solve: (32 * 133) / 133", "answer": "The result of (32 * 133) / 133 is 32.0", "a": 32, "b": 133, "c": 133, "op1": "*", "op2": "/", "result": 32.0}
{"question": "Solve: (96 + 133.89) - 93", "answer": "The result of (96 + 133.89) - 93 is 136.89", "a": 96, "b": 133.89, "c": 93, "op1": "+", "op2": "-", "result": 136.89}
{"question": "Solve: (172.0 / 36) * 1", "answer": "The result of (172.0 / 36) * 1 is 4.78", "a": 172.0, "b": 36, "c": 1, "op1": "/", "op2": "*", "result": 4.78}
{"question": "Solve: (137.88 * 150) * 96", "answer": "The result of (137.88 * 150) * 96 is 1985472.0", "a": 137.88, "b": 150, "c": 96, "op1": "*", "op2": "*", "result": 1985472.0}
{"question": "Solve: (178.08 - 144.23) - 17", "answer": "The result of (178.08 - 144.23) - 17 is 16.85", "a": 178.08, "b": 144.23, "c": 17, "op1": "-", "op2": "-", "result": 16.85}
{"question": "Solve: (73 - 124) + 64", "answer": "The result of (73 - 124) + 64 is 13", "a": 73, "b": 124, "c": 64, "op1": "-", "op2": "+", "result": 13}
{"question": "Solve: (178 + 84) * 114.41", "answer": "The result of (178 + 84) * 114.41 is 29975.42", "a": 178, "b": 84, "c": 114.41, "op1": "+", "op2": "*", "result": 29975.42}
{"question": "Solve: (38 + 126) - 122", "answer": "The result of (38 + 126) - 122 is 42", "a": 38, "b": 126, "c": 122, "op1": "+", "op2": "-", "result": 42}
{"question": "Solve: (17.92 * 47.59) * 164.7", "answer": "The result of (17.92 * 47.59) * 164.7 is 140458.27", "a": 17.92, "b": 47.59, "c": 164.7, "op1": "*", "op2": "*", "result": 140458.27}
{"question": "Solve: (106 * 22) + 199", "answer": "The result of (106 * 22) + 199 is 2531", "a": 106, "b": 22, "c": 199, "op1": "*", "op2": "+", "result": 2531}
{"question": "Solve: (104 * 171.46) * 168", "answer": "The result of (104 * 171.46) * 168 is 2995749.12", "a": 104, "b": 171.46, "c": 168, "op1": "*", "op2": "*", "result": 2995749.12}
{"question": "Solve: (41 + 32) * 140", "answer": "The result of (41 + 32) * 140 is 10220", "a": 41, "b": 32, "c": 140, "op1": "+", "op2": "*", "result": 10220}
{"question": "Solve: (32.43 - 85.64) + 195", "answer": "The result of (32.43 - 85.64) + 195 is 141.79", "a": 32.43, "b": 85.64, "c": 195, "op1": "-", "op2": "+", "result": 141.79}
{"question": "Solve: (117.41 * 47) * 30", "answer": "The result of (117.41 * 47) * 30 is 165548.1", "a": 117.41, "b": 47, "c": 30, "op1": "*", "op2": "*", "result": 165548.1}
{"question": "Solve: (135 + 14) - 156", "answer": "The result of (135 + 14) - 156 is -7", "a": 135, "b": 14, "c": 156, "op1": "+", "op2": "-", "result": -7}
{"question": "Solve: (28 - 142.88) + 55", "answer": "The result of (28 - 142.88) + 55 is -59.88", "a": 28, "b": 142.88, "c": 55, "op1": "-", "op2": "+", "result": -59.88}
{"question": "Solve: (7.43 + 78) * 119", "answer": "The result of (7.43 + 78) * 119 is 10166.17", "a": 7.43, "b": 78, "c": 119, "op1": "+", "op2": "*", "result": 10166.17}
{"question": "Solve: (126 / 58) - 56.98", "answer": "The result of (126 / 58) - 56.98 is -54.81", "a": 126, "b": 58, "c": 56.98, "op1": "/", "op2": "-", "result": -54.81}
{"question": "Solve: (47 + 144) * 4", "answer": "The result of (47 + 144) * 4 is 764", "a": 47, "b": 144, "c": 4, "op1": "+", "op2": "*", "result": 764}
{"question": "Solve: (155 - 87) / 89", "answer": "The result of (155 - 87) / 89 is 0.76", "a": 155, "b": 87, "c": 89, "op1": "-", "op2": "/", "result": 0.76}
{"question": "Solve: (55.25 + 94) + 94.8", "answer": "The result of (55.25 + 94) + 94.8 is 244.05", "a": 55.25, "b": 94, "c": 94.8, "op1": "+", "op2": "+", "result": 244.05}
{"question": "Solve: (130 - 156.36) + 89.58", "answer": "The result of (130 - 156.36) + 89.58 is 63.22", "a": 130, "b": 156.36, "c": 89.58, "op1": "-", "op2": "+", "result": 63.22}
{"question": "Solve: (43 / 48) * 88", "answer": "The result of (43 / 48) * 88 is 78.83", "a": 43, "b": 48, "c": 88, "op1": "/", "op2": "*", "result": 78.83}
{"question": "Solve: (15 / 72) - 108", "answer": "The result of (15 / 72) - 108 is -107.79", "a": 15, "b": 72, "c": 108, "op1": "/", "op2": "-", "result": -107.79}
{"question": "Solve: (121 - 191.17) / 180.9", "answer": "The result of (121 - 191.17) / 180.9 is -0.39", "a": 121, "b": 191.17, "c": 180.9, "op1": "-", "op2": "/", "result": -0.39}
{"question": "Solve: (106.57 - 103.31) + 199", "answer": "The result of (106.57 - 103.31) + 199 is 202.26", "a": 106.57, "b": 103.31, "c": 199, "op1": "-", "op2": "+", "result": 202.26}
{"question": "Solve: (129.37 / 27) + 165.0", "answer": "The result of (129.37 / 27) + 165.0 is 169.79", "a": 129.37, "b": 27, "c": 165.0, "op1": "/", "op2": "+", "result": 169.79}
{"question": "Solve: (134 * 57) * 56", "answer": "The result of (134 * 57) * 56 is 427728", "a": 134, "b": 57, "c": 56, "op1": "*", "op2": "*", "result": 427728}
{"question": "Solve: (156 + 124) - 63", "answer": "The result of (156 + 124) - 63 is 217", "a": 156, "b": 124, "c": 63, "op1": "+", "op2": "-", "result": 217}
{"question": "Solve: (51 / 192) + 140", "answer": "The result of (51 / 192) + 140 is 140.27", "a": 51, "b": 192, "c": 140, "op1": "/", "op2": "+", "result": 140.27}
{"question": "Solve: (103.19 + 181.56) + 105", "answer": "The result of (103.19 + 181.56) + 105 is 389.75", "a": 103.19, "b": 181.56, "c": 105, "op1": "+", "op2": "+", "result": 389.75}
{"question": "Solve: (42.32 * 79.59) + 82", "answer": "The result of (42.32 * 79.59) + 82 is 3450.25", "a": 42.32, "b": 79.59, "c": 82, "op1": "*", "op2": "+", "result": 3450.25}
{"question": "Solve: (192.89 + 40) * 151", "answer": "The result of (192.89 + 40) * 151 is 35166.39", "a": 192.89, "b": 40, "c": 151, "op1": "+", "op2": "*", "result": 35166.39}
{"question": "Solve: (187 + 109.63) + 195", "answer": "The result of (187 + 109.63) + 195 is 491.63", "a": 187, "b": 109.63, "c": 195, "op1": "+", "op2": "+", "result": 491.63}
{"question": "Solve: (18.2 - 186.28) + 171", "answer": "The result of (18.2 - 186.28) + 171 is 2.92", "a": 18.2, "b": 186.28, "c": 171, "op1": "-", "op2": "+", "result": 2.92}
{"question": "Solve: (136 * 85) * 168", "answer": "The result of (136 * 85) * 168 is 1942080", "a": 136, "b": 85, "c": 168, "op1": "*", "op2": "*", "result": 1942080}
{"question": "Solve: (167 - 113) - 118", "answer": "The result of (167 - 113) - 118 is -64", "a": 167, "b": 113, "c": 118, "op1": "-", "op2": "-", "result": -64}
{"question": "Solve: (61 - 27) * 165.75", "answer": "The result of (61 - 27) * 165.75 is 5635.5", "a": 61, "b": 27, "c": 165.75, "op1": "-", "op2": "*", "result": 5635.5}
{"question": "Solve: (167 * 69) - 12", "answer": "The result of (167 * 69) - 12 is 11511", "a": 167, "b": 69, "c": 12, "op1": "*", "op2": "-", "result": 11511}
{"question": "Solve: (17.38 + 106.35) / 85.03", "answer": "The result of (17.38 + 106.35) / 85.03 is 1.46", "a": 17.38, "b": 106.35, "c": 85.03, "op1": "+", "op2": "/", "result": 1.46}
{"question": "Solve: (99.46 * 197) + 189", "answer": "The result of (99.46 * 197) + 189 is 19782.62", "a": 99.46, "b": 197, "c": 189, "op1": "*", "op2": "+", "result": 19782.62}
{"question": "Solve: (144.75 + 189) + 7.64", "answer": "The result of (144.75 + 189) + 7.64 is 341.39", "a": 144.75, "b": 189, "c": 7.64, "op1": "+", "op2": "+", "result": 341.39}
{"question": "Solve: (36.23 - 19) + 116", "answer": "The result of (36.23 - 19) + 116 is 133.23", "a": 36.23, "b": 19, "c": 116, "op1": "-", "op2": "+", "result": 133.23}
{"question": "Solve: (170.0 / 24) / 131.0", "answer": "The result of (170.0 / 24) / 131.0 is 0.05", "a": 170.0, "b": 24, "c": 131.0, "op1": "/", "op2": "/", "result": 0.05}
{"question": "Solve: (23.35 * 86) + 66", "answer": "The result of (23.35 * 86) + 66 is 2074.1", "a": 23.35, "b": 86, "c": 66, "op1": "*", "op2": "+", "result": 2074.1}
{"question": "Solve: (83.51 * 177.21) + 66", "answer": "The result of (83.51 * 177.21) + 66 is 14864.81", "a": 83.51, "b": 177.21, "c": 66, "op1": "*", "op2": "+", "result": 14864.81}
{"question": "Solve: (15 - 18) - 80.5", "answer": "The result of (15 - 18) - 80.5 is -83.5", "a": 15, "b": 18, "c": 80.5, "op1": "-", "op2": "-", "result": -83.5}
{"question": "Solve: (182 * 141) / 191", "answer": "The result of (182 * 141) / 191 is 134.36", "a": 182, "b": 141, "c": 191, "op1": "*", "op2": "/", "result": 134.36}
{"question": "Solve: (59 + 80) + 80", "answer": "The result of (59 + 80) + 80 is 219", "a": 59, "b": 80, "c": 80, "op1": "+", "op2": "+", "result": 219}
{"question": "Solve: (67 - 61) / 28.82", "answer": "The result of (67 - 61) / 28.82 is 0.21", "a": 67, "b": 61, "c": 28.82, "op1": "-", "op2": "/", "result": 0.21}
{"question": "Solve: (5 * 171) / 50", "answer": "The result of (5 * 171) / 50 is 17.1", "a": 5, "b": 171, "c": 50, "op1": "*", "op2": "/", "result": 17.1}
{"question": "Solve: (165 * 82.23) / 4", "answer": "The result of (165 * 82.23) / 4 is 3391.99", "a": 165, "b": 82.23, "c": 4, "op1": "*", "op2": "/", "result": 3391.99}
{"question": "Solve: (50 + 99) - 192", "answer": "The result of (50 + 99) - 192 is -43", "a": 50, "b": 99, "c": 192, "op1": "+", "op2": "-", "result": -43}
{"question": "Solve: (107 * 17) - 129.61", "answer": "The result of (107 * 17) - 129.61 is 1689.39", "a": 107, "b": 17, "c": 129.61, "op1": "*", "op2": "-", "result": 1689.39}
{"question": "Solve: (147.77 - 165) - 74", "answer": "The result of (147.77 - 165) - 74 is -91.23", "a": 147.77, "b": 165, "c": 74, "op1": "-", "op2": "-", "result": -91.23}
{"question": "Solve: (18 * 13) / 36.35", "answer": "The result of (18 * 13) / 36.35 is 6.44", "a": 18, "b": 13, "c": 36.35, "op1": "*", "op2": "/", "result": 6.44}
{"question": "Solve: (71 + 137) / 150", "answer": "The result of (71 + 137) / 150 is 1.39", "a": 71, "b": 137, "c": 150, "op1": "+", "op2": "/", "result": 1.39}
{"question": "Solve: (146 / 88) * 115", "answer": "The result of (146 / 88) * 115 is 190.8", "a": 146, "b": 88, "c": 115, "op1": "/", "op2": "*", "result": 190.8}
{"question": "Solve: (59 - 174) * 180", "answer": "The result of (59 - 174) * 180 is -20700", "a": 59, "b": 174, "c": 180, "op1": "-", "op2": "*", "result": -20700}
{"question": "Solve: (127 * 197.22) - 162.43", "answer": "The result of (127 * 197.22) - 162.43 is 24884.51", "a": 127, "b": 197.22, "c": 162.43, "op1": "*", "op2": "-", "result": 24884.51}
{"question": "Solve: (146 / 191) * 54", "answer": "The result of (146 / 191) * 54 is 41.28", "a": 146, "b": 191, "c": 54, "op1": "/", "op2": "*", "result": 41.28}
{"question": "Solve: (131 - 165.92) + 112", "answer": "The result of (131 - 165.92) + 112 is 77.08", "a": 131, "b": 165.92, "c": 112, "op1": "-", "op2": "+", "result": 77.08}
{"question": "Solve: (85.58 - 86) * 120.92", "answer": "The result of (85.58 - 86) * 120.92 is -50.79", "a": 85.58, "b": 86, "c": 120.92, "op1": "-", "op2": "*", "result": -50.79}
{"question": "Solve: (14 + 50) - 126.87", "answer": "The result of (14 + 50) - 126.87 is -62.87", "a": 14, "b": 50, "c": 126.87, "op1": "+", "op2": "-", "result": -62.87}
{"question": "Solve: (86 - 9) * 10", "answer": "The result of (86 - 9) * 10 is 770", "a": 86, "b": 9, "c": 10, "op1": "-", "op2": "*", "result": 770}
{"question": "Solve: (114 * 113) - 8.05", "answer": "The result of (114 * 113) - 8.05 is 12873.95", "a": 114, "b": 113, "c": 8.05, "op1": "*", "op2": "-", "result": 12873.95}
{"question": "Solve: (93.85 * 69) + 146", "answer": "The result of (93.85 * 69) + 146 is 6621.65", "a": 93.85, "b": 69, "c": 146, "op1": "*", "op2": "+", "result": 6621.65}
{"question": "Solve: (189.29 + 27) - 10", "answer": "The result of (189.29 + 27) - 10 is 206.29", "a": 189.29, "b": 27, "c": 10, "op1": "+", "op2": "-", "result": 206.29}
{"question": "Solve: (23.87 + 100) + 151", "answer": "The result of (23.87 + 100) + 151 is 274.87", "a": 23.87, "b": 100, "c": 151, "op1": "+", "op2": "+", "result": 274.87}
{"question": "Solve: (98 / 52) - 34", "answer": "The result of (98 / 52) - 34 is -32.12", "a": 98, "b": 52, "c": 34, "op1": "/", "op2": "-", "result": -32.12}
{"question": "Solve: (146 + 14) - 180", "answer": "The result of (146 + 14) - 180 is -20", "a": 146, "b": 14, "c": 180, "op1": "+", "op2": "-", "result": -20}
{"question": "Solve: (37 - 108) / 165", "answer": "The result of (37 - 108) / 165 is -0.43", "a": 37, "b": 108, "c": 165, "op1": "-", "op2": "/", "result": -0.43}
{"question": "Solve: (15 - 171) * 160", "answer": "The result of (15 - 171) * 160 is -24960", "a": 15, "b": 171, "c": 160, "op1": "-", "op2": "*", "result": -24960}
{"question": "Solve: (65 * 110) / 26", "answer": "The result of (65 * 110) / 26 is 275.0", "a": 65, "b": 110, "c": 26, "op1": "*", "op2": "/", "result": 275.0}
{"question": "Solve: (101 - 116.89) * 43", "answer": "The result of (101 - 116.89) * 43 is -683.27", "a": 101, "b": 116.89, "c": 43, "op1": "-", "op2": "*", "result": -683.27}
{"question": "Solve: (143 - 53) / 174", "answer": "The result of (143 - 53) / 174 is 0.52", "a": 143, "b": 53, "c": 174, "op1": "-", "op2": "/", "result": 0.52}
{"question": "Solve: (40 + 154) / 183.13", "answer": "The result of (40 + 154) / 183.13 is 1.06", "a": 40, "b": 154, "c": 183.13, "op1": "+", "op2": "/", "result": 1.06}
{"question": "Solve: (187 + 143) / 180", "answer": "The result of (187 + 143) / 180 is 1.83", "a": 187, "b": 143, "c": 180, "op1": "+", "op2": "/", "result": 1.83}
{"question": "Solve: (191 * 30) * 98.8", "answer": "The result of (191 * 30) * 98.8 is 566124.0", "a": 191, "b": 30, "c": 98.8, "op1": "*", "op2": "*", "result": 566124.0}
{"question": "Solve: (3 - 95.43) - 190", "answer": "The result of (3 - 95.43) - 190 is -282.43", "a": 3, "b": 95.43, "c": 190, "op1": "-", "op2": "-", "result": -282.43}
{"question": "Solve: (192.08 - 133) * 147", "answer": "The result of (192.08 - 133) * 147 is 8684.76", "a": 192.08, "b": 133, "c": 147, "op1": "-", "op2": "*", "result": 8684.76}
{"question": "Solve: (191 - 132) - 73", "answer": "The result of (191 - 132) - 73 is -14", "a": 191, "b": 132, "c": 73, "op1": "-", "op2": "-", "result": -14}
{"question": "Solve: (176 + 36) * 149", "answer": "The result of (176 + 36) * 149 is 31588", "a": 176, "b": 36, "c": 149, "op1": "+", "op2": "*", "result": 31588}
{"question": "Solve: (27 + 52) + 180", "answer": "The result of (27 + 52) + 180 is 259", "a": 27, "b": 52, "c": 180, "op1": "+", "op2": "+", "result": 259}
{"question": "Solve: (131 / 40) * 11.88", "answer": "The result of (131 / 40) * 11.88 is 38.91", "a": 131, "b": 40, "c": 11.88, "op1": "/", "op2": "*", "result": 38.91}
{"question": "Solve: (69 * 128.42) / 47", "answer": "The result of (69 * 128.42) / 47 is 188.53", "a": 69, "b": 128.42, "c": 47, "op1": "*", "op2": "/", "result": 188.53}
{"question": "Solve: (30 * 47) + 101.1", "answer": "The result of (30 * 47) + 101.1 is 1511.1", "a": 30, "b": 47, "c": 101.1, "op1": "*", "op2": "+", "result": 1511.1}
{"question": "Solve: (68.2 * 11) / 62.08", "answer": "The result of (68.2 * 11) / 62.08 is 12.08", "a": 68.2, "b": 11, "c": 62.08, "op1": "*", "op2": "/", "result": 12.08}
{"question": "Solve: (187.93 + 84.42) + 24", "answer": "The result of (187.93 + 84.42) + 24 is 296.35", "a": 187.93, "b": 84.42, "c": 24, "op1": "+", "op2": "+", "result": 296.35}
{"question": "Solve: (135 - 15) / 141.22", "answer": "The result of (135 - 15) / 141.22 is 0.85", "a": 135, "b": 15, "c": 141.22, "op1": "-", "op2": "/", "result": 0.85}
{"question": "Solve: (105 - 196.47) - 16.0", "answer": "The result of (105 - 196.47) - 16.0 is -107.47", "a": 105, "b": 196.47, "c": 16.0, "op1": "-", "op2": "-", "result": -107.47}
{"question": "Solve: (196.63 * 86) - 26.71", "answer": "The result of (196.63 * 86) - 26.71 is 16883.47", "a": 196.63, "b": 86, "c": 26.71, "op1": "*", "op2": "-", "result": 16883.47}
{"question": "Solve: (36.98 - 21) * 79", "answer": "The result of (36.98 - 21) * 79 is 1262.42", "a": 36.98, "b": 21, "c": 79, "op1": "-", "op2": "*", "result": 1262.42}
{"question": "Solve: (6 + 80) * 59.78", "answer": "The result of (6 + 80) * 59.78 is 5141.08", "a": 6, "b": 80, "c": 59.78, "op1": "+", "op2": "*", "result": 5141.08}
{"question": "Solve: (45 - 69) + 195.04", "answer": "The result of (45 - 69) + 195.04 is 171.04", "a": 45, "b": 69, "c": 195.04, "op1": "-", "op2": "+", "result": 171.04}
{"question": "Solve: (51 + 117) * 69", "answer": "The result of (51 + 117) * 69 is 11592", "a": 51, "b": 117, "c": 69, "op1": "+", "op2": "*", "result": 11592}
{"question": "Solve: (77 + 14) + 18.08", "answer": "The result of (77 + 14) + 18.08 is 109.08", "a": 77, "b": 14, "c": 18.08, "op1": "+", "op2": "+", "result": 109.08}
{"question": "Solve: (86 - 143) + 124", "answer": "The result of (86 - 143) + 124 is 67", "a": 86, "b": 143, "c": 124, "op1": "-", "op2": "+", "result": 67}
{"question": "Solve: (138 / 182) + 154", "answer": "The result of (138 / 182) + 154 is 154.76", "a": 138, "b": 182, "c": 154, "op1": "/", "op2": "+", "result": 154.76}
{"question": "Solve: (24.55 * 96) - 72.42", "answer": "The result of (24.55 * 96) - 72.42 is 2284.38", "a": 24.55, "b": 96, "c": 72.42, "op1": "*", "op2": "-", "result": 2284.38}
{"question": "Solve: (114 - 16.32) * 106", "answer": "The result of (114 - 16.32) * 106 is 10354.08", "a": 114, "b": 16.32, "c": 106, "op1": "-", "op2": "*", "result": 10354.08}
{"question": "Solve: (41 * 35) * 200", "answer": "The result of (41 * 35) * 200 is 287000", "a": 41, "b": 35, "c": 200, "op1": "*", "op2": "*", "result": 287000}
{"question": "Solve: (97.78 * 65) - 110", "answer": "The result of (97.78 * 65) - 110 is 6245.7", "a": 97.78, "b": 65, "c": 110, "op1": "*", "op2": "-", "result": 6245.7}
{"question": "Solve: (21 - 13) + 80", "answer": "The result of (21 - 13) + 80 is 88", "a": 21, "b": 13, "c": 80, "op1": "-", "op2": "+", "result": 88}
{"question": "Solve: (105.48 / 59.66) * 86", "answer": "The result of (105.48 / 59.66) * 86 is 152.05", "a": 105.48, "b": 59.66, "c": 86, "op1": "/", "op2": "*", "result": 152.05}
{"question": "Solve: (128 * 187) - 122", "answer": "The result of (128 * 187) - 122 is 23814", "a": 128, "b": 187, "c": 122, "op1": "*", "op2": "-", "result": 23814}
{"question": "Solve: (46 * 198) * 45.86", "answer": "The result of (46 * 198) * 45.86 is 417692.88", "a": 46, "b": 198, "c": 45.86, "op1": "*", "op2": "*", "result": 417692.88}
{"question": "Solve: (144 / 127) + 61.62", "answer": "The result of (144 / 127) + 61.62 is 62.75", "a": 144, "b": 127, "c": 61.62, "op1": "/", "op2": "+", "result": 62.75}
{"question": "Solve: (15 * 77.82) / 65", "answer": "The result of (15 * 77.82) / 65 is 17.96", "a": 15, "b": 77.82, "c": 65, "op1": "*", "op2": "/", "result": 17.96}
{"question": "Solve: (74 + 137.32) + 146", "answer": "The result of (74 + 137.32) + 146 is 357.32", "a": 74, "b": 137.32, "c": 146, "op1": "+", "op2": "+", "result": 357.32}
{"question": "Solve: (134.95 * 2.28) - 102.21", "answer": "The result of (134.95 * 2.28) - 102.21 is 205.48", "a": 134.95, "b": 2.28, "c": 102.21, "op1": "*", "op2": "-", "result": 205.48}
{"question": "Solve: (185.35 + 176) + 112.29", "answer": "The result of (185.35 + 176) + 112.29 is 473.64", "a": 185.35, "b": 176, "c": 112.29, "op1": "+", "op2": "+", "result": 473.64}
{"question": "Solve: (76.17 - 189) / 12", "answer": "The result of (76.17 - 189) / 12 is -9.4", "a": 76.17, "b": 189, "c": 12, "op1": "-", "op2": "/", "result": -9.4}
{"question": "Solve: (43 / 84) / 42", "answer": "The result of (43 / 84) / 42 is 0.01", "a": 43, "b": 84, "c": 42, "op1": "/", "op2": "/", "result": 0.01}
{"question": "Solve: (45.6 + 170.11) + 191.7", "answer": "The result of (45.6 + 170.11) + 191.7 is 407.41", "a": 45.6, "b": 170.11, "c": 191.7, "op1": "+", "op2": "+", "result": 407.41}
{"question": "Solve: (184 + 79) + 28", "answer": "The result of (184 + 79) + 28 is 291", "a": 184, "b": 79, "c": 28, "op1": "+", "op2": "+", "result": 291}
{"question": "Solve: (3.98 * 78) + 186", "answer": "The result of (3.98 * 78) + 186 is 496.44", "a": 3.98, "b": 78, "c": 186, "op1": "*", "op2": "+", "result": 496.44}
{"question": "Solve: (38 / 131) - 101.08", "answer": "The result of (38 / 131) - 101.08 is -100.79", "a": 38, "b": 131, "c": 101.08, "op1": "/", "op2": "-", "result": -100.79}
{"question": "Solve: (151.63 / 109) / 23.67", "answer": "The result of (151.63 / 109) / 23.67 is 0.06", "a": 151.63, "b": 109, "c": 23.67, "op1": "/", "op2": "/", "result": 0.06}
{"question": "Solve: (25.17 * 142.41) + 79", "answer": "The result of (25.17 * 142.41) + 79 is 3663.46", "a": 25.17, "b": 142.41, "c": 79, "op1": "*", "op2": "+", "result": 3663.46}
{"question": "Solve: (42 * 161) - 145", "answer": "The result of (42 * 161) - 145 is 6617", "a": 42, "b": 161, "c": 145, "op1": "*", "op2": "-", "result": 6617}
{"question": "Solve: (159.0 / 81.27) * 50", "answer": "The result of (159.0 / 81.27) * 50 is 97.82", "a": 159.0, "b": 81.27, "c": 50, "op1": "/", "op2": "*", "result": 97.82}
{"question": "Solve: (13 + 13) - 73.56", "answer": "The result of (13 + 13) - 73.56 is -47.56", "a": 13, "b": 13, "c": 73.56, "op1": "+", "op2": "-", "result": -47.56}
{"question": "Solve: (100 + 103) / 143", "answer": "The result of (100 + 103) / 143 is 1.42", "a": 100, "b": 103, "c": 143, "op1": "+", "op2": "/", "result": 1.42}
{"question": "Solve: (152 / 120) - 136.83", "answer": "The result of (152 / 120) - 136.83 is -135.56", "a": 152, "b": 120, "c": 136.83, "op1": "/", "op2": "-", "result": -135.56}
{"question": "Solve: (37 - 163) + 53", "answer": "The result of (37 - 163) + 53 is -73", "a": 37, "b": 163, "c": 53, "op1": "-", "op2": "+", "result": -73}
{"question": "Solve: (98 * 49) + 134", "answer": "The result of (98 * 49) + 134 is 4936", "a": 98, "b": 49, "c": 134, "op1": "*", "op2": "+", "result": 4936}
{"question": "Solve: (155 + 195) * 163", "answer": "The result of (155 + 195) * 163 is 57050", "a": 155, "b": 195, "c": 163, "op1": "+", "op2": "*", "result": 57050}
{"question": "Solve: (135 + 20.49) + 6.72", "answer": "The result of (135 + 20.49) + 6.72 is 162.21", "a": 135, "b": 20.49, "c": 6.72, "op1": "+", "op2": "+", "result": 162.21}
{"question": "Solve: (125 + 117) - 124", "answer": "The result of (125 + 117) - 124 is 118", "a": 125, "b": 117, "c": 124, "op1": "+", "op2": "-", "result": 118}
{"question": "Solve: (185 + 19.27) + 192.34", "answer": "The result of (185 + 19.27) + 192.34 is 396.61", "a": 185, "b": 19.27, "c": 192.34, "op1": "+", "op2": "+", "result": 396.61}
{"question": "Solve: (67 - 89) - 126.92", "answer": "The result of (67 - 89) - 126.92 is -148.92", "a": 67, "b": 89, "c": 126.92, "op1": "-", "op2": "-", "result": -148.92}
{"question": "Solve: (157 + 36) + 172.92", "answer": "The result of (157 + 36) + 172.92 is 365.92", "a": 157, "b": 36, "c": 172.92, "op1": "+", "op2": "+", "result": 365.92}
{"question": "Solve: (141.52 * 28) - 185.53", "answer": "The result of (141.52 * 28) - 185.53 is 3777.03", "a": 141.52, "b": 28, "c": 185.53, "op1": "*", "op2": "-", "result": 3777.03}
{"question": "Solve: (75.33 * 65.65) + 193", "answer": "The result of (75.33 * 65.65) + 193 is 5138.41", "a": 75.33, "b": 65.65, "c": 193, "op1": "*", "op2": "+", "result": 5138.41}
{"question": "Solve: (51 * 46.4) * 77", "answer": "The result of (51 * 46.4) * 77 is 182212.8", "a": 51, "b": 46.4, "c": 77, "op1": "*", "op2": "*", "result": 182212.8}
{"question": "Solve: (146.96 / 171) * 32.02", "answer": "The result of (146.96 / 171) * 32.02 is 27.52", "a": 146.96, "b": 171, "c": 32.02, "op1": "/", "op2": "*", "result": 27.52}
{"question": "Solve: (185.35 + 195.28) * 190", "answer": "The result of (185.35 + 195.28) * 190 is 72319.7", "a": 185.35, "b": 195.28, "c": 190, "op1": "+", "op2": "*", "result": 72319.7}
{"question": "Solve: (37 - 165) * 34", "answer": "The result of (37 - 165) * 34 is -4352", "a": 37, "b": 165, "c": 34, "op1": "-", "op2": "*", "result": -4352}
{"question": "Solve: (11.75 + 43) / 67.06", "answer": "The result of (11.75 + 43) / 67.06 is 0.82", "a": 11.75, "b": 43, "c": 67.06, "op1": "+", "op2": "/", "result": 0.82}
{"question": "Solve: (96 * 18) * 147.35", "answer": "The result of (96 * 18) * 147.35 is 254620.8", "a": 96, "b": 18, "c": 147.35, "op1": "*", "op2": "*", "result": 254620.8}
{"question": "Solve: (3 * 178) * 45", "answer": "The result of (3 * 178) * 45 is 24030", "a": 3, "b": 178, "c": 45, "op1": "*", "op2": "*", "result": 24030}
{"question": "Solve: (103 - 141) + 86.5", "answer": "The result of (103 - 141) + 86.5 is 48.5", "a": 103, "b": 141, "c": 86.5, "op1": "-", "op2": "+", "result": 48.5}
{"question": "Solve: (182.14 * 198.25) * 76.54", "answer": "The result of (182.14 * 198.25) * 76.54 is 2763802.38", "a": 182.14, "b": 198.25, "c": 76.54, "op1": "*", "op2": "*", "result": 2763802.38}
{"question": "Solve: (95 - 104) / 158.18", "answer": "The result of (95 - 104) / 158.18 is -0.06", "a": 95, "b": 104, "c": 158.18, "op1": "-", "op2": "/", "result": -0.06}
{"question": "Solve: (71.28 + 87.27) * 38", "answer": "The result of (71.28 + 87.27) * 38 is 6024.9", "a": 71.28, "b": 87.27, "c": 38, "op1": "+", "op2": "*", "result": 6024.9}
{"question": "Solve: (14 / 86) - 191", "answer": "The result of (14 / 86) - 191 is -190.84", "a": 14, "b": 86, "c": 191, "op1": "/", "op2": "-", "result": -190.84}
{"question": "Solve: (124 - 130) * 61", "answer": "The result of (124 - 130) * 61 is -366", "a": 124, "b": 130, "c": 61, "op1": "-", "op2": "*", "result": -366}
{"question": "Solve: (79 + 146) + 138.33", "answer": "The result of (79 + 146) + 138.33 is 363.33", "a": 79, "b": 146, "c": 138.33, "op1": "+", "op2": "+", "result": 363.33}
{"question": "Solve: (75.11 - 181) * 129.08", "answer": "The result of (75.11 - 181) * 129.08 is -13668.28", "a": 75.11, "b": 181, "c": 129.08, "op1": "-", "op2": "*", "result": -13668.28}
{"question": "Solve: (50 - 111) / 102", "answer": "The result of (50 - 111) / 102 is -0.6", "a": 50, "b": 111, "c": 102, "op1": "-", "op2": "/", "result": -0.6}
{"question": "Solve: (135 + 172) + 121", "answer": "The result of (135 + 172) + 121 is 428", "a": 135, "b": 172, "c": 121, "op1": "+", "op2": "+", "result": 428}
{"question": "Solve: (95 + 40.74) * 91", "answer": "The result of (95 + 40.74) * 91 is 12352.34", "a": 95, "b": 40.74, "c": 91, "op1": "+", "op2": "*", "result": 12352.34}
{"question": "Solve: (4 * 146.7) / 96", "answer": "The result of (4 * 146.7) / 96 is 6.11", "a": 4, "b": 146.7, "c": 96, "op1": "*", "op2": "/", "result": 6.11}
{"question": "Solve: (37 / 90) - 179", "answer": "The result of (37 / 90) - 179 is -178.59", "a": 37, "b": 90, "c": 179, "op1": "/", "op2": "-", "result": -178.59}
{"question": "Solve: (174 * 11.67) * 31", "answer": "The result of (174 * 11.67) * 31 is 62947.98", "a": 174, "b": 11.67, "c": 31, "op1": "*", "op2": "*", "result": 62947.98}
{"question": "Solve: (107 - 143) - 40", "answer": "The result of (107 - 143) - 40 is -76", "a": 107, "b": 143, "c": 40, "op1": "-", "op2": "-", "result": -76}
{"question": "Solve: (190.71 * 56) * 131", "answer": "The result of (190.71 * 56) * 131 is 1399048.56", "a": 190.71, "b": 56, "c": 131, "op1": "*", "op2": "*", "result": 1399048.56}
{"question": "Solve: (125 + 60.31) + 26", "answer": "The result of (125 + 60.31) + 26 is 211.31", "a": 125, "b": 60.31, "c": 26, "op1": "+", "op2": "+", "result": 211.31}
{"question": "Solve: (76 * 6) * 99", "answer": "The result of (76 * 6) * 99 is 45144", "a": 76, "b": 6, "c": 99, "op1": "*", "op2": "*", "result": 45144}
{"question": "Solve: (32 + 14) + 136", "answer": "The result of (32 + 14) + 136 is 182", "a": 32, "b": 14, "c": 136, "op1": "+", "op2": "+", "result": 182}
{"question": "Solve: (180 / 31.23) + 91.12", "answer": "The result of (180 / 31.23) + 91.12 is 96.88", "a": 180, "b": 31.23, "c": 91.12, "op1": "/", "op2": "+", "result": 96.88}
{"question": "Solve: (199 / 139) - 124", "answer": "The result of (199 / 139) - 124 is -122.57", "a": 199, "b": 139, "c": 124, "op1": "/", "op2": "-", "result": -122.57}
{"question": "Solve: (133 - 113) * 169", "answer": "The result of (133 - 113) * 169 is 3380", "a": 133, "b": 113, "c": 169, "op1": "-", "op2": "*", "result": 3380}
{"question": "Solve: (155.57 * 101) + 94", "answer": "The result of (155.57 * 101) + 94 is 15806.57", "a": 155.57, "b": 101, "c": 94, "op1": "*", "op2": "+", "result": 15806.57}
{"question": "Solve: (57 * 183.46) / 144.05", "answer": "The result of (57 * 183.46) / 144.05 is 72.59", "a": 57, "b": 183.46, "c": 144.05, "op1": "*", "op2": "/", "result": 72.59}
{"question": "Solve: (71 + 53) - 13", "answer": "The result of (71 + 53) - 13 is 111", "a": 71, "b": 53, "c": 13, "op1": "+", "op2": "-", "result": 111}
{"question": "Solve: (62 * 24) - 150", "answer": "The result of (62 * 24) - 150 is 1338", "a": 62, "b": 24, "c": 150, "op1": "*", "op2": "-", "result": 1338}
{"question": "Solve: (135 + 173) + 187", "answer": "The result of (135 + 173) + 187 is 495", "a": 135, "b": 173, "c": 187, "op1": "+", "op2": "+", "result": 495}
{"question": "Solve: (173 + 175.95) - 25", "answer": "The result of (173 + 175.95) - 25 is 323.95", "a": 173, "b": 175.95, "c": 25, "op1": "+", "op2": "-", "result": 323.95}
{"question": "Solve: (118 / 131) / 42", "answer": "The result of (118 / 131) / 42 is 0.02", "a": 118, "b": 131, "c": 42, "op1": "/", "op2": "/", "result": 0.02}
{"question": "Solve: (117 * 127) / 200", "answer": "The result of (117 * 127) / 200 is 74.3", "a": 117, "b": 127, "c": 200, "op1": "*", "op2": "/", "result": 74.3}
{"question": "Solve: (68 + 198) * 179", "answer": "The result of (68 + 198) * 179 is 47614", "a": 68, "b": 198, "c": 179, "op1": "+", "op2": "*", "result": 47614}
{"question": "Solve: (118 - 79.81) * 37", "answer": "The result of (118 - 79.81) * 37 is 1413.03", "a": 118, "b": 79.81, "c": 37, "op1": "-", "op2": "*", "result": 1413.03}
{"question": "Solve: (122.66 * 7.68) / 20", "answer": "The result of (122.66 * 7.68) / 20 is 47.1", "a": 122.66, "b": 7.68, "c": 20, "op1": "*", "op2": "/", "result": 47.1}
{"question": "Solve: (73 - 93.55) - 97", "answer": "The result of (73 - 93.55) - 97 is -117.55", "a": 73, "b": 93.55, "c": 97, "op1": "-", "op2": "-", "result": -117.55}
{"question": "Solve: (163 - 11) - 60", "answer": "The result of (163 - 11) - 60 is 92", "a": 163, "b": 11, "c": 60, "op1": "-", "op2": "-", "result": 92}
{"question": "Solve: (154 - 28) * 10", "answer": "The result of (154 - 28) * 10 is 1260", "a": 154, "b": 28, "c": 10, "op1": "-", "op2": "*", "result": 1260}
{"question": "Solve: (148 - 8) + 92", "answer": "The result of (148 - 8) + 92 is 232", "a": 148, "b": 8, "c": 92, "op1": "-", "op2": "+", "result": 232}
{"question": "Solve: (187 - 170) / 188.25", "answer": "The result of (187 - 170) / 188.25 is 0.09", "a": 187, "b": 170, "c": 188.25, "op1": "-", "op2": "/", "result": 0.09}
{"question": "Solve: (9 * 88) + 112.53", "answer": "The result of (9 * 88) + 112.53 is 904.53", "a": 9, "b": 88, "c": 112.53, "op1": "*", "op2": "+", "result": 904.53}
{"question": "Solve: (189 + 132.34) * 15", "answer": "The result of (189 + 132.34) * 15 is 4820.1", "a": 189, "b": 132.34, "c": 15, "op1": "+", "op2": "*", "result": 4820.1}
{"question": "Solve: (72 - 129) / 46", "answer": "The result of (72 - 129) / 46 is -1.24", "a": 72, "b": 129, "c": 46, "op1": "-", "op2": "/", "result": -1.24}
{"question": "Solve: (106 * 109) - 51", "answer": "The result of (106 * 109) - 51 is 11503", "a": 106, "b": 109, "c": 51, "op1": "*", "op2": "-", "result": 11503}
{"question": "Solve: (120 * 150) / 104", "answer": "The result of (120 * 150) / 104 is 173.08", "a": 120, "b": 150, "c": 104, "op1": "*", "op2": "/", "result": 173.08}
{"question": "Solve: (56 / 79) - 147.37", "answer": "The result of (56 / 79) - 147.37 is -146.66", "a": 56, "b": 79, "c": 147.37, "op1": "/", "op2": "-", "result": -146.66}
{"question": "Solve: (9 + 54) / 19.49", "answer": "The result of (9 + 54) / 19.49 is 3.23", "a": 9, "b": 54, "c": 19.49, "op1": "+", "op2": "/", "result": 3.23}
{"question": "Solve: (135 - 107) + 198", "answer": "The result of (135 - 107) + 198 is 226", "a": 135, "b": 107, "c": 198, "op1": "-", "op2": "+", "result": 226}
{"question": "Solve: (62 - 174) + 94", "answer": "The result of (62 - 174) + 94 is -18", "a": 62, "b": 174, "c": 94, "op1": "-", "op2": "+", "result": -18}
{"question": "Solve: (32.75 - 95.97) - 98", "answer": "The result of (32.75 - 95.97) - 98 is -161.22", "a": 32.75, "b": 95.97, "c": 98, "op1": "-", "op2": "-", "result": -161.22}
{"question": "Solve: (150 / 33) + 167", "answer": "The result of (150 / 33) + 167 is 171.55", "a": 150, "b": 33, "c": 167, "op1": "/", "op2": "+", "result": 171.55}
{"question": "Solve: (19.61 - 41) * 113.53", "answer": "The result of (19.61 - 41) * 113.53 is -2428.41", "a": 19.61, "b": 41, "c": 113.53, "op1": "-", "op2": "*", "result": -2428.41}
{"question": "Solve: (112 * 196) - 156", "answer": "The result of (112 * 196) - 156 is 21796", "a": 112, "b": 196, "c": 156, "op1": "*", "op2": "-", "result": 21796}
{"question": "Solve: (86 + 181) - 34", "answer": "The result of (86 + 181) - 34 is 233", "a": 86, "b": 181, "c": 34, "op1": "+", "op2": "-", "result": 233}
{"question": "Solve: (68.56 * 27) * 138.9", "answer": "The result of (68.56 * 27) * 138.9 is 257120.57", "a": 68.56, "b": 27, "c": 138.9, "op1": "*", "op2": "*", "result": 257120.57}
{"question": "Solve: (122.31 * 196) + 30", "answer": "The result of (122.31 * 196) + 30 is 24002.76", "a": 122.31, "b": 196, "c": 30, "op1": "*", "op2": "+", "result": 24002.76}
{"question": "Solve: (197 + 1) - 24", "answer": "The result of (197 + 1) - 24 is 174", "a": 197, "b": 1, "c": 24, "op1": "+", "op2": "-", "result": 174}
{"question": "Solve: (61 * 167.29) * 162", "answer": "The result of (61 * 167.29) * 162 is 1653159.78", "a": 61, "b": 167.29, "c": 162, "op1": "*", "op2": "*", "result": 1653159.78}
{"question": "Solve: (15 / 14) + 7", "answer": "The result of (15 / 14) + 7 is 8.07", "a": 15, "b": 14, "c": 7, "op1": "/", "op2": "+", "result": 8.07}
{"question": "Solve: (198 - 100) + 80.15", "answer": "The result of (198 - 100) + 80.15 is 178.15", "a": 198, "b": 100, "c": 80.15, "op1": "-", "op2": "+", "result": 178.15}
{"question": "Solve: (8 + 49) + 148", "answer": "The result of (8 + 49) + 148 is 205", "a": 8, "b": 49, "c": 148, "op1": "+", "op2": "+", "result": 205}
{"question": "Solve: (185 + 78) - 60", "answer": "The result of (185 + 78) - 60 is 203", "a": 185, "b": 78, "c": 60, "op1": "+", "op2": "-", "result": 203}
{"question": "Solve: (89 - 112) - 55.88", "answer": "The result of (89 - 112) - 55.88 is -78.88", "a": 89, "b": 112, "c": 55.88, "op1": "-", "op2": "-", "result": -78.88}
{"question": "Solve: (182 - 130) + 45.88", "answer": "The result of (182 - 130) + 45.88 is 97.88", "a": 182, "b": 130, "c": 45.88, "op1": "-", "op2": "+", "result": 97.88}
{"question": "Solve: (114 + 28) + 196", "answer": "The result of (114 + 28) + 196 is 338", "a": 114, "b": 28, "c": 196, "op1": "+", "op2": "+", "result": 338}
{"question": "Solve: (52 / 69) * 86.84", "answer": "The result of (52 / 69) * 86.84 is 65.44", "a": 52, "b": 69, "c": 86.84, "op1": "/", "op2": "*", "result": 65.44}
{"question": "Solve: (144 - 36) + 107.17", "answer": "The result of (144 - 36) + 107.17 is 215.17", "a": 144, "b": 36, "c": 107.17, "op1": "-", "op2": "+", "result": 215.17}
{"question": "Solve: (169 + 9.59) / 57", "answer": "The result of (169 + 9.59) / 57 is 3.13", "a": 169, "b": 9.59, "c": 57, "op1": "+", "op2": "/", "result": 3.13}
{"question": "Solve: (99.09 * 16.04) + 106", "answer": "The result of (99.09 * 16.04) + 106 is 1695.4", "a": 99.09, "b": 16.04, "c": 106, "op1": "*", "op2": "+", "result": 1695.4}
{"question": "Solve: (40.66 - 16) + 92", "answer": "The result of (40.66 - 16) + 92 is 116.66", "a": 40.66, "b": 16, "c": 92, "op1": "-", "op2": "+", "result": 116.66}
{"question": "Solve: (76.12 - 12) / 51.16", "answer": "The result of (76.12 - 12) / 51.16 is 1.25", "a": 76.12, "b": 12, "c": 51.16, "op1": "-", "op2": "/", "result": 1.25}
{"question": "Solve: (41 - 108.84) * 104.54", "answer": "The result of (41 - 108.84) * 104.54 is -7091.99", "a": 41, "b": 108.84, "c": 104.54, "op1": "-", "op2": "*", "result": -7091.99}
{"question": "Solve: (92 / 180) - 90", "answer": "The result of (92 / 180) - 90 is -89.49", "a": 92, "b": 180, "c": 90, "op1": "/", "op2": "-", "result": -89.49}
{"question": "Solve: (194 + 114) + 150", "answer": "The result of (194 + 114) + 150 is 458", "a": 194, "b": 114, "c": 150, "op1": "+", "op2": "+", "result": 458}
{"question": "Solve: (136 + 191.86) - 48", "answer": "The result of (136 + 191.86) - 48 is 279.86", "a": 136, "b": 191.86, "c": 48, "op1": "+", "op2": "-", "result": 279.86}
{"question": "Solve: (31 + 20.02) * 109", "answer": "The result of (31 + 20.02) * 109 is 5561.18", "a": 31, "b": 20.02, "c": 109, "op1": "+", "op2": "*", "result": 5561.18}
{"question": "Solve: (84 * 11.76) / 69", "answer": "The result of (84 * 11.76) / 69 is 14.32", "a": 84, "b": 11.76, "c": 69, "op1": "*", "op2": "/", "result": 14.32}
{"question": "Solve: (2 - 11) * 99", "answer": "The result of (2 - 11) * 99 is -891", "a": 2, "b": 11, "c": 99, "op1": "-", "op2": "*", "result": -891}
{"question": "Solve: (82 + 116) + 196", "answer": "The result of (82 + 116) + 196 is 394", "a": 82, "b": 116, "c": 196, "op1": "+", "op2": "+", "result": 394}
{"question": "Solve: (43 + 43) + 196", "answer": "The result of (43 + 43) + 196 is 282", "a": 43, "b": 43, "c": 196, "op1": "+", "op2": "+", "result": 282}
{"question": "Solve: (80.72 - 143.46) * 59", "answer": "The result of (80.72 - 143.46) * 59 is -3701.66", "a": 80.72, "b": 143.46, "c": 59, "op1": "-", "op2": "*", "result": -3701.66}
{"question": "Solve: (138.65 - 1) + 147.76", "answer": "The result of (138.65 - 1) + 147.76 is 285.41", "a": 138.65, "b": 1, "c": 147.76, "op1": "-", "op2": "+", "result": 285.41}
{"question": "Solve: (79 + 39) + 90.87", "answer": "The result of (79 + 39) + 90.87 is 208.87", "a": 79, "b": 39, "c": 90.87, "op1": "+", "op2": "+", "result": 208.87}
{"question": "Solve: (116 + 90) + 29", "answer": "The result of (116 + 90) + 29 is 235", "a": 116, "b": 90, "c": 29, "op1": "+", "op2": "+", "result": 235}
{"question": "Solve: (160 + 134) - 52", "answer": "The result of (160 + 134) - 52 is 242", "a": 160, "b": 134, "c": 52, "op1": "+", "op2": "-", "result": 242}
{"question": "Solve: (68 * 17.19) + 119", "answer": "The result of (68 * 17.19) + 119 is 1287.92", "a": 68, "b": 17.19, "c": 119, "op1": "*", "op2": "+", "result": 1287.92}
{"question": "Solve: (185.11 - 163) + 31", "answer": "The result of (185.11 - 163) + 31 is 53.11", "a": 185.11, "b": 163, "c": 31, "op1": "-", "op2": "+", "result": 53.11}
{"question": "Solve: (134.45 * 72) / 35", "answer": "The result of (134.45 * 72) / 35 is 276.58", "a": 134.45, "b": 72, "c": 35, "op1": "*", "op2": "/", "result": 276.58}
{"question": "Solve: (168 * 56) + 194", "answer": "The result of (168 * 56) + 194 is 9602", "a": 168, "b": 56, "c": 194, "op1": "*", "op2": "+", "result": 9602}
{"question": "Solve: (23.96 / 132) - 102.79", "answer": "The result of (23.96 / 132) - 102.79 is -102.61", "a": 23.96, "b": 132, "c": 102.79, "op1": "/", "op2": "-", "result": -102.61}
{"question": "Solve: (72 / 17) * 60", "answer": "The result of (72 / 17) * 60 is 254.12", "a": 72, "b": 17, "c": 60, "op1": "/", "op2": "*", "result": 254.12}
{"question": "Solve: (186 * 94) * 121.8", "answer": "The result of (186 * 94) * 121.8 is 2129551.2", "a": 186, "b": 94, "c": 121.8, "op1": "*", "op2": "*", "result": 2129551.2}
{"question": "Solve: (121 - 131) / 128", "answer": "The result of (121 - 131) / 128 is -0.08", "a": 121, "b": 131, "c": 128, "op1": "-", "op2": "/", "result": -0.08}
{"question": "Solve: (32.12 / 129) * 198.57", "answer": "The result of (32.12 / 129) * 198.57 is 49.44", "a": 32.12, "b": 129, "c": 198.57, "op1": "/", "op2": "*", "result": 49.44}
{"question": "Solve: (174 + 152.74) + 161.59", "answer": "The result of (174 + 152.74) + 161.59 is 488.33", "a": 174, "b": 152.74, "c": 161.59, "op1": "+", "op2": "+", "result": 488.33}
{"question": "Solve: (177 + 32) + 154.64", "answer": "The result of (177 + 32) + 154.64 is 363.64", "a": 177, "b": 32, "c": 154.64, "op1": "+", "op2": "+", "result": 363.64}
{"question": "Solve: (139.38 + 116) * 124.94", "answer": "The result of (139.38 + 116) * 124.94 is 31907.18", "a": 139.38, "b": 116, "c": 124.94, "op1": "+", "op2": "*", "result": 31907.18}
{"question": "Solve: (72.73 - 14) / 170", "answer": "The result of (72.73 - 14) / 170 is 0.35", "a": 72.73, "b": 14, "c": 170, "op1": "-", "op2": "/", "result": 0.35}
{"question": "Solve: (49.92 + 184) / 170.6", "answer": "The result of (49.92 + 184) / 170.6 is 1.37", "a": 49.92, "b": 184, "c": 170.6, "op1": "+", "op2": "/", "result": 1.37}
{"question": "Solve: (22.78 * 75) - 166", "answer": "The result of (22.78 * 75) - 166 is 1542.5", "a": 22.78, "b": 75, "c": 166, "op1": "*", "op2": "-", "result": 1542.5}
{"question": "Solve: (175 * 191.11) + 111", "answer": "The result of (175 * 191.11) + 111 is 33555.25", "a": 175, "b": 191.11, "c": 111, "op1": "*", "op2": "+", "result": 33555.25}
{"question": "Solve: (120.2 + 110) / 13.33", "answer": "The result of (120.2 + 110) / 13.33 is 17.27", "a": 120.2, "b": 110, "c": 13.33, "op1": "+", "op2": "/", "result": 17.27}
{"question": "Solve: (72 + 178) + 137", "answer": "The result of (72 + 178) + 137 is 387", "a": 72, "b": 178, "c": 137, "op1": "+", "op2": "+", "result": 387}
{"question": "Solve: (62 * 130) - 5", "answer": "The result of (62 * 130) - 5 is 8055", "a": 62, "b": 130, "c": 5, "op1": "*", "op2": "-", "result": 8055}
{"question": "Solve: (86 * 69) + 94", "answer": "The result of (86 * 69) + 94 is 6028", "a": 86, "b": 69, "c": 94, "op1": "*", "op2": "+", "result": 6028}
{"question": "Solve: (51 + 27.22) - 170", "answer": "The result of (51 + 27.22) - 170 is -91.78", "a": 51, "b": 27.22, "c": 170, "op1": "+", "op2": "-", "result": -91.78}
{"question": "Solve: (53 * 146) + 173.72", "answer": "The result of (53 * 146) + 173.72 is 7911.72", "a": 53, "b": 146, "c": 173.72, "op1": "*", "op2": "+", "result": 7911.72}
{"question": "Solve: (58.18 / 195) / 198.29", "answer": "The result of (58.18 / 195) / 198.29 is 0.0", "a": 58.18, "b": 195, "c": 198.29, "op1": "/", "op2": "/", "result": 0.0}
{"question": "Solve: (88 - 46) / 168.17", "answer": "The result of (88 - 46) / 168.17 is 0.25", "a": 88, "b": 46, "c": 168.17, "op1": "-", "op2": "/", "result": 0.25}
{"question": "Solve: (122 - 162) * 116", "answer": "The result of (122 - 162) * 116 is -4640", "a": 122, "b": 162, "c": 116, "op1": "-", "op2": "*", "result": -4640}
{"question": "Solve: (108.2 + 81) / 86", "answer": "The result of (108.2 + 81) / 86 is 2.2", "a": 108.2, "b": 81, "c": 86, "op1": "+", "op2": "/", "result": 2.2}
{"question": "Solve: (170 - 96) + 74.98", "answer": "The result of (170 - 96) + 74.98 is 148.98", "a": 170, "b": 96, "c": 74.98, "op1": "-", "op2": "+", "result": 148.98}
{"question": "Solve: (155 + 29.31) + 178", "answer": "The result of (155 + 29.31) + 178 is 362.31", "a": 155, "b": 29.31, "c": 178, "op1": "+", "op2": "+", "result": 362.31}
{"question": "Solve: (91.47 * 40.99) * 79.16", "answer": "The result of (91.47 * 40.99) * 79.16 is 296798.97", "a": 91.47, "b": 40.99, "c": 79.16, "op1": "*", "op2": "*", "result": 296798.97}
{"question": "Solve: (56 / 87.25) * 75", "answer": "The result of (56 / 87.25) * 75 is 48.14", "a": 56, "b": 87.25, "c": 75, "op1": "/", "op2": "*", "result": 48.14}
{"question": "Solve: (144 - 190) / 83", "answer": "The result of (144 - 190) / 83 is -0.55", "a": 144, "b": 190, "c": 83, "op1": "-", "op2": "/", "result": -0.55}
{"question": "Solve: (100 / 85) - 66.5", "answer": "The result of (100 / 85) - 66.5 is -65.32", "a": 100, "b": 85, "c": 66.5, "op1": "/", "op2": "-", "result": -65.32}
{"question": "Solve: (163.94 - 114) / 193.04", "answer": "The result of (163.94 - 114) / 193.04 is 0.26", "a": 163.94, "b": 114, "c": 193.04, "op1": "-", "op2": "/", "result": 0.26}
{"question": "Solve: (7 * 14.2) + 17", "answer": "The result of (7 * 14.2) + 17 is 116.4", "a": 7, "b": 14.2, "c": 17, "op1": "*", "op2": "+", "result": 116.4}
{"question": "Solve: (118.23 - 94) * 89.67", "answer": "The result of (118.23 - 94) * 89.67 is 2172.7", "a": 118.23, "b": 94, "c": 89.67, "op1": "-", "op2": "*", "result": 2172.7}
{"question": "Solve: (163 * 72) / 182", "answer": "The result of (163 * 72) / 182 is 64.48", "a": 163, "b": 72, "c": 182, "op1": "*", "op2": "/", "result": 64.48}
{"question": "Solve: (57 + 118) - 111.6", "answer": "The result of (57 + 118) - 111.6 is 63.4", "a": 57, "b": 118, "c": 111.6, "op1": "+", "op2": "-", "result": 63.4}
{"question": "Solve: (168 * 48) / 117.45", "answer": "The result of (168 * 48) / 117.45 is 68.66", "a": 168, "b": 48, "c": 117.45, "op1": "*", "op2": "/", "result": 68.66}
{"question": "Solve: (129.83 + 190.51) + 136.86", "answer": "The result of (129.83 + 190.51) + 136.86 is 457.2", "a": 129.83, "b": 190.51, "c": 136.86, "op1": "+", "op2": "+", "result": 457.2}
{"question": "Solve: (133.28 * 30.73) - 139.03", "answer": "The result of (133.28 * 30.73) - 139.03 is 3956.66", "a": 133.28, "b": 30.73, "c": 139.03, "op1": "*", "op2": "-", "result": 3956.66}
{"question": "Solve: (179 - 74) / 57", "answer": "The result of (179 - 74) / 57 is 1.84", "a": 179, "b": 74, "c": 57, "op1": "-", "op2": "/", "result": 1.84}
{"question": "Solve: (121 * 132) * 48", "answer": "The result of (121 * 132) * 48 is 766656", "a": 121, "b": 132, "c": 48, "op1": "*", "op2": "*", "result": 766656}
{"question": "Solve: (28.2 / 85.62) - 196", "answer": "The result of (28.2 / 85.62) - 196 is -195.67", "a": 28.2, "b": 85.62, "c": 196, "op1": "/", "op2": "-", "result": -195.67}
{"question": "Solve: (75 + 175) - 166.48", "answer": "The result of (75 + 175) - 166.48 is 83.52", "a": 75, "b": 175, "c": 166.48, "op1": "+", "op2": "-", "result": 83.52}
{"question": "Solve: (171 * 88.18) / 170.48", "answer": "The result of (171 * 88.18) / 170.48 is 88.45", "a": 171, "b": 88.18, "c": 170.48, "op1": "*", "op2": "/", "result": 88.45}
{"question": "Solve: (153.11 - 94) * 118", "answer": "The result of (153.11 - 94) * 118 is 6974.98", "a": 153.11, "b": 94, "c": 118, "op1": "-", "op2": "*", "result": 6974.98}
{"question": "Solve: (197.65 + 128) / 62.93", "answer": "The result of (197.65 + 128) / 62.93 is 5.17", "a": 197.65, "b": 128, "c": 62.93, "op1": "+", "op2": "/", "result": 5.17}
{"question": "Solve: (171.54 + 140) - 3", "answer": "The result of (171.54 + 140) - 3 is 308.54", "a": 171.54, "b": 140, "c": 3, "op1": "+", "op2": "-", "result": 308.54}
{"question": "Solve: (181 * 37) - 185.42", "answer": "The result of (181 * 37) - 185.42 is 6511.58", "a": 181, "b": 37, "c": 185.42, "op1": "*", "op2": "-", "result": 6511.58}
{"question": "Solve: (97.08 - 106.49) + 170", "answer": "The result of (97.08 - 106.49) + 170 is 160.59", "a": 97.08, "b": 106.49, "c": 170, "op1": "-", "op2": "+", "result": 160.59}
{"question": "Solve: (168.88 + 90.33) * 174", "answer": "The result of (168.88 + 90.33) * 174 is 45102.54", "a": 168.88, "b": 90.33, "c": 174, "op1": "+", "op2": "*", "result": 45102.54}
{"question": "Solve: (93 + 34) * 81", "answer": "The result of (93 + 34) * 81 is 10287", "a": 93, "b": 34, "c": 81, "op1": "+", "op2": "*", "result": 10287}
{"question": "Solve: (47 * 150.19) - 133", "answer": "The result of (47 * 150.19) - 133 is 6925.93", "a": 47, "b": 150.19, "c": 133, "op1": "*", "op2": "-", "result": 6925.93}
{"question": "Solve: (65 * 182.32) - 71.07", "answer": "The result of (65 * 182.32) - 71.07 is 11779.73", "a": 65, "b": 182.32, "c": 71.07, "op1": "*", "op2": "-", "result": 11779.73}
{"question": "Solve: (93 + 169) + 115.4", "answer": "The result of (93 + 169) + 115.4 is 377.4", "a": 93, "b": 169, "c": 115.4, "op1": "+", "op2": "+", "result": 377.4}
{"question": "Solve: (119.67 + 41) * 92.01", "answer": "The result of (119.67 + 41) * 92.01 is 14783.25", "a": 119.67, "b": 41, "c": 92.01, "op1": "+", "op2": "*", "result": 14783.25}
{"question": "Solve: (48 + 137) + 188", "answer": "The result of (48 + 137) + 188 is 373", "a": 48, "b": 137, "c": 188, "op1": "+", "op2": "+", "result": 373}
{"question": "Solve: (148.73 + 32) - 123", "answer": "The result of (148.73 + 32) - 123 is 57.73", "a": 148.73, "b": 32, "c": 123, "op1": "+", "op2": "-", "result": 57.73}
{"question": "Solve: (149.53 + 33.13) - 83.72", "answer": "The result of (149.53 + 33.13) - 83.72 is 98.94", "a": 149.53, "b": 33.13, "c": 83.72, "op1": "+", "op2": "-", "result": 98.94}
{"question": "Solve: (94 - 29.99) - 13", "answer": "The result of (94 - 29.99) - 13 is 51.01", "a": 94, "b": 29.99, "c": 13, "op1": "-", "op2": "-", "result": 51.01}
{"question": "Solve: (80 * 83.92) + 153", "answer": "The result of (80 * 83.92) + 153 is 6866.6", "a": 80, "b": 83.92, "c": 153, "op1": "*", "op2": "+", "result": 6866.6}
{"question": "Solve: (179 / 161.4) - 188", "answer": "The result of (179 / 161.4) - 188 is -186.89", "a": 179, "b": 161.4, "c": 188, "op1": "/", "op2": "-", "result": -186.89}
{"question": "Solve: (191 * 106) - 102.56", "answer": "The result of (191 * 106) - 102.56 is 20143.44", "a": 191, "b": 106, "c": 102.56, "op1": "*", "op2": "-", "result": 20143.44}
{"question": "Solve: (198.52 / 48) / 6", "answer": "The result of (198.52 / 48) / 6 is 0.69", "a": 198.52, "b": 48, "c": 6, "op1": "/", "op2": "/", "result": 0.69}
{"question": "Solve: (61.07 * 24) + 174", "answer": "The result of (61.07 * 24) + 174 is 1639.68", "a": 61.07, "b": 24, "c": 174, "op1": "*", "op2": "+", "result": 1639.68}
{"question": "Solve: (148 / 101.75) * 150.76", "answer": "The result of (148 / 101.75) * 150.76 is 219.29", "a": 148, "b": 101.75, "c": 150.76, "op1": "/", "op2": "*", "result": 219.29}
{"question": "Solve: (141.55 + 157) - 69.04", "answer": "The result of (141.55 + 157) - 69.04 is 229.51", "a": 141.55, "b": 157, "c": 69.04, "op1": "+", "op2": "-", "result": 229.51}
{"question": "Solve: (71 + 46.63) * 69", "answer": "The result of (71 + 46.63) * 69 is 8116.47", "a": 71, "b": 46.63, "c": 69, "op1": "+", "op2": "*", "result": 8116.47}
{"question": "Solve: (148 + 79) - 62.42", "answer": "The result of (148 + 79) - 62.42 is 164.58", "a": 148, "b": 79, "c": 62.42, "op1": "+", "op2": "-", "result": 164.58}
{"question": "Solve: (169.97 + 76) * 175", "answer": "The result of (169.97 + 76) * 175 is 43044.75", "a": 169.97, "b": 76, "c": 175, "op1": "+", "op2": "*", "result": 43044.75}
{"question": "Solve: (5.14 + 130) * 35.89", "answer": "The result of (5.14 + 130) * 35.89 is 4850.17", "a": 5.14, "b": 130, "c": 35.89, "op1": "+", "op2": "*", "result": 4850.17}
{"question": "Solve: (25 + 138.6) * 152.44", "answer": "The result of (25 + 138.6) * 152.44 is 24939.18", "a": 25, "b": 138.6, "c": 152.44, "op1": "+", "op2": "*", "result": 24939.18}
{"question": "Solve: (110 + 175) + 101.52", "answer": "The result of (110 + 175) + 101.52 is 386.52", "a": 110, "b": 175, "c": 101.52, "op1": "+", "op2": "+", "result": 386.52}
{"question": "Solve: (18 - 87.55) * 108", "answer": "The result of (18 - 87.55) * 108 is -7511.4", "a": 18, "b": 87.55, "c": 108, "op1": "-", "op2": "*", "result": -7511.4}
{"question": "Solve: (67 - 109) - 37", "answer": "The result of (67 - 109) - 37 is -79", "a": 67, "b": 109, "c": 37, "op1": "-", "op2": "-", "result": -79}
{"question": "Solve: (13 / 108) - 194", "answer": "The result of (13 / 108) - 194 is -193.88", "a": 13, "b": 108, "c": 194, "op1": "/", "op2": "-", "result": -193.88}
{"question": "Solve: (106.62 - 88.69) + 83", "answer": "The result of (106.62 - 88.69) + 83 is 100.93", "a": 106.62, "b": 88.69, "c": 83, "op1": "-", "op2": "+", "result": 100.93}
{"question": "Solve: (146.0 + 194) + 187", "answer": "The result of (146.0 + 194) + 187 is 527.0", "a": 146.0, "b": 194, "c": 187, "op1": "+", "op2": "+", "result": 527.0}
{"question": "Solve: (29 * 123.73) / 101", "answer": "The result of (29 * 123.73) / 101 is 35.53", "a": 29, "b": 123.73, "c": 101, "op1": "*", "op2": "/", "result": 35.53}
{"question": "Solve: (183 * 27) - 188", "answer": "The result of (183 * 27) - 188 is 4753", "a": 183, "b": 27, "c": 188, "op1": "*", "op2": "-", "result": 4753}
{"question": "Solve: (138.81 + 185) - 62", "answer": "The result of (138.81 + 185) - 62 is 261.81", "a": 138.81, "b": 185, "c": 62, "op1": "+", "op2": "-", "result": 261.81}
{"question": "Solve: (29.91 * 37) + 10", "answer": "The result of (29.91 * 37) + 10 is 1116.67", "a": 29.91, "b": 37, "c": 10, "op1": "*", "op2": "+", "result": 1116.67}
{"question": "Solve: (178.09 - 17.9) + 176", "answer": "The result of (178.09 - 17.9) + 176 is 336.19", "a": 178.09, "b": 17.9, "c": 176, "op1": "-", "op2": "+", "result": 336.19}
{"question": "Solve: (159.41 - 98) - 171", "answer": "The result of (159.41 - 98) - 171 is -109.59", "a": 159.41, "b": 98, "c": 171, "op1": "-", "op2": "-", "result": -109.59}
{"question": "Solve: (52 + 172.85) + 105.76", "answer": "The result of (52 + 172.85) + 105.76 is 330.61", "a": 52, "b": 172.85, "c": 105.76, "op1": "+", "op2": "+", "result": 330.61}
{"question": "Solve: (19 * 76) + 32.67", "answer": "The result of (19 * 76) + 32.67 is 1476.67", "a": 19, "b": 76, "c": 32.67, "op1": "*", "op2": "+", "result": 1476.67}
{"question": "Solve: (199 / 38) + 176.34", "answer": "The result of (199 / 38) + 176.34 is 181.58", "a": 199, "b": 38, "c": 176.34, "op1": "/", "op2": "+", "result": 181.58}
{"question": "Solve: (142 * 42) * 115", "answer": "The result of (142 * 42) * 115 is 685860", "a": 142, "b": 42, "c": 115, "op1": "*", "op2": "*", "result": 685860}
{"question": "Solve: (14 + 35) / 29.06", "answer": "The result of (14 + 35) / 29.06 is 1.69", "a": 14, "b": 35, "c": 29.06, "op1": "+", "op2": "/", "result": 1.69}
{"question": "Solve: (161 + 161) * 34.02", "answer": "The result of (161 + 161) * 34.02 is 10954.44", "a": 161, "b": 161, "c": 34.02, "op1": "+", "op2": "*", "result": 10954.44}
{"question": "Solve: (192 / 158) * 39.23", "answer": "The result of (192 / 158) * 39.23 is 47.67", "a": 192, "b": 158, "c": 39.23, "op1": "/", "op2": "*", "result": 47.67}
{"question": "Solve: (32 * 32) - 97", "answer": "The result of (32 * 32) - 97 is 927", "a": 32, "b": 32, "c": 97, "op1": "*", "op2": "-", "result": 927}
{"question": "Solve: (31 - 160) + 95", "answer": "The result of (31 - 160) + 95 is -34", "a": 31, "b": 160, "c": 95, "op1": "-", "op2": "+", "result": -34}
{"question": "Solve: (91.2 - 9) + 116.6", "answer": "The result of (91.2 - 9) + 116.6 is 198.8", "a": 91.2, "b": 9, "c": 116.6, "op1": "-", "op2": "+", "result": 198.8}
{"question": "Solve: (121 - 108) * 63", "answer": "The result of (121 - 108) * 63 is 819", "a": 121, "b": 108, "c": 63, "op1": "-", "op2": "*", "result": 819}
{"question": "Solve: (183 + 168.47) / 36", "answer": "The result of (183 + 168.47) / 36 is 9.76", "a": 183, "b": 168.47, "c": 36, "op1": "+", "op2": "/", "result": 9.76}
{"question": "Solve: (123 * 86) + 4", "answer": "The result of (123 * 86) + 4 is 10582", "a": 123, "b": 86, "c": 4, "op1": "*", "op2": "+", "result": 10582}
{"question": "Solve: (45 - 181) / 16", "answer": "The result of (45 - 181) / 16 is -8.5", "a": 45, "b": 181, "c": 16, "op1": "-", "op2": "/", "result": -8.5}
{"question": "Solve: (160 - 132.03) + 149.11", "answer": "The result of (160 - 132.03) + 149.11 is 177.08", "a": 160, "b": 132.03, "c": 149.11, "op1": "-", "op2": "+", "result": 177.08}
{"question": "Solve: (185 / 118.24) + 43", "answer": "The result of (185 / 118.24) + 43 is 44.56", "a": 185, "b": 118.24, "c": 43, "op1": "/", "op2": "+", "result": 44.56}
{"question": "Solve: (157 * 173) * 55", "answer": "The result of (157 * 173) * 55 is 1493855", "a": 157, "b": 173, "c": 55, "op1": "*", "op2": "*", "result": 1493855}
{"question": "Solve: (129 / 198) / 19", "answer": "The result of (129 / 198) / 19 is 0.03", "a": 129, "b": 198, "c": 19, "op1": "/", "op2": "/", "result": 0.03}
{"question": "Solve: (71 / 115) / 191.78", "answer": "The result of (71 / 115) / 191.78 is 0.0", "a": 71, "b": 115, "c": 191.78, "op1": "/", "op2": "/", "result": 0.0}
{"question": "Solve: (65 + 162) * 24", "answer": "The result of (65 + 162) * 24 is 5448", "a": 65, "b": 162, "c": 24, "op1": "+", "op2": "*", "result": 5448}
{"question": "Solve: (61 + 152) / 54", "answer": "The result of (61 + 152) / 54 is 3.94", "a": 61, "b": 152, "c": 54, "op1": "+", "op2": "/", "result": 3.94}
{"question": "Solve: (53.15 * 98.74) - 8", "answer": "The result of (53.15 * 98.74) - 8 is 5240.03", "a": 53.15, "b": 98.74, "c": 8, "op1": "*", "op2": "-", "result": 5240.03}
{"question": "Solve: (41 * 153) * 195.46", "answer": "The result of (41 * 153) * 195.46 is 1226120.58", "a": 41, "b": 153, "c": 195.46, "op1": "*", "op2": "*", "result": 1226120.58}
{"question": "Solve: (32 + 26) + 58", "answer": "The result of (32 + 26) + 58 is 116", "a": 32, "b": 26, "c": 58, "op1": "+", "op2": "+", "result": 116}
{"question": "Solve: (193.19 - 133) - 125", "answer": "The result of (193.19 - 133) - 125 is -64.81", "a": 193.19, "b": 133, "c": 125, "op1": "-", "op2": "-", "result": -64.81}
{"question": "Solve: (36 - 200) + 19", "answer": "The result of (36 - 200) + 19 is -145", "a": 36, "b": 200, "c": 19, "op1": "-", "op2": "+", "result": -145}
{"question": "Solve: (82 * 29) + 175", "answer": "The result of (82 * 29) + 175 is 2553", "a": 82, "b": 29, "c": 175, "op1": "*", "op2": "+", "result": 2553}
{"question": "Solve: (44 - 187) * 63", "answer": "The result of (44 - 187) * 63 is -9009", "a": 44, "b": 187, "c": 63, "op1": "-", "op2": "*", "result": -9009}
{"question": "Solve: (33 - 181.09) * 40", "answer": "The result of (33 - 181.09) * 40 is -5923.6", "a": 33, "b": 181.09, "c": 40, "op1": "-", "op2": "*", "result": -5923.6}
{"question": "Solve: (9.35 * 23.04) * 18.98", "answer": "The result of (9.35 * 23.04) * 18.98 is 4088.75", "a": 9.35, "b": 23.04, "c": 18.98, "op1": "*", "op2": "*", "result": 4088.75}
{"question": "Solve: (143 / 87) - 86", "answer": "The result of (143 / 87) - 86 is -84.36", "a": 143, "b": 87, "c": 86, "op1": "/", "op2": "-", "result": -84.36}
{"question": "Solve: (133.59 * 28.62) - 6", "answer": "The result of (133.59 * 28.62) - 6 is 3817.35", "a": 133.59, "b": 28.62, "c": 6, "op1": "*", "op2": "-", "result": 3817.35}
{"question": "Solve: (29.91 - 4.08) + 167", "answer": "The result of (29.91 - 4.08) + 167 is 192.83", "a": 29.91, "b": 4.08, "c": 167, "op1": "-", "op2": "+", "result": 192.83}
{"question": "Solve: (186.17 * 105) - 28", "answer": "The result of (186.17 * 105) - 28 is 19519.85", "a": 186.17, "b": 105, "c": 28, "op1": "*", "op2": "-", "result": 19519.85}
{"question": "Solve: (40 + 171.87) / 19", "answer": "The result of (40 + 171.87) / 19 is 11.15", "a": 40, "b": 171.87, "c": 19, "op1": "+", "op2": "/", "result": 11.15}
{"question": "Solve: (199.55 + 147.07) + 101", "answer": "The result of (199.55 + 147.07) + 101 is 447.62", "a": 199.55, "b": 147.07, "c": 101, "op1": "+", "op2": "+", "result": 447.62}
{"question": "Solve: (170.88 * 37) / 112", "answer": "The result of (170.88 * 37) / 112 is 56.45", "a": 170.88, "b": 37, "c": 112, "op1": "*", "op2": "/", "result": 56.45}
{"question": "Solve: (66.13 - 169.31) - 117", "answer": "The result of (66.13 - 169.31) - 117 is -220.18", "a": 66.13, "b": 169.31, "c": 117, "op1": "-", "op2": "-", "result": -220.18}
{"question": "Solve: (39.42 + 57) / 124", "answer": "The result of (39.42 + 57) / 124 is 0.78", "a": 39.42, "b": 57, "c": 124, "op1": "+", "op2": "/", "result": 0.78}
{"question": "Solve: (97 + 37) * 131", "answer": "The result of (97 + 37) * 131 is 17554", "a": 97, "b": 37, "c": 131, "op1": "+", "op2": "*", "result": 17554}
{"question": "Solve: (171.21 * 63) / 113", "answer": "The result of (171.21 * 63) / 113 is 95.45", "a": 171.21, "b": 63, "c": 113, "op1": "*", "op2": "/", "result": 95.45}
{"question": "Solve: (64.55 + 77) - 161.63", "answer": "The result of (64.55 + 77) - 161.63 is -20.08", "a": 64.55, "b": 77, "c": 161.63, "op1": "+", "op2": "-", "result": -20.08}
{"question": "Solve: (195 - 57) - 67", "answer": "The result of (195 - 57) - 67 is 71", "a": 195, "b": 57, "c": 67, "op1": "-", "op2": "-", "result": 71}
{"question": "Solve: (14.12 / 154) * 78", "answer": "The result of (14.12 / 154) * 78 is 7.15", "a": 14.12, "b": 154, "c": 78, "op1": "/", "op2": "*", "result": 7.15}
{"question": "Solve: (127 + 193) - 4.79", "answer": "The result of (127 + 193) - 4.79 is 315.21", "a": 127, "b": 193, "c": 4.79, "op1": "+", "op2": "-", "result": 315.21}
{"question": "Solve: (13.2 / 152) + 171", "answer": "The result of (13.2 / 152) + 171 is 171.09", "a": 13.2, "b": 152, "c": 171, "op1": "/", "op2": "+", "result": 171.09}
{"question": "Solve: (194 * 88) - 53", "answer": "The result of (194 * 88) - 53 is 17019", "a": 194, "b": 88, "c": 53, "op1": "*", "op2": "-", "result": 17019}
{"question": "Solve: (44 / 185.61) - 163", "answer": "The result of (44 / 185.61) - 163 is -162.76", "a": 44, "b": 185.61, "c": 163, "op1": "/", "op2": "-", "result": -162.76}
{"question": "Solve: (102.23 * 89) + 75.5", "answer": "The result of (102.23 * 89) + 75.5 is 9173.97", "a": 102.23, "b": 89, "c": 75.5, "op1": "*", "op2": "+", "result": 9173.97}
{"question": "Solve: (32 * 74.84) + 115", "answer": "The result of (32 * 74.84) + 115 is 2509.88", "a": 32, "b": 74.84, "c": 115, "op1": "*", "op2": "+", "result": 2509.88}
{"question": "Solve: (72.32 - 130) * 196", "answer": "The result of (72.32 - 130) * 196 is -11305.28", "a": 72.32, "b": 130, "c": 196, "op1": "-", "op2": "*", "result": -11305.28}
{"question": "Solve: (25 + 86) - 13", "answer": "The result of (25 + 86) - 13 is 98", "a": 25, "b": 86, "c": 13, "op1": "+", "op2": "-", "result": 98}
{"question": "Solve: (1 * 112) - 12", "answer": "The result of (1 * 112) - 12 is 100", "a": 1, "b": 112, "c": 12, "op1": "*", "op2": "-", "result": 100}
{"question": "Solve: (13.33 - 175) + 19", "answer": "The result of (13.33 - 175) + 19 is -142.67", "a": 13.33, "b": 175, "c": 19, "op1": "-", "op2": "+", "result": -142.67}
{"question": "Solve: (48 - 151.54) * 188", "answer": "The result of (48 - 151.54) * 188 is -19465.52", "a": 48, "b": 151.54, "c": 188, "op1": "-", "op2": "*", "result": -19465.52}
{"question": "Solve: (44 * 19.71) - 8", "answer": "The result of (44 * 19.71) - 8 is 859.24", "a": 44, "b": 19.71, "c": 8, "op1": "*", "op2": "-", "result": 859.24}
{"question": "Solve: (36 * 16) + 119.51", "answer": "The result of (36 * 16) + 119.51 is 695.51", "a": 36, "b": 16, "c": 119.51, "op1": "*", "op2": "+", "result": 695.51}
{"question": "Solve: (104 + 20) * 30.35", "answer": "The result of (104 + 20) * 30.35 is 3763.4", "a": 104, "b": 20, "c": 30.35, "op1": "+", "op2": "*", "result": 3763.4}
{"question": "Solve: (128 + 133.6) + 6.12", "answer": "The result of (128 + 133.6) + 6.12 is 267.72", "a": 128, "b": 133.6, "c": 6.12, "op1": "+", "op2": "+", "result": 267.72}
{"question": "Solve: (6.45 - 55.21) + 146", "answer": "The result of (6.45 - 55.21) + 146 is 97.24", "a": 6.45, "b": 55.21, "c": 146, "op1": "-", "op2": "+", "result": 97.24}
{"question": "Solve: (73 + 200) - 53", "answer": "The result of (73 + 200) - 53 is 220", "a": 73, "b": 200, "c": 53, "op1": "+", "op2": "-", "result": 220}
{"question": "Solve: (11 + 186.86) + 26", "answer": "The result of (11 + 186.86) + 26 is 223.86", "a": 11, "b": 186.86, "c": 26, "op1": "+", "op2": "+", "result": 223.86}
{"question": "Solve: (46 / 98) + 193", "answer": "The result of (46 / 98) + 193 is 193.47", "a": 46, "b": 98, "c": 193, "op1": "/", "op2": "+", "result": 193.47}
{"question": "Solve: (89 - 74) + 128", "answer": "The result of (89 - 74) + 128 is 143", "a": 89, "b": 74, "c": 128, "op1": "-", "op2": "+", "result": 143}
{"question": "Solve: (73 - 25.59) / 85.99", "answer": "The result of (73 - 25.59) / 85.99 is 0.55", "a": 73, "b": 25.59, "c": 85.99, "op1": "-", "op2": "/", "result": 0.55}
{"question": "Solve: (9 - 145) / 101", "answer": "The result of (9 - 145) / 101 is -1.35", "a": 9, "b": 145, "c": 101, "op1": "-", "op2": "/", "result": -1.35}
{"question": "Solve: (160.6 * 104) - 157", "answer": "The result of (160.6 * 104) - 157 is 16545.4", "a": 160.6, "b": 104, "c": 157, "op1": "*", "op2": "-", "result": 16545.4}
{"question": "Solve: (79.12 - 48) * 189", "answer": "The result of (79.12 - 48) * 189 is 5881.68", "a": 79.12, "b": 48, "c": 189, "op1": "-", "op2": "*", "result": 5881.68}
{"question": "Solve: (80.05 - 172) / 76", "answer": "The result of (80.05 - 172) / 76 is -1.21", "a": 80.05, "b": 172, "c": 76, "op1": "-", "op2": "/", "result": -1.21}
{"question": "Solve: (129 * 180.58) + 122", "answer": "The result of (129 * 180.58) + 122 is 23416.82", "a": 129, "b": 180.58, "c": 122, "op1": "*", "op2": "+", "result": 23416.82}
{"question": "Solve: (120 / 46.01) + 12.32", "answer": "The result of (120 / 46.01) + 12.32 is 14.93", "a": 120, "b": 46.01, "c": 12.32, "op1": "/", "op2": "+", "result": 14.93}
{"question": "Solve: (99 + 192.68) * 192.04", "answer": "The result of (99 + 192.68) * 192.04 is 56014.23", "a": 99, "b": 192.68, "c": 192.04, "op1": "+", "op2": "*", "result": 56014.23}
{"question": "Solve: (36 / 107) / 129", "answer": "The result of (36 / 107) / 129 is 0.0", "a": 36, "b": 107, "c": 129, "op1": "/", "op2": "/", "result": 0.0}
{"question": "Solve: (104.94 * 164) * 169.52", "answer": "The result of (104.94 * 164) * 169.52 is 2917466.32", "a": 104.94, "b": 164, "c": 169.52, "op1": "*", "op2": "*", "result": 2917466.32}
{"question": "Solve: (124 + 112) * 42", "answer": "The result of (124 + 112) * 42 is 9912", "a": 124, "b": 112, "c": 42, "op1": "+", "op2": "*", "result": 9912}
{"question": "Solve: (103 + 79.76) + 101", "answer": "The result of (103 + 79.76) + 101 is 283.76", "a": 103, "b": 79.76, "c": 101, "op1": "+", "op2": "+", "result": 283.76}
{"question": "Solve: (147.23 - 100.37) * 47", "answer": "The result of (147.23 - 100.37) * 47 is 2202.42", "a": 147.23, "b": 100.37, "c": 47, "op1": "-", "op2": "*", "result": 2202.42}
{"question": "Solve: (174 * 87) - 17", "answer": "The result of (174 * 87) - 17 is 15121", "a": 174, "b": 87, "c": 17, "op1": "*", "op2": "-", "result": 15121}
{"question": "Solve: (172 - 178) - 168", "answer": "The result of (172 - 178) - 168 is -174", "a": 172, "b": 178, "c": 168, "op1": "-", "op2": "-", "result": -174}
{"question": "Solve: (47.91 - 75.49) - 183", "answer": "The result of (47.91 - 75.49) - 183 is -210.58", "a": 47.91, "b": 75.49, "c": 183, "op1": "-", "op2": "-", "result": -210.58}
{"question": "Solve: (187 * 42) - 54", "answer": "The result of (187 * 42) - 54 is 7800", "a": 187, "b": 42, "c": 54, "op1": "*", "op2": "-", "result": 7800}
{"question": "Solve: (40.59 - 171) * 7", "answer": "The result of (40.59 - 171) * 7 is -912.87", "a": 40.59, "b": 171, "c": 7, "op1": "-", "op2": "*", "result": -912.87}
{"question": "Solve: (52 + 106.79) - 119.55", "answer": "The result of (52 + 106.79) - 119.55 is 39.24", "a": 52, "b": 106.79, "c": 119.55, "op1": "+", "op2": "-", "result": 39.24}
{"question": "Solve: (117 + 94) + 90", "answer": "The result of (117 + 94) + 90 is 301", "a": 117, "b": 94, "c": 90, "op1": "+", "op2": "+", "result": 301}
{"question": "Solve: (102.89 - 145.7) / 147", "answer": "The result of (102.89 - 145.7) / 147 is -0.29", "a": 102.89, "b": 145.7, "c": 147, "op1": "-", "op2": "/", "result": -0.29}
{"question": "Solve: (99 / 54) + 152.65", "answer": "The result of (99 / 54) + 152.65 is 154.48", "a": 99, "b": 54, "c": 152.65, "op1": "/", "op2": "+", "result": 154.48}
{"question": "Solve: (42.1 + 57) / 38", "answer": "The result of (42.1 + 57) / 38 is 2.61", "a": 42.1, "b": 57, "c": 38, "op1": "+", "op2": "/", "result": 2.61}
{"question": "Solve: (87 * 135) + 114", "answer": "The result of (87 * 135) + 114 is 11859", "a": 87, "b": 135, "c": 114, "op1": "*", "op2": "+", "result": 11859}
{"question": "Solve: (97 * 190) - 166.31", "answer": "The result of (97 * 190) - 166.31 is 18263.69", "a": 97, "b": 190, "c": 166.31, "op1": "*", "op2": "-", "result": 18263.69}
{"question": "Solve: (86.57 + 159) * 29", "answer": "The result of (86.57 + 159) * 29 is 7121.53", "a": 86.57, "b": 159, "c": 29, "op1": "+", "op2": "*", "result": 7121.53}
{"question": "Solve: (40 - 100) * 119", "answer": "The result of (40 - 100) * 119 is -7140", "a": 40, "b": 100, "c": 119, "op1": "-", "op2": "*", "result": -7140}
{"question": "Solve: (188 * 123) + 197", "answer": "The result of (188 * 123) + 197 is 23321", "a": 188, "b": 123, "c": 197, "op1": "*", "op2": "+", "result": 23321}
{"question": "Solve: (186 * 192) + 89.6", "answer": "The result of (186 * 192) + 89.6 is 35801.6", "a": 186, "b": 192, "c": 89.6, "op1": "*", "op2": "+", "result": 35801.6}
{"question": "Solve: (143 * 105.62) + 130", "answer": "The result of (143 * 105.62) + 130 is 15233.66", "a": 143, "b": 105.62, "c": 130, "op1": "*", "op2": "+", "result": 15233.66}
{"question": "Solve: (54 / 154) + 106", "answer": "The result of (54 / 154) + 106 is 106.35", "a": 54, "b": 154, "c": 106, "op1": "/", "op2": "+", "result": 106.35}
{"question": "Solve: (146 / 124) - 183", "answer": "The result of (146 / 124) - 183 is -181.82", "a": 146, "b": 124, "c": 183, "op1": "/", "op2": "-", "result": -181.82}
{"question": "Solve: (183 + 4) + 62", "answer": "The result of (183 + 4) + 62 is 249", "a": 183, "b": 4, "c": 62, "op1": "+", "op2": "+", "result": 249}
{"question": "Solve: (40.14 + 125) - 193", "answer": "The result of (40.14 + 125) - 193 is -27.86", "a": 40.14, "b": 125, "c": 193, "op1": "+", "op2": "-", "result": -27.86}
{"question": "Solve: (10.66 * 54) * 183", "answer": "The result of (10.66 * 54) * 183 is 105342.12", "a": 10.66, "b": 54, "c": 183, "op1": "*", "op2": "*", "result": 105342.12}
{"question": "Solve: (128 * 5) + 104", "answer": "The result of (128 * 5) + 104 is 744", "a": 128, "b": 5, "c": 104, "op1": "*", "op2": "+", "result": 744}
{"question": "Solve: (147 + 151.18) * 22", "answer": "The result of (147 + 151.18) * 22 is 6559.96", "a": 147, "b": 151.18, "c": 22, "op1": "+", "op2": "*", "result": 6559.96}
{"question": "Solve: (64.26 + 147) - 20", "answer": "The result of (64.26 + 147) - 20 is 191.26", "a": 64.26, "b": 147, "c": 20, "op1": "+", "op2": "-", "result": 191.26}
{"question": "Solve: (27.5 - 79) - 42.02", "answer": "The result of (27.5 - 79) - 42.02 is -93.52", "a": 27.5, "b": 79, "c": 42.02, "op1": "-", "op2": "-", "result": -93.52}
{"question": "Solve: (77 - 71) / 22", "answer": "The result of (77 - 71) / 22 is 0.27", "a": 77, "b": 71, "c": 22, "op1": "-", "op2": "/", "result": 0.27}
{"question": "Solve: (4 * 189) + 120.54", "answer": "The result of (4 * 189) + 120.54 is 876.54", "a": 4, "b": 189, "c": 120.54, "op1": "*", "op2": "+", "result": 876.54}
{"question": "Solve: (180 / 105) * 28", "answer": "The result of (180 / 105) * 28 is 48.0", "a": 180, "b": 105, "c": 28, "op1": "/", "op2": "*", "result": 48.0}
{"question": "Solve: (51.95 + 111) + 188", "answer": "The result of (51.95 + 111) + 188 is 350.95", "a": 51.95, "b": 111, "c": 188, "op1": "+", "op2": "+", "result": 350.95}
{"question": "Solve: (37 + 147.48) - 26", "answer": "The result of (37 + 147.48) - 26 is 158.48", "a": 37, "b": 147.48, "c": 26, "op1": "+", "op2": "-", "result": 158.48}
{"question": "Solve: (53 - 61) - 170", "answer": "The result of (53 - 61) - 170 is -178", "a": 53, "b": 61, "c": 170, "op1": "-", "op2": "-", "result": -178}
{"question": "Solve: (93 + 138.12) - 172", "answer": "The result of (93 + 138.12) - 172 is 59.12", "a": 93, "b": 138.12, "c": 172, "op1": "+", "op2": "-", "result": 59.12}
{"question": "Solve: (49.68 + 40) + 4.46", "answer": "The result of (49.68 + 40) + 4.46 is 94.14", "a": 49.68, "b": 40, "c": 4.46, "op1": "+", "op2": "+", "result": 94.14}
{"question": "Solve: (30.07 + 110) * 139", "answer": "The result of (30.07 + 110) * 139 is 19469.73", "a": 30.07, "b": 110, "c": 139, "op1": "+", "op2": "*", "result": 19469.73}
{"question": "Solve: (142 / 47) + 127.65", "answer": "The result of (142 / 47) + 127.65 is 130.67", "a": 142, "b": 47, "c": 127.65, "op1": "/", "op2": "+", "result": 130.67}
{"question": "Solve: (163 + 138) / 187", "answer": "The result of (163 + 138) / 187 is 1.61", "a": 163, "b": 138, "c": 187, "op1": "+", "op2": "/", "result": 1.61}
{"question": "Solve: (133 + 91) * 128", "answer": "The result of (133 + 91) * 128 is 28672", "a": 133, "b": 91, "c": 128, "op1": "+", "op2": "*", "result": 28672}
{"question": "Solve: (169 - 66.25) * 27", "answer": "The result of (169 - 66.25) * 27 is 2774.25", "a": 169, "b": 66.25, "c": 27, "op1": "-", "op2": "*", "result": 2774.25}
{"question": "Solve: (122 - 55) * 67.02", "answer": "The result of (122 - 55) * 67.02 is 4490.34", "a": 122, "b": 55, "c": 67.02, "op1": "-", "op2": "*", "result": 4490.34}
{"question": "Solve: (115 / 13) * 11", "answer": "The result of (115 / 13) * 11 is 97.31", "a": 115, "b": 13, "c": 11, "op1": "/", "op2": "*", "result": 97.31}
{"question": "Solve: (99 + 198) + 104", "answer": "The result of (99 + 198) + 104 is 401", "a": 99, "b": 198, "c": 104, "op1": "+", "op2": "+", "result": 401}
{"question": "Solve: (102 + 160) - 30", "answer": "The result of (102 + 160) - 30 is 232", "a": 102, "b": 160, "c": 30, "op1": "+", "op2": "-", "result": 232}
{"question": "Solve: (60.13 - 91) + 78", "answer": "The result of (60.13 - 91) + 78 is 47.13", "a": 60.13, "b": 91, "c": 78, "op1": "-", "op2": "+", "result": 47.13}
{"question": "Solve: (10 - 57) * 81.69", "answer": "The result of (10 - 57) * 81.69 is -3839.43", "a": 10, "b": 57, "c": 81.69, "op1": "-", "op2": "*", "result": -3839.43}
{"question": "Solve: (194 * 152.37) - 25", "answer": "The result of (194 * 152.37) - 25 is 29534.78", "a": 194, "b": 152.37, "c": 25, "op1": "*", "op2": "-", "result": 29534.78}
{"question": "Solve: (109.91 - 145) * 144", "answer": "The result of (109.91 - 145) * 144 is -5052.96", "a": 109.91, "b": 145, "c": 144, "op1": "-", "op2": "*", "result": -5052.96}
{"question": "Solve: (180.77 - 172) / 190", "answer": "The result of (180.77 - 172) / 190 is 0.05", "a": 180.77, "b": 172, "c": 190, "op1": "-", "op2": "/", "result": 0.05}
{"question": "Solve: (30 / 135) * 40", "answer": "The result of (30 / 135) * 40 is 8.89", "a": 30, "b": 135, "c": 40, "op1": "/", "op2": "*", "result": 8.89}
{"question": "Solve: (140.18 + 1.6) * 161", "answer": "The result of (140.18 + 1.6) * 161 is 22826.58", "a": 140.18, "b": 1.6, "c": 161, "op1": "+", "op2": "*", "result": 22826.58}
{"question": "Solve: (182.93 + 32) - 117", "answer": "The result of (182.93 + 32) - 117 is 97.93", "a": 182.93, "b": 32, "c": 117, "op1": "+", "op2": "-", "result": 97.93}
{"question": "Solve: (14 + 84.37) + 163", "answer": "The result of (14 + 84.37) + 163 is 261.37", "a": 14, "b": 84.37, "c": 163, "op1": "+", "op2": "+", "result": 261.37}
{"question": "Solve: (168 * 47) - 67", "answer": "The result of (168 * 47) - 67 is 7829", "a": 168, "b": 47, "c": 67, "op1": "*", "op2": "-", "result": 7829}
{"question": "Solve: (182 * 172) + 18.71", "answer": "The result of (182 * 172) + 18.71 is 31322.71", "a": 182, "b": 172, "c": 18.71, "op1": "*", "op2": "+", "result": 31322.71}
{"question": "Solve: (88 - 164) / 166.5", "answer": "The result of (88 - 164) / 166.5 is -0.46", "a": 88, "b": 164, "c": 166.5, "op1": "-", "op2": "/", "result": -0.46}
{"question": "Solve: (151 - 70) - 166", "answer": "The result of (151 - 70) - 166 is -85", "a": 151, "b": 70, "c": 166, "op1": "-", "op2": "-", "result": -85}
{"question": "Solve: (73 - 151) * 131", "answer": "The result of (73 - 151) * 131 is -10218", "a": 73, "b": 151, "c": 131, "op1": "-", "op2": "*", "result": -10218}
{"question": "Solve: (160.51 + 73) + 129", "answer": "The result of (160.51 + 73) + 129 is 362.51", "a": 160.51, "b": 73, "c": 129, "op1": "+", "op2": "+", "result": 362.51}
{"question": "Solve: (43 * 182) - 123.23", "answer": "The result of (43 * 182) - 123.23 is 7702.77", "a": 43, "b": 182, "c": 123.23, "op1": "*", "op2": "-", "result": 7702.77}
{"question": "Solve: (52.8 * 154.03) * 34", "answer": "The result of (52.8 * 154.03) * 34 is 276514.66", "a": 52.8, "b": 154.03, "c": 34, "op1": "*", "op2": "*", "result": 276514.66}
{"question": "Solve: (169 / 155) - 115", "answer": "The result of (169 / 155) - 115 is -113.91", "a": 169, "b": 155, "c": 115, "op1": "/", "op2": "-", "result": -113.91}
{"question": "Solve: (119 + 119) - 197", "answer": "The result of (119 + 119) - 197 is 41", "a": 119, "b": 119, "c": 197, "op1": "+", "op2": "-", "result": 41}
{"question": "Solve: (104 - 21.52) - 157", "answer": "The result of (104 - 21.52) - 157 is -74.52", "a": 104, "b": 21.52, "c": 157, "op1": "-", "op2": "-", "result": -74.52}
{"question": "Solve: (29 - 72) - 90", "answer": "The result of (29 - 72) - 90 is -133", "a": 29, "b": 72, "c": 90, "op1": "-", "op2": "-", "result": -133}
{"question": "Solve: (141.7 + 157) + 23", "answer": "The result of (141.7 + 157) + 23 is 321.7", "a": 141.7, "b": 157, "c": 23, "op1": "+", "op2": "+", "result": 321.7}
{"question": "Solve: (108 + 174.59) + 76", "answer": "The result of (108 + 174.59) + 76 is 358.59", "a": 108, "b": 174.59, "c": 76, "op1": "+", "op2": "+", "result": 358.59}
{"question": "Solve: (72 - 145) / 171", "answer": "The result of (72 - 145) / 171 is -0.43", "a": 72, "b": 145, "c": 171, "op1": "-", "op2": "/", "result": -0.43}
{"question": "Solve: (64 + 18) / 185", "answer": "The result of (64 + 18) / 185 is 0.44", "a": 64, "b": 18, "c": 185, "op1": "+", "op2": "/", "result": 0.44}
{"question": "Solve: (99.07 / 99) * 147", "answer": "The result of (99.07 / 99) * 147 is 147.1", "a": 99.07, "b": 99, "c": 147, "op1": "/", "op2": "*", "result": 147.1}
{"question": "Solve: (128 / 184) / 120", "answer": "The result of (128 / 184) / 120 is 0.01", "a": 128, "b": 184, "c": 120, "op1": "/", "op2": "/", "result": 0.01}
{"question": "Solve: (146 * 175) * 142.48", "answer": "The result of (146 * 175) * 142.48 is 3640364.0", "a": 146, "b": 175, "c": 142.48, "op1": "*", "op2": "*", "result": 3640364.0}
{"question": "Solve: (45.13 - 47.96) + 5.73", "answer": "The result of (45.13 - 47.96) + 5.73 is 2.9", "a": 45.13, "b": 47.96, "c": 5.73, "op1": "-", "op2": "+", "result": 2.9}
{"question": "Solve: (185.6 + 80.93) / 111", "answer": "The result of (185.6 + 80.93) / 111 is 2.4", "a": 185.6, "b": 80.93, "c": 111, "op1": "+", "op2": "/", "result": 2.4}
{"question": "Solve: (173 + 72.08) + 152", "answer": "The result of (173 + 72.08) + 152 is 397.08", "a": 173, "b": 72.08, "c": 152, "op1": "+", "op2": "+", "result": 397.08}
{"question": "Solve: (60.84 * 140) / 43", "answer": "The result of (60.84 * 140) / 43 is 198.08", "a": 60.84, "b": 140, "c": 43, "op1": "*", "op2": "/", "result": 198.08}
{"question": "Solve: (132 * 102.07) + 8.16", "answer": "The result of (132 * 102.07) + 8.16 is 13481.4", "a": 132, "b": 102.07, "c": 8.16, "op1": "*", "op2": "+", "result": 13481.4}
{"question": "Solve: (197 + 112) / 49", "answer": "The result of (197 + 112) / 49 is 6.31", "a": 197, "b": 112, "c": 49, "op1": "+", "op2": "/", "result": 6.31}
{"question": "Solve: (17 - 196.97) * 67", "answer": "The result of (17 - 196.97) * 67 is -12057.99", "a": 17, "b": 196.97, "c": 67, "op1": "-", "op2": "*", "result": -12057.99}
{"question": "Solve: (82 - 118) + 128", "answer": "The result of (82 - 118) + 128 is 92", "a": 82, "b": 118, "c": 128, "op1": "-", "op2": "+", "result": 92}
{"question": "Solve: (132 * 46.61) - 114", "answer": "The result of (132 * 46.61) - 114 is 6038.52", "a": 132, "b": 46.61, "c": 114, "op1": "*", "op2": "-", "result": 6038.52}
{"question": "Solve: (72.14 - 98) * 193.7", "answer": "The result of (72.14 - 98) * 193.7 is -5009.08", "a": 72.14, "b": 98, "c": 193.7, "op1": "-", "op2": "*", "result": -5009.08}
{"question": "Solve: (134 + 113) * 147", "answer": "The result of (134 + 113) * 147 is 36309", "a": 134, "b": 113, "c": 147, "op1": "+", "op2": "*", "result": 36309}
{"question": "Solve: (37.99 - 11) / 76", "answer": "The result of (37.99 - 11) / 76 is 0.36", "a": 37.99, "b": 11, "c": 76, "op1": "-", "op2": "/", "result": 0.36}
{"question": "Solve: (53 + 134) + 99", "answer": "The result of (53 + 134) + 99 is 286", "a": 53, "b": 134, "c": 99, "op1": "+", "op2": "+", "result": 286}
{"question": "Solve: (24 / 108) - 181", "answer": "The result of (24 / 108) - 181 is -180.78", "a": 24, "b": 108, "c": 181, "op1": "/", "op2": "-", "result": -180.78}
{"question": "Solve: (13 * 2.11) - 130", "answer": "The result of (13 * 2.11) - 130 is -102.57", "a": 13, "b": 2.11, "c": 130, "op1": "*", "op2": "-", "result": -102.57}
{"question": "Solve: (19 / 67) * 144", "answer": "The result of (19 / 67) * 144 is 40.84", "a": 19, "b": 67, "c": 144, "op1": "/", "op2": "*", "result": 40.84}
{"question": "Solve: (189 - 118) + 124", "answer": "The result of (189 - 118) + 124 is 195", "a": 189, "b": 118, "c": 124, "op1": "-", "op2": "+", "result": 195}
{"question": "Solve: (142 / 178) * 154.56", "answer": "The result of (142 / 178) * 154.56 is 123.3", "a": 142, "b": 178, "c": 154.56, "op1": "/", "op2": "*", "result": 123.3}
{"question": "Solve: (177.05 / 174) + 141", "answer": "The result of (177.05 / 174) + 141 is 142.02", "a": 177.05, "b": 174, "c": 141, "op1": "/", "op2": "+", "result": 142.02}
{"question": "Solve: (25 * 178) - 60", "answer": "The result of (25 * 178) - 60 is 4390", "a": 25, "b": 178, "c": 60, "op1": "*", "op2": "-", "result": 4390}
{"question": "Solve: (156.65 - 100) - 50.14", "answer": "The result of (156.65 - 100) - 50.14 is 6.51", "a": 156.65, "b": 100, "c": 50.14, "op1": "-", "op2": "-", "result": 6.51}
{"question": "Solve: (40 - 63) + 119", "answer": "The result of (40 - 63) + 119 is 96", "a": 40, "b": 63, "c": 119, "op1": "-", "op2": "+", "result": 96}
{"question": "Solve: (59.38 * 152) * 10", "answer": "The result of (59.38 * 152) * 10 is 90257.6", "a": 59.38, "b": 152, "c": 10, "op1": "*", "op2": "*", "result": 90257.6}
{"question": "Solve: (154.66 + 140.41) - 177", "answer": "The result of (154.66 + 140.41) - 177 is 118.07", "a": 154.66, "b": 140.41, "c": 177, "op1": "+", "op2": "-", "result": 118.07}
{"question": "Solve: (13 + 190.45) - 169", "answer": "The result of (13 + 190.45) - 169 is 34.45", "a": 13, "b": 190.45, "c": 169, "op1": "+", "op2": "-", "result": 34.45}
{"question": "Solve: (142 - 131) * 167", "answer": "The result of (142 - 131) * 167 is 1837", "a": 142, "b": 131, "c": 167, "op1": "-", "op2": "*", "result": 1837}
{"question": "Solve: (175 * 104) + 59.05", "answer": "The result of (175 * 104) + 59.05 is 18259.05", "a": 175, "b": 104, "c": 59.05, "op1": "*", "op2": "+", "result": 18259.05}
{"question": "Solve: (4 / 121.78) * 146.25", "answer": "The result of (4 / 121.78) * 146.25 is 4.8", "a": 4, "b": 121.78, "c": 146.25, "op1": "/", "op2": "*", "result": 4.8}
{"question": "Solve: (14.9 - 159) - 52.79", "answer": "The result of (14.9 - 159) - 52.79 is -196.89", "a": 14.9, "b": 159, "c": 52.79, "op1": "-", "op2": "-", "result": -196.89}
{"question": "Solve: (84 - 120) * 159", "answer": "The result of (84 - 120) * 159 is -5724", "a": 84, "b": 120, "c": 159, "op1": "-", "op2": "*", "result": -5724}
{"question": "Solve: (74 - 153) - 120", "answer": "The result of (74 - 153) - 120 is -199", "a": 74, "b": 153, "c": 120, "op1": "-", "op2": "-", "result": -199}
{"question": "Solve: (157 + 178.37) + 191", "answer": "The result of (157 + 178.37) + 191 is 526.37", "a": 157, "b": 178.37, "c": 191, "op1": "+", "op2": "+", "result": 526.37}
{"question": "Solve: (9 / 4) - 55", "answer": "The result of (9 / 4) - 55 is -52.75", "a": 9, "b": 4, "c": 55, "op1": "/", "op2": "-", "result": -52.75}
{"question": "Solve: (147 - 112.8) + 14.01", "answer": "The result of (147 - 112.8) + 14.01 is 48.21", "a": 147, "b": 112.8, "c": 14.01, "op1": "-", "op2": "+", "result": 48.21}
{"question": "Solve: (71 * 199) + 52", "answer": "The result of (71 * 199) + 52 is 14181", "a": 71, "b": 199, "c": 52, "op1": "*", "op2": "+", "result": 14181}
{"question": "Solve: (77 * 175) / 137", "answer": "The result of (77 * 175) / 137 is 98.36", "a": 77, "b": 175, "c": 137, "op1": "*", "op2": "/", "result": 98.36}
{"question": "Solve: (47 - 6) * 92", "answer": "The result of (47 - 6) * 92 is 3772", "a": 47, "b": 6, "c": 92, "op1": "-", "op2": "*", "result": 3772}
{"question": "Solve: (181 + 144.38) / 66.62", "answer": "The result of (181 + 144.38) / 66.62 is 4.88", "a": 181, "b": 144.38, "c": 66.62, "op1": "+", "op2": "/", "result": 4.88}
{"question": "Solve: (5 + 157.52) + 68.72", "answer": "The result of (5 + 157.52) + 68.72 is 231.24", "a": 5, "b": 157.52, "c": 68.72, "op1": "+", "op2": "+", "result": 231.24}
{"question": "Solve: (189 - 186) + 181", "answer": "The result of (189 - 186) + 181 is 184", "a": 189, "b": 186, "c": 181, "op1": "-", "op2": "+", "result": 184}
{"question": "Solve: (150.01 / 166) + 28", "answer": "The result of (150.01 / 166) + 28 is 28.9", "a": 150.01, "b": 166, "c": 28, "op1": "/", "op2": "+", "result": 28.9}
{"question": "Solve: (159.49 - 187) * 159.36", "answer": "The result of (159.49 - 187) * 159.36 is -4383.99", "a": 159.49, "b": 187, "c": 159.36, "op1": "-", "op2": "*", "result": -4383.99}
{"question": "Solve: (7.15 - 158) - 6", "answer": "The result of (7.15 - 158) - 6 is -156.85", "a": 7.15, "b": 158, "c": 6, "op1": "-", "op2": "-", "result": -156.85}
{"question": "Solve: (175 + 170) + 15", "answer": "The result of (175 + 170) + 15 is 360", "a": 175, "b": 170, "c": 15, "op1": "+", "op2": "+", "result": 360}
{"question": "Solve: (29 * 51) - 172.43", "answer": "The result of (29 * 51) - 172.43 is 1306.57", "a": 29, "b": 51, "c": 172.43, "op1": "*", "op2": "-", "result": 1306.57}
{"question": "Solve: (146.25 - 198.01) - 27.55", "answer": "The result of (146.25 - 198.01) - 27.55 is -79.31", "a": 146.25, "b": 198.01, "c": 27.55, "op1": "-", "op2": "-", "result": -79.31}
{"question": "Solve: (15 + 157) + 118", "answer": "The result of (15 + 157) + 118 is 290", "a": 15, "b": 157, "c": 118, "op1": "+", "op2": "+", "result": 290}
{"question": "Solve: (108 * 30) / 178.11", "answer": "The result of (108 * 30) / 178.11 is 18.19", "a": 108, "b": 30, "c": 178.11, "op1": "*", "op2": "/", "result": 18.19}
{"question": "Solve: (18 - 21) + 127", "answer": "The result of (18 - 21) + 127 is 124", "a": 18, "b": 21, "c": 127, "op1": "-", "op2": "+", "result": 124}
{"question": "Solve: (92 - 178) - 155", "answer": "The result of (92 - 178) - 155 is -241", "a": 92, "b": 178, "c": 155, "op1": "-", "op2": "-", "result": -241}
{"question": "Solve: (76.59 * 190) + 131.41", "answer": "The result of (76.59 * 190) + 131.41 is 14683.51", "a": 76.59, "b": 190, "c": 131.41, "op1": "*", "op2": "+", "result": 14683.51}
{"question": "Solve: (178 + 12.05) * 43", "answer": "The result of (178 + 12.05) * 43 is 8172.15", "a": 178, "b": 12.05, "c": 43, "op1": "+", "op2": "*", "result": 8172.15}
{"question": "Solve: (74 - 157) - 105.43", "answer": "The result of (74 - 157) - 105.43 is -188.43", "a": 74, "b": 157, "c": 105.43, "op1": "-", "op2": "-", "result": -188.43}
{"question": "Solve: (132 * 5.46) * 135", "answer": "The result of (132 * 5.46) * 135 is 97297.2", "a": 132, "b": 5.46, "c": 135, "op1": "*", "op2": "*", "result": 97297.2}
{"question": "Solve: (17 / 45.14) + 90.66", "answer": "The result of (17 / 45.14) + 90.66 is 91.04", "a": 17, "b": 45.14, "c": 90.66, "op1": "/", "op2": "+", "result": 91.04}
{"question": "Solve: (1.96 - 37) / 102", "answer": "The result of (1.96 - 37) / 102 is -0.34", "a": 1.96, "b": 37, "c": 102, "op1": "-", "op2": "/", "result": -0.34}
{"question": "Solve: (180.64 + 88.24) - 20", "answer": "The result of (180.64 + 88.24) - 20 is 248.88", "a": 180.64, "b": 88.24, "c": 20, "op1": "+", "op2": "-", "result": 248.88}
{"question": "Solve: (118 - 122) * 129", "answer": "The result of (118 - 122) * 129 is -516", "a": 118, "b": 122, "c": 129, "op1": "-", "op2": "*", "result": -516}
{"question": "Solve: (116 + 126) * 95", "answer": "The result of (116 + 126) * 95 is 22990", "a": 116, "b": 126, "c": 95, "op1": "+", "op2": "*", "result": 22990}
{"question": "Solve: (76 / 123) + 63.43", "answer": "The result of (76 / 123) + 63.43 is 64.05", "a": 76, "b": 123, "c": 63.43, "op1": "/", "op2": "+", "result": 64.05}
{"question": "Solve: (191.42 - 125.18) - 64.16", "answer": "The result of (191.42 - 125.18) - 64.16 is 2.08", "a": 191.42, "b": 125.18, "c": 64.16, "op1": "-", "op2": "-", "result": 2.08}
{"question": "Solve: (91 - 147) * 58", "answer": "The result of (91 - 147) * 58 is -3248", "a": 91, "b": 147, "c": 58, "op1": "-", "op2": "*", "result": -3248}
{"question": "Solve: (13 * 109.12) / 116.68", "answer": "The result of (13 * 109.12) / 116.68 is 12.16", "a": 13, "b": 109.12, "c": 116.68, "op1": "*", "op2": "/", "result": 12.16}
{"question": "Solve: (153.87 - 7.03) - 35.33", "answer": "The result of (153.87 - 7.03) - 35.33 is 111.51", "a": 153.87, "b": 7.03, "c": 35.33, "op1": "-", "op2": "-", "result": 111.51}
{"question": "Solve: (143 + 23) * 26.99", "answer": "The result of (143 + 23) * 26.99 is 4480.34", "a": 143, "b": 23, "c": 26.99, "op1": "+", "op2": "*", "result": 4480.34}
{"question": "Solve: (117.51 + 120) * 195.69", "answer": "The result of (117.51 + 120) * 195.69 is 46478.33", "a": 117.51, "b": 120, "c": 195.69, "op1": "+", "op2": "*", "result": 46478.33}
{"question": "Solve: (29.29 * 55.49) * 65", "answer": "The result of (29.29 * 55.49) * 65 is 105644.64", "a": 29.29, "b": 55.49, "c": 65, "op1": "*", "op2": "*", "result": 105644.64}
{"question": "Solve: (27.17 / 184) - 101", "answer": "The result of (27.17 / 184) - 101 is -100.85", "a": 27.17, "b": 184, "c": 101, "op1": "/", "op2": "-", "result": -100.85}
{"question": "Solve: (102 / 68) - 19.17", "answer": "The result of (102 / 68) - 19.17 is -17.67", "a": 102, "b": 68, "c": 19.17, "op1": "/", "op2": "-", "result": -17.67}
{"question": "Solve: (111 - 137) / 68", "answer": "The result of (111 - 137) / 68 is -0.38", "a": 111, "b": 137, "c": 68, "op1": "-", "op2": "/", "result": -0.38}
{"question": "Solve: (30 + 26) + 12", "answer": "The result of (30 + 26) + 12 is 68", "a": 30, "b": 26, "c": 12, "op1": "+", "op2": "+", "result": 68}
{"question": "Solve: (196 - 200) / 148", "answer": "The result of (196 - 200) / 148 is -0.03", "a": 196, "b": 200, "c": 148, "op1": "-", "op2": "/", "result": -0.03}
{"question": "Solve: (168 - 44.13) * 54", "answer": "The result of (168 - 44.13) * 54 is 6688.98", "a": 168, "b": 44.13, "c": 54, "op1": "-", "op2": "*", "result": 6688.98}
{"question": "Solve: (140 / 19) * 76", "answer": "The result of (140 / 19) * 76 is 560.0", "a": 140, "b": 19, "c": 76, "op1": "/", "op2": "*", "result": 560.0}
{"question": "Solve: (115 * 128) / 168.08", "answer": "The result of (115 * 128) / 168.08 is 87.58", "a": 115, "b": 128, "c": 168.08, "op1": "*", "op2": "/", "result": 87.58}
{"question": "Solve: (2 + 60) + 112.92", "answer": "The result of (2 + 60) + 112.92 is 174.92", "a": 2, "b": 60, "c": 112.92, "op1": "+", "op2": "+", "result": 174.92}
{"question": "Solve: (134 + 57.3) - 121", "answer": "The result of (134 + 57.3) - 121 is 70.3", "a": 134, "b": 57.3, "c": 121, "op1": "+", "op2": "-", "result": 70.3}
{"question": "Solve: (69 + 185) * 64.99", "answer": "The result of (69 + 185) * 64.99 is 16507.46", "a": 69, "b": 185, "c": 64.99, "op1": "+", "op2": "*", "result": 16507.46}
{"question": "Solve: (14 + 99) + 119", "answer": "The result of (14 + 99) + 119 is 232", "a": 14, "b": 99, "c": 119, "op1": "+", "op2": "+", "result": 232}
{"question": "Solve: (74 + 132) - 15.44", "answer": "The result of (74 + 132) - 15.44 is 190.56", "a": 74, "b": 132, "c": 15.44, "op1": "+", "op2": "-", "result": 190.56}
{"question": "Solve: (189 / 88) + 175.19", "answer": "The result of (189 / 88) + 175.19 is 177.34", "a": 189, "b": 88, "c": 175.19, "op1": "/", "op2": "+", "result": 177.34}
{"question": "Solve: (6 / 133) * 71", "answer": "The result of (6 / 133) * 71 is 3.2", "a": 6, "b": 133, "c": 71, "op1": "/", "op2": "*", "result": 3.2}
{"question": "Solve: (101 - 100) + 97", "answer": "The result of (101 - 100) + 97 is 98", "a": 101, "b": 100, "c": 97, "op1": "-", "op2": "+", "result": 98}
{"question": "Solve: (161 - 119.37) / 133", "answer": "The result of (161 - 119.37) / 133 is 0.31", "a": 161, "b": 119.37, "c": 133, "op1": "-", "op2": "/", "result": 0.31}
{"question": "Solve: (173 - 76) / 6", "answer": "The result of (173 - 76) / 6 is 16.17", "a": 173, "b": 76, "c": 6, "op1": "-", "op2": "/", "result": 16.17}
{"question": "Solve: (14.75 / 70) * 87.67", "answer": "The result of (14.75 / 70) * 87.67 is 18.47", "a": 14.75, "b": 70, "c": 87.67, "op1": "/", "op2": "*", "result": 18.47}
{"question": "Solve: (81.76 - 64) * 99", "answer": "The result of (81.76 - 64) * 99 is 1758.24", "a": 81.76, "b": 64, "c": 99, "op1": "-", "op2": "*", "result": 1758.24}
{"question": "Solve: (91 + 51.52) + 31", "answer": "The result of (91 + 51.52) + 31 is 173.52", "a": 91, "b": 51.52, "c": 31, "op1": "+", "op2": "+", "result": 173.52}
{"question": "Solve: (59 * 100) * 28.44", "answer": "The result of (59 * 100) * 28.44 is 167796.0", "a": 59, "b": 100, "c": 28.44, "op1": "*", "op2": "*", "result": 167796.0}
{"question": "Solve: (48.86 + 34) - 52", "answer": "The result of (48.86 + 34) - 52 is 30.86", "a": 48.86, "b": 34, "c": 52, "op1": "+", "op2": "-", "result": 30.86}
{"question": "Solve: (123 - 183) / 104.82", "answer": "The result of (123 - 183) / 104.82 is -0.57", "a": 123, "b": 183, "c": 104.82, "op1": "-", "op2": "/", "result": -0.57}
{"question": "Solve: (22 / 159.83) + 81", "answer": "The result of (22 / 159.83) + 81 is 81.14", "a": 22, "b": 159.83, "c": 81, "op1": "/", "op2": "+", "result": 81.14}
{"question": "Solve: (32.48 - 116.7) * 84.03", "answer": "The result of (32.48 - 116.7) * 84.03 is -7077.01", "a": 32.48, "b": 116.7, "c": 84.03, "op1": "-", "op2": "*", "result": -7077.01}
{"question": "Solve: (85 * 187) * 146", "answer": "The result of (85 * 187) * 146 is 2320670", "a": 85, "b": 187, "c": 146, "op1": "*", "op2": "*", "result": 2320670}
{"question": "Solve: (159 / 41) / 148", "answer": "The result of (159 / 41) / 148 is 0.03", "a": 159, "b": 41, "c": 148, "op1": "/", "op2": "/", "result": 0.03}
{"question": "Solve: (77 - 77.64) * 82", "answer": "The result of (77 - 77.64) * 82 is -52.48", "a": 77, "b": 77.64, "c": 82, "op1": "-", "op2": "*", "result": -52.48}
{"question": "Solve: (118.07 - 22) - 69", "answer": "The result of (118.07 - 22) - 69 is 27.07", "a": 118.07, "b": 22, "c": 69, "op1": "-", "op2": "-", "result": 27.07}
{"question": "Solve: (48 + 54) - 182", "answer": "The result of (48 + 54) - 182 is -80", "a": 48, "b": 54, "c": 182, "op1": "+", "op2": "-", "result": -80}
{"question": "Solve: (105 + 27.47) + 44.06", "answer": "The result of (105 + 27.47) + 44.06 is 176.53", "a": 105, "b": 27.47, "c": 44.06, "op1": "+", "op2": "+", "result": 176.53}
{"question": "Solve: (135 + 77.65) * 176", "answer": "The result of (135 + 77.65) * 176 is 37426.4", "a": 135, "b": 77.65, "c": 176, "op1": "+", "op2": "*", "result": 37426.4}
{"question": "Solve: (6 * 31) - 92", "answer": "The result of (6 * 31) - 92 is 94", "a": 6, "b": 31, "c": 92, "op1": "*", "op2": "-", "result": 94}
{"question": "Solve: (14 + 46) + 13", "answer": "The result of (14 + 46) + 13 is 73", "a": 14, "b": 46, "c": 13, "op1": "+", "op2": "+", "result": 73}
{"question": "Solve: (197 - 144) + 180.42", "answer": "The result of (197 - 144) + 180.42 is 233.42", "a": 197, "b": 144, "c": 180.42, "op1": "-", "op2": "+", "result": 233.42}
{"question": "Solve: (120 - 79) + 13", "answer": "The result of (120 - 79) + 13 is 54", "a": 120, "b": 79, "c": 13, "op1": "-", "op2": "+", "result": 54}
{"question": "Solve: (95 - 11) + 158.01", "answer": "The result of (95 - 11) + 158.01 is 242.01", "a": 95, "b": 11, "c": 158.01, "op1": "-", "op2": "+", "result": 242.01}
{"question": "Solve: (20 * 125.98) + 133", "answer": "The result of (20 * 125.98) + 133 is 2652.6", "a": 20, "b": 125.98, "c": 133, "op1": "*", "op2": "+", "result": 2652.6}
{"question": "Solve: (96 + 15) + 57", "answer": "The result of (96 + 15) + 57 is 168", "a": 96, "b": 15, "c": 57, "op1": "+", "op2": "+", "result": 168}
{"question": "Solve: (117 / 116) - 93.71", "answer": "The result of (117 / 116) - 93.71 is -92.7", "a": 117, "b": 116, "c": 93.71, "op1": "/", "op2": "-", "result": -92.7}
{"question": "Solve: (36.76 * 80.55) - 120", "answer": "The result of (36.76 * 80.55) - 120 is 2841.02", "a": 36.76, "b": 80.55, "c": 120, "op1": "*", "op2": "-", "result": 2841.02}
{"question": "Solve: (100.15 - 186) - 13.3", "answer": "The result of (100.15 - 186) - 13.3 is -99.15", "a": 100.15, "b": 186, "c": 13.3, "op1": "-", "op2": "-", "result": -99.15}
{"question": "Solve: (165.56 - 31) + 21", "answer": "The result of (165.56 - 31) + 21 is 155.56", "a": 165.56, "b": 31, "c": 21, "op1": "-", "op2": "+", "result": 155.56}
{"question": "Solve: (180.94 - 157) / 53.69", "answer": "The result of (180.94 - 157) / 53.69 is 0.45", "a": 180.94, "b": 157, "c": 53.69, "op1": "-", "op2": "/", "result": 0.45}
{"question": "Solve: (8 * 169) * 133", "answer": "The result of (8 * 169) * 133 is 179816", "a": 8, "b": 169, "c": 133, "op1": "*", "op2": "*", "result": 179816}
{"question": "Solve: (12 - 95) * 78.11", "answer": "The result of (12 - 95) * 78.11 is -6483.13", "a": 12, "b": 95, "c": 78.11, "op1": "-", "op2": "*", "result": -6483.13}
{"question": "Solve: (124 - 196) - 133", "answer": "The result of (124 - 196) - 133 is -205", "a": 124, "b": 196, "c": 133, "op1": "-", "op2": "-", "result": -205}
{"question": "Solve: (147.5 - 50) / 55", "answer": "The result of (147.5 - 50) / 55 is 1.77", "a": 147.5, "b": 50, "c": 55, "op1": "-", "op2": "/", "result": 1.77}
{"question": "Solve: (118.99 - 176) - 82", "answer": "The result of (118.99 - 176) - 82 is -139.01", "a": 118.99, "b": 176, "c": 82, "op1": "-", "op2": "-", "result": -139.01}
{"question": "Solve: (146 / 52) - 104.56", "answer": "The result of (146 / 52) - 104.56 is -101.75", "a": 146, "b": 52, "c": 104.56, "op1": "/", "op2": "-", "result": -101.75}
{"question": "Solve: (113 + 155) - 8", "answer": "The result of (113 + 155) - 8 is 260", "a": 113, "b": 155, "c": 8, "op1": "+", "op2": "-", "result": 260}
{"question": "Solve: (147 - 194.78) + 54.16", "answer": "The result of (147 - 194.78) + 54.16 is 6.38", "a": 147, "b": 194.78, "c": 54.16, "op1": "-", "op2": "+", "result": 6.38}
{"question": "Solve: (106 * 55) * 145", "answer": "The result of (106 * 55) * 145 is 845350", "a": 106, "b": 55, "c": 145, "op1": "*", "op2": "*", "result": 845350}
{"question": "Solve: (47 * 148) / 37", "answer": "The result of (47 * 148) / 37 is 188.0", "a": 47, "b": 148, "c": 37, "op1": "*", "op2": "/", "result": 188.0}
{"question": "Solve: (110.52 - 195) - 17.1", "answer": "The result of (110.52 - 195) - 17.1 is -101.58", "a": 110.52, "b": 195, "c": 17.1, "op1": "-", "op2": "-", "result": -101.58}
{"question": "Solve: (109 - 48) * 139", "answer": "The result of (109 - 48) * 139 is 8479", "a": 109, "b": 48, "c": 139, "op1": "-", "op2": "*", "result": 8479}
{"question": "Solve: (82.18 * 157.85) - 142", "answer": "The result of (82.18 * 157.85) - 142 is 12830.11", "a": 82.18, "b": 157.85, "c": 142, "op1": "*", "op2": "-", "result": 12830.11}
{"question": "Solve: (1 - 195) / 136.58", "answer": "The result of (1 - 195) / 136.58 is -1.42", "a": 1, "b": 195, "c": 136.58, "op1": "-", "op2": "/", "result": -1.42}
{"question": "Solve: (74 - 70) + 118", "answer": "The result of (74 - 70) + 118 is 122", "a": 74, "b": 70, "c": 118, "op1": "-", "op2": "+", "result": 122}
{"question": "Solve: (151 * 91.94) - 3", "answer": "The result of (151 * 91.94) - 3 is 13879.94", "a": 151, "b": 91.94, "c": 3, "op1": "*", "op2": "-", "result": 13879.94}
{"question": "Solve: (133 + 123) - 6.7", "answer": "The result of (133 + 123) - 6.7 is 249.3", "a": 133, "b": 123, "c": 6.7, "op1": "+", "op2": "-", "result": 249.3}
{"question": "Solve: (89 + 128) + 174.72", "answer": "The result of (89 + 128) + 174.72 is 391.72", "a": 89, "b": 128, "c": 174.72, "op1": "+", "op2": "+", "result": 391.72}
{"question": "Solve: (4 - 136.25) * 164.34", "answer": "The result of (4 - 136.25) * 164.34 is -21733.97", "a": 4, "b": 136.25, "c": 164.34, "op1": "-", "op2": "*", "result": -21733.97}
{"question": "Solve: (141.86 / 180) + 70", "answer": "The result of (141.86 / 180) + 70 is 70.79", "a": 141.86, "b": 180, "c": 70, "op1": "/", "op2": "+", "result": 70.79}
{"question": "Solve: (199 * 47) + 138.98", "answer": "The result of (199 * 47) + 138.98 is 9491.98", "a": 199, "b": 47, "c": 138.98, "op1": "*", "op2": "+", "result": 9491.98}
{"question": "Solve: (77 * 185) - 127.63", "answer": "The result of (77 * 185) - 127.63 is 14117.37", "a": 77, "b": 185, "c": 127.63, "op1": "*", "op2": "-", "result": 14117.37}
{"question": "Solve: (81.37 / 105.07) + 21", "answer": "The result of (81.37 / 105.07) + 21 is 21.77", "a": 81.37, "b": 105.07, "c": 21, "op1": "/", "op2": "+", "result": 21.77}
{"question": "Solve: (112.84 + 130) / 64.73", "answer": "The result of (112.84 + 130) / 64.73 is 3.75", "a": 112.84, "b": 130, "c": 64.73, "op1": "+", "op2": "/", "result": 3.75}
{"question": "Solve: (174.48 + 13.86) / 25.65", "answer": "The result of (174.48 + 13.86) / 25.65 is 7.34", "a": 174.48, "b": 13.86, "c": 25.65, "op1": "+", "op2": "/", "result": 7.34}
{"question": "Solve: (29 - 68) * 101", "answer": "The result of (29 - 68) * 101 is -3939", "a": 29, "b": 68, "c": 101, "op1": "-", "op2": "*", "result": -3939}
{"question": "Solve: (126.03 * 90.81) + 151", "answer": "The result of (126.03 * 90.81) + 151 is 11595.78", "a": 126.03, "b": 90.81, "c": 151, "op1": "*", "op2": "+", "result": 11595.78}
{"question": "Solve: (111.5 - 193) + 77", "answer": "The result of (111.5 - 193) + 77 is -4.5", "a": 111.5, "b": 193, "c": 77, "op1": "-", "op2": "+", "result": -4.5}
{"question": "Solve: (91 + 46.8) - 134", "answer": "The result of (91 + 46.8) - 134 is 3.8", "a": 91, "b": 46.8, "c": 134, "op1": "+", "op2": "-", "result": 3.8}
{"question": "Solve: (151 + 129.4) - 192", "answer": "The result of (151 + 129.4) - 192 is 88.4", "a": 151, "b": 129.4, "c": 192, "op1": "+", "op2": "-", "result": 88.4}
{"question": "Solve: (41 - 60) * 116.98", "answer": "The result of (41 - 60) * 116.98 is -2222.62", "a": 41, "b": 60, "c": 116.98, "op1": "-", "op2": "*", "result": -2222.62}
{"question": "Solve: (85 / 76.11) - 159", "answer": "The result of (85 / 76.11) - 159 is -157.88", "a": 85, "b": 76.11, "c": 159, "op1": "/", "op2": "-", "result": -157.88}
{"question": "Solve: (120.52 + 151) - 34", "answer": "The result of (120.52 + 151) - 34 is 237.52", "a": 120.52, "b": 151, "c": 34, "op1": "+", "op2": "-", "result": 237.52}
{"question": "Solve: (95 * 179.73) / 199", "answer": "The result of (95 * 179.73) / 199 is 85.8", "a": 95, "b": 179.73, "c": 199, "op1": "*", "op2": "/", "result": 85.8}
{"question": "Solve: (186.88 * 188) * 143", "answer": "The result of (186.88 * 188) * 143 is 5024081.92", "a": 186.88, "b": 188, "c": 143, "op1": "*", "op2": "*", "result": 5024081.92}
{"question": "Solve: (10.16 * 26) / 75", "answer": "The result of (10.16 * 26) / 75 is 3.52", "a": 10.16, "b": 26, "c": 75, "op1": "*", "op2": "/", "result": 3.52}
{"question": "Solve: (190 - 13) * 144.8", "answer": "The result of (190 - 13) * 144.8 is 25629.6", "a": 190, "b": 13, "c": 144.8, "op1": "-", "op2": "*", "result": 25629.6}
{"question": "Solve: (176.5 * 55) - 172.34", "answer": "The result of (176.5 * 55) - 172.34 is 9535.16", "a": 176.5, "b": 55, "c": 172.34, "op1": "*", "op2": "-", "result": 9535.16}
{"question": "Solve: (26.92 * 16) / 135", "answer": "The result of (26.92 * 16) / 135 is 3.19", "a": 26.92, "b": 16, "c": 135, "op1": "*", "op2": "/", "result": 3.19}
{"question": "Solve: (75.48 - 188) + 17.72", "answer": "The result of (75.48 - 188) + 17.72 is -94.8", "a": 75.48, "b": 188, "c": 17.72, "op1": "-", "op2": "+", "result": -94.8}
{"question": "Solve: (98.0 / 27.29) / 140", "answer": "The result of (98.0 / 27.29) / 140 is 0.03", "a": 98.0, "b": 27.29, "c": 140, "op1": "/", "op2": "/", "result": 0.03}
{"question": "Solve: (197 * 109) + 23", "answer": "The result of (197 * 109) + 23 is 21496", "a": 197, "b": 109, "c": 23, "op1": "*", "op2": "+", "result": 21496}
{"question": "Solve: (140.81 * 164.32) / 59", "answer": "The result of (140.81 * 164.32) / 59 is 392.17", "a": 140.81, "b": 164.32, "c": 59, "op1": "*", "op2": "/", "result": 392.17}
{"question": "Solve: (107 + 127.55) + 78", "answer": "The result of (107 + 127.55) + 78 is 312.55", "a": 107, "b": 127.55, "c": 78, "op1": "+", "op2": "+", "result": 312.55}
{"question": "Solve: (165 + 127) * 19.64", "answer": "The result of (165 + 127) * 19.64 is 5734.88", "a": 165, "b": 127, "c": 19.64, "op1": "+", "op2": "*", "result": 5734.88}
{"question": "Solve: (54 * 147.86) * 197.46", "answer": "The result of (54 * 147.86) * 197.46 is 1576607.52", "a": 54, "b": 147.86, "c": 197.46, "op1": "*", "op2": "*", "result": 1576607.52}
{"question": "Solve: (31 + 114.89) + 180", "answer": "The result of (31 + 114.89) + 180 is 325.89", "a": 31, "b": 114.89, "c": 180, "op1": "+", "op2": "+", "result": 325.89}
{"question": "Solve: (171 - 3) / 43", "answer": "The result of (171 - 3) / 43 is 3.91", "a": 171, "b": 3, "c": 43, "op1": "-", "op2": "/", "result": 3.91}
{"question": "Solve: (65 + 159.09) - 168", "answer": "The result of (65 + 159.09) - 168 is 56.09", "a": 65, "b": 159.09, "c": 168, "op1": "+", "op2": "-", "result": 56.09}
{"question": "Solve: (150 * 115) + 42", "answer": "The result of (150 * 115) + 42 is 17292", "a": 150, "b": 115, "c": 42, "op1": "*", "op2": "+", "result": 17292}
{"question": "Solve: (96.02 - 15.36) + 154", "answer": "The result of (96.02 - 15.36) + 154 is 234.66", "a": 96.02, "b": 15.36, "c": 154, "op1": "-", "op2": "+", "result": 234.66}
{"question": "Solve: (42.16 - 138) - 146", "answer": "The result of (42.16 - 138) - 146 is -241.84", "a": 42.16, "b": 138, "c": 146, "op1": "-", "op2": "-", "result": -241.84}
{"question": "Solve: (4.14 / 22) + 46.11", "answer": "The result of (4.14 / 22) + 46.11 is 46.3", "a": 4.14, "b": 22, "c": 46.11, "op1": "/", "op2": "+", "result": 46.3}
{"question": "Solve: (99.66 * 110) / 52", "answer": "The result of (99.66 * 110) / 52 is 210.82", "a": 99.66, "b": 110, "c": 52, "op1": "*", "op2": "/", "result": 210.82}
{"question": "Solve: (136 * 11.68) + 15", "answer": "The result of (136 * 11.68) + 15 is 1603.48", "a": 136, "b": 11.68, "c": 15, "op1": "*", "op2": "+", "result": 1603.48}
{"question": "Solve: (169 / 73) - 50.98", "answer": "The result of (169 / 73) - 50.98 is -48.66", "a": 169, "b": 73, "c": 50.98, "op1": "/", "op2": "-", "result": -48.66}
{"question": "Solve: (27 / 147.89) - 35", "answer": "The result of (27 / 147.89) - 35 is -34.82", "a": 27, "b": 147.89, "c": 35, "op1": "/", "op2": "-", "result": -34.82}
{"question": "Solve: (75 + 55) + 26.24", "answer": "The result of (75 + 55) + 26.24 is 156.24", "a": 75, "b": 55, "c": 26.24, "op1": "+", "op2": "+", "result": 156.24}
{"question": "Solve: (159 + 35) - 31", "answer": "The result of (159 + 35) - 31 is 163", "a": 159, "b": 35, "c": 31, "op1": "+", "op2": "-", "result": 163}
{"question": "Solve: (100 + 19) + 60", "answer": "The result of (100 + 19) + 60 is 179", "a": 100, "b": 19, "c": 60, "op1": "+", "op2": "+", "result": 179}
{"question": "Solve: (91 * 43) - 187.25", "answer": "The result of (91 * 43) - 187.25 is 3725.75", "a": 91, "b": 43, "c": 187.25, "op1": "*", "op2": "-", "result": 3725.75}
{"question": "Solve: (189 - 123.47) / 75", "answer": "The result of (189 - 123.47) / 75 is 0.87", "a": 189, "b": 123.47, "c": 75, "op1": "-", "op2": "/", "result": 0.87}
{"question": "Solve: (194.0 + 30) * 7.58", "answer": "The result of (194.0 + 30) * 7.58 is 1697.92", "a": 194.0, "b": 30, "c": 7.58, "op1": "+", "op2": "*", "result": 1697.92}
{"question": "Solve: (18 + 32) * 175.46", "answer": "The result of (18 + 32) * 175.46 is 8773.0", "a": 18, "b": 32, "c": 175.46, "op1": "+", "op2": "*", "result": 8773.0}
{"question": "Solve: (7.42 * 198) - 15", "answer": "The result of (7.42 * 198) - 15 is 1454.16", "a": 7.42, "b": 198, "c": 15, "op1": "*", "op2": "-", "result": 1454.16}
{"question": "Solve: (156 * 77.22) * 186", "answer": "The result of (156 * 77.22) * 186 is 2240615.52", "a": 156, "b": 77.22, "c": 186, "op1": "*", "op2": "*", "result": 2240615.52}
{"question": "Solve: (163 * 193.84) * 108", "answer": "The result of (163 * 193.84) * 108 is 3412359.36", "a": 163, "b": 193.84, "c": 108, "op1": "*", "op2": "*", "result": 3412359.36}
{"question": "Solve: (150.8 / 69.67) * 184", "answer": "The result of (150.8 / 69.67) * 184 is 398.27", "a": 150.8, "b": 69.67, "c": 184, "op1": "/", "op2": "*", "result": 398.27}
{"question": "Solve: (61 / 147.53) - 113.78", "answer": "The result of (61 / 147.53) - 113.78 is -113.37", "a": 61, "b": 147.53, "c": 113.78, "op1": "/", "op2": "-", "result": -113.37}
{"question": "Solve: (67 - 196) - 167.84", "answer": "The result of (67 - 196) - 167.84 is -296.84", "a": 67, "b": 196, "c": 167.84, "op1": "-", "op2": "-", "result": -296.84}
{"question": "Solve: (154.75 / 143.55) / 99.78", "answer": "The result of (154.75 / 143.55) / 99.78 is 0.01", "a": 154.75, "b": 143.55, "c": 99.78, "op1": "/", "op2": "/", "result": 0.01}
{"question": "Solve: (70.45 + 24) / 86", "answer": "The result of (70.45 + 24) / 86 is 1.1", "a": 70.45, "b": 24, "c": 86, "op1": "+", "op2": "/", "result": 1.1}
{"question": "Solve: (111 + 61) * 126.56", "answer": "The result of (111 + 61) * 126.56 is 21768.32", "a": 111, "b": 61, "c": 126.56, "op1": "+", "op2": "*", "result": 21768.32}
{"question": "Solve: (3.6 / 53) / 82", "answer": "The result of (3.6 / 53) / 82 is 0.0", "a": 3.6, "b": 53, "c": 82, "op1": "/", "op2": "/", "result": 0.0}
{"question": "Solve: (145 + 68.2) * 43", "answer": "The result of (145 + 68.2) * 43 is 9167.6", "a": 145, "b": 68.2, "c": 43, "op1": "+", "op2": "*", "result": 9167.6}
{"question": "Solve: (74 * 45) - 29", "answer": "The result of (74 * 45) - 29 is 3301", "a": 74, "b": 45, "c": 29, "op1": "*", "op2": "-", "result": 3301}
{"question": "Solve: (43.62 * 103) + 153", "answer": "The result of (43.62 * 103) + 153 is 4645.86", "a": 43.62, "b": 103, "c": 153, "op1": "*", "op2": "+", "result": 4645.86}
{"question": "Solve: (149 + 48) * 70", "answer": "The result of (149 + 48) * 70 is 13790", "a": 149, "b": 48, "c": 70, "op1": "+", "op2": "*", "result": 13790}
{"question": "Solve: (87 / 40) - 162", "answer": "The result of (87 / 40) - 162 is -159.82", "a": 87, "b": 40, "c": 162, "op1": "/", "op2": "-", "result": -159.82}
{"question": "Solve: (97.68 * 137.32) / 125", "answer": "The result of (97.68 * 137.32) / 125 is 107.31", "a": 97.68, "b": 137.32, "c": 125, "op1": "*", "op2": "/", "result": 107.31}
{"question": "Solve: (22 / 164) - 130", "answer": "The result of (22 / 164) - 130 is -129.87", "a": 22, "b": 164, "c": 130, "op1": "/", "op2": "-", "result": -129.87}
{"question": "Solve: (161.05 / 200) + 63", "answer": "The result of (161.05 / 200) + 63 is 63.81", "a": 161.05, "b": 200, "c": 63, "op1": "/", "op2": "+", "result": 63.81}
{"question": "Solve: (99.09 - 74.16) - 59", "answer": "The result of (99.09 - 74.16) - 59 is -34.07", "a": 99.09, "b": 74.16, "c": 59, "op1": "-", "op2": "-", "result": -34.07}
{"question": "Solve: (105.32 - 157.88) * 197.95", "answer": "The result of (105.32 - 157.88) * 197.95 is -10404.25", "a": 105.32, "b": 157.88, "c": 197.95, "op1": "-", "op2": "*", "result": -10404.25}
{"question": "Solve: (179 * 176) + 105", "answer": "The result of (179 * 176) + 105 is 31609", "a": 179, "b": 176, "c": 105, "op1": "*", "op2": "+", "result": 31609}
{"question": "Solve: (179 + 189.83) / 81", "answer": "The result of (179 + 189.83) / 81 is 4.55", "a": 179, "b": 189.83, "c": 81, "op1": "+", "op2": "/", "result": 4.55}
{"question": "Solve: (130 * 144.86) * 166", "answer": "The result of (130 * 144.86) * 166 is 3126078.8", "a": 130, "b": 144.86, "c": 166, "op1": "*", "op2": "*", "result": 3126078.8}
{"question": "Solve: (41 - 30) + 143.5", "answer": "The result of (41 - 30) + 143.5 is 154.5", "a": 41, "b": 30, "c": 143.5, "op1": "-", "op2": "+", "result": 154.5}
{"question": "Solve: (177.08 / 47) / 5.49", "answer": "The result of (177.08 / 47) / 5.49 is 0.69", "a": 177.08, "b": 47, "c": 5.49, "op1": "/", "op2": "/", "result": 0.69}
{"question": "Solve: (136 + 121.74) * 174", "answer": "The result of (136 + 121.74) * 174 is 44846.76", "a": 136, "b": 121.74, "c": 174, "op1": "+", "op2": "*", "result": 44846.76}
{"question": "Solve: (15 - 48) + 111", "answer": "The result of (15 - 48) + 111 is 78", "a": 15, "b": 48, "c": 111, "op1": "-", "op2": "+", "result": 78}
{"question": "Solve: (179.54 / 178) + 111.71", "answer": "The result of (179.54 / 178) + 111.71 is 112.72", "a": 179.54, "b": 178, "c": 111.71, "op1": "/", "op2": "+", "result": 112.72}
{"question": "Solve: (92.92 + 16) / 145", "answer": "The result of (92.92 + 16) / 145 is 0.75", "a": 92.92, "b": 16, "c": 145, "op1": "+", "op2": "/", "result": 0.75}
{"question": "Solve: (46 - 59) + 9.56", "answer": "The result of (46 - 59) + 9.56 is -3.44", "a": 46, "b": 59, "c": 9.56, "op1": "-", "op2": "+", "result": -3.44}
{"question": "Solve: (100 / 82) + 43.77", "answer": "The result of (100 / 82) + 43.77 is 44.99", "a": 100, "b": 82, "c": 43.77, "op1": "/", "op2": "+", "result": 44.99}
{"question": "Solve: (78.59 * 44.16) * 148.51", "answer": "The result of (78.59 * 44.16) * 148.51 is 515409.06", "a": 78.59, "b": 44.16, "c": 148.51, "op1": "*", "op2": "*", "result": 515409.06}
{"question": "Solve: (158.56 + 105.22) + 185", "answer": "The result of (158.56 + 105.22) + 185 is 448.78", "a": 158.56, "b": 105.22, "c": 185, "op1": "+", "op2": "+", "result": 448.78}
{"question": "Solve: (110 / 86) + 189.49", "answer": "The result of (110 / 86) + 189.49 is 190.77", "a": 110, "b": 86, "c": 189.49, "op1": "/", "op2": "+", "result": 190.77}
{"question": "Solve: (95.42 - 78.12) + 196", "answer": "The result of (95.42 - 78.12) + 196 is 213.3", "a": 95.42, "b": 78.12, "c": 196, "op1": "-", "op2": "+", "result": 213.3}
{"question": "Solve: (26 - 190) * 77", "answer": "The result of (26 - 190) * 77 is -12628", "a": 26, "b": 190, "c": 77, "op1": "-", "op2": "*", "result": -12628}
{"question": "Solve: (110 + 13) + 95.08", "answer": "The result of (110 + 13) + 95.08 is 218.08", "a": 110, "b": 13, "c": 95.08, "op1": "+", "op2": "+", "result": 218.08}
{"question": "Solve: (85 * 41.92) - 120", "answer": "The result of (85 * 41.92) - 120 is 3443.2", "a": 85, "b": 41.92, "c": 120, "op1": "*", "op2": "-", "result": 3443.2}
{"question": "Solve: (143.05 + 158) - 111", "answer": "The result of (143.05 + 158) - 111 is 190.05", "a": 143.05, "b": 158, "c": 111, "op1": "+", "op2": "-", "result": 190.05}
{"question": "Solve: (41.93 - 23) + 188", "answer": "The result of (41.93 - 23) + 188 is 206.93", "a": 41.93, "b": 23, "c": 188, "op1": "-", "op2": "+", "result": 206.93}
{"question": "Solve: (18 + 45) - 28.65", "answer": "The result of (18 + 45) - 28.65 is 34.35", "a": 18, "b": 45, "c": 28.65, "op1": "+", "op2": "-", "result": 34.35}
{"question": "Solve: (187 + 191) + 191", "answer": "The result of (187 + 191) + 191 is 569", "a": 187, "b": 191, "c": 191, "op1": "+", "op2": "+", "result": 569}
{"question": "Solve: (116.56 + 17) - 159.63", "answer": "The result of (116.56 + 17) - 159.63 is -26.07", "a": 116.56, "b": 17, "c": 159.63, "op1": "+", "op2": "-", "result": -26.07}
{"question": "Solve: (137 + 105) - 92", "answer": "The result of (137 + 105) - 92 is 150", "a": 137, "b": 105, "c": 92, "op1": "+", "op2": "-", "result": 150}
{"question": "Solve: (195 / 55.78) * 53.87", "answer": "The result of (195 / 55.78) * 53.87 is 188.32", "a": 195, "b": 55.78, "c": 53.87, "op1": "/", "op2": "*", "result": 188.32}
{"question": "Solve: (63 + 4.21) + 7", "answer": "The result of (63 + 4.21) + 7 is 74.21", "a": 63, "b": 4.21, "c": 7, "op1": "+", "op2": "+", "result": 74.21}
{"question": "Solve: (143 + 19) - 194", "answer": "The result of (143 + 19) - 194 is -32", "a": 143, "b": 19, "c": 194, "op1": "+", "op2": "-", "result": -32}
{"question": "Solve: (128 * 136.66) + 16", "answer": "The result of (128 * 136.66) + 16 is 17508.48", "a": 128, "b": 136.66, "c": 16, "op1": "*", "op2": "+", "result": 17508.48}
{"question": "Solve: (180 * 85) - 124", "answer": "The result of (180 * 85) - 124 is 15176", "a": 180, "b": 85, "c": 124, "op1": "*", "op2": "-", "result": 15176}
{"question": "Solve: (28.94 + 5) - 7", "answer": "The result of (28.94 + 5) - 7 is 26.94", "a": 28.94, "b": 5, "c": 7, "op1": "+", "op2": "-", "result": 26.94}
{"question": "Solve: (179 * 1) - 88", "answer": "The result of (179 * 1) - 88 is 91", "a": 179, "b": 1, "c": 88, "op1": "*", "op2": "-", "result": 91}
{"question": "Solve: (60 * 39) - 31", "answer": "The result of (60 * 39) - 31 is 2309", "a": 60, "b": 39, "c": 31, "op1": "*", "op2": "-", "result": 2309}
{"question": "Solve: (116 * 127.38) * 113.18", "answer": "The result of (116 * 127.38) * 113.18 is 1672356.73", "a": 116, "b": 127.38, "c": 113.18, "op1": "*", "op2": "*", "result": 1672356.73}
{"question": "Solve: (116 - 131) + 111", "answer": "The result of (116 - 131) + 111 is 96", "a": 116, "b": 131, "c": 111, "op1": "-", "op2": "+", "result": 96}
{"question": "Solve: (117 * 146) + 87", "answer": "The result of (117 * 146) + 87 is 17169", "a": 117, "b": 146, "c": 87, "op1": "*", "op2": "+", "result": 17169}
{"question": "Solve: (151 + 2.4) - 33", "answer": "The result of (151 + 2.4) - 33 is 120.4", "a": 151, "b": 2.4, "c": 33, "op1": "+", "op2": "-", "result": 120.4}
{"question": "Solve: (54 * 200) * 71", "answer": "The result of (54 * 200) * 71 is 766800", "a": 54, "b": 200, "c": 71, "op1": "*", "op2": "*", "result": 766800}
{"question": "Solve: (19.82 * 134.78) / 92", "answer": "The result of (19.82 * 134.78) / 92 is 29.04", "a": 19.82, "b": 134.78, "c": 92, "op1": "*", "op2": "/", "result": 29.04}
{"question": "Solve: (168.66 + 191) + 14.33", "answer": "The result of (168.66 + 191) + 14.33 is 373.99", "a": 168.66, "b": 191, "c": 14.33, "op1": "+", "op2": "+", "result": 373.99}
{"question": "Solve: (58.81 + 108) + 175", "answer": "The result of (58.81 + 108) + 175 is 341.81", "a": 58.81, "b": 108, "c": 175, "op1": "+", "op2": "+", "result": 341.81}
{"question": "Solve: (20 + 178) + 150.8", "answer": "The result of (20 + 178) + 150.8 is 348.8", "a": 20, "b": 178, "c": 150.8, "op1": "+", "op2": "+", "result": 348.8}
{"question": "Solve: (143.14 - 39) + 193", "answer": "The result of (143.14 - 39) + 193 is 297.14", "a": 143.14, "b": 39, "c": 193, "op1": "-", "op2": "+", "result": 297.14}
{"question": "Solve: (164.09 * 81.38) - 157", "answer": "The result of (164.09 * 81.38) - 157 is 13196.64", "a": 164.09, "b": 81.38, "c": 157, "op1": "*", "op2": "-", "result": 13196.64}
{"question": "Solve: (61 + 7) - 61", "answer": "The result of (61 + 7) - 61 is 7", "a": 61, "b": 7, "c": 61, "op1": "+", "op2": "-", "result": 7}
{"question": "Solve: (84 * 148) - 1.7", "answer": "The result of (84 * 148) - 1.7 is 12430.3", "a": 84, "b": 148, "c": 1.7, "op1": "*", "op2": "-", "result": 12430.3}
{"question": "Solve: (3 - 150) * 11.52", "answer": "The result of (3 - 150) * 11.52 is -1693.44", "a": 3, "b": 150, "c": 11.52, "op1": "-", "op2": "*", "result": -1693.44}
{"question": "Solve: (17 + 136) * 199", "answer": "The result of (17 + 136) * 199 is 30447", "a": 17, "b": 136, "c": 199, "op1": "+", "op2": "*", "result": 30447}
{"question": "Solve: (139 + 87.51) * 100.95", "answer": "The result of (139 + 87.51) * 100.95 is 22866.18", "a": 139, "b": 87.51, "c": 100.95, "op1": "+", "op2": "*", "result": 22866.18}
{"question": "Solve: (116 - 120.7) - 93", "answer": "The result of (116 - 120.7) - 93 is -97.7", "a": 116, "b": 120.7, "c": 93, "op1": "-", "op2": "-", "result": -97.7}
{"question": "Solve: (164 - 65.89) / 39.32", "answer": "The result of (164 - 65.89) / 39.32 is 2.5", "a": 164, "b": 65.89, "c": 39.32, "op1": "-", "op2": "/", "result": 2.5}
{"question": "Solve: (12 * 34) - 34", "answer": "The result of (12 * 34) - 34 is 374", "a": 12, "b": 34, "c": 34, "op1": "*", "op2": "-", "result": 374}
{"question": "Solve: (39.16 - 155.08) / 26", "answer": "The result of (39.16 - 155.08) / 26 is -4.46", "a": 39.16, "b": 155.08, "c": 26, "op1": "-", "op2": "/", "result": -4.46}
{"question": "Solve: (97.76 * 156) * 181", "answer": "The result of (97.76 * 156) * 181 is 2760351.36", "a": 97.76, "b": 156, "c": 181, "op1": "*", "op2": "*", "result": 2760351.36}
{"question": "Solve: (1 * 84) / 37", "answer": "The result of (1 * 84) / 37 is 2.27", "a": 1, "b": 84, "c": 37, "op1": "*", "op2": "/", "result": 2.27}
{"question": "Solve: (154 - 98.94) - 63.89", "answer": "The result of (154 - 98.94) - 63.89 is -8.83", "a": 154, "b": 98.94, "c": 63.89, "op1": "-", "op2": "-", "result": -8.83}
{"question": "Solve: (117 * 19) * 121.45", "answer": "The result of (117 * 19) * 121.45 is 269983.35", "a": 117, "b": 19, "c": 121.45, "op1": "*", "op2": "*", "result": 269983.35}
{"question": "Solve: (99.71 - 153) / 146", "answer": "The result of (99.71 - 153) / 146 is -0.37", "a": 99.71, "b": 153, "c": 146, "op1": "-", "op2": "/", "result": -0.37}
{"question": "Solve: (84 + 147) - 131", "answer": "The result of (84 + 147) - 131 is 100", "a": 84, "b": 147, "c": 131, "op1": "+", "op2": "-", "result": 100}
{"question": "Solve: (131.36 * 127) + 115", "answer": "The result of (131.36 * 127) + 115 is 16797.72", "a": 131.36, "b": 127, "c": 115, "op1": "*", "op2": "+", "result": 16797.72}
{"question": "Solve: (174 + 8) / 197", "answer": "The result of (174 + 8) / 197 is 0.92", "a": 174, "b": 8, "c": 197, "op1": "+", "op2": "/", "result": 0.92}
{"question": "Solve: (18 * 148) - 127", "answer": "The result of (18 * 148) - 127 is 2537", "a": 18, "b": 148, "c": 127, "op1": "*", "op2": "-", "result": 2537}
{"question": "Solve: (159.45 * 125) + 78.27", "answer": "The result of (159.45 * 125) + 78.27 is 20009.52", "a": 159.45, "b": 125, "c": 78.27, "op1": "*", "op2": "+", "result": 20009.52}
{"question": "Solve: (29 * 41) * 28", "answer": "The result of (29 * 41) * 28 is 33292", "a": 29, "b": 41, "c": 28, "op1": "*", "op2": "*", "result": 33292}
{"question": "Solve: (163 + 152) / 100", "answer": "The result of (163 + 152) / 100 is 3.15", "a": 163, "b": 152, "c": 100, "op1": "+", "op2": "/", "result": 3.15}
{"question": "Solve: (102 + 115) + 32.01", "answer": "The result of (102 + 115) + 32.01 is 249.01", "a": 102, "b": 115, "c": 32.01, "op1": "+", "op2": "+", "result": 249.01}
{"question": "Solve: (86 + 13) + 157", "answer": "The result of (86 + 13) + 157 is 256", "a": 86, "b": 13, "c": 157, "op1": "+", "op2": "+", "result": 256}
{"question": "Solve: (119.39 + 103) * 142", "answer": "The result of (119.39 + 103) * 142 is 31579.38", "a": 119.39, "b": 103, "c": 142, "op1": "+", "op2": "*", "result": 31579.38}
{"question": "Solve: (181 / 34.09) + 67.8", "answer": "The result of (181 / 34.09) + 67.8 is 73.11", "a": 181, "b": 34.09, "c": 67.8, "op1": "/", "op2": "+", "result": 73.11}
{"question": "Solve: (50 + 172) + 153.55", "answer": "The result of (50 + 172) + 153.55 is 375.55", "a": 50, "b": 172, "c": 153.55, "op1": "+", "op2": "+", "result": 375.55}
{"question": "Solve: (167.38 / 33) - 125", "answer": "The result of (167.38 / 33) - 125 is -119.93", "a": 167.38, "b": 33, "c": 125, "op1": "/", "op2": "-", "result": -119.93}
{"question": "Solve: (103 / 13) * 130", "answer": "The result of (103 / 13) * 130 is 1030.0", "a": 103, "b": 13, "c": 130, "op1": "/", "op2": "*", "result": 1030.0}
{"question": "Solve: (99 - 152.54) * 192.43", "answer": "The result of (99 - 152.54) * 192.43 is -10302.7", "a": 99, "b": 152.54, "c": 192.43, "op1": "-", "op2": "*", "result": -10302.7}
{"question": "Solve: (46.45 - 38) - 172", "answer": "The result of (46.45 - 38) - 172 is -163.55", "a": 46.45, "b": 38, "c": 172, "op1": "-", "op2": "-", "result": -163.55}
{"question": "Solve: (175.27 + 106) + 161", "answer": "The result of (175.27 + 106) + 161 is 442.27", "a": 175.27, "b": 106, "c": 161, "op1": "+", "op2": "+", "result": 442.27}
{"question": "Solve: (9 - 93) / 136", "answer": "The result of (9 - 93) / 136 is -0.62", "a": 9, "b": 93, "c": 136, "op1": "-", "op2": "/", "result": -0.62}
{"question": "Solve: (163 - 142) - 178", "answer": "The result of (163 - 142) - 178 is -157", "a": 163, "b": 142, "c": 178, "op1": "-", "op2": "-", "result": -157}
{"question": "Solve: (118.33 + 110.87) * 166", "answer": "The result of (118.33 + 110.87) * 166 is 38047.2", "a": 118.33, "b": 110.87, "c": 166, "op1": "+", "op2": "*", "result": 38047.2}
{"question": "Solve: (96 * 123) - 4.93", "answer": "The result of (96 * 123) - 4.93 is 11803.07", "a": 96, "b": 123, "c": 4.93, "op1": "*", "op2": "-", "result": 11803.07}
{"question": "Solve: (79 + 56.4) - 129", "answer": "The result of (79 + 56.4) - 129 is 6.4", "a": 79, "b": 56.4, "c": 129, "op1": "+", "op2": "-", "result": 6.4}
{"question": "Solve: (4 - 85.35) * 160", "answer": "The result of (4 - 85.35) * 160 is -13016.0", "a": 4, "b": 85.35, "c": 160, "op1": "-", "op2": "*", "result": -13016.0}
{"question": "Solve: (191.99 * 17) - 113", "answer": "The result of (191.99 * 17) - 113 is 3150.83", "a": 191.99, "b": 17, "c": 113, "op1": "*", "op2": "-", "result": 3150.83}
{"question": "Solve: (136 + 142) - 57", "answer": "The result of (136 + 142) - 57 is 221", "a": 136, "b": 142, "c": 57, "op1": "+", "op2": "-", "result": 221}
{"question": "Solve: (61 + 97) - 117", "answer": "The result of (61 + 97) - 117 is 41", "a": 61, "b": 97, "c": 117, "op1": "+", "op2": "-", "result": 41}
{"question": "Solve: (98 / 104) - 20", "answer": "The result of (98 / 104) - 20 is -19.06", "a": 98, "b": 104, "c": 20, "op1": "/", "op2": "-", "result": -19.06}
{"question": "Solve: (169 + 108.26) - 34.4", "answer": "The result of (169 + 108.26) - 34.4 is 242.86", "a": 169, "b": 108.26, "c": 34.4, "op1": "+", "op2": "-", "result": 242.86}
{"question": "Solve: (158 * 162) + 163.99", "answer": "The result of (158 * 162) + 163.99 is 25759.99", "a": 158, "b": 162, "c": 163.99, "op1": "*", "op2": "+", "result": 25759.99}
{"question": "Solve: (121.17 - 55) / 11.99", "answer": "The result of (121.17 - 55) / 11.99 is 5.52", "a": 121.17, "b": 55, "c": 11.99, "op1": "-", "op2": "/", "result": 5.52}
{"question": "Solve: (109.77 / 116) + 77", "answer": "The result of (109.77 / 116) + 77 is 77.95", "a": 109.77, "b": 116, "c": 77, "op1": "/", "op2": "+", "result": 77.95}
{"question": "Solve: (86 - 24) - 135", "answer": "The result of (86 - 24) - 135 is -73", "a": 86, "b": 24, "c": 135, "op1": "-", "op2": "-", "result": -73}
{"question": "Solve: (34 * 80) * 7.81", "answer": "The result of (34 * 80) * 7.81 is 21243.2", "a": 34, "b": 80, "c": 7.81, "op1": "*", "op2": "*", "result": 21243.2}
{"question": "Solve: (100.6 - 35) + 32.54", "answer": "The result of (100.6 - 35) + 32.54 is 98.14", "a": 100.6, "b": 35, "c": 32.54, "op1": "-", "op2": "+", "result": 98.14}
{"question": "Solve: (135.91 * 31) + 59", "answer": "The result of (135.91 * 31) + 59 is 4272.21", "a": 135.91, "b": 31, "c": 59, "op1": "*", "op2": "+", "result": 4272.21}
{"question": "Solve: (58 - 160) * 186", "answer": "The result of (58 - 160) * 186 is -18972", "a": 58, "b": 160, "c": 186, "op1": "-", "op2": "*", "result": -18972}
{"question": "Solve: (154.6 + 42) - 168.16", "answer": "The result of (154.6 + 42) - 168.16 is 28.44", "a": 154.6, "b": 42, "c": 168.16, "op1": "+", "op2": "-", "result": 28.44}
{"question": "Solve: (95 * 179) - 185.64", "answer": "The result of (95 * 179) - 185.64 is 16819.36", "a": 95, "b": 179, "c": 185.64, "op1": "*", "op2": "-", "result": 16819.36}
{"question": "Solve: (94 / 178.59) / 19", "answer": "The result of (94 / 178.59) / 19 is 0.03", "a": 94, "b": 178.59, "c": 19, "op1": "/", "op2": "/", "result": 0.03}
{"question": "Solve: (127.98 * 37) / 28", "answer": "The result of (127.98 * 37) / 28 is 169.12", "a": 127.98, "b": 37, "c": 28, "op1": "*", "op2": "/", "result": 169.12}
{"question": "Solve: (162.83 * 20.38) + 163.0", "answer": "The result of (162.83 * 20.38) + 163.0 is 3481.48", "a": 162.83, "b": 20.38, "c": 163.0, "op1": "*", "op2": "+", "result": 3481.48}
{"question": "Solve: (111 - 93) + 66.86", "answer": "The result of (111 - 93) + 66.86 is 84.86", "a": 111, "b": 93, "c": 66.86, "op1": "-", "op2": "+", "result": 84.86}
{"question": "Solve: (32.98 + 89) * 29", "answer": "The result of (32.98 + 89) * 29 is 3537.42", "a": 32.98, "b": 89, "c": 29, "op1": "+", "op2": "*", "result": 3537.42}
{"question": "Solve: (40 * 166.52) - 173", "answer": "The result of (40 * 166.52) - 173 is 6487.8", "a": 40, "b": 166.52, "c": 173, "op1": "*", "op2": "-", "result": 6487.8}
{"question": "Solve: (85.13 - 57.43) * 15.75", "answer": "The result of (85.13 - 57.43) * 15.75 is 436.27", "a": 85.13, "b": 57.43, "c": 15.75, "op1": "-", "op2": "*", "result": 436.27}
{"question": "Solve: (68.17 - 57.89) + 26", "answer": "The result of (68.17 - 57.89) + 26 is 36.28", "a": 68.17, "b": 57.89, "c": 26, "op1": "-", "op2": "+", "result": 36.28}
{"question": "Solve: (78 - 25) / 151.05", "answer": "The result of (78 - 25) / 151.05 is 0.35", "a": 78, "b": 25, "c": 151.05, "op1": "-", "op2": "/", "result": 0.35}
{"question": "Solve: (116 + 48) + 8.05", "answer": "The result of (116 + 48) + 8.05 is 172.05", "a": 116, "b": 48, "c": 8.05, "op1": "+", "op2": "+", "result": 172.05}
{"question": "Solve: (30 + 130.98) - 137", "answer": "The result of (30 + 130.98) - 137 is 23.98", "a": 30, "b": 130.98, "c": 137, "op1": "+", "op2": "-", "result": 23.98}
{"question": "Solve: (24 + 89) - 55", "answer": "The result of (24 + 89) - 55 is 58", "a": 24, "b": 89, "c": 55, "op1": "+", "op2": "-", "result": 58}
{"question": "Solve: (133 * 155) / 2", "answer": "The result of (133 * 155) / 2 is 10307.5", "a": 133, "b": 155, "c": 2, "op1": "*", "op2": "/", "result": 10307.5}
{"question": "Solve: (169.72 * 152) / 36", "answer": "The result of (169.72 * 152) / 36 is 716.6", "a": 169.72, "b": 152, "c": 36, "op1": "*", "op2": "/", "result": 716.6}
{"question": "Solve: (125 * 24) + 52.34", "answer": "The result of (125 * 24) + 52.34 is 3052.34", "a": 125, "b": 24, "c": 52.34, "op1": "*", "op2": "+", "result": 3052.34}
{"question": "Solve: (87 + 89) - 18.94", "answer": "The result of (87 + 89) - 18.94 is 157.06", "a": 87, "b": 89, "c": 18.94, "op1": "+", "op2": "-", "result": 157.06}
{"question": "Solve: (2 - 48) - 126", "answer": "The result of (2 - 48) - 126 is -172", "a": 2, "b": 48, "c": 126, "op1": "-", "op2": "-", "result": -172}
{"question": "Solve: (66 / 8.27) + 104.61", "answer": "The result of (66 / 8.27) + 104.61 is 112.59", "a": 66, "b": 8.27, "c": 104.61, "op1": "/", "op2": "+", "result": 112.59}
{"question": "Solve: (21 - 76) + 8", "answer": "The result of (21 - 76) + 8 is -47", "a": 21, "b": 76, "c": 8, "op1": "-", "op2": "+", "result": -47}
{"question": "Solve: (143.18 * 11.26) - 98.73", "answer": "The result of (143.18 * 11.26) - 98.73 is 1513.48", "a": 143.18, "b": 11.26, "c": 98.73, "op1": "*", "op2": "-", "result": 1513.48}
{"question": "Solve: (87.48 + 101) / 123.59", "answer": "The result of (87.48 + 101) / 123.59 is 1.53", "a": 87.48, "b": 101, "c": 123.59, "op1": "+", "op2": "/", "result": 1.53}
{"question": "Solve: (51 - 110) * 51", "answer": "The result of (51 - 110) * 51 is -3009", "a": 51, "b": 110, "c": 51, "op1": "-", "op2": "*", "result": -3009}
{"question": "Solve: (21 + 110) / 63.12", "answer": "The result of (21 + 110) / 63.12 is 2.08", "a": 21, "b": 110, "c": 63.12, "op1": "+", "op2": "/", "result": 2.08}
{"question": "Solve: (106 * 100) - 1.85", "answer": "The result of (106 * 100) - 1.85 is 10598.15", "a": 106, "b": 100, "c": 1.85, "op1": "*", "op2": "-", "result": 10598.15}
{"question": "Solve: (18 - 182) + 109", "answer": "The result of (18 - 182) + 109 is -55", "a": 18, "b": 182, "c": 109, "op1": "-", "op2": "+", "result": -55}
{"question": "Solve: (80 - 14) * 116.28", "answer": "The result of (80 - 14) * 116.28 is 7674.48", "a": 80, "b": 14, "c": 116.28, "op1": "-", "op2": "*", "result": 7674.48}
{"question": "Solve: (110.11 * 134) + 143", "answer": "The result of (110.11 * 134) + 143 is 14897.74", "a": 110.11, "b": 134, "c": 143, "op1": "*", "op2": "+", "result": 14897.74}
{"question": "Solve: (60 * 172.19) * 101", "answer": "The result of (60 * 172.19) * 101 is 1043471.4", "a": 60, "b": 172.19, "c": 101, "op1": "*", "op2": "*", "result": 1043471.4}
{"question": "Solve: (4.28 * 195) - 127", "answer": "The result of (4.28 * 195) - 127 is 707.6", "a": 4.28, "b": 195, "c": 127, "op1": "*", "op2": "-", "result": 707.6}
{"question": "Solve: (142 * 21) - 186", "answer": "The result of (142 * 21) - 186 is 2796", "a": 142, "b": 21, "c": 186, "op1": "*", "op2": "-", "result": 2796}
{"question": "Solve: (193 + 8.67) * 189", "answer": "The result of (193 + 8.67) * 189 is 38115.63", "a": 193, "b": 8.67, "c": 189, "op1": "+", "op2": "*", "result": 38115.63}
{"question": "Solve: (93 * 144) / 67", "answer": "The result of (93 * 144) / 67 is 199.88", "a": 93, "b": 144, "c": 67, "op1": "*", "op2": "/", "result": 199.88}
{"question": "Solve: (198.8 / 57) * 49.42", "answer": "The result of (198.8 / 57) * 49.42 is 172.36", "a": 198.8, "b": 57, "c": 49.42, "op1": "/", "op2": "*", "result": 172.36}
{"question": "Solve: (153.31 - 139) - 132", "answer": "The result of (153.31 - 139) - 132 is -117.69", "a": 153.31, "b": 139, "c": 132, "op1": "-", "op2": "-", "result": -117.69}
{"question": "Solve: (163 - 118) - 174", "answer": "The result of (163 - 118) - 174 is -129", "a": 163, "b": 118, "c": 174, "op1": "-", "op2": "-", "result": -129}
{"question": "Solve: (117 - 46.73) * 160", "answer": "The result of (117 - 46.73) * 160 is 11243.2", "a": 117, "b": 46.73, "c": 160, "op1": "-", "op2": "*", "result": 11243.2}
{"question": "Solve: (6 - 24) - 24.98", "answer": "The result of (6 - 24) - 24.98 is -42.98", "a": 6, "b": 24, "c": 24.98, "op1": "-", "op2": "-", "result": -42.98}
{"question": "Solve: (44 + 186) + 139.19", "answer": "The result of (44 + 186) + 139.19 is 369.19", "a": 44, "b": 186, "c": 139.19, "op1": "+", "op2": "+", "result": 369.19}
{"question": "Solve: (196.07 + 171.52) * 168", "answer": "The result of (196.07 + 171.52) * 168 is 61755.12", "a": 196.07, "b": 171.52, "c": 168, "op1": "+", "op2": "*", "result": 61755.12}
{"question": "Solve: (57 + 50) * 56", "answer": "The result of (57 + 50) * 56 is 5992", "a": 57, "b": 50, "c": 56, "op1": "+", "op2": "*", "result": 5992}
{"question": "Solve: (167 / 194) * 88", "answer": "The result of (167 / 194) * 88 is 75.75", "a": 167, "b": 194, "c": 88, "op1": "/", "op2": "*", "result": 75.75}
{"question": "Solve: (192 + 130) / 150", "answer": "The result of (192 + 130) / 150 is 2.15", "a": 192, "b": 130, "c": 150, "op1": "+", "op2": "/", "result": 2.15}
{"question": "Solve: (4 - 7) / 155", "answer": "The result of (4 - 7) / 155 is -0.02", "a": 4, "b": 7, "c": 155, "op1": "-", "op2": "/", "result": -0.02}
{"question": "Solve: (188 * 65) * 141", "answer": "The result of (188 * 65) * 141 is 1723020", "a": 188, "b": 65, "c": 141, "op1": "*", "op2": "*", "result": 1723020}
{"question": "Solve: (86 - 196) * 55", "answer": "The result of (86 - 196) * 55 is -6050", "a": 86, "b": 196, "c": 55, "op1": "-", "op2": "*", "result": -6050}
{"question": "Solve: (109 * 175.14) - 72", "answer": "The result of (109 * 175.14) - 72 is 19018.26", "a": 109, "b": 175.14, "c": 72, "op1": "*", "op2": "-", "result": 19018.26}
{"question": "Solve: (106 * 137) + 146", "answer": "The result of (106 * 137) + 146 is 14668", "a": 106, "b": 137, "c": 146, "op1": "*", "op2": "+", "result": 14668}
{"question": "Solve: (132 + 3.51) + 106", "answer": "The result of (132 + 3.51) + 106 is 241.51", "a": 132, "b": 3.51, "c": 106, "op1": "+", "op2": "+", "result": 241.51}
{"question": "Solve: (95.95 + 189) - 115.81", "answer": "The result of (95.95 + 189) - 115.81 is 169.14", "a": 95.95, "b": 189, "c": 115.81, "op1": "+", "op2": "-", "result": 169.14}
{"question": "Solve: (145 * 86.35) * 14.57", "answer": "The result of (145 * 86.35) * 14.57 is 182427.33", "a": 145, "b": 86.35, "c": 14.57, "op1": "*", "op2": "*", "result": 182427.33}
{"question": "Solve: (117.94 - 150.52) / 166.85", "answer": "The result of (117.94 - 150.52) / 166.85 is -0.2", "a": 117.94, "b": 150.52, "c": 166.85, "op1": "-", "op2": "/", "result": -0.2}
{"question": "Solve: (103.34 + 8.57) + 169.56", "answer": "The result of (103.34 + 8.57) + 169.56 is 281.47", "a": 103.34, "b": 8.57, "c": 169.56, "op1": "+", "op2": "+", "result": 281.47}
{"question": "Solve: (153.85 + 187.85) * 110", "answer": "The result of (153.85 + 187.85) * 110 is 37587.0", "a": 153.85, "b": 187.85, "c": 110, "op1": "+", "op2": "*", "result": 37587.0}
{"question": "Solve: (137 + 108) / 180.23", "answer": "The result of (137 + 108) / 180.23 is 1.36", "a": 137, "b": 108, "c": 180.23, "op1": "+", "op2": "/", "result": 1.36}
{"question": "Solve: (183.76 + 152.7) / 10", "answer": "The result of (183.76 + 152.7) / 10 is 33.65", "a": 183.76, "b": 152.7, "c": 10, "op1": "+", "op2": "/", "result": 33.65}
{"question": "Solve: (165 - 30) + 190.44", "answer": "The result of (165 - 30) + 190.44 is 325.44", "a": 165, "b": 30, "c": 190.44, "op1": "-", "op2": "+", "result": 325.44}
{"question": "Solve: (63 * 131) + 53.59", "answer": "The result of (63 * 131) + 53.59 is 8306.59", "a": 63, "b": 131, "c": 53.59, "op1": "*", "op2": "+", "result": 8306.59}
{"question": "Solve: (70 / 88) + 147.92", "answer": "The result of (70 / 88) + 147.92 is 148.72", "a": 70, "b": 88, "c": 147.92, "op1": "/", "op2": "+", "result": 148.72}
{"question": "Solve: (62.75 + 54) + 66", "answer": "The result of (62.75 + 54) + 66 is 182.75", "a": 62.75, "b": 54, "c": 66, "op1": "+", "op2": "+", "result": 182.75}
{"question": "Solve: (167 + 84) - 71.16", "answer": "The result of (167 + 84) - 71.16 is 179.84", "a": 167, "b": 84, "c": 71.16, "op1": "+", "op2": "-", "result": 179.84}
{"question": "Solve: (60.84 - 164) + 132", "answer": "The result of (60.84 - 164) + 132 is 28.84", "a": 60.84, "b": 164, "c": 132, "op1": "-", "op2": "+", "result": 28.84}
{"question": "Solve: (137 - 128) + 37.83", "answer": "The result of (137 - 128) + 37.83 is 46.83", "a": 137, "b": 128, "c": 37.83, "op1": "-", "op2": "+", "result": 46.83}
{"question": "Solve: (82 / 195) - 195.51", "answer": "The result of (82 / 195) - 195.51 is -195.09", "a": 82, "b": 195, "c": 195.51, "op1": "/", "op2": "-", "result": -195.09}
{"question": "Solve: (19.31 / 71) - 174", "answer": "The result of (19.31 / 71) - 174 is -173.73", "a": 19.31, "b": 71, "c": 174, "op1": "/", "op2": "-", "result": -173.73}
{"question": "Solve: (170.56 - 61) + 26", "answer": "The result of (170.56 - 61) + 26 is 135.56", "a": 170.56, "b": 61, "c": 26, "op1": "-", "op2": "+", "result": 135.56}
{"question": "Solve: (195 + 174.21) - 14.81", "answer": "The result of (195 + 174.21) - 14.81 is 354.4", "a": 195, "b": 174.21, "c": 14.81, "op1": "+", "op2": "-", "result": 354.4}
{"question": "Solve: (198 - 45.41) - 171", "answer": "The result of (198 - 45.41) - 171 is -18.41", "a": 198, "b": 45.41, "c": 171, "op1": "-", "op2": "-", "result": -18.41}
{"question": "Solve: (82 - 167) / 96", "answer": "The result of (82 - 167) / 96 is -0.89", "a": 82, "b": 167, "c": 96, "op1": "-", "op2": "/", "result": -0.89}
{"question": "Solve: (108 - 10.43) + 79", "answer": "The result of (108 - 10.43) + 79 is 176.57", "a": 108, "b": 10.43, "c": 79, "op1": "-", "op2": "+", "result": 176.57}
{"question": "Solve: (56.82 - 71) - 87.23", "answer": "The result of (56.82 - 71) - 87.23 is -101.41", "a": 56.82, "b": 71, "c": 87.23, "op1": "-", "op2": "-", "result": -101.41}
{"question": "Solve: (68.35 * 174.18) - 140", "answer": "The result of (68.35 * 174.18) - 140 is 11765.2", "a": 68.35, "b": 174.18, "c": 140, "op1": "*", "op2": "-", "result": 11765.2}
{"question": "Solve: (75 - 56.47) * 135", "answer": "The result of (75 - 56.47) * 135 is 2501.55", "a": 75, "b": 56.47, "c": 135, "op1": "-", "op2": "*", "result": 2501.55}
{"question": "Solve: (165.12 - 128.45) - 153.3", "answer": "The result of (165.12 - 128.45) - 153.3 is -116.63", "a": 165.12, "b": 128.45, "c": 153.3, "op1": "-", "op2": "-", "result": -116.63}
{"question": "Solve: (148 - 14) * 161", "answer": "The result of (148 - 14) * 161 is 21574", "a": 148, "b": 14, "c": 161, "op1": "-", "op2": "*", "result": 21574}
{"question": "Solve: (198 * 88.52) - 60.29", "answer": "The result of (198 * 88.52) - 60.29 is 17466.67", "a": 198, "b": 88.52, "c": 60.29, "op1": "*", "op2": "-", "result": 17466.67}
{"question": "Solve: (160 + 51.97) - 28", "answer": "The result of (160 + 51.97) - 28 is 183.97", "a": 160, "b": 51.97, "c": 28, "op1": "+", "op2": "-", "result": 183.97}
{"question": "Solve: (99.15 + 29.1) + 65", "answer": "The result of (99.15 + 29.1) + 65 is 193.25", "a": 99.15, "b": 29.1, "c": 65, "op1": "+", "op2": "+", "result": 193.25}
{"question": "Solve: (13.96 - 69.34) + 193", "answer": "The result of (13.96 - 69.34) + 193 is 137.62", "a": 13.96, "b": 69.34, "c": 193, "op1": "-", "op2": "+", "result": 137.62}
{"question": "Solve: (140 * 26) + 97", "answer": "The result of (140 * 26) + 97 is 3737", "a": 140, "b": 26, "c": 97, "op1": "*", "op2": "+", "result": 3737}
{"question": "Solve: (191 - 48) * 127.83", "answer": "The result of (191 - 48) * 127.83 is 18279.69", "a": 191, "b": 48, "c": 127.83, "op1": "-", "op2": "*", "result": 18279.69}
{"question": "Solve: (152 - 152) + 162", "answer": "The result of (152 - 152) + 162 is 162", "a": 152, "b": 152, "c": 162, "op1": "-", "op2": "+", "result": 162}
{"question": "Solve: (94 / 73) - 75.0", "answer": "The result of (94 / 73) - 75.0 is -73.71", "a": 94, "b": 73, "c": 75.0, "op1": "/", "op2": "-", "result": -73.71}
{"question": "Solve: (24 / 175) / 163", "answer": "The result of (24 / 175) / 163 is 0.0", "a": 24, "b": 175, "c": 163, "op1": "/", "op2": "/", "result": 0.0}
{"question": "Solve: (36 + 37.47) / 180.48", "answer": "The result of (36 + 37.47) / 180.48 is 0.41", "a": 36, "b": 37.47, "c": 180.48, "op1": "+", "op2": "/", "result": 0.41}
{"question": "Solve: (173.5 + 63.08) / 100.28", "answer": "The result of (173.5 + 63.08) / 100.28 is 2.36", "a": 173.5, "b": 63.08, "c": 100.28, "op1": "+", "op2": "/", "result": 2.36}
{"question": "Solve: (128 + 127) + 2", "answer": "The result of (128 + 127) + 2 is 257", "a": 128, "b": 127, "c": 2, "op1": "+", "op2": "+", "result": 257}
{"question": "Solve: (193 - 187.57) - 78", "answer": "The result of (193 - 187.57) - 78 is -72.57", "a": 193, "b": 187.57, "c": 78, "op1": "-", "op2": "-", "result": -72.57}
{"question": "Solve: (117 / 149) / 124", "answer": "The result of (117 / 149) / 124 is 0.01", "a": 117, "b": 149, "c": 124, "op1": "/", "op2": "/", "result": 0.01}
{"question": "Solve: (95 * 110) * 182", "answer": "The result of (95 * 110) * 182 is 1901900", "a": 95, "b": 110, "c": 182, "op1": "*", "op2": "*", "result": 1901900}
{"question": "Solve: (28.23 / 192) + 144", "answer": "The result of (28.23 / 192) + 144 is 144.15", "a": 28.23, "b": 192, "c": 144, "op1": "/", "op2": "+", "result": 144.15}
{"question": "Solve: (135.59 * 13) / 84", "answer": "The result of (135.59 * 13) / 84 is 20.98", "a": 135.59, "b": 13, "c": 84, "op1": "*", "op2": "/", "result": 20.98}
{"question": "Solve: (7 - 162.14) + 70.83", "answer": "The result of (7 - 162.14) + 70.83 is -84.31", "a": 7, "b": 162.14, "c": 70.83, "op1": "-", "op2": "+", "result": -84.31}
{"question": "Solve: (154 + 149) + 53.92", "answer": "The result of (154 + 149) + 53.92 is 356.92", "a": 154, "b": 149, "c": 53.92, "op1": "+", "op2": "+", "result": 356.92}
{"question": "Solve: (148 * 7) * 179", "answer": "The result of (148 * 7) * 179 is 185444", "a": 148, "b": 7, "c": 179, "op1": "*", "op2": "*", "result": 185444}
{"question": "Solve: (126 * 142) / 121", "answer": "The result of (126 * 142) / 121 is 147.87", "a": 126, "b": 142, "c": 121, "op1": "*", "op2": "/", "result": 147.87}
{"question": "Solve: (72 + 50) + 79", "answer": "The result of (72 + 50) + 79 is 201", "a": 72, "b": 50, "c": 79, "op1": "+", "op2": "+", "result": 201}
{"question": "Solve: (104 + 140) + 187", "answer": "The result of (104 + 140) + 187 is 431", "a": 104, "b": 140, "c": 187, "op1": "+", "op2": "+", "result": 431}
{"question": "Solve: (161.32 * 26.19) - 106", "answer": "The result of (161.32 * 26.19) - 106 is 4118.97", "a": 161.32, "b": 26.19, "c": 106, "op1": "*", "op2": "-", "result": 4118.97}
{"question": "Solve: (25 * 25.78) + 9", "answer": "The result of (25 * 25.78) + 9 is 653.5", "a": 25, "b": 25.78, "c": 9, "op1": "*", "op2": "+", "result": 653.5}
{"question": "Solve: (96 / 41) - 7", "answer": "The result of (96 / 41) - 7 is -4.66", "a": 96, "b": 41, "c": 7, "op1": "/", "op2": "-", "result": -4.66}
{"question": "Solve: (125 - 147) * 51", "answer": "The result of (125 - 147) * 51 is -1122", "a": 125, "b": 147, "c": 51, "op1": "-", "op2": "*", "result": -1122}
{"question": "Solve: (25 + 17) / 110", "answer": "The result of (25 + 17) / 110 is 0.38", "a": 25, "b": 17, "c": 110, "op1": "+", "op2": "/", "result": 0.38}
{"question": "Solve: (122 + 62.25) + 58", "answer": "The result of (122 + 62.25) + 58 is 242.25", "a": 122, "b": 62.25, "c": 58, "op1": "+", "op2": "+", "result": 242.25}
{"question": "Solve: (187 - 65) * 42", "answer": "The result of (187 - 65) * 42 is 5124", "a": 187, "b": 65, "c": 42, "op1": "-", "op2": "*", "result": 5124}
{"question": "Solve: (163 * 117.06) / 162.54", "answer": "The result of (163 * 117.06) / 162.54 is 117.39", "a": 163, "b": 117.06, "c": 162.54, "op1": "*", "op2": "/", "result": 117.39}
{"question": "Solve: (16 + 106) - 2", "answer": "The result of (16 + 106) - 2 is 120", "a": 16, "b": 106, "c": 2, "op1": "+", "op2": "-", "result": 120}
{"question": "Solve: (3.3 + 1.14) * 141", "answer": "The result of (3.3 + 1.14) * 141 is 626.04", "a": 3.3, "b": 1.14, "c": 141, "op1": "+", "op2": "*", "result": 626.04}
{"question": "Solve: (175.25 + 198) + 134.66", "answer": "The result of (175.25 + 198) + 134.66 is 507.91", "a": 175.25, "b": 198, "c": 134.66, "op1": "+", "op2": "+", "result": 507.91}
{"question": "Solve: (193 - 15) - 111", "answer": "The result of (193 - 15) - 111 is 67", "a": 193, "b": 15, "c": 111, "op1": "-", "op2": "-", "result": 67}
{"question": "Solve: (182 * 180) + 172", "answer": "The result of (182 * 180) + 172 is 32932", "a": 182, "b": 180, "c": 172, "op1": "*", "op2": "+", "result": 32932}
{"question": "Solve: (68 / 53) - 13.44", "answer": "The result of (68 / 53) - 13.44 is -12.16", "a": 68, "b": 53, "c": 13.44, "op1": "/", "op2": "-", "result": -12.16}
{"question": "Solve: (130 * 26) - 75.92", "answer": "The result of (130 * 26) - 75.92 is 3304.08", "a": 130, "b": 26, "c": 75.92, "op1": "*", "op2": "-", "result": 3304.08}
{"question": "Solve: (186 + 61) / 152", "answer": "The result of (186 + 61) / 152 is 1.62", "a": 186, "b": 61, "c": 152, "op1": "+", "op2": "/", "result": 1.62}
{"question": "Solve: (61.97 * 103.79) - 195", "answer": "The result of (61.97 * 103.79) - 195 is 6236.87", "a": 61.97, "b": 103.79, "c": 195, "op1": "*", "op2": "-", "result": 6236.87}
{"question": "Solve: (12 * 28) * 83", "answer": "The result of (12 * 28) * 83 is 27888", "a": 12, "b": 28, "c": 83, "op1": "*", "op2": "*", "result": 27888}
{"question": "Solve: (38 - 72) * 161", "answer": "The result of (38 - 72) * 161 is -5474", "a": 38, "b": 72, "c": 161, "op1": "-", "op2": "*", "result": -5474}
{"question": "Solve: (150 * 173) - 165", "answer": "The result of (150 * 173) - 165 is 25785", "a": 150, "b": 173, "c": 165, "op1": "*", "op2": "-", "result": 25785}
{"question": "Solve: (191.41 + 67) * 170", "answer": "The result of (191.41 + 67) * 170 is 43929.7", "a": 191.41, "b": 67, "c": 170, "op1": "+", "op2": "*", "result": 43929.7}
{"question": "Solve: (113 * 9) - 80", "answer": "The result of (113 * 9) - 80 is 937", "a": 113, "b": 9, "c": 80, "op1": "*", "op2": "-", "result": 937}
{"question": "Solve: (183.03 - 12) - 6", "answer": "The result of (183.03 - 12) - 6 is 165.03", "a": 183.03, "b": 12, "c": 6, "op1": "-", "op2": "-", "result": 165.03}
{"question": "Solve: (62.2 + 43.94) * 184", "answer": "The result of (62.2 + 43.94) * 184 is 19529.76", "a": 62.2, "b": 43.94, "c": 184, "op1": "+", "op2": "*", "result": 19529.76}
{"question": "Solve: (27 + 190.62) * 15.24", "answer": "The result of (27 + 190.62) * 15.24 is 3316.53", "a": 27, "b": 190.62, "c": 15.24, "op1": "+", "op2": "*", "result": 3316.53}
{"question": "Solve: (89.98 + 193) / 161", "answer": "The result of (89.98 + 193) / 161 is 1.76", "a": 89.98, "b": 193, "c": 161, "op1": "+", "op2": "/", "result": 1.76}
{"question": "Solve: (186 * 185.93) * 91", "answer": "The result of (186 * 185.93) * 91 is 3147051.18", "a": 186, "b": 185.93, "c": 91, "op1": "*", "op2": "*", "result": 3147051.18}
{"question": "Solve: (188 - 15) + 25", "answer": "The result of (188 - 15) + 25 is 198", "a": 188, "b": 15, "c": 25, "op1": "-", "op2": "+", "result": 198}
{"question": "Solve: (19 + 13) - 59.71", "answer": "The result of (19 + 13) - 59.71 is -27.71", "a": 19, "b": 13, "c": 59.71, "op1": "+", "op2": "-", "result": -27.71}
{"question": "Solve: (199 - 75) - 167.89", "answer": "The result of (199 - 75) - 167.89 is -43.89", "a": 199, "b": 75, "c": 167.89, "op1": "-", "op2": "-", "result": -43.89}
{"question": "Solve: (78.49 - 6) - 18", "answer": "The result of (78.49 - 6) - 18 is 54.49", "a": 78.49, "b": 6, "c": 18, "op1": "-", "op2": "-", "result": 54.49}
{"question": "Solve: (91 * 1) - 20.84", "answer": "The result of (91 * 1) - 20.84 is 70.16", "a": 91, "b": 1, "c": 20.84, "op1": "*", "op2": "-", "result": 70.16}
{"question": "Solve: (29 - 92.69) * 111", "answer": "The result of (29 - 92.69) * 111 is -7069.59", "a": 29, "b": 92.69, "c": 111, "op1": "-", "op2": "*", "result": -7069.59}
{"question": "Solve: (116 - 59) * 126", "answer": "The result of (116 - 59) * 126 is 7182", "a": 116, "b": 59, "c": 126, "op1": "-", "op2": "*", "result": 7182}
{"question": "Solve: (19 + 62.52) * 115.37", "answer": "The result of (19 + 62.52) * 115.37 is 9404.96", "a": 19, "b": 62.52, "c": 115.37, "op1": "+", "op2": "*", "result": 9404.96}
{"question": "Solve: (57 + 2) / 103.48", "answer": "The result of (57 + 2) / 103.48 is 0.57", "a": 57, "b": 2, "c": 103.48, "op1": "+", "op2": "/", "result": 0.57}
{"question": "Solve: (92.11 + 176.76) * 143.64", "answer": "The result of (92.11 + 176.76) * 143.64 is 38620.49", "a": 92.11, "b": 176.76, "c": 143.64, "op1": "+", "op2": "*", "result": 38620.49}
{"question": "Solve: (160 + 109) + 24", "answer": "The result of (160 + 109) + 24 is 293", "a": 160, "b": 109, "c": 24, "op1": "+", "op2": "+", "result": 293}
{"question": "Solve: (73.33 + 172) / 158", "answer": "The result of (73.33 + 172) / 158 is 1.55", "a": 73.33, "b": 172, "c": 158, "op1": "+", "op2": "/", "result": 1.55}
{"question": "Solve: (150 + 29) - 55", "answer": "The result of (150 + 29) - 55 is 124", "a": 150, "b": 29, "c": 55, "op1": "+", "op2": "-", "result": 124}
{"question": "Solve: (184.28 * 55.75) + 35", "answer": "The result of (184.28 * 55.75) + 35 is 10308.61", "a": 184.28, "b": 55.75, "c": 35, "op1": "*", "op2": "+", "result": 10308.61}
{"question": "Solve: (117 - 138) + 126.67", "answer": "The result of (117 - 138) + 126.67 is 105.67", "a": 117, "b": 138, "c": 126.67, "op1": "-", "op2": "+", "result": 105.67}
{"question": "Solve: (145 + 119) - 14", "answer": "The result of (145 + 119) - 14 is 250", "a": 145, "b": 119, "c": 14, "op1": "+", "op2": "-", "result": 250}
{"question": "Solve: (163.08 - 112) * 32", "answer": "The result of (163.08 - 112) * 32 is 1634.56", "a": 163.08, "b": 112, "c": 32, "op1": "-", "op2": "*", "result": 1634.56}
{"question": "Solve: (179.27 / 156) + 192", "answer": "The result of (179.27 / 156) + 192 is 193.15", "a": 179.27, "b": 156, "c": 192, "op1": "/", "op2": "+", "result": 193.15}
{"question": "Solve: (159 * 196.63) * 52.87", "answer": "The result of (159 * 196.63) * 52.87 is 1652936.67", "a": 159, "b": 196.63, "c": 52.87, "op1": "*", "op2": "*", "result": 1652936.67}
{"question": "Solve: (74.39 + 55) / 97", "answer": "The result of (74.39 + 55) / 97 is 1.33", "a": 74.39, "b": 55, "c": 97, "op1": "+", "op2": "/", "result": 1.33}
{"question": "Solve: (17 / 135.3) / 120.77", "answer": "The result of (17 / 135.3) / 120.77 is 0.0", "a": 17, "b": 135.3, "c": 120.77, "op1": "/", "op2": "/", "result": 0.0}
{"question": "Solve: (122 * 110.32) + 37", "answer": "The result of (122 * 110.32) + 37 is 13496.04", "a": 122, "b": 110.32, "c": 37, "op1": "*", "op2": "+", "result": 13496.04}
{"question": "Solve: (35 * 55.39) + 85", "answer": "The result of (35 * 55.39) + 85 is 2023.65", "a": 35, "b": 55.39, "c": 85, "op1": "*", "op2": "+", "result": 2023.65}
{"question": "Solve: (59 - 181) - 10", "answer": "The result of (59 - 181) - 10 is -132", "a": 59, "b": 181, "c": 10, "op1": "-", "op2": "-", "result": -132}
{"question": "Solve: (156.94 - 191) + 31", "answer": "The result of (156.94 - 191) + 31 is -3.06", "a": 156.94, "b": 191, "c": 31, "op1": "-", "op2": "+", "result": -3.06}
{"question": "Solve: (177.9 + 17) / 97.23", "answer": "The result of (177.9 + 17) / 97.23 is 2.0", "a": 177.9, "b": 17, "c": 97.23, "op1": "+", "op2": "/", "result": 2.0}
{"question": "Solve: (172 - 57.48) - 4", "answer": "The result of (172 - 57.48) - 4 is 110.52", "a": 172, "b": 57.48, "c": 4, "op1": "-", "op2": "-", "result": 110.52}
{"question": "Solve: (72.13 - 127) - 24", "answer": "The result of (72.13 - 127) - 24 is -78.87", "a": 72.13, "b": 127, "c": 24, "op1": "-", "op2": "-", "result": -78.87}
{"question": "Solve: (153.29 - 71) + 190", "answer": "The result of (153.29 - 71) + 190 is 272.29", "a": 153.29, "b": 71, "c": 190, "op1": "-", "op2": "+", "result": 272.29}
{"question": "Solve: (115.25 * 83) - 69", "answer": "The result of (115.25 * 83) - 69 is 9496.75", "a": 115.25, "b": 83, "c": 69, "op1": "*", "op2": "-", "result": 9496.75}
{"question": "Solve: (118.42 - 141) - 67.21", "answer": "The result of (118.42 - 141) - 67.21 is -89.79", "a": 118.42, "b": 141, "c": 67.21, "op1": "-", "op2": "-", "result": -89.79}
{"question": "Solve: (88 - 4) * 173", "answer": "The result of (88 - 4) * 173 is 14532", "a": 88, "b": 4, "c": 173, "op1": "-", "op2": "*", "result": 14532}
{"question": "Solve: (108 + 163.61) * 170", "answer": "The result of (108 + 163.61) * 170 is 46173.7", "a": 108, "b": 163.61, "c": 170, "op1": "+", "op2": "*", "result": 46173.7}
{"question": "Solve: (9.95 / 79) / 146", "answer": "The result of (9.95 / 79) / 146 is 0.0", "a": 9.95, "b": 79, "c": 146, "op1": "/", "op2": "/", "result": 0.0}
{"question": "Solve: (106 + 109) * 155", "answer": "The result of (106 + 109) * 155 is 33325", "a": 106, "b": 109, "c": 155, "op1": "+", "op2": "*", "result": 33325}
{"question": "Solve: (6 + 164) * 114", "answer": "The result of (6 + 164) * 114 is 19380", "a": 6, "b": 164, "c": 114, "op1": "+", "op2": "*", "result": 19380}
{"question": "Solve: (47 * 191) + 21.98", "answer": "The result of (47 * 191) + 21.98 is 8998.98", "a": 47, "b": 191, "c": 21.98, "op1": "*", "op2": "+", "result": 8998.98}
{"question": "Solve: (16 - 161.17) + 180", "answer": "The result of (16 - 161.17) + 180 is 34.83", "a": 16, "b": 161.17, "c": 180, "op1": "-", "op2": "+", "result": 34.83}
{"question": "Solve: (106 - 89) * 17", "answer": "The result of (106 - 89) * 17 is 289", "a": 106, "b": 89, "c": 17, "op1": "-", "op2": "*", "result": 289}
{"question": "Solve: (131 * 30) - 39.48", "answer": "The result of (131 * 30) - 39.48 is 3890.52", "a": 131, "b": 30, "c": 39.48, "op1": "*", "op2": "-", "result": 3890.52}
{"question": "Solve: (199 * 127.56) - 96.01", "answer": "The result of (199 * 127.56) - 96.01 is 25288.43", "a": 199, "b": 127.56, "c": 96.01, "op1": "*", "op2": "-", "result": 25288.43}
{"question": "Solve: (161 * 73) - 153", "answer": "The result of (161 * 73) - 153 is 11600", "a": 161, "b": 73, "c": 153, "op1": "*", "op2": "-", "result": 11600}
{"question": "Solve: (15.88 + 200) * 157.77", "answer": "The result of (15.88 + 200) * 157.77 is 34059.39", "a": 15.88, "b": 200, "c": 157.77, "op1": "+", "op2": "*", "result": 34059.39}
{"question": "Solve: (173 / 16.18) * 123.86", "answer": "The result of (173 / 16.18) * 123.86 is 1324.34", "a": 173, "b": 16.18, "c": 123.86, "op1": "/", "op2": "*", "result": 1324.34}
{"question": "Solve: (99.51 * 192) + 33.6", "answer": "The result of (99.51 * 192) + 33.6 is 19139.52", "a": 99.51, "b": 192, "c": 33.6, "op1": "*", "op2": "+", "result": 19139.52}
{"question": "Solve: (115 * 114) * 3", "answer": "The result of (115 * 114) * 3 is 39330", "a": 115, "b": 114, "c": 3, "op1": "*", "op2": "*", "result": 39330}
{"question": "Solve: (33 - 3.35) + 138", "answer": "The result of (33 - 3.35) + 138 is 167.65", "a": 33, "b": 3.35, "c": 138, "op1": "-", "op2": "+", "result": 167.65}
{"question": "Solve: (156 / 184.3) - 60.79", "answer": "The result of (156 / 184.3) - 60.79 is -59.94", "a": 156, "b": 184.3, "c": 60.79, "op1": "/", "op2": "-", "result": -59.94}
{"question": "Solve: (186.34 + 192.82) * 55.13", "answer": "The result of (186.34 + 192.82) * 55.13 is 20903.09", "a": 186.34, "b": 192.82, "c": 55.13, "op1": "+", "op2": "*", "result": 20903.09}
{"question": "Solve: (171 - 134) + 72", "answer": "The result of (171 - 134) + 72 is 109", "a": 171, "b": 134, "c": 72, "op1": "-", "op2": "+", "result": 109}
{"question": "Solve: (150 + 183) / 154", "answer": "The result of (150 + 183) / 154 is 2.16", "a": 150, "b": 183, "c": 154, "op1": "+", "op2": "/", "result": 2.16}
{"question": "Solve: (8 / 25) + 190", "answer": "The result of (8 / 25) + 190 is 190.32", "a": 8, "b": 25, "c": 190, "op1": "/", "op2": "+", "result": 190.32}
{"question": "Solve: (107 / 8) + 157", "answer": "The result of (107 / 8) + 157 is 170.38", "a": 107, "b": 8, "c": 157, "op1": "/", "op2": "+", "result": 170.38}
{"question": "Solve: (73 + 133) / 15", "answer": "The result of (73 + 133) / 15 is 13.73", "a": 73, "b": 133, "c": 15, "op1": "+", "op2": "/", "result": 13.73}
{"question": "Solve: (160 - 107.46) - 110", "answer": "The result of (160 - 107.46) - 110 is -57.46", "a": 160, "b": 107.46, "c": 110, "op1": "-", "op2": "-", "result": -57.46}
{"question": "Solve: (67 * 121.13) - 165", "answer": "The result of (67 * 121.13) - 165 is 7950.71", "a": 67, "b": 121.13, "c": 165, "op1": "*", "op2": "-", "result": 7950.71}
{"question": "Solve: (184 * 130) - 135", "answer": "The result of (184 * 130) - 135 is 23785", "a": 184, "b": 130, "c": 135, "op1": "*", "op2": "-", "result": 23785}
{"question": "Solve: (144 + 49) / 140", "answer": "The result of (144 + 49) / 140 is 1.38", "a": 144, "b": 49, "c": 140, "op1": "+", "op2": "/", "result": 1.38}
{"question": "Solve: (65.04 * 165) * 6", "answer": "The result of (65.04 * 165) * 6 is 64389.6", "a": 65.04, "b": 165, "c": 6, "op1": "*", "op2": "*", "result": 64389.6}
{"question": "Solve: (166.51 - 180) * 58", "answer": "The result of (166.51 - 180) * 58 is -782.42", "a": 166.51, "b": 180, "c": 58, "op1": "-", "op2": "*", "result": -782.42}
{"question": "Solve: (162.5 / 6) * 59", "answer": "The result of (162.5 / 6) * 59 is 1597.92", "a": 162.5, "b": 6, "c": 59, "op1": "/", "op2": "*", "result": 1597.92}
{"question": "Solve: (170 / 170) - 70", "answer": "The result of (170 / 170) - 70 is -69.0", "a": 170, "b": 170, "c": 70, "op1": "/", "op2": "-", "result": -69.0}
{"question": "Solve: (166 * 171) - 33.68", "answer": "The result of (166 * 171) - 33.68 is 28352.32", "a": 166, "b": 171, "c": 33.68, "op1": "*", "op2": "-", "result": 28352.32}
{"question": "Solve: (134 * 69) * 108", "answer": "The result of (134 * 69) * 108 is 998568", "a": 134, "b": 69, "c": 108, "op1": "*", "op2": "*", "result": 998568}
{"question": "Solve: (28 - 149) * 11.46", "answer": "The result of (28 - 149) * 11.46 is -1386.66", "a": 28, "b": 149, "c": 11.46, "op1": "-", "op2": "*", "result": -1386.66}
{"question": "Solve: (69 - 133.59) * 57", "answer": "The result of (69 - 133.59) * 57 is -3681.63", "a": 69, "b": 133.59, "c": 57, "op1": "-", "op2": "*", "result": -3681.63}
{"question": "Solve: (123.46 - 50) + 85", "answer": "The result of (123.46 - 50) + 85 is 158.46", "a": 123.46, "b": 50, "c": 85, "op1": "-", "op2": "+", "result": 158.46}
{"question": "Solve: (155.24 * 177) + 14.91", "answer": "The result of (155.24 * 177) + 14.91 is 27492.39", "a": 155.24, "b": 177, "c": 14.91, "op1": "*", "op2": "+", "result": 27492.39}
{"question": "Solve: (187 / 76.84) + 183", "answer": "The result of (187 / 76.84) + 183 is 185.43", "a": 187, "b": 76.84, "c": 183, "op1": "/", "op2": "+", "result": 185.43}
{"question": "Solve: (56 - 153) + 171", "answer": "The result of (56 - 153) + 171 is 74", "a": 56, "b": 153, "c": 171, "op1": "-", "op2": "+", "result": 74}
{"question": "Solve: (119 + 38) + 150", "answer": "The result of (119 + 38) + 150 is 307", "a": 119, "b": 38, "c": 150, "op1": "+", "op2": "+", "result": 307}
{"question": "Solve: (53.43 - 153) - 35", "answer": "The result of (53.43 - 153) - 35 is -134.57", "a": 53.43, "b": 153, "c": 35, "op1": "-", "op2": "-", "result": -134.57}
{"question": "Solve: (177 + 155) - 54", "answer": "The result of (177 + 155) - 54 is 278", "a": 177, "b": 155, "c": 54, "op1": "+", "op2": "-", "result": 278}
{"question": "Solve: (85.28 * 90.32) - 108.91", "answer": "The result of (85.28 * 90.32) - 108.91 is 7593.58", "a": 85.28, "b": 90.32, "c": 108.91, "op1": "*", "op2": "-", "result": 7593.58}
{"question": "Solve: (66 * 126.92) * 38.48", "answer": "The result of (66 * 126.92) * 38.48 is 322336.19", "a": 66, "b": 126.92, "c": 38.48, "op1": "*", "op2": "*", "result": 322336.19}
{"question": "Solve: (191 + 191) * 73", "answer": "The result of (191 + 191) * 73 is 27886", "a": 191, "b": 191, "c": 73, "op1": "+", "op2": "*", "result": 27886}
{"question": "Solve: (46 * 84) + 116", "answer": "The result of (46 * 84) + 116 is 3980", "a": 46, "b": 84, "c": 116, "op1": "*", "op2": "+", "result": 3980}
{"question": "Solve: (174 - 44.78) * 133.0", "answer": "The result of (174 - 44.78) * 133.0 is 17186.26", "a": 174, "b": 44.78, "c": 133.0, "op1": "-", "op2": "*", "result": 17186.26}
{"question": "Solve: (191 + 115) * 127", "answer": "The result of (191 + 115) * 127 is 38862", "a": 191, "b": 115, "c": 127, "op1": "+", "op2": "*", "result": 38862}
{"question": "Solve: (96 + 93) + 192", "answer": "The result of (96 + 93) + 192 is 381", "a": 96, "b": 93, "c": 192, "op1": "+", "op2": "+", "result": 381}
{"question": "Solve: (57 - 39) * 33", "answer": "The result of (57 - 39) * 33 is 594", "a": 57, "b": 39, "c": 33, "op1": "-", "op2": "*", "result": 594}
{"question": "Solve: (30 + 22.47) * 172", "answer": "The result of (30 + 22.47) * 172 is 9024.84", "a": 30, "b": 22.47, "c": 172, "op1": "+", "op2": "*", "result": 9024.84}
{"question": "Solve: (21 * 79) + 113", "answer": "The result of (21 * 79) + 113 is 1772", "a": 21, "b": 79, "c": 113, "op1": "*", "op2": "+", "result": 1772}
{"question": "Solve: (30 - 162.46) - 145.15", "answer": "The result of (30 - 162.46) - 145.15 is -277.61", "a": 30, "b": 162.46, "c": 145.15, "op1": "-", "op2": "-", "result": -277.61}
{"question": "Solve: (83 / 45.74) + 174.53", "answer": "The result of (83 / 45.74) + 174.53 is 176.34", "a": 83, "b": 45.74, "c": 174.53, "op1": "/", "op2": "+", "result": 176.34}
{"question": "Solve: (145 * 170.13) + 59", "answer": "The result of (145 * 170.13) + 59 is 24727.85", "a": 145, "b": 170.13, "c": 59, "op1": "*", "op2": "+", "result": 24727.85}
{"question": "Solve: (96 - 149.45) / 33", "answer": "The result of (96 - 149.45) / 33 is -1.62", "a": 96, "b": 149.45, "c": 33, "op1": "-", "op2": "/", "result": -1.62}
{"question": "Solve: (24 - 1) / 172.97", "answer": "The result of (24 - 1) / 172.97 is 0.13", "a": 24, "b": 1, "c": 172.97, "op1": "-", "op2": "/", "result": 0.13}
{"question": "Solve: (73 - 142.36) * 186", "answer": "The result of (73 - 142.36) * 186 is -12900.96", "a": 73, "b": 142.36, "c": 186, "op1": "-", "op2": "*", "result": -12900.96}
{"question": "Solve: (182 - 24) - 109.36", "answer": "The result of (182 - 24) - 109.36 is 48.64", "a": 182, "b": 24, "c": 109.36, "op1": "-", "op2": "-", "result": 48.64}
{"question": "Solve: (99 * 46) + 101", "answer": "The result of (99 * 46) + 101 is 4655", "a": 99, "b": 46, "c": 101, "op1": "*", "op2": "+", "result": 4655}
{"question": "Solve: (199 * 11.59) - 67", "answer": "The result of (199 * 11.59) - 67 is 2239.41", "a": 199, "b": 11.59, "c": 67, "op1": "*", "op2": "-", "result": 2239.41}
{"question": "Solve: (86 + 195) - 116", "answer": "The result of (86 + 195) - 116 is 165", "a": 86, "b": 195, "c": 116, "op1": "+", "op2": "-", "result": 165}
{"question": "Solve: (103 * 105.95) / 144.58", "answer": "The result of (103 * 105.95) / 144.58 is 75.48", "a": 103, "b": 105.95, "c": 144.58, "op1": "*", "op2": "/", "result": 75.48}
{"question": "Solve: (101 * 93) + 8", "answer": "The result of (101 * 93) + 8 is 9401", "a": 101, "b": 93, "c": 8, "op1": "*", "op2": "+", "result": 9401}
{"question": "Solve: (193 - 193.45) + 78", "answer": "The result of (193 - 193.45) + 78 is 77.55", "a": 193, "b": 193.45, "c": 78, "op1": "-", "op2": "+", "result": 77.55}
{"question": "Solve: (197 - 146) / 154", "answer": "The result of (197 - 146) / 154 is 0.33", "a": 197, "b": 146, "c": 154, "op1": "-", "op2": "/", "result": 0.33}
{"question": "Solve: (123.03 * 197) + 26", "answer": "The result of (123.03 * 197) + 26 is 24262.91", "a": 123.03, "b": 197, "c": 26, "op1": "*", "op2": "+", "result": 24262.91}
{"question": "Solve: (129.52 - 151) + 98", "answer": "The result of (129.52 - 151) + 98 is 76.52", "a": 129.52, "b": 151, "c": 98, "op1": "-", "op2": "+", "result": 76.52}
{"question": "Solve: (122 + 41) + 7", "answer": "The result of (122 + 41) + 7 is 170", "a": 122, "b": 41, "c": 7, "op1": "+", "op2": "+", "result": 170}
{"question": "Solve: (34.1 * 63) + 163.23", "answer": "The result of (34.1 * 63) + 163.23 is 2311.53", "a": 34.1, "b": 63, "c": 163.23, "op1": "*", "op2": "+", "result": 2311.53}
{"question": "Solve: (86.72 + 124) - 117", "answer": "The result of (86.72 + 124) - 117 is 93.72", "a": 86.72, "b": 124, "c": 117, "op1": "+", "op2": "-", "result": 93.72}
{"question": "Solve: (88 + 89) - 100", "answer": "The result of (88 + 89) - 100 is 77", "a": 88, "b": 89, "c": 100, "op1": "+", "op2": "-", "result": 77}
{"question": "Solve: (137 + 10) * 141", "answer": "The result of (137 + 10) * 141 is 20727", "a": 137, "b": 10, "c": 141, "op1": "+", "op2": "*", "result": 20727}
{"question": "Solve: (112.19 + 97) + 132", "answer": "The result of (112.19 + 97) + 132 is 341.19", "a": 112.19, "b": 97, "c": 132, "op1": "+", "op2": "+", "result": 341.19}
{"question": "Solve: (57 - 136) - 180", "answer": "The result of (57 - 136) - 180 is -259", "a": 57, "b": 136, "c": 180, "op1": "-", "op2": "-", "result": -259}
{"question": "Solve: (52 - 177.74) / 99", "answer": "The result of (52 - 177.74) / 99 is -1.27", "a": 52, "b": 177.74, "c": 99, "op1": "-", "op2": "/", "result": -1.27}
{"question": "Solve: (162 * 190.02) - 36", "answer": "The result of (162 * 190.02) - 36 is 30747.24", "a": 162, "b": 190.02, "c": 36, "op1": "*", "op2": "-", "result": 30747.24}
{"question": "Solve: (145 / 83) - 179", "answer": "The result of (145 / 83) - 179 is -177.25", "a": 145, "b": 83, "c": 179, "op1": "/", "op2": "-", "result": -177.25}
{"question": "Solve: (176 * 89.7) + 49", "answer": "The result of (176 * 89.7) + 49 is 15836.2", "a": 176, "b": 89.7, "c": 49, "op1": "*", "op2": "+", "result": 15836.2}
{"question": "Solve: (33 * 48) * 191", "answer": "The result of (33 * 48) * 191 is 302544", "a": 33, "b": 48, "c": 191, "op1": "*", "op2": "*", "result": 302544}
{"question": "Solve: (152.99 + 122.19) + 11", "answer": "The result of (152.99 + 122.19) + 11 is 286.18", "a": 152.99, "b": 122.19, "c": 11, "op1": "+", "op2": "+", "result": 286.18}
{"question": "Solve: (27.61 + 186) / 3.87", "answer": "The result of (27.61 + 186) / 3.87 is 55.2", "a": 27.61, "b": 186, "c": 3.87, "op1": "+", "op2": "/", "result": 55.2}
{"question": "Solve: (79 + 124) * 32", "answer": "The result of (79 + 124) * 32 is 6496", "a": 79, "b": 124, "c": 32, "op1": "+", "op2": "*", "result": 6496}
{"question": "Solve: (150 * 75) * 47.94", "answer": "The result of (150 * 75) * 47.94 is 539325.0", "a": 150, "b": 75, "c": 47.94, "op1": "*", "op2": "*", "result": 539325.0}
{"question": "Solve: (189 * 96) + 147.39", "answer": "The result of (189 * 96) + 147.39 is 18291.39", "a": 189, "b": 96, "c": 147.39, "op1": "*", "op2": "+", "result": 18291.39}
{"question": "Solve: (137 * 72) - 3", "answer": "The result of (137 * 72) - 3 is 9861", "a": 137, "b": 72, "c": 3, "op1": "*", "op2": "-", "result": 9861}
{"question": "Solve: (79 + 137) - 36", "answer": "The result of (79 + 137) - 36 is 180", "a": 79, "b": 137, "c": 36, "op1": "+", "op2": "-", "result": 180}
{"question": "Solve: (99 * 106) * 74", "answer": "The result of (99 * 106) * 74 is 776556", "a": 99, "b": 106, "c": 74, "op1": "*", "op2": "*", "result": 776556}
{"question": "Solve: (187.84 * 36) * 195", "answer": "The result of (187.84 * 36) * 195 is 1318636.8", "a": 187.84, "b": 36, "c": 195, "op1": "*", "op2": "*", "result": 1318636.8}
{"question": "Solve: (6 * 79) / 42", "answer": "The result of (6 * 79) / 42 is 11.29", "a": 6, "b": 79, "c": 42, "op1": "*", "op2": "/", "result": 11.29}
{"question": "Solve: (103 + 122) - 183", "answer": "The result of (103 + 122) - 183 is 42", "a": 103, "b": 122, "c": 183, "op1": "+", "op2": "-", "result": 42}
{"question": "Solve: (74 * 33.54) * 151", "answer": "The result of (74 * 33.54) * 151 is 374775.96", "a": 74, "b": 33.54, "c": 151, "op1": "*", "op2": "*", "result": 374775.96}
{"question": "Solve: (75 - 145) * 188", "answer": "The result of (75 - 145) * 188 is -13160", "a": 75, "b": 145, "c": 188, "op1": "-", "op2": "*", "result": -13160}
{"question": "Solve: (165 - 45.93) - 3.53", "answer": "The result of (165 - 45.93) - 3.53 is 115.54", "a": 165, "b": 45.93, "c": 3.53, "op1": "-", "op2": "-", "result": 115.54}
{"question": "Solve: (67 - 34) * 37", "answer": "The result of (67 - 34) * 37 is 1221", "a": 67, "b": 34, "c": 37, "op1": "-", "op2": "*", "result": 1221}
{"question": "Solve: (41 - 79) + 117", "answer": "The result of (41 - 79) + 117 is 79", "a": 41, "b": 79, "c": 117, "op1": "-", "op2": "+", "result": 79}
{"question": "Solve: (120.95 / 12) + 39", "answer": "The result of (120.95 / 12) + 39 is 49.08", "a": 120.95, "b": 12, "c": 39, "op1": "/", "op2": "+", "result": 49.08}
{"question": "Solve: (32.58 + 93) - 125", "answer": "The result of (32.58 + 93) - 125 is 0.58", "a": 32.58, "b": 93, "c": 125, "op1": "+", "op2": "-", "result": 0.58}
{"question": "Solve: (139.77 - 175) / 125.56", "answer": "The result of (139.77 - 175) / 125.56 is -0.28", "a": 139.77, "b": 175, "c": 125.56, "op1": "-", "op2": "/", "result": -0.28}
{"question": "Solve: (128.34 + 167) - 102", "answer": "The result of (128.34 + 167) - 102 is 193.34", "a": 128.34, "b": 167, "c": 102, "op1": "+", "op2": "-", "result": 193.34}
{"question": "Solve: (82 - 73) + 71", "answer": "The result of (82 - 73) + 71 is 80", "a": 82, "b": 73, "c": 71, "op1": "-", "op2": "+", "result": 80}
{"question": "Solve: (138 - 95) + 28", "answer": "The result of (138 - 95) + 28 is 71", "a": 138, "b": 95, "c": 28, "op1": "-", "op2": "+", "result": 71}
{"question": "Solve: (120.94 - 194.97) * 200", "answer": "The result of (120.94 - 194.97) * 200 is -14806.0", "a": 120.94, "b": 194.97, "c": 200, "op1": "-", "op2": "*", "result": -14806.0}
{"question": "Solve: (68.36 - 63) - 15", "answer": "The result of (68.36 - 63) - 15 is -9.64", "a": 68.36, "b": 63, "c": 15, "op1": "-", "op2": "-", "result": -9.64}
{"question": "Solve: (125.89 - 134) - 126", "answer": "The result of (125.89 - 134) - 126 is -134.11", "a": 125.89, "b": 134, "c": 126, "op1": "-", "op2": "-", "result": -134.11}
{"question": "Solve: (27 + 95) * 40.77", "answer": "The result of (27 + 95) * 40.77 is 4973.94", "a": 27, "b": 95, "c": 40.77, "op1": "+", "op2": "*", "result": 4973.94}
{"question": "Solve: (119.04 - 73) / 37", "answer": "The result of (119.04 - 73) / 37 is 1.24", "a": 119.04, "b": 73, "c": 37, "op1": "-", "op2": "/", "result": 1.24}
{"question": "Solve: (161 / 176.31) + 78.94", "answer": "The result of (161 / 176.31) + 78.94 is 79.85", "a": 161, "b": 176.31, "c": 78.94, "op1": "/", "op2": "+", "result": 79.85}
{"question": "Solve: (103 * 153) + 102", "answer": "The result of (103 * 153) + 102 is 15861", "a": 103, "b": 153, "c": 102, "op1": "*", "op2": "+", "result": 15861}
{"question": "Solve: (177 / 139.0) - 104", "answer": "The result of (177 / 139.0) - 104 is -102.73", "a": 177, "b": 139.0, "c": 104, "op1": "/", "op2": "-", "result": -102.73}
{"question": "Solve: (22 * 110) * 65", "answer": "The result of (22 * 110) * 65 is 157300", "a": 22, "b": 110, "c": 65, "op1": "*", "op2": "*", "result": 157300}
{"question": "Solve: (115 - 188) - 60.47", "answer": "The result of (115 - 188) - 60.47 is -133.47", "a": 115, "b": 188, "c": 60.47, "op1": "-", "op2": "-", "result": -133.47}
{"question": "Solve: (79 + 8.48) + 83", "answer": "The result of (79 + 8.48) + 83 is 170.48", "a": 79, "b": 8.48, "c": 83, "op1": "+", "op2": "+", "result": 170.48}
{"question": "Solve: (31.59 - 47.78) + 63", "answer": "The result of (31.59 - 47.78) + 63 is 46.81", "a": 31.59, "b": 47.78, "c": 63, "op1": "-", "op2": "+", "result": 46.81}
{"question": "Solve: (50 * 199) * 175", "answer": "The result of (50 * 199) * 175 is 1741250", "a": 50, "b": 199, "c": 175, "op1": "*", "op2": "*", "result": 1741250}
{"question": "Solve: (45 + 131) * 19", "answer": "The result of (45 + 131) * 19 is 3344", "a": 45, "b": 131, "c": 19, "op1": "+", "op2": "*", "result": 3344}
{"question": "Solve: (72 - 24) * 174.25", "answer": "The result of (72 - 24) * 174.25 is 8364.0", "a": 72, "b": 24, "c": 174.25, "op1": "-", "op2": "*", "result": 8364.0}
{"question": "Solve: (190 * 188) * 191", "answer": "The result of (190 * 188) * 191 is 6822520", "a": 190, "b": 188, "c": 191, "op1": "*", "op2": "*", "result": 6822520}
{"question": "Solve: (90 * 194.06) - 186", "answer": "The result of (90 * 194.06) - 186 is 17279.4", "a": 90, "b": 194.06, "c": 186, "op1": "*", "op2": "-", "result": 17279.4}
{"question": "Solve: (151 / 179.86) / 128", "answer": "The result of (151 / 179.86) / 128 is 0.01", "a": 151, "b": 179.86, "c": 128, "op1": "/", "op2": "/", "result": 0.01}
{"question": "Solve: (175 - 185) / 108", "answer": "The result of (175 - 185) / 108 is -0.09", "a": 175, "b": 185, "c": 108, "op1": "-", "op2": "/", "result": -0.09}
{"question": "Solve: (161 * 130) - 103", "answer": "The result of (161 * 130) - 103 is 20827", "a": 161, "b": 130, "c": 103, "op1": "*", "op2": "-", "result": 20827}
{"question": "Solve: (57 - 58) * 189", "answer": "The result of (57 - 58) * 189 is -189", "a": 57, "b": 58, "c": 189, "op1": "-", "op2": "*", "result": -189}
{"question": "Solve: (17 * 64) - 128", "answer": "The result of (17 * 64) - 128 is 960", "a": 17, "b": 64, "c": 128, "op1": "*", "op2": "-", "result": 960}
{"question": "Solve: (20 + 117) - 96", "answer": "The result of (20 + 117) - 96 is 41", "a": 20, "b": 117, "c": 96, "op1": "+", "op2": "-", "result": 41}
{"question": "Solve: (74 + 22) + 123", "answer": "The result of (74 + 22) + 123 is 219", "a": 74, "b": 22, "c": 123, "op1": "+", "op2": "+", "result": 219}
{"question": "Solve: (60 / 69) / 48.97", "answer": "The result of (60 / 69) / 48.97 is 0.02", "a": 60, "b": 69, "c": 48.97, "op1": "/", "op2": "/", "result": 0.02}
{"question": "Solve: (128 / 67) * 52", "answer": "The result of (128 / 67) * 52 is 99.34", "a": 128, "b": 67, "c": 52, "op1": "/", "op2": "*", "result": 99.34}
{"question": "Solve: (157.44 + 70.23) + 188", "answer": "The result of (157.44 + 70.23) + 188 is 415.67", "a": 157.44, "b": 70.23, "c": 188, "op1": "+", "op2": "+", "result": 415.67}
{"question": "Solve: (27.51 - 9.72) / 92", "answer": "The result of (27.51 - 9.72) / 92 is 0.19", "a": 27.51, "b": 9.72, "c": 92, "op1": "-", "op2": "/", "result": 0.19}
{"question": "Solve: (57 - 165.3) - 139", "answer": "The result of (57 - 165.3) - 139 is -247.3", "a": 57, "b": 165.3, "c": 139, "op1": "-", "op2": "-", "result": -247.3}
{"question": "Solve: (15 / 71) + 20.24", "answer": "The result of (15 / 71) + 20.24 is 20.45", "a": 15, "b": 71, "c": 20.24, "op1": "/", "op2": "+", "result": 20.45}
{"question": "Solve: (105 * 169) - 33", "answer": "The result of (105 * 169) - 33 is 17712", "a": 105, "b": 169, "c": 33, "op1": "*", "op2": "-", "result": 17712}
{"question": "Solve: (88 * 163) * 140.97", "answer": "The result of (88 * 163) * 140.97 is 2022073.68", "a": 88, "b": 163, "c": 140.97, "op1": "*", "op2": "*", "result": 2022073.68}
{"question": "Solve: (40.14 - 155) - 164", "answer": "The result of (40.14 - 155) - 164 is -278.86", "a": 40.14, "b": 155, "c": 164, "op1": "-", "op2": "-", "result": -278.86}
{"question": "Solve: (152 - 167) + 8", "answer": "The result of (152 - 167) + 8 is -7", "a": 152, "b": 167, "c": 8, "op1": "-", "op2": "+", "result": -7}
{"question": "Solve: (139.49 - 30) * 152", "answer": "The result of (139.49 - 30) * 152 is 16642.48", "a": 139.49, "b": 30, "c": 152, "op1": "-", "op2": "*", "result": 16642.48}
{"question": "Solve: (48 - 137.87) / 60.65", "answer": "The result of (48 - 137.87) / 60.65 is -1.48", "a": 48, "b": 137.87, "c": 60.65, "op1": "-", "op2": "/", "result": -1.48}
{"question": "Solve: (188.42 + 197.5) * 38", "answer": "The result of (188.42 + 197.5) * 38 is 14664.96", "a": 188.42, "b": 197.5, "c": 38, "op1": "+", "op2": "*", "result": 14664.96}
{"question": "Solve: (57 + 17) + 63", "answer": "The result of (57 + 17) + 63 is 137", "a": 57, "b": 17, "c": 63, "op1": "+", "op2": "+", "result": 137}
{"question": "Solve: (7 - 74) - 10", "answer": "The result of (7 - 74) - 10 is -77", "a": 7, "b": 74, "c": 10, "op1": "-", "op2": "-", "result": -77}
{"question": "Solve: (143 - 109) * 147", "answer": "The result of (143 - 109) * 147 is 4998", "a": 143, "b": 109, "c": 147, "op1": "-", "op2": "*", "result": 4998}
{"question": "Solve: (91 + 155) - 4.81", "answer": "The result of (91 + 155) - 4.81 is 241.19", "a": 91, "b": 155, "c": 4.81, "op1": "+", "op2": "-", "result": 241.19}
{"question": "Solve: (20 + 196) * 146.8", "answer": "The result of (20 + 196) * 146.8 is 31708.8", "a": 20, "b": 196, "c": 146.8, "op1": "+", "op2": "*", "result": 31708.8}
{"question": "Solve: (64 - 60) / 20", "answer": "The result of (64 - 60) / 20 is 0.2", "a": 64, "b": 60, "c": 20, "op1": "-", "op2": "/", "result": 0.2}
{"question": "Solve: (117 - 57) * 99", "answer": "The result of (117 - 57) * 99 is 5940", "a": 117, "b": 57, "c": 99, "op1": "-", "op2": "*", "result": 5940}
{"question": "Solve: (108.92 - 178.68) / 169", "answer": "The result of (108.92 - 178.68) / 169 is -0.41", "a": 108.92, "b": 178.68, "c": 169, "op1": "-", "op2": "/", "result": -0.41}
{"question": "Solve: (7.9 * 100) - 69.89", "answer": "The result of (7.9 * 100) - 69.89 is 720.11", "a": 7.9, "b": 100, "c": 69.89, "op1": "*", "op2": "-", "result": 720.11}
{"question": "Solve: (198 + 21) + 117", "answer": "The result of (198 + 21) + 117 is 336", "a": 198, "b": 21, "c": 117, "op1": "+", "op2": "+", "result": 336}
{"question": "Solve: (111 + 71) - 130", "answer": "The result of (111 + 71) - 130 is 52", "a": 111, "b": 71, "c": 130, "op1": "+", "op2": "-", "result": 52}
{"question": "Solve: (120 - 116.19) * 63.83", "answer": "The result of (120 - 116.19) * 63.83 is 243.19", "a": 120, "b": 116.19, "c": 63.83, "op1": "-", "op2": "*", "result": 243.19}
{"question": "Solve: (66 + 162.12) * 140.5", "answer": "The result of (66 + 162.12) * 140.5 is 32050.86", "a": 66, "b": 162.12, "c": 140.5, "op1": "+", "op2": "*", "result": 32050.86}
{"question": "Solve: (129 - 90.9) - 79", "answer": "The result of (129 - 90.9) - 79 is -40.9", "a": 129, "b": 90.9, "c": 79, "op1": "-", "op2": "-", "result": -40.9}
{"question": "Solve: (80.44 * 52) - 178", "answer": "The result of (80.44 * 52) - 178 is 4004.88", "a": 80.44, "b": 52, "c": 178, "op1": "*", "op2": "-", "result": 4004.88}
{"question": "Solve: (135 + 120) * 79", "answer": "The result of (135 + 120) * 79 is 20145", "a": 135, "b": 120, "c": 79, "op1": "+", "op2": "*", "result": 20145}
{"question": "Solve: (200 / 77) + 113", "answer": "The result of (200 / 77) + 113 is 115.6", "a": 200, "b": 77, "c": 113, "op1": "/", "op2": "+", "result": 115.6}
{"question": "Solve: (80 - 30.2) - 192", "answer": "The result of (80 - 30.2) - 192 is -142.2", "a": 80, "b": 30.2, "c": 192, "op1": "-", "op2": "-", "result": -142.2}
{"question": "Solve: (166.17 - 64.37) + 40", "answer": "The result of (166.17 - 64.37) + 40 is 141.8", "a": 166.17, "b": 64.37, "c": 40, "op1": "-", "op2": "+", "result": 141.8}
{"question": "Solve: (39 + 49) / 157", "answer": "The result of (39 + 49) / 157 is 0.56", "a": 39, "b": 49, "c": 157, "op1": "+", "op2": "/", "result": 0.56}
{"question": "Solve: (71 * 59) - 68.58", "answer": "The result of (71 * 59) - 68.58 is 4120.42", "a": 71, "b": 59, "c": 68.58, "op1": "*", "op2": "-", "result": 4120.42}
{"question": "Solve: (101 - 91.36) + 92", "answer": "The result of (101 - 91.36) + 92 is 101.64", "a": 101, "b": 91.36, "c": 92, "op1": "-", "op2": "+", "result": 101.64}
{"question": "Solve: (94 + 13) * 7", "answer": "The result of (94 + 13) * 7 is 749", "a": 94, "b": 13, "c": 7, "op1": "+", "op2": "*", "result": 749}
{"question": "Solve: (76 - 71) / 193", "answer": "The result of (76 - 71) / 193 is 0.03", "a": 76, "b": 71, "c": 193, "op1": "-", "op2": "/", "result": 0.03}
{"question": "Solve: (175 + 69) * 169", "answer": "The result of (175 + 69) * 169 is 41236", "a": 175, "b": 69, "c": 169, "op1": "+", "op2": "*", "result": 41236}
{"question": "Solve: (32 * 81.2) * 74", "answer": "The result of (32 * 81.2) * 74 is 192281.6", "a": 32, "b": 81.2, "c": 74, "op1": "*", "op2": "*", "result": 192281.6}
{"question": "Solve: (122.33 - 174) * 125.6", "answer": "The result of (122.33 - 174) * 125.6 is -6489.75", "a": 122.33, "b": 174, "c": 125.6, "op1": "-", "op2": "*", "result": -6489.75}
{"question": "Solve: (156 / 35) / 194", "answer": "The result of (156 / 35) / 194 is 0.02", "a": 156, "b": 35, "c": 194, "op1": "/", "op2": "/", "result": 0.02}
{"question": "Solve: (20 - 199.12) - 94.56", "answer": "The result of (20 - 199.12) - 94.56 is -273.68", "a": 20, "b": 199.12, "c": 94.56, "op1": "-", "op2": "-", "result": -273.68}
{"question": "Solve: (140.59 + 69) - 174.82", "answer": "The result of (140.59 + 69) - 174.82 is 34.77", "a": 140.59, "b": 69, "c": 174.82, "op1": "+", "op2": "-", "result": 34.77}
{"question": "Solve: (30 / 129) + 185.79", "answer": "The result of (30 / 129) + 185.79 is 186.02", "a": 30, "b": 129, "c": 185.79, "op1": "/", "op2": "+", "result": 186.02}
{"question": "Solve: (38.59 + 182.54) * 129", "answer": "The result of (38.59 + 182.54) * 129 is 28525.77", "a": 38.59, "b": 182.54, "c": 129, "op1": "+", "op2": "*", "result": 28525.77}
{"question": "Solve: (14 * 86) * 111.93", "answer": "The result of (14 * 86) * 111.93 is 134763.72", "a": 14, "b": 86, "c": 111.93, "op1": "*", "op2": "*", "result": 134763.72}
{"question": "Solve: (161.55 * 11) - 107", "answer": "The result of (161.55 * 11) - 107 is 1670.05", "a": 161.55, "b": 11, "c": 107, "op1": "*", "op2": "-", "result": 1670.05}
{"question": "Solve: (187 + 65.22) * 38", "answer": "The result of (187 + 65.22) * 38 is 9584.36", "a": 187, "b": 65.22, "c": 38, "op1": "+", "op2": "*", "result": 9584.36}
{"question": "Solve: (56.59 * 73) / 58", "answer": "The result of (56.59 * 73) / 58 is 71.23", "a": 56.59, "b": 73, "c": 58, "op1": "*", "op2": "/", "result": 71.23}
{"question": "Solve: (164 - 64) * 186.25", "answer": "The result of (164 - 64) * 186.25 is 18625.0", "a": 164, "b": 64, "c": 186.25, "op1": "-", "op2": "*", "result": 18625.0}
{"question": "Solve: (11 - 161) + 24", "answer": "The result of (11 - 161) + 24 is -126", "a": 11, "b": 161, "c": 24, "op1": "-", "op2": "+", "result": -126}
{"question": "Solve: (21.64 + 13) * 38.55", "answer": "The result of (21.64 + 13) * 38.55 is 1335.37", "a": 21.64, "b": 13, "c": 38.55, "op1": "+", "op2": "*", "result": 1335.37}
{"question": "Solve: (193 / 54) - 30", "answer": "The result of (193 / 54) - 30 is -26.43", "a": 193, "b": 54, "c": 30, "op1": "/", "op2": "-", "result": -26.43}
{"question": "Solve: (153 - 87) + 56", "answer": "The result of (153 - 87) + 56 is 122", "a": 153, "b": 87, "c": 56, "op1": "-", "op2": "+", "result": 122}
{"question": "Solve: (90.13 + 118) - 99", "answer": "The result of (90.13 + 118) - 99 is 109.13", "a": 90.13, "b": 118, "c": 99, "op1": "+", "op2": "-", "result": 109.13}
{"question": "Solve: (196 / 102) + 187", "answer": "The result of (196 / 102) + 187 is 188.92", "a": 196, "b": 102, "c": 187, "op1": "/", "op2": "+", "result": 188.92}
{"question": "Solve: (144.91 / 171) * 109", "answer": "The result of (144.91 / 171) * 109 is 92.37", "a": 144.91, "b": 171, "c": 109, "op1": "/", "op2": "*", "result": 92.37}
{"question": "Solve: (129 - 165) / 101.09", "answer": "The result of (129 - 165) / 101.09 is -0.36", "a": 129, "b": 165, "c": 101.09, "op1": "-", "op2": "/", "result": -0.36}
{"question": "Solve: (166 - 8) - 151.6", "answer": "The result of (166 - 8) - 151.6 is 6.4", "a": 166, "b": 8, "c": 151.6, "op1": "-", "op2": "-", "result": 6.4}
{"question": "Solve: (29.82 - 39) + 180", "answer": "The result of (29.82 - 39) + 180 is 170.82", "a": 29.82, "b": 39, "c": 180, "op1": "-", "op2": "+", "result": 170.82}
{"question": "Solve: (108 * 118) / 79", "answer": "The result of (108 * 118) / 79 is 161.32", "a": 108, "b": 118, "c": 79, "op1": "*", "op2": "/", "result": 161.32}
{"question": "Solve: (63 + 171.54) - 89.33", "answer": "The result of (63 + 171.54) - 89.33 is 145.21", "a": 63, "b": 171.54, "c": 89.33, "op1": "+", "op2": "-", "result": 145.21}
{"question": "Solve: (171 + 186) - 117", "answer": "The result of (171 + 186) - 117 is 240", "a": 171, "b": 186, "c": 117, "op1": "+", "op2": "-", "result": 240}
{"question": "Solve: (168 + 29.08) * 66", "answer": "The result of (168 + 29.08) * 66 is 13007.28", "a": 168, "b": 29.08, "c": 66, "op1": "+", "op2": "*", "result": 13007.28}
{"question": "Solve: (63.87 * 182) * 158", "answer": "The result of (63.87 * 182) * 158 is 1836645.72", "a": 63.87, "b": 182, "c": 158, "op1": "*", "op2": "*", "result": 1836645.72}
{"question": "Solve: (28 - 16.76) + 111.8", "answer": "The result of (28 - 16.76) + 111.8 is 123.04", "a": 28, "b": 16.76, "c": 111.8, "op1": "-", "op2": "+", "result": 123.04}
{"question": "Solve: (77.56 + 5) / 122", "answer": "The result of (77.56 + 5) / 122 is 0.68", "a": 77.56, "b": 5, "c": 122, "op1": "+", "op2": "/", "result": 0.68}
{"question": "Solve: (102 + 109.89) * 69", "answer": "The result of (102 + 109.89) * 69 is 14620.41", "a": 102, "b": 109.89, "c": 69, "op1": "+", "op2": "*", "result": 14620.41}
{"question": "Solve: (48 / 4) + 183.51", "answer": "The result of (48 / 4) + 183.51 is 195.51", "a": 48, "b": 4, "c": 183.51, "op1": "/", "op2": "+", "result": 195.51}
{"question": "Solve: (9 * 117) - 10.3", "answer": "The result of (9 * 117) - 10.3 is 1042.7", "a": 9, "b": 117, "c": 10.3, "op1": "*", "op2": "-", "result": 1042.7}
{"question": "Solve: (166 - 58) + 100.23", "answer": "The result of (166 - 58) + 100.23 is 208.23", "a": 166, "b": 58, "c": 100.23, "op1": "-", "op2": "+", "result": 208.23}
{"question": "Solve: (107 + 121.24) - 91", "answer": "The result of (107 + 121.24) - 91 is 137.24", "a": 107, "b": 121.24, "c": 91, "op1": "+", "op2": "-", "result": 137.24}
{"question": "Solve: (25 / 28) - 19.98", "answer": "The result of (25 / 28) - 19.98 is -19.09", "a": 25, "b": 28, "c": 19.98, "op1": "/", "op2": "-", "result": -19.09}
{"question": "Solve: (135.21 + 169.66) - 18", "answer": "The result of (135.21 + 169.66) - 18 is 286.87", "a": 135.21, "b": 169.66, "c": 18, "op1": "+", "op2": "-", "result": 286.87}
{"question": "Solve: (51 + 189) + 177.22", "answer": "The result of (51 + 189) + 177.22 is 417.22", "a": 51, "b": 189, "c": 177.22, "op1": "+", "op2": "+", "result": 417.22}
{"question": "Solve: (57.93 - 87) - 124.73", "answer": "The result of (57.93 - 87) - 124.73 is -153.8", "a": 57.93, "b": 87, "c": 124.73, "op1": "-", "op2": "-", "result": -153.8}
{"question": "Solve: (67 * 112.18) + 84", "answer": "The result of (67 * 112.18) + 84 is 7600.06", "a": 67, "b": 112.18, "c": 84, "op1": "*", "op2": "+", "result": 7600.06}
{"question": "Solve: (199 / 196) + 107", "answer": "The result of (199 / 196) + 107 is 108.02", "a": 199, "b": 196, "c": 107, "op1": "/", "op2": "+", "result": 108.02}
{"question": "Solve: (189 * 73) + 136.81", "answer": "The result of (189 * 73) + 136.81 is 13933.81", "a": 189, "b": 73, "c": 136.81, "op1": "*", "op2": "+", "result": 13933.81}
{"question": "Solve: (191 * 43) / 148", "answer": "The result of (191 * 43) / 148 is 55.49", "a": 191, "b": 43, "c": 148, "op1": "*", "op2": "/", "result": 55.49}
{"question": "Solve: (95.65 - 15) * 150", "answer": "The result of (95.65 - 15) * 150 is 12097.5", "a": 95.65, "b": 15, "c": 150, "op1": "-", "op2": "*", "result": 12097.5}
{"question": "Solve: (13 - 155) * 58", "answer": "The result of (13 - 155) * 58 is -8236", "a": 13, "b": 155, "c": 58, "op1": "-", "op2": "*", "result": -8236}
{"question": "Solve: (141 * 182.89) * 25.93", "answer": "The result of (141 * 182.89) * 25.93 is 668669.62", "a": 141, "b": 182.89, "c": 25.93, "op1": "*", "op2": "*", "result": 668669.62}
{"question": "Solve: (36 / 81) / 56.75", "answer": "The result of (36 / 81) / 56.75 is 0.01", "a": 36, "b": 81, "c": 56.75, "op1": "/", "op2": "/", "result": 0.01}
{"question": "Solve: (172 - 93) / 72", "answer": "The result of (172 - 93) / 72 is 1.1", "a": 172, "b": 93, "c": 72, "op1": "-", "op2": "/", "result": 1.1}
{"question": "Solve: (50 + 183) / 167", "answer": "The result of (50 + 183) / 167 is 1.4", "a": 50, "b": 183, "c": 167, "op1": "+", "op2": "/", "result": 1.4}
{"question": "Solve: (111.71 / 155) * 40", "answer": "The result of (111.71 / 155) * 40 is 28.83", "a": 111.71, "b": 155, "c": 40, "op1": "/", "op2": "*", "result": 28.83}
{"question": "Solve: (7 - 93) + 33", "answer": "The result of (7 - 93) + 33 is -53", "a": 7, "b": 93, "c": 33, "op1": "-", "op2": "+", "result": -53}
{"question": "Solve: (189.21 + 161) + 134.16", "answer": "The result of (189.21 + 161) + 134.16 is 484.37", "a": 189.21, "b": 161, "c": 134.16, "op1": "+", "op2": "+", "result": 484.37}
{"question": "Solve: (131 + 142) + 127", "answer": "The result of (131 + 142) + 127 is 400", "a": 131, "b": 142, "c": 127, "op1": "+", "op2": "+", "result": 400}
{"question": "Solve: (156 - 159) / 89.22", "answer": "The result of (156 - 159) / 89.22 is -0.03", "a": 156, "b": 159, "c": 89.22, "op1": "-", "op2": "/", "result": -0.03}
{"question": "Solve: (92 - 63) + 61", "answer": "The result of (92 - 63) + 61 is 90", "a": 92, "b": 63, "c": 61, "op1": "-", "op2": "+", "result": 90}
{"question": "Solve: (191.98 - 79) + 164", "answer": "The result of (191.98 - 79) + 164 is 276.98", "a": 191.98, "b": 79, "c": 164, "op1": "-", "op2": "+", "result": 276.98}
{"question": "Solve: (195 + 170.09) / 176", "answer": "The result of (195 + 170.09) / 176 is 2.07", "a": 195, "b": 170.09, "c": 176, "op1": "+", "op2": "/", "result": 2.07}
{"question": "Solve: (33 - 80.05) / 159", "answer": "The result of (33 - 80.05) / 159 is -0.3", "a": 33, "b": 80.05, "c": 159, "op1": "-", "op2": "/", "result": -0.3}
{"question": "Solve: (67.77 * 151) / 107", "answer": "The result of (67.77 * 151) / 107 is 95.64", "a": 67.77, "b": 151, "c": 107, "op1": "*", "op2": "/", "result": 95.64}
{"question": "Solve: (185.09 + 22) + 161", "answer": "The result of (185.09 + 22) + 161 is 368.09", "a": 185.09, "b": 22, "c": 161, "op1": "+", "op2": "+", "result": 368.09}
{"question": "Solve: (144 - 48) + 169", "answer": "The result of (144 - 48) + 169 is 265", "a": 144, "b": 48, "c": 169, "op1": "-", "op2": "+", "result": 265}
{"question": "Solve: (190 * 117) + 67.74", "answer": "The result of (190 * 117) + 67.74 is 22297.74", "a": 190, "b": 117, "c": 67.74, "op1": "*", "op2": "+", "result": 22297.74}
{"question": "Solve: (140 + 132) + 64", "answer": "The result of (140 + 132) + 64 is 336", "a": 140, "b": 132, "c": 64, "op1": "+", "op2": "+", "result": 336}
{"question": "Solve: (10 * 88) + 192", "answer": "The result of (10 * 88) + 192 is 1072", "a": 10, "b": 88, "c": 192, "op1": "*", "op2": "+", "result": 1072}
{"question": "Solve: (56 * 81) + 26", "answer": "The result of (56 * 81) + 26 is 4562", "a": 56, "b": 81, "c": 26, "op1": "*", "op2": "+", "result": 4562}
{"question": "Solve: (42 * 169) * 116", "answer": "The result of (42 * 169) * 116 is 823368", "a": 42, "b": 169, "c": 116, "op1": "*", "op2": "*", "result": 823368}
{"question": "Solve: (138 + 122) - 112.51", "answer": "The result of (138 + 122) - 112.51 is 147.49", "a": 138, "b": 122, "c": 112.51, "op1": "+", "op2": "-", "result": 147.49}
{"question": "Solve: (194 + 28) + 123.95", "answer": "The result of (194 + 28) + 123.95 is 345.95", "a": 194, "b": 28, "c": 123.95, "op1": "+", "op2": "+", "result": 345.95}
{"question": "Solve: (38.47 + 60) * 148", "answer": "The result of (38.47 + 60) * 148 is 14573.56", "a": 38.47, "b": 60, "c": 148, "op1": "+", "op2": "*", "result": 14573.56}
{"question": "Solve: (143 + 157.23) + 103", "answer": "The result of (143 + 157.23) + 103 is 403.23", "a": 143, "b": 157.23, "c": 103, "op1": "+", "op2": "+", "result": 403.23}
{"question": "Solve: (178 + 90) + 3", "answer": "The result of (178 + 90) + 3 is 271", "a": 178, "b": 90, "c": 3, "op1": "+", "op2": "+", "result": 271}
{"question": "Solve: (147 + 153) + 158", "answer": "The result of (147 + 153) + 158 is 458", "a": 147, "b": 153, "c": 158, "op1": "+", "op2": "+", "result": 458}
{"question": "Solve: (6.04 + 112.8) / 113", "answer": "The result of (6.04 + 112.8) / 113 is 1.05", "a": 6.04, "b": 112.8, "c": 113, "op1": "+", "op2": "/", "result": 1.05}
{"question": "Solve: (95.18 + 97) / 146", "answer": "The result of (95.18 + 97) / 146 is 1.32", "a": 95.18, "b": 97, "c": 146, "op1": "+", "op2": "/", "result": 1.32}
{"question": "Solve: (84 + 178) - 20", "answer": "The result of (84 + 178) - 20 is 242", "a": 84, "b": 178, "c": 20, "op1": "+", "op2": "-", "result": 242}
{"question": "Solve: (85 * 14) * 136.26", "answer": "The result of (85 * 14) * 136.26 is 162149.4", "a": 85, "b": 14, "c": 136.26, "op1": "*", "op2": "*", "result": 162149.4}
{"question": "Solve: (106 + 41) - 53", "answer": "The result of (106 + 41) - 53 is 94", "a": 106, "b": 41, "c": 53, "op1": "+", "op2": "-", "result": 94}
{"question": "Solve: (181 + 11) - 134", "answer": "The result of (181 + 11) - 134 is 58", "a": 181, "b": 11, "c": 134, "op1": "+", "op2": "-", "result": 58}
{"question": "Solve: (97 - 86.29) - 172.83", "answer": "The result of (97 - 86.29) - 172.83 is -162.12", "a": 97, "b": 86.29, "c": 172.83, "op1": "-", "op2": "-", "result": -162.12}
{"question": "Solve: (172 / 69) * 77", "answer": "The result of (172 / 69) * 77 is 191.94", "a": 172, "b": 69, "c": 77, "op1": "/", "op2": "*", "result": 191.94}
{"question": "Solve: (164.19 / 158) + 60", "answer": "The result of (164.19 / 158) + 60 is 61.04", "a": 164.19, "b": 158, "c": 60, "op1": "/", "op2": "+", "result": 61.04}
{"question": "Solve: (91 * 149) * 177", "answer": "The result of (91 * 149) * 177 is 2399943", "a": 91, "b": 149, "c": 177, "op1": "*", "op2": "*", "result": 2399943}
{"question": "Solve: (195 + 61.65) * 24", "answer": "The result of (195 + 61.65) * 24 is 6159.6", "a": 195, "b": 61.65, "c": 24, "op1": "+", "op2": "*", "result": 6159.6}
{"question": "Solve: (167 - 43.83) - 109.24", "answer": "The result of (167 - 43.83) - 109.24 is 13.93", "a": 167, "b": 43.83, "c": 109.24, "op1": "-", "op2": "-", "result": 13.93}
{"question": "Solve: (121 + 155.94) - 43", "answer": "The result of (121 + 155.94) - 43 is 233.94", "a": 121, "b": 155.94, "c": 43, "op1": "+", "op2": "-", "result": 233.94}
{"question": "Solve: (76 / 51) * 168", "answer": "The result of (76 / 51) * 168 is 250.35", "a": 76, "b": 51, "c": 168, "op1": "/", "op2": "*", "result": 250.35}
{"question": "Solve: (120.12 + 114) - 190", "answer": "The result of (120.12 + 114) - 190 is 44.12", "a": 120.12, "b": 114, "c": 190, "op1": "+", "op2": "-", "result": 44.12}
{"question": "Solve: (125.62 + 142.05) + 12", "answer": "The result of (125.62 + 142.05) + 12 is 279.67", "a": 125.62, "b": 142.05, "c": 12, "op1": "+", "op2": "+", "result": 279.67}
{"question": "Solve: (154 * 11) + 23", "answer": "The result of (154 * 11) + 23 is 1717", "a": 154, "b": 11, "c": 23, "op1": "*", "op2": "+", "result": 1717}
{"question": "Solve: (102 * 151) / 153.36", "answer": "The result of (102 * 151) / 153.36 is 100.43", "a": 102, "b": 151, "c": 153.36, "op1": "*", "op2": "/", "result": 100.43}
{"question": "Solve: (131 - 159) + 95", "answer": "The result of (131 - 159) + 95 is 67", "a": 131, "b": 159, "c": 95, "op1": "-", "op2": "+", "result": 67}
{"question": "Solve: (167 / 105) + 132.03", "answer": "The result of (167 / 105) + 132.03 is 133.62", "a": 167, "b": 105, "c": 132.03, "op1": "/", "op2": "+", "result": 133.62}
{"question": "Solve: (95 / 132) + 156", "answer": "The result of (95 / 132) + 156 is 156.72", "a": 95, "b": 132, "c": 156, "op1": "/", "op2": "+", "result": 156.72}
{"question": "Solve: (165 * 196.27) - 101", "answer": "The result of (165 * 196.27) - 101 is 32283.55", "a": 165, "b": 196.27, "c": 101, "op1": "*", "op2": "-", "result": 32283.55}
{"question": "Solve: (22 * 180) * 198", "answer": "The result of (22 * 180) * 198 is 784080", "a": 22, "b": 180, "c": 198, "op1": "*", "op2": "*", "result": 784080}
{"question": "Solve: (28 + 137) - 86", "answer": "The result of (28 + 137) - 86 is 79", "a": 28, "b": 137, "c": 86, "op1": "+", "op2": "-", "result": 79}
{"question": "Solve: (63 - 57) / 177.78", "answer": "The result of (63 - 57) / 177.78 is 0.03", "a": 63, "b": 57, "c": 177.78, "op1": "-", "op2": "/", "result": 0.03}
{"question": "Solve: (141 * 189.85) - 111.28", "answer": "The result of (141 * 189.85) - 111.28 is 26657.57", "a": 141, "b": 189.85, "c": 111.28, "op1": "*", "op2": "-", "result": 26657.57}
{"question": "Solve: (68 + 192) - 197.21", "answer": "The result of (68 + 192) - 197.21 is 62.79", "a": 68, "b": 192, "c": 197.21, "op1": "+", "op2": "-", "result": 62.79}
{"question": "Solve: (56.43 + 63) + 19", "answer": "The result of (56.43 + 63) + 19 is 138.43", "a": 56.43, "b": 63, "c": 19, "op1": "+", "op2": "+", "result": 138.43}
{"question": "Solve: (126 / 23) / 10", "answer": "The result of (126 / 23) / 10 is 0.55", "a": 126, "b": 23, "c": 10, "op1": "/", "op2": "/", "result": 0.55}
{"question": "Solve: (185.02 * 148) * 133.0", "answer": "The result of (185.02 * 148) * 133.0 is 3641933.68", "a": 185.02, "b": 148, "c": 133.0, "op1": "*", "op2": "*", "result": 3641933.68}
{"question": "Solve: (145.26 - 197) - 142.51", "answer": "The result of (145.26 - 197) - 142.51 is -194.25", "a": 145.26, "b": 197, "c": 142.51, "op1": "-", "op2": "-", "result": -194.25}
{"question": "Solve: (178.66 / 185) - 192", "answer": "The result of (178.66 / 185) - 192 is -191.03", "a": 178.66, "b": 185, "c": 192, "op1": "/", "op2": "-", "result": -191.03}
{"question": "Solve: (143 - 35) - 30", "answer": "The result of (143 - 35) - 30 is 78", "a": 143, "b": 35, "c": 30, "op1": "-", "op2": "-", "result": 78}
{"question": "Solve: (10 * 108.59) * 59", "answer": "The result of (10 * 108.59) * 59 is 64068.1", "a": 10, "b": 108.59, "c": 59, "op1": "*", "op2": "*", "result": 64068.1}
{"question": "Solve: (48 - 187) - 82", "answer": "The result of (48 - 187) - 82 is -221", "a": 48, "b": 187, "c": 82, "op1": "-", "op2": "-", "result": -221}
{"question": "Solve: (160 - 103) + 170", "answer": "The result of (160 - 103) + 170 is 227", "a": 160, "b": 103, "c": 170, "op1": "-", "op2": "+", "result": 227}
{"question": "Solve: (181 / 73.06) + 181.61", "answer": "The result of (181 / 73.06) + 181.61 is 184.09", "a": 181, "b": 73.06, "c": 181.61, "op1": "/", "op2": "+", "result": 184.09}
{"question": "Solve: (20.3 * 187) * 57.99", "answer": "The result of (20.3 * 187) * 57.99 is 220135.84", "a": 20.3, "b": 187, "c": 57.99, "op1": "*", "op2": "*", "result": 220135.84}
{"question": "Solve: (14 - 137) + 38.65", "answer": "The result of (14 - 137) + 38.65 is -84.35", "a": 14, "b": 137, "c": 38.65, "op1": "-", "op2": "+", "result": -84.35}
{"question": "Solve: (157 / 14) - 134.97", "answer": "The result of (157 / 14) - 134.97 is -123.76", "a": 157, "b": 14, "c": 134.97, "op1": "/", "op2": "-", "result": -123.76}
{"question": "Solve: (66.14 + 148) + 40.32", "answer": "The result of (66.14 + 148) + 40.32 is 254.46", "a": 66.14, "b": 148, "c": 40.32, "op1": "+", "op2": "+", "result": 254.46}
{"question": "Solve: (104 * 6.6) + 150", "answer": "The result of (104 * 6.6) + 150 is 836.4", "a": 104, "b": 6.6, "c": 150, "op1": "*", "op2": "+", "result": 836.4}
{"question": "Solve: (30 / 88) + 157", "answer": "The result of (30 / 88) + 157 is 157.34", "a": 30, "b": 88, "c": 157, "op1": "/", "op2": "+", "result": 157.34}
{"question": "Solve: (84.58 * 166) - 166", "answer": "The result of (84.58 * 166) - 166 is 13874.28", "a": 84.58, "b": 166, "c": 166, "op1": "*", "op2": "-", "result": 13874.28}
{"question": "Solve: (163 / 68) * 93.84", "answer": "The result of (163 / 68) * 93.84 is 224.94", "a": 163, "b": 68, "c": 93.84, "op1": "/", "op2": "*", "result": 224.94}
{"question": "Solve: (197 + 22) - 193", "answer": "The result of (197 + 22) - 193 is 26", "a": 197, "b": 22, "c": 193, "op1": "+", "op2": "-", "result": 26}
{"question": "Solve: (39.93 / 37) - 24.32", "answer": "The result of (39.93 / 37) - 24.32 is -23.24", "a": 39.93, "b": 37, "c": 24.32, "op1": "/", "op2": "-", "result": -23.24}
{"question": "Solve: (44.06 - 67) - 174", "answer": "The result of (44.06 - 67) - 174 is -196.94", "a": 44.06, "b": 67, "c": 174, "op1": "-", "op2": "-", "result": -196.94}
{"question": "Solve: (120 * 43) - 35", "answer": "The result of (120 * 43) - 35 is 5125", "a": 120, "b": 43, "c": 35, "op1": "*", "op2": "-", "result": 5125}
{"question": "Solve: (198.68 * 153) * 185", "answer": "The result of (198.68 * 153) * 185 is 5623637.4", "a": 198.68, "b": 153, "c": 185, "op1": "*", "op2": "*", "result": 5623637.4}
{"question": "Solve: (100 / 187.7) + 67.19", "answer": "The result of (100 / 187.7) + 67.19 is 67.72", "a": 100, "b": 187.7, "c": 67.19, "op1": "/", "op2": "+", "result": 67.72}
{"question": "Solve: (78 - 63.11) - 197.67", "answer": "The result of (78 - 63.11) - 197.67 is -182.78", "a": 78, "b": 63.11, "c": 197.67, "op1": "-", "op2": "-", "result": -182.78}
{"question": "Solve: (9 - 83.53) - 21", "answer": "The result of (9 - 83.53) - 21 is -95.53", "a": 9, "b": 83.53, "c": 21, "op1": "-", "op2": "-", "result": -95.53}
{"question": "Solve: (102 * 150) + 99", "answer": "The result of (102 * 150) + 99 is 15399", "a": 102, "b": 150, "c": 99, "op1": "*", "op2": "+", "result": 15399}
{"question": "Solve: (74.84 - 118.05) + 104.18", "answer": "The result of (74.84 - 118.05) + 104.18 is 60.97", "a": 74.84, "b": 118.05, "c": 104.18, "op1": "-", "op2": "+", "result": 60.97}
{"question": "Solve: (59 * 144) * 26.78", "answer": "The result of (59 * 144) * 26.78 is 227522.88", "a": 59, "b": 144, "c": 26.78, "op1": "*", "op2": "*", "result": 227522.88}
{"question": "Solve: (133.64 + 56.42) - 106", "answer": "The result of (133.64 + 56.42) - 106 is 84.06", "a": 133.64, "b": 56.42, "c": 106, "op1": "+", "op2": "-", "result": 84.06}
{"question": "Solve: (23 * 167) * 10", "answer": "The result of (23 * 167) * 10 is 38410", "a": 23, "b": 167, "c": 10, "op1": "*", "op2": "*", "result": 38410}
{"question": "Solve: (172 + 134.98) + 52.17", "answer": "The result of (172 + 134.98) + 52.17 is 359.15", "a": 172, "b": 134.98, "c": 52.17, "op1": "+", "op2": "+", "result": 359.15}
{"question": "Solve: (189 * 173.42) + 123", "answer": "The result of (189 * 173.42) + 123 is 32899.38", "a": 189, "b": 173.42, "c": 123, "op1": "*", "op2": "+", "result": 32899.38}
{"question": "Solve: (63.26 - 154) * 139", "answer": "The result of (63.26 - 154) * 139 is -12612.86", "a": 63.26, "b": 154, "c": 139, "op1": "-", "op2": "*", "result": -12612.86}
{"question": "Solve: (126 + 59) + 20", "answer": "The result of (126 + 59) + 20 is 205", "a": 126, "b": 59, "c": 20, "op1": "+", "op2": "+", "result": 205}
{"question": "Solve: (89 / 142) * 84", "answer": "The result of (89 / 142) * 84 is 52.65", "a": 89, "b": 142, "c": 84, "op1": "/", "op2": "*", "result": 52.65}
{"question": "Solve: (49.84 * 76) + 18", "answer": "The result of (49.84 * 76) + 18 is 3805.84", "a": 49.84, "b": 76, "c": 18, "op1": "*", "op2": "+", "result": 3805.84}
{"question": "Solve: (103 * 48) / 147", "answer": "The result of (103 * 48) / 147 is 33.63", "a": 103, "b": 48, "c": 147, "op1": "*", "op2": "/", "result": 33.63}
{"question": "Solve: (128 + 173) + 7", "answer": "The result of (128 + 173) + 7 is 308", "a": 128, "b": 173, "c": 7, "op1": "+", "op2": "+", "result": 308}
{"question": "Solve: (186 / 60.39) * 171", "answer": "The result of (186 / 60.39) * 171 is 526.68", "a": 186, "b": 60.39, "c": 171, "op1": "/", "op2": "*", "result": 526.68}
{"question": "Solve: (184.51 - 183) - 147.23", "answer": "The result of (184.51 - 183) - 147.23 is -145.72", "a": 184.51, "b": 183, "c": 147.23, "op1": "-", "op2": "-", "result": -145.72}
{"question": "Solve: (80 - 184.1) * 97", "answer": "The result of (80 - 184.1) * 97 is -10097.7", "a": 80, "b": 184.1, "c": 97, "op1": "-", "op2": "*", "result": -10097.7}
{"question": "Solve: (52 - 134.05) - 172", "answer": "The result of (52 - 134.05) - 172 is -254.05", "a": 52, "b": 134.05, "c": 172, "op1": "-", "op2": "-", "result": -254.05}
{"question": "Solve: (84 - 52) - 160", "answer": "The result of (84 - 52) - 160 is -128", "a": 84, "b": 52, "c": 160, "op1": "-", "op2": "-", "result": -128}
{"question": "Solve: (44 + 41.06) + 51.5", "answer": "The result of (44 + 41.06) + 51.5 is 136.56", "a": 44, "b": 41.06, "c": 51.5, "op1": "+", "op2": "+", "result": 136.56}
{"question": "Solve: (38 * 49) * 3", "answer": "The result of (38 * 49) * 3 is 5586", "a": 38, "b": 49, "c": 3, "op1": "*", "op2": "*", "result": 5586}
{"question": "Solve: (145.67 - 182.0) + 50", "answer": "The result of (145.67 - 182.0) + 50 is 13.67", "a": 145.67, "b": 182.0, "c": 50, "op1": "-", "op2": "+", "result": 13.67}
{"question": "Solve: (35.87 + 129) + 199.53", "answer": "The result of (35.87 + 129) + 199.53 is 364.4", "a": 35.87, "b": 129, "c": 199.53, "op1": "+", "op2": "+", "result": 364.4}
{"question": "Solve: (200 - 48) - 185", "answer": "The result of (200 - 48) - 185 is -33", "a": 200, "b": 48, "c": 185, "op1": "-", "op2": "-", "result": -33}
{"question": "Solve: (164 + 187.39) - 113", "answer": "The result of (164 + 187.39) - 113 is 238.39", "a": 164, "b": 187.39, "c": 113, "op1": "+", "op2": "-", "result": 238.39}
{"question": "Solve: (123.09 + 80) / 198", "answer": "The result of (123.09 + 80) / 198 is 1.03", "a": 123.09, "b": 80, "c": 198, "op1": "+", "op2": "/", "result": 1.03}
{"question": "Solve: (23 - 187.78) + 193.85", "answer": "The result of (23 - 187.78) + 193.85 is 29.07", "a": 23, "b": 187.78, "c": 193.85, "op1": "-", "op2": "+", "result": 29.07}
{"question": "Solve: (115 + 68) / 21.48", "answer": "The result of (115 + 68) / 21.48 is 8.52", "a": 115, "b": 68, "c": 21.48, "op1": "+", "op2": "/", "result": 8.52}
{"question": "Solve: (163 + 49) - 32", "answer": "The result of (163 + 49) - 32 is 180", "a": 163, "b": 49, "c": 32, "op1": "+", "op2": "-", "result": 180}
{"question": "Solve: (33 * 197) + 87.0", "answer": "The result of (33 * 197) + 87.0 is 6588.0", "a": 33, "b": 197, "c": 87.0, "op1": "*", "op2": "+", "result": 6588.0}
{"question": "Solve: (98 + 25.24) + 190.48", "answer": "The result of (98 + 25.24) + 190.48 is 313.72", "a": 98, "b": 25.24, "c": 190.48, "op1": "+", "op2": "+", "result": 313.72}
{"question": "Solve: (82 + 168.31) / 29", "answer": "The result of (82 + 168.31) / 29 is 8.63", "a": 82, "b": 168.31, "c": 29, "op1": "+", "op2": "/", "result": 8.63}
{"question": "Solve: (198 / 49.63) + 185", "answer": "The result of (198 / 49.63) + 185 is 188.99", "a": 198, "b": 49.63, "c": 185, "op1": "/", "op2": "+", "result": 188.99}
{"question": "Solve: (73 / 114) + 105", "answer": "The result of (73 / 114) + 105 is 105.64", "a": 73, "b": 114, "c": 105, "op1": "/", "op2": "+", "result": 105.64}
{"question": "Solve: (90 + 13.22) * 138", "answer": "The result of (90 + 13.22) * 138 is 14244.36", "a": 90, "b": 13.22, "c": 138, "op1": "+", "op2": "*", "result": 14244.36}
{"question": "Solve: (30 * 161) + 40", "answer": "The result of (30 * 161) + 40 is 4870", "a": 30, "b": 161, "c": 40, "op1": "*", "op2": "+", "result": 4870}
{"question": "Solve: (51.72 + 30) * 148.73", "answer": "The result of (51.72 + 30) * 148.73 is 12154.22", "a": 51.72, "b": 30, "c": 148.73, "op1": "+", "op2": "*", "result": 12154.22}
{"question": "Solve: (33 + 171) + 95", "answer": "The result of (33 + 171) + 95 is 299", "a": 33, "b": 171, "c": 95, "op1": "+", "op2": "+", "result": 299}
{"question": "Solve: (34 + 59.89) + 177.57", "answer": "The result of (34 + 59.89) + 177.57 is 271.46", "a": 34, "b": 59.89, "c": 177.57, "op1": "+", "op2": "+", "result": 271.46}
{"question": "Solve: (148.07 - 35) * 29", "answer": "The result of (148.07 - 35) * 29 is 3279.03", "a": 148.07, "b": 35, "c": 29, "op1": "-", "op2": "*", "result": 3279.03}
{"question": "Solve: (72 * 59.79) * 3", "answer": "The result of (72 * 59.79) * 3 is 12914.64", "a": 72, "b": 59.79, "c": 3, "op1": "*", "op2": "*", "result": 12914.64}
{"question": "Solve: (69.53 - 2) + 114.45", "answer": "The result of (69.53 - 2) + 114.45 is 181.98", "a": 69.53, "b": 2, "c": 114.45, "op1": "-", "op2": "+", "result": 181.98}
{"question": "Solve: (60 + 56) + 9", "answer": "The result of (60 + 56) + 9 is 125", "a": 60, "b": 56, "c": 9, "op1": "+", "op2": "+", "result": 125}
{"question": "Solve: (68 + 108) / 51", "answer": "The result of (68 + 108) / 51 is 3.45", "a": 68, "b": 108, "c": 51, "op1": "+", "op2": "/", "result": 3.45}
{"question": "Solve: (31.15 + 105) + 38", "answer": "The result of (31.15 + 105) + 38 is 174.15", "a": 31.15, "b": 105, "c": 38, "op1": "+", "op2": "+", "result": 174.15}
{"question": "Solve: (90.16 / 108) + 152", "answer": "The result of (90.16 / 108) + 152 is 152.83", "a": 90.16, "b": 108, "c": 152, "op1": "/", "op2": "+", "result": 152.83}
{"question": "Solve: (54 * 198.66) - 126", "answer": "The result of (54 * 198.66) - 126 is 10601.64", "a": 54, "b": 198.66, "c": 126, "op1": "*", "op2": "-", "result": 10601.64}
{"question": "Solve: (183.95 - 104.22) + 123", "answer": "The result of (183.95 - 104.22) + 123 is 202.73", "a": 183.95, "b": 104.22, "c": 123, "op1": "-", "op2": "+", "result": 202.73}
{"question": "Solve: (52.8 / 193) + 19", "answer": "The result of (52.8 / 193) + 19 is 19.27", "a": 52.8, "b": 193, "c": 19, "op1": "/", "op2": "+", "result": 19.27}
{"question": "Solve: (146.95 - 173) + 32", "answer": "The result of (146.95 - 173) + 32 is 5.95", "a": 146.95, "b": 173, "c": 32, "op1": "-", "op2": "+", "result": 5.95}
{"question": "Solve: (50 - 93.47) * 64", "answer": "The result of (50 - 93.47) * 64 is -2782.08", "a": 50, "b": 93.47, "c": 64, "op1": "-", "op2": "*", "result": -2782.08}
{"question": "Solve: (48 * 9) - 33", "answer": "The result of (48 * 9) - 33 is 399", "a": 48, "b": 9, "c": 33, "op1": "*", "op2": "-", "result": 399}
{"question": "Solve: (132 - 98.81) / 177", "answer": "The result of (132 - 98.81) / 177 is 0.19", "a": 132, "b": 98.81, "c": 177, "op1": "-", "op2": "/", "result": 0.19}
{"question": "Solve: (180 - 145) - 83.24", "answer": "The result of (180 - 145) - 83.24 is -48.24", "a": 180, "b": 145, "c": 83.24, "op1": "-", "op2": "-", "result": -48.24}
{"question": "Solve: (137 - 68.12) - 16.15", "answer": "The result of (137 - 68.12) - 16.15 is 52.73", "a": 137, "b": 68.12, "c": 16.15, "op1": "-", "op2": "-", "result": 52.73}
{"question": "Solve: (172 * 189) / 101", "answer": "The result of (172 * 189) / 101 is 321.86", "a": 172, "b": 189, "c": 101, "op1": "*", "op2": "/", "result": 321.86}
{"question": "Solve: (50 - 165) - 161", "answer": "The result of (50 - 165) - 161 is -276", "a": 50, "b": 165, "c": 161, "op1": "-", "op2": "-", "result": -276}
{"question": "Solve: (180.18 * 108) / 178", "answer": "The result of (180.18 * 108) / 178 is 109.32", "a": 180.18, "b": 108, "c": 178, "op1": "*", "op2": "/", "result": 109.32}
{"question": "Solve: (70 + 137) + 181", "answer": "The result of (70 + 137) + 181 is 388", "a": 70, "b": 137, "c": 181, "op1": "+", "op2": "+", "result": 388}
{"question": "Solve: (3 * 170.05) - 17.04", "answer": "The result of (3 * 170.05) - 17.04 is 493.11", "a": 3, "b": 170.05, "c": 17.04, "op1": "*", "op2": "-", "result": 493.11}
{"question": "Solve: (124 + 200) / 35.02", "answer": "The result of (124 + 200) / 35.02 is 9.25", "a": 124, "b": 200, "c": 35.02, "op1": "+", "op2": "/", "result": 9.25}
{"question": "Solve: (129.98 - 168.43) - 63.78", "answer": "The result of (129.98 - 168.43) - 63.78 is -102.23", "a": 129.98, "b": 168.43, "c": 63.78, "op1": "-", "op2": "-", "result": -102.23}
{"question": "Solve: (101.76 * 101) - 145.57", "answer": "The result of (101.76 * 101) - 145.57 is 10132.19", "a": 101.76, "b": 101, "c": 145.57, "op1": "*", "op2": "-", "result": 10132.19}
{"question": "Solve: (69.6 * 41.8) - 4", "answer": "The result of (69.6 * 41.8) - 4 is 2905.28", "a": 69.6, "b": 41.8, "c": 4, "op1": "*", "op2": "-", "result": 2905.28}
{"question": "Solve: (89.14 - 165) / 68.43", "answer": "The result of (89.14 - 165) / 68.43 is -1.11", "a": 89.14, "b": 165, "c": 68.43, "op1": "-", "op2": "/", "result": -1.11}
{"question": "Solve: (149 + 89) * 194", "answer": "The result of (149 + 89) * 194 is 46172", "a": 149, "b": 89, "c": 194, "op1": "+", "op2": "*", "result": 46172}
{"question": "Solve: (123 / 145.42) / 16", "answer": "The result of (123 / 145.42) / 16 is 0.05", "a": 123, "b": 145.42, "c": 16, "op1": "/", "op2": "/", "result": 0.05}
{"question": "Solve: (62 / 113) * 71", "answer": "The result of (62 / 113) * 71 is 38.96", "a": 62, "b": 113, "c": 71, "op1": "/", "op2": "*", "result": 38.96}
{"question": "Solve: (30 - 126.4) - 64", "answer": "The result of (30 - 126.4) - 64 is -160.4", "a": 30, "b": 126.4, "c": 64, "op1": "-", "op2": "-", "result": -160.4}
{"question": "Solve: (66 * 113.36) + 61", "answer": "The result of (66 * 113.36) + 61 is 7542.76", "a": 66, "b": 113.36, "c": 61, "op1": "*", "op2": "+", "result": 7542.76}
{"question": "Solve: (133 + 31) * 3.55", "answer": "The result of (133 + 31) * 3.55 is 582.2", "a": 133, "b": 31, "c": 3.55, "op1": "+", "op2": "*", "result": 582.2}
{"question": "Solve: (106 / 69) - 12.49", "answer": "The result of (106 / 69) - 12.49 is -10.95", "a": 106, "b": 69, "c": 12.49, "op1": "/", "op2": "-", "result": -10.95}
{"question": "Solve: (75 - 152) - 188", "answer": "The result of (75 - 152) - 188 is -265", "a": 75, "b": 152, "c": 188, "op1": "-", "op2": "-", "result": -265}
{"question": "Solve: (77 + 105) - 23", "answer": "The result of (77 + 105) - 23 is 159", "a": 77, "b": 105, "c": 23, "op1": "+", "op2": "-", "result": 159}
{"question": "Solve: (78 + 87.94) / 128.13", "answer": "The result of (78 + 87.94) / 128.13 is 1.3", "a": 78, "b": 87.94, "c": 128.13, "op1": "+", "op2": "/", "result": 1.3}
{"question": "Solve: (90 - 4) / 150.37", "answer": "The result of (90 - 4) / 150.37 is 0.57", "a": 90, "b": 4, "c": 150.37, "op1": "-", "op2": "/", "result": 0.57}
{"question": "Solve: (148 + 48) + 179.25", "answer": "The result of (148 + 48) + 179.25 is 375.25", "a": 148, "b": 48, "c": 179.25, "op1": "+", "op2": "+", "result": 375.25}
{"question": "Solve: (179.92 - 121.18) * 138", "answer": "The result of (179.92 - 121.18) * 138 is 8106.12", "a": 179.92, "b": 121.18, "c": 138, "op1": "-", "op2": "*", "result": 8106.12}
{"question": "Solve: (137.56 + 68) + 200", "answer": "The result of (137.56 + 68) + 200 is 405.56", "a": 137.56, "b": 68, "c": 200, "op1": "+", "op2": "+", "result": 405.56}
{"question": "Solve: (55.22 + 93.4) / 137", "answer": "The result of (55.22 + 93.4) / 137 is 1.08", "a": 55.22, "b": 93.4, "c": 137, "op1": "+", "op2": "/", "result": 1.08}
{"question": "Solve: (16 / 48.44) * 93", "answer": "The result of (16 / 48.44) * 93 is 30.72", "a": 16, "b": 48.44, "c": 93, "op1": "/", "op2": "*", "result": 30.72}
{"question": "Solve: (187 / 173) * 135", "answer": "The result of (187 / 173) * 135 is 145.92", "a": 187, "b": 173, "c": 135, "op1": "/", "op2": "*", "result": 145.92}
{"question": "Solve: (35 - 5) - 104", "answer": "The result of (35 - 5) - 104 is -74", "a": 35, "b": 5, "c": 104, "op1": "-", "op2": "-", "result": -74}
{"question": "Solve: (153.88 + 8.56) + 113.26", "answer": "The result of (153.88 + 8.56) + 113.26 is 275.7", "a": 153.88, "b": 8.56, "c": 113.26, "op1": "+", "op2": "+", "result": 275.7}
{"question": "Solve: (170.36 - 86.54) - 173", "answer": "The result of (170.36 - 86.54) - 173 is -89.18", "a": 170.36, "b": 86.54, "c": 173, "op1": "-", "op2": "-", "result": -89.18}
{"question": "Solve: (4 - 37) * 73", "answer": "The result of (4 - 37) * 73 is -2409", "a": 4, "b": 37, "c": 73, "op1": "-", "op2": "*", "result": -2409}
{"question": "Solve: (86 - 113.48) / 36", "answer": "The result of (86 - 113.48) / 36 is -0.76", "a": 86, "b": 113.48, "c": 36, "op1": "-", "op2": "/", "result": -0.76}
{"question": "Solve: (3.97 * 182.34) * 44", "answer": "The result of (3.97 * 182.34) * 44 is 31851.15", "a": 3.97, "b": 182.34, "c": 44, "op1": "*", "op2": "*", "result": 31851.15}
{"question": "Solve: (87 - 165) * 172", "answer": "The result of (87 - 165) * 172 is -13416", "a": 87, "b": 165, "c": 172, "op1": "-", "op2": "*", "result": -13416}
{"question": "Solve: (152 * 1) - 171", "answer": "The result of (152 * 1) - 171 is -19", "a": 152, "b": 1, "c": 171, "op1": "*", "op2": "-", "result": -19}
{"question": "Solve: (64 / 181.36) - 31", "answer": "The result of (64 / 181.36) - 31 is -30.65", "a": 64, "b": 181.36, "c": 31, "op1": "/", "op2": "-", "result": -30.65}
{"question": "Solve: (183 * 197) + 97", "answer": "The result of (183 * 197) + 97 is 36148", "a": 183, "b": 197, "c": 97, "op1": "*", "op2": "+", "result": 36148}
{"question": "Solve: (56 / 108) - 167.84", "answer": "The result of (56 / 108) - 167.84 is -167.32", "a": 56, "b": 108, "c": 167.84, "op1": "/", "op2": "-", "result": -167.32}
{"question": "Solve: (52 * 54) - 14", "answer": "The result of (52 * 54) - 14 is 2794", "a": 52, "b": 54, "c": 14, "op1": "*", "op2": "-", "result": 2794}
{"question": "Solve: (55.72 + 57) / 193", "answer": "The result of (55.72 + 57) / 193 is 0.58", "a": 55.72, "b": 57, "c": 193, "op1": "+", "op2": "/", "result": 0.58}
{"question": "Solve: (106 - 23) - 60.97", "answer": "The result of (106 - 23) - 60.97 is 22.03", "a": 106, "b": 23, "c": 60.97, "op1": "-", "op2": "-", "result": 22.03}
{"question": "Solve: (115 + 1) - 89.16", "answer": "The result of (115 + 1) - 89.16 is 26.84", "a": 115, "b": 1, "c": 89.16, "op1": "+", "op2": "-", "result": 26.84}
{"question": "Solve: (61.16 / 56) * 60.72", "answer": "The result of (61.16 / 56) * 60.72 is 66.31", "a": 61.16, "b": 56, "c": 60.72, "op1": "/", "op2": "*", "result": 66.31}
{"question": "Solve: (16.6 - 59.23) + 61.57", "answer": "The result of (16.6 - 59.23) + 61.57 is 18.94", "a": 16.6, "b": 59.23, "c": 61.57, "op1": "-", "op2": "+", "result": 18.94}
{"question": "Solve: (104.36 + 45) * 179", "answer": "The result of (104.36 + 45) * 179 is 26735.44", "a": 104.36, "b": 45, "c": 179, "op1": "+", "op2": "*", "result": 26735.44}
{"question": "Solve: (143 + 131) - 107", "answer": "The result of (143 + 131) - 107 is 167", "a": 143, "b": 131, "c": 107, "op1": "+", "op2": "-", "result": 167}
{"question": "Solve: (86 / 199) - 79", "answer": "The result of (86 / 199) - 79 is -78.57", "a": 86, "b": 199, "c": 79, "op1": "/", "op2": "-", "result": -78.57}
{"question": "Solve: (88.52 * 133) * 142.27", "answer": "The result of (88.52 * 133) * 142.27 is 1674967.47", "a": 88.52, "b": 133, "c": 142.27, "op1": "*", "op2": "*", "result": 1674967.47}
{"question": "Solve: (51.33 + 102) * 129", "answer": "The result of (51.33 + 102) * 129 is 19779.57", "a": 51.33, "b": 102, "c": 129, "op1": "+", "op2": "*", "result": 19779.57}
{"question": "Solve: (127 - 94) - 166", "answer": "The result of (127 - 94) - 166 is -133", "a": 127, "b": 94, "c": 166, "op1": "-", "op2": "-", "result": -133}
{"question": "Solve: (52.1 * 29.69) + 178", "answer": "The result of (52.1 * 29.69) + 178 is 1724.85", "a": 52.1, "b": 29.69, "c": 178, "op1": "*", "op2": "+", "result": 1724.85}
{"question": "Solve: (134 + 48) - 122", "answer": "The result of (134 + 48) - 122 is 60", "a": 134, "b": 48, "c": 122, "op1": "+", "op2": "-", "result": 60}
{"question": "Solve: (100 - 20) * 159", "answer": "The result of (100 - 20) * 159 is 12720", "a": 100, "b": 20, "c": 159, "op1": "-", "op2": "*", "result": 12720}
{"question": "Solve: (96.62 * 166.27) + 25", "answer": "The result of (96.62 * 166.27) + 25 is 16090.01", "a": 96.62, "b": 166.27, "c": 25, "op1": "*", "op2": "+", "result": 16090.01}
{"question": "Solve: (163 / 2.66) + 122", "answer": "The result of (163 / 2.66) + 122 is 183.28", "a": 163, "b": 2.66, "c": 122, "op1": "/", "op2": "+", "result": 183.28}
{"question": "Solve: (66 * 61.45) - 199.26", "answer": "The result of (66 * 61.45) - 199.26 is 3856.44", "a": 66, "b": 61.45, "c": 199.26, "op1": "*", "op2": "-", "result": 3856.44}
{"question": "Solve: (109 + 183) * 102", "answer": "The result of (109 + 183) * 102 is 29784", "a": 109, "b": 183, "c": 102, "op1": "+", "op2": "*", "result": 29784}
{"question": "Solve: (69 + 122) / 14.93", "answer": "The result of (69 + 122) / 14.93 is 12.79", "a": 69, "b": 122, "c": 14.93, "op1": "+", "op2": "/", "result": 12.79}
{"question": "Solve: (109.04 - 73) - 106", "answer": "The result of (109.04 - 73) - 106 is -69.96", "a": 109.04, "b": 73, "c": 106, "op1": "-", "op2": "-", "result": -69.96}
{"question": "Solve: (42 - 42) + 124", "answer": "The result of (42 - 42) + 124 is 124", "a": 42, "b": 42, "c": 124, "op1": "-", "op2": "+", "result": 124}
{"question": "Solve: (196.45 * 79) - 161", "answer": "The result of (196.45 * 79) - 161 is 15358.55", "a": 196.45, "b": 79, "c": 161, "op1": "*", "op2": "-", "result": 15358.55}
{"question": "Solve: (75 * 4) * 91", "answer": "The result of (75 * 4) * 91 is 27300", "a": 75, "b": 4, "c": 91, "op1": "*", "op2": "*", "result": 27300}
{"question": "Solve: (142 * 70.05) / 58.48", "answer": "The result of (142 * 70.05) / 58.48 is 170.09", "a": 142, "b": 70.05, "c": 58.48, "op1": "*", "op2": "/", "result": 170.09}
{"question": "Solve: (153 - 1) - 5", "answer": "The result of (153 - 1) - 5 is 147", "a": 153, "b": 1, "c": 5, "op1": "-", "op2": "-", "result": 147}
{"question": "Solve: (163 * 38) - 95", "answer": "The result of (163 * 38) - 95 is 6099", "a": 163, "b": 38, "c": 95, "op1": "*", "op2": "-", "result": 6099}
{"question": "Solve: (42 + 85) * 97", "answer": "The result of (42 + 85) * 97 is 12319", "a": 42, "b": 85, "c": 97, "op1": "+", "op2": "*", "result": 12319}
{"question": "Solve: (98 - 130) + 176", "answer": "The result of (98 - 130) + 176 is 144", "a": 98, "b": 130, "c": 176, "op1": "-", "op2": "+", "result": 144}
{"question": "Solve: (85 + 115) + 73.84", "answer": "The result of (85 + 115) + 73.84 is 273.84", "a": 85, "b": 115, "c": 73.84, "op1": "+", "op2": "+", "result": 273.84}
{"question": "Solve: (93.76 - 65) * 157", "answer": "The result of (93.76 - 65) * 157 is 4515.32", "a": 93.76, "b": 65, "c": 157, "op1": "-", "op2": "*", "result": 4515.32}
{"question": "Solve: (28 + 43) * 189.19", "answer": "The result of (28 + 43) * 189.19 is 13432.49", "a": 28, "b": 43, "c": 189.19, "op1": "+", "op2": "*", "result": 13432.49}
{"question": "Solve: (141 + 49.54) / 13.63", "answer": "The result of (141 + 49.54) / 13.63 is 13.98", "a": 141, "b": 49.54, "c": 13.63, "op1": "+", "op2": "/", "result": 13.98}
{"question": "Solve: (190 - 6) * 94", "answer": "The result of (190 - 6) * 94 is 17296", "a": 190, "b": 6, "c": 94, "op1": "-", "op2": "*", "result": 17296}
{"question": "Solve: (82 + 130) / 187", "answer": "The result of (82 + 130) / 187 is 1.13", "a": 82, "b": 130, "c": 187, "op1": "+", "op2": "/", "result": 1.13}
{"question": "Solve: (141 + 170) * 121.71", "answer": "The result of (141 + 170) * 121.71 is 37851.81", "a": 141, "b": 170, "c": 121.71, "op1": "+", "op2": "*", "result": 37851.81}
{"question": "Solve: (25.78 + 101) + 123", "answer": "The result of (25.78 + 101) + 123 is 249.78", "a": 25.78, "b": 101, "c": 123, "op1": "+", "op2": "+", "result": 249.78}
{"question": "Solve: (90 - 167) - 143", "answer": "The result of (90 - 167) - 143 is -220", "a": 90, "b": 167, "c": 143, "op1": "-", "op2": "-", "result": -220}
{"question": "Solve: (185 - 89.1) * 50.37", "answer": "The result of (185 - 89.1) * 50.37 is 4830.48", "a": 185, "b": 89.1, "c": 50.37, "op1": "-", "op2": "*", "result": 4830.48}
{"question": "Solve: (47 * 105) - 107", "answer": "The result of (47 * 105) - 107 is 4828", "a": 47, "b": 105, "c": 107, "op1": "*", "op2": "-", "result": 4828}
{"question": "Solve: (78 - 126.78) - 134", "answer": "The result of (78 - 126.78) - 134 is -182.78", "a": 78, "b": 126.78, "c": 134, "op1": "-", "op2": "-", "result": -182.78}
{"question": "Solve: (62 + 125) * 96.45", "answer": "The result of (62 + 125) * 96.45 is 18036.15", "a": 62, "b": 125, "c": 96.45, "op1": "+", "op2": "*", "result": 18036.15}
{"question": "Solve: (69.99 / 38) * 135", "answer": "The result of (69.99 / 38) * 135 is 248.65", "a": 69.99, "b": 38, "c": 135, "op1": "/", "op2": "*", "result": 248.65}
{"question": "Solve: (58 + 136.76) * 191", "answer": "The result of (58 + 136.76) * 191 is 37199.16", "a": 58, "b": 136.76, "c": 191, "op1": "+", "op2": "*", "result": 37199.16}
{"question": "Solve: (61.07 + 43) * 42.49", "answer": "The result of (61.07 + 43) * 42.49 is 4421.93", "a": 61.07, "b": 43, "c": 42.49, "op1": "+", "op2": "*", "result": 4421.93}
{"question": "Solve: (101 - 3) - 44", "answer": "The result of (101 - 3) - 44 is 54", "a": 101, "b": 3, "c": 44, "op1": "-", "op2": "-", "result": 54}
{"question": "Solve: (44 * 164) + 18", "answer": "The result of (44 * 164) + 18 is 7234", "a": 44, "b": 164, "c": 18, "op1": "*", "op2": "+", "result": 7234}
{"question": "Solve: (142 * 146) + 58", "answer": "The result of (142 * 146) + 58 is 20790", "a": 142, "b": 146, "c": 58, "op1": "*", "op2": "+", "result": 20790}
{"question": "Solve: (63 - 195.55) - 74", "answer": "The result of (63 - 195.55) - 74 is -206.55", "a": 63, "b": 195.55, "c": 74, "op1": "-", "op2": "-", "result": -206.55}
{"question": "Solve: (115 / 98) / 36", "answer": "The result of (115 / 98) / 36 is 0.03", "a": 115, "b": 98, "c": 36, "op1": "/", "op2": "/", "result": 0.03}
{"question": "Solve: (158 * 137.81) * 162.41", "answer": "The result of (158 * 137.81) * 162.41 is 3536312.09", "a": 158, "b": 137.81, "c": 162.41, "op1": "*", "op2": "*", "result": 3536312.09}
{"question": "Solve: (81.57 * 168) - 72", "answer": "The result of (81.57 * 168) - 72 is 13631.76", "a": 81.57, "b": 168, "c": 72, "op1": "*", "op2": "-", "result": 13631.76}
{"question": "Solve: (139 + 83) - 29", "answer": "The result of (139 + 83) - 29 is 193", "a": 139, "b": 83, "c": 29, "op1": "+", "op2": "-", "result": 193}
{"question": "Solve: (7.91 - 131) * 143", "answer": "The result of (7.91 - 131) * 143 is -17601.87", "a": 7.91, "b": 131, "c": 143, "op1": "-", "op2": "*", "result": -17601.87}
{"question": "Solve: (188.36 - 63) + 2", "answer": "The result of (188.36 - 63) + 2 is 127.36", "a": 188.36, "b": 63, "c": 2, "op1": "-", "op2": "+", "result": 127.36}
{"question": "Solve: (19.69 / 23) - 131.49", "answer": "The result of (19.69 / 23) - 131.49 is -130.63", "a": 19.69, "b": 23, "c": 131.49, "op1": "/", "op2": "-", "result": -130.63}
{"question": "Solve: (43 - 129.96) + 50", "answer": "The result of (43 - 129.96) + 50 is -36.96", "a": 43, "b": 129.96, "c": 50, "op1": "-", "op2": "+", "result": -36.96}
{"question": "Solve: (149.51 - 176.95) * 88", "answer": "The result of (149.51 - 176.95) * 88 is -2414.72", "a": 149.51, "b": 176.95, "c": 88, "op1": "-", "op2": "*", "result": -2414.72}
{"question": "Solve: (62 - 175) + 51", "answer": "The result of (62 - 175) + 51 is -62", "a": 62, "b": 175, "c": 51, "op1": "-", "op2": "+", "result": -62}
{"question": "Solve: (42 + 66) - 157", "answer": "The result of (42 + 66) - 157 is -49", "a": 42, "b": 66, "c": 157, "op1": "+", "op2": "-", "result": -49}
{"question": "Solve: (176 / 106) - 133", "answer": "The result of (176 / 106) - 133 is -131.34", "a": 176, "b": 106, "c": 133, "op1": "/", "op2": "-", "result": -131.34}
{"question": "Solve: (50 - 47) / 39.5", "answer": "The result of (50 - 47) / 39.5 is 0.08", "a": 50, "b": 47, "c": 39.5, "op1": "-", "op2": "/", "result": 0.08}
{"question": "Solve: (166 / 182) - 175", "answer": "The result of (166 / 182) - 175 is -174.09", "a": 166, "b": 182, "c": 175, "op1": "/", "op2": "-", "result": -174.09}
{"question": "Solve: (60.88 + 130.43) * 21", "answer": "The result of (60.88 + 130.43) * 21 is 4017.51", "a": 60.88, "b": 130.43, "c": 21, "op1": "+", "op2": "*", "result": 4017.51}
{"question": "Solve: (21.29 + 175.07) * 123", "answer": "The result of (21.29 + 175.07) * 123 is 24152.28", "a": 21.29, "b": 175.07, "c": 123, "op1": "+", "op2": "*", "result": 24152.28}
{"question": "Solve: (8 * 91) / 128.87", "answer": "The result of (8 * 91) / 128.87 is 5.65", "a": 8, "b": 91, "c": 128.87, "op1": "*", "op2": "/", "result": 5.65}
{"question": "Solve: (170.07 - 133) - 97.71", "answer": "The result of (170.07 - 133) - 97.71 is -60.64", "a": 170.07, "b": 133, "c": 97.71, "op1": "-", "op2": "-", "result": -60.64}
{"question": "Solve: (90 / 50.0) - 54", "answer": "The result of (90 / 50.0) - 54 is -52.2", "a": 90, "b": 50.0, "c": 54, "op1": "/", "op2": "-", "result": -52.2}
{"question": "Solve: (74 * 83.13) * 193", "answer": "The result of (74 * 83.13) * 193 is 1187262.66", "a": 74, "b": 83.13, "c": 193, "op1": "*", "op2": "*", "result": 1187262.66}
{"question": "Solve: (156 / 94) - 86.25", "answer": "The result of (156 / 94) - 86.25 is -84.59", "a": 156, "b": 94, "c": 86.25, "op1": "/", "op2": "-", "result": -84.59}
{"question": "Solve: (64 * 56) * 61", "answer": "The result of (64 * 56) * 61 is 218624", "a": 64, "b": 56, "c": 61, "op1": "*", "op2": "*", "result": 218624}
{"question": "Solve: (169 / 58) - 28", "answer": "The result of (169 / 58) - 28 is -25.09", "a": 169, "b": 58, "c": 28, "op1": "/", "op2": "-", "result": -25.09}
{"question": "Solve: (109.06 * 104) - 43", "answer": "The result of (109.06 * 104) - 43 is 11299.24", "a": 109.06, "b": 104, "c": 43, "op1": "*", "op2": "-", "result": 11299.24}
{"question": "Solve: (163.92 + 179) * 105", "answer": "The result of (163.92 + 179) * 105 is 36006.6", "a": 163.92, "b": 179, "c": 105, "op1": "+", "op2": "*", "result": 36006.6}
{"question": "Solve: (114.18 * 76) * 27", "answer": "The result of (114.18 * 76) * 27 is 234297.36", "a": 114.18, "b": 76, "c": 27, "op1": "*", "op2": "*", "result": 234297.36}
{"question": "Solve: (68 - 156) - 134.5", "answer": "The result of (68 - 156) - 134.5 is -222.5", "a": 68, "b": 156, "c": 134.5, "op1": "-", "op2": "-", "result": -222.5}
{"question": "Solve: (108 + 126) + 182", "answer": "The result of (108 + 126) + 182 is 416", "a": 108, "b": 126, "c": 182, "op1": "+", "op2": "+", "result": 416}
{"question": "Solve: (100 + 134.14) - 189", "answer": "The result of (100 + 134.14) - 189 is 45.14", "a": 100, "b": 134.14, "c": 189, "op1": "+", "op2": "-", "result": 45.14}
{"question": "Solve: (158.84 - 93.77) + 158", "answer": "The result of (158.84 - 93.77) + 158 is 223.07", "a": 158.84, "b": 93.77, "c": 158, "op1": "-", "op2": "+", "result": 223.07}
{"question": "Solve: (195 * 59.21) + 186", "answer": "The result of (195 * 59.21) + 186 is 11731.95", "a": 195, "b": 59.21, "c": 186, "op1": "*", "op2": "+", "result": 11731.95}
{"question": "Solve: (112.91 * 180) - 165", "answer": "The result of (112.91 * 180) - 165 is 20158.8", "a": 112.91, "b": 180, "c": 165, "op1": "*", "op2": "-", "result": 20158.8}
{"question": "Solve: (85 / 76.88) - 84", "answer": "The result of (85 / 76.88) - 84 is -82.89", "a": 85, "b": 76.88, "c": 84, "op1": "/", "op2": "-", "result": -82.89}
{"question": "Solve: (132 - 52) * 24", "answer": "The result of (132 - 52) * 24 is 1920", "a": 132, "b": 52, "c": 24, "op1": "-", "op2": "*", "result": 1920}
{"question": "Solve: (130 - 119) + 3", "answer": "The result of (130 - 119) + 3 is 14", "a": 130, "b": 119, "c": 3, "op1": "-", "op2": "+", "result": 14}
{"question": "Solve: (153.47 - 171.56) + 105", "answer": "The result of (153.47 - 171.56) + 105 is 86.91", "a": 153.47, "b": 171.56, "c": 105, "op1": "-", "op2": "+", "result": 86.91}
{"question": "Solve: (9.14 + 33) * 172", "answer": "The result of (9.14 + 33) * 172 is 7248.08", "a": 9.14, "b": 33, "c": 172, "op1": "+", "op2": "*", "result": 7248.08}
{"question": "Solve: (21 * 96.11) / 96", "answer": "The result of (21 * 96.11) / 96 is 21.02", "a": 21, "b": 96.11, "c": 96, "op1": "*", "op2": "/", "result": 21.02}
{"question": "Solve: (196 - 170) + 173", "answer": "The result of (196 - 170) + 173 is 199", "a": 196, "b": 170, "c": 173, "op1": "-", "op2": "+", "result": 199}
{"question": "Solve: (39 + 47) - 96", "answer": "The result of (39 + 47) - 96 is -10", "a": 39, "b": 47, "c": 96, "op1": "+", "op2": "-", "result": -10}
{"question": "Solve: (140 * 140) * 51", "answer": "The result of (140 * 140) * 51 is 999600", "a": 140, "b": 140, "c": 51, "op1": "*", "op2": "*", "result": 999600}
{"question": "Solve: (23.92 + 124) - 140", "answer": "The result of (23.92 + 124) - 140 is 7.92", "a": 23.92, "b": 124, "c": 140, "op1": "+", "op2": "-", "result": 7.92}
{"question": "Solve: (15 + 102) / 162", "answer": "The result of (15 + 102) / 162 is 0.72", "a": 15, "b": 102, "c": 162, "op1": "+", "op2": "/", "result": 0.72}
{"question": "Solve: (16 - 110.36) - 45.02", "answer": "The result of (16 - 110.36) - 45.02 is -139.38", "a": 16, "b": 110.36, "c": 45.02, "op1": "-", "op2": "-", "result": -139.38}
{"question": "Solve: (183 - 23) / 193", "answer": "The result of (183 - 23) / 193 is 0.83", "a": 183, "b": 23, "c": 193, "op1": "-", "op2": "/", "result": 0.83}
{"question": "Solve: (78 + 164) - 92.74", "answer": "The result of (78 + 164) - 92.74 is 149.26", "a": 78, "b": 164, "c": 92.74, "op1": "+", "op2": "-", "result": 149.26}
{"question": "Solve: (4.47 * 145) / 141.73", "answer": "The result of (4.47 * 145) / 141.73 is 4.57", "a": 4.47, "b": 145, "c": 141.73, "op1": "*", "op2": "/", "result": 4.57}
{"question": "Solve: (126 - 158) + 162.44", "answer": "The result of (126 - 158) + 162.44 is 130.44", "a": 126, "b": 158, "c": 162.44, "op1": "-", "op2": "+", "result": 130.44}
{"question": "Solve: (155 / 75) - 169", "answer": "The result of (155 / 75) - 169 is -166.93", "a": 155, "b": 75, "c": 169, "op1": "/", "op2": "-", "result": -166.93}
{"question": "Solve: (200 / 6.79) - 177", "answer": "The result of (200 / 6.79) - 177 is -147.54", "a": 200, "b": 6.79, "c": 177, "op1": "/", "op2": "-", "result": -147.54}
{"question": "Solve: (123.21 * 95) * 110", "answer": "The result of (123.21 * 95) * 110 is 1287544.5", "a": 123.21, "b": 95, "c": 110, "op1": "*", "op2": "*", "result": 1287544.5}
{"question": "Solve: (86 + 84) + 68", "answer": "The result of (86 + 84) + 68 is 238", "a": 86, "b": 84, "c": 68, "op1": "+", "op2": "+", "result": 238}
{"question": "Solve: (181 + 123) + 39", "answer": "The result of (181 + 123) + 39 is 343", "a": 181, "b": 123, "c": 39, "op1": "+", "op2": "+", "result": 343}
{"question": "Solve: (136.88 * 85.67) + 185.3", "answer": "The result of (136.88 * 85.67) + 185.3 is 11911.81", "a": 136.88, "b": 85.67, "c": 185.3, "op1": "*", "op2": "+", "result": 11911.81}
{"question": "Solve: (137 * 6.29) / 187.36", "answer": "The result of (137 * 6.29) / 187.36 is 4.6", "a": 137, "b": 6.29, "c": 187.36, "op1": "*", "op2": "/", "result": 4.6}
{"question": "Solve: (160 + 46.1) - 36.97", "answer": "The result of (160 + 46.1) - 36.97 is 169.13", "a": 160, "b": 46.1, "c": 36.97, "op1": "+", "op2": "-", "result": 169.13}
{"question": "Solve: (79 - 13) * 102", "answer": "The result of (79 - 13) * 102 is 6732", "a": 79, "b": 13, "c": 102, "op1": "-", "op2": "*", "result": 6732}
{"question": "Solve: (24.88 - 166.31) * 140.58", "answer": "The result of (24.88 - 166.31) * 140.58 is -19882.23", "a": 24.88, "b": 166.31, "c": 140.58, "op1": "-", "op2": "*", "result": -19882.23}
{"question": "Solve: (192 + 108) + 108.58", "answer": "The result of (192 + 108) + 108.58 is 408.58", "a": 192, "b": 108, "c": 108.58, "op1": "+", "op2": "+", "result": 408.58}
{"question": "Solve: (131 * 191.13) * 73.79", "answer": "The result of (131 * 191.13) * 73.79 is 1847556.23", "a": 131, "b": 191.13, "c": 73.79, "op1": "*", "op2": "*", "result": 1847556.23}
{"question": "Solve: (148 / 143.36) - 49", "answer": "The result of (148 / 143.36) - 49 is -47.97", "a": 148, "b": 143.36, "c": 49, "op1": "/", "op2": "-", "result": -47.97}
{"question": "Solve: (52.17 + 127) + 70.28", "answer": "The result of (52.17 + 127) + 70.28 is 249.45", "a": 52.17, "b": 127, "c": 70.28, "op1": "+", "op2": "+", "result": 249.45}
{"question": "Solve: (77 - 194) * 147.83", "answer": "The result of (77 - 194) * 147.83 is -17296.11", "a": 77, "b": 194, "c": 147.83, "op1": "-", "op2": "*", "result": -17296.11}
{"question": "Solve: (96 / 126) - 154.2", "answer": "The result of (96 / 126) - 154.2 is -153.44", "a": 96, "b": 126, "c": 154.2, "op1": "/", "op2": "-", "result": -153.44}
{"question": "Solve: (109.71 + 26) - 94", "answer": "The result of (109.71 + 26) - 94 is 41.71", "a": 109.71, "b": 26, "c": 94, "op1": "+", "op2": "-", "result": 41.71}
{"question": "Solve: (150 - 178) - 32", "answer": "The result of (150 - 178) - 32 is -60", "a": 150, "b": 178, "c": 32, "op1": "-", "op2": "-", "result": -60}
{"question": "Solve: (161 - 173.77) + 63.95", "answer": "The result of (161 - 173.77) + 63.95 is 51.18", "a": 161, "b": 173.77, "c": 63.95, "op1": "-", "op2": "+", "result": 51.18}
{"question": "Solve: (160 * 154) + 195", "answer": "The result of (160 * 154) + 195 is 24835", "a": 160, "b": 154, "c": 195, "op1": "*", "op2": "+", "result": 24835}
{"question": "Solve: (46.91 + 141) + 54", "answer": "The result of (46.91 + 141) + 54 is 241.91", "a": 46.91, "b": 141, "c": 54, "op1": "+", "op2": "+", "result": 241.91}
{"question": "Solve: (66 + 138) * 91", "answer": "The result of (66 + 138) * 91 is 18564", "a": 66, "b": 138, "c": 91, "op1": "+", "op2": "*", "result": 18564}
{"question": "Solve: (114.01 - 88) * 163", "answer": "The result of (114.01 - 88) * 163 is 4239.63", "a": 114.01, "b": 88, "c": 163, "op1": "-", "op2": "*", "result": 4239.63}
{"question": "Solve: (38 + 144) - 133", "answer": "The result of (38 + 144) - 133 is 49", "a": 38, "b": 144, "c": 133, "op1": "+", "op2": "-", "result": 49}
{"question": "Solve: (148 + 135) * 54.15", "answer": "The result of (148 + 135) * 54.15 is 15324.45", "a": 148, "b": 135, "c": 54.15, "op1": "+", "op2": "*", "result": 15324.45}
{"question": "Solve: (169.53 - 179.94) - 47", "answer": "The result of (169.53 - 179.94) - 47 is -57.41", "a": 169.53, "b": 179.94, "c": 47, "op1": "-", "op2": "-", "result": -57.41}
{"question": "Solve: (38 + 91) + 112", "answer": "The result of (38 + 91) + 112 is 241", "a": 38, "b": 91, "c": 112, "op1": "+", "op2": "+", "result": 241}
{"question": "Solve: (45 - 125) * 43", "answer": "The result of (45 - 125) * 43 is -3440", "a": 45, "b": 125, "c": 43, "op1": "-", "op2": "*", "result": -3440}
{"question": "Solve: (149 * 54.1) + 39", "answer": "The result of (149 * 54.1) + 39 is 8099.9", "a": 149, "b": 54.1, "c": 39, "op1": "*", "op2": "+", "result": 8099.9}
{"question": "Solve: (105 * 162) + 89", "answer": "The result of (105 * 162) + 89 is 17099", "a": 105, "b": 162, "c": 89, "op1": "*", "op2": "+", "result": 17099}
{"question": "Solve: (123 - 136) + 74", "answer": "The result of (123 - 136) + 74 is 61", "a": 123, "b": 136, "c": 74, "op1": "-", "op2": "+", "result": 61}
{"question": "Solve: (43 * 99) * 134.51", "answer": "The result of (43 * 99) * 134.51 is 572609.07", "a": 43, "b": 99, "c": 134.51, "op1": "*", "op2": "*", "result": 572609.07}
{"question": "Solve: (192 - 167) - 192", "answer": "The result of (192 - 167) - 192 is -167", "a": 192, "b": 167, "c": 192, "op1": "-", "op2": "-", "result": -167}
{"question": "Solve: (98 / 108) + 30", "answer": "The result of (98 / 108) + 30 is 30.91", "a": 98, "b": 108, "c": 30, "op1": "/", "op2": "+", "result": 30.91}
{"question": "Solve: (148.74 + 39) - 198", "answer": "The result of (148.74 + 39) - 198 is -10.26", "a": 148.74, "b": 39, "c": 198, "op1": "+", "op2": "-", "result": -10.26}
{"question": "Solve: (74 + 98.82) + 154", "answer": "The result of (74 + 98.82) + 154 is 326.82", "a": 74, "b": 98.82, "c": 154, "op1": "+", "op2": "+", "result": 326.82}
{"question": "Solve: (180 - 123) * 115", "answer": "The result of (180 - 123) * 115 is 6555", "a": 180, "b": 123, "c": 115, "op1": "-", "op2": "*", "result": 6555}
{"question": "Solve: (145 / 68) * 118", "answer": "The result of (145 / 68) * 118 is 251.62", "a": 145, "b": 68, "c": 118, "op1": "/", "op2": "*", "result": 251.62}
{"question": "Solve: (183 + 108) / 83.83", "answer": "The result of (183 + 108) / 83.83 is 3.47", "a": 183, "b": 108, "c": 83.83, "op1": "+", "op2": "/", "result": 3.47}
{"question": "Solve: (50 - 90) / 194", "answer": "The result of (50 - 90) / 194 is -0.21", "a": 50, "b": 90, "c": 194, "op1": "-", "op2": "/", "result": -0.21}
{"question": "Solve: (16 * 181.74) + 78.82", "answer": "The result of (16 * 181.74) + 78.82 is 2986.66", "a": 16, "b": 181.74, "c": 78.82, "op1": "*", "op2": "+", "result": 2986.66}
{"question": "Solve: (119.49 / 187) * 134.06", "answer": "The result of (119.49 / 187) * 134.06 is 85.66", "a": 119.49, "b": 187, "c": 134.06, "op1": "/", "op2": "*", "result": 85.66}
{"question": "Solve: (120 - 101.32) + 91.14", "answer": "The result of (120 - 101.32) + 91.14 is 109.82", "a": 120, "b": 101.32, "c": 91.14, "op1": "-", "op2": "+", "result": 109.82}
{"question": "Solve: (59 - 130.13) - 101", "answer": "The result of (59 - 130.13) - 101 is -172.13", "a": 59, "b": 130.13, "c": 101, "op1": "-", "op2": "-", "result": -172.13}
{"question": "Solve: (80 / 99.69) + 61.49", "answer": "The result of (80 / 99.69) + 61.49 is 62.29", "a": 80, "b": 99.69, "c": 61.49, "op1": "/", "op2": "+", "result": 62.29}
{"question": "Solve: (19 + 41) / 12", "answer": "The result of (19 + 41) / 12 is 5.0", "a": 19, "b": 41, "c": 12, "op1": "+", "op2": "/", "result": 5.0}
{"question": "Solve: (117.82 - 195.24) + 99", "answer": "The result of (117.82 - 195.24) + 99 is 21.58", "a": 117.82, "b": 195.24, "c": 99, "op1": "-", "op2": "+", "result": 21.58}
{"question": "Solve: (87 + 166) + 196", "answer": "The result of (87 + 166) + 196 is 449", "a": 87, "b": 166, "c": 196, "op1": "+", "op2": "+", "result": 449}
{"question": "Solve: (78 * 149) - 97", "answer": "The result of (78 * 149) - 97 is 11525", "a": 78, "b": 149, "c": 97, "op1": "*", "op2": "-", "result": 11525}
{"question": "Solve: (14.02 - 29) * 143", "answer": "The result of (14.02 - 29) * 143 is -2142.14", "a": 14.02, "b": 29, "c": 143, "op1": "-", "op2": "*", "result": -2142.14}
{"question": "Solve: (73 + 142) * 14", "answer": "The result of (73 + 142) * 14 is 3010", "a": 73, "b": 142, "c": 14, "op1": "+", "op2": "*", "result": 3010}
{"question": "Solve: (16 + 55.22) / 22", "answer": "The result of (16 + 55.22) / 22 is 3.24", "a": 16, "b": 55.22, "c": 22, "op1": "+", "op2": "/", "result": 3.24}
{"question": "Solve: (65 * 88) * 80.94", "answer": "The result of (65 * 88) * 80.94 is 462976.8", "a": 65, "b": 88, "c": 80.94, "op1": "*", "op2": "*", "result": 462976.8}
{"question": "Solve: (178 + 188) / 139", "answer": "The result of (178 + 188) / 139 is 2.63", "a": 178, "b": 188, "c": 139, "op1": "+", "op2": "/", "result": 2.63}
{"question": "Solve: (1 - 113) - 178", "answer": "The result of (1 - 113) - 178 is -290", "a": 1, "b": 113, "c": 178, "op1": "-", "op2": "-", "result": -290}
{"question": "Solve: (66 + 178) - 28", "answer": "The result of (66 + 178) - 28 is 216", "a": 66, "b": 178, "c": 28, "op1": "+", "op2": "-", "result": 216}
{"question": "Solve: (42 - 3.33) + 122.61", "answer": "The result of (42 - 3.33) + 122.61 is 161.28", "a": 42, "b": 3.33, "c": 122.61, "op1": "-", "op2": "+", "result": 161.28}
{"question": "Solve: (147.12 + 140) / 158.18", "answer": "The result of (147.12 + 140) / 158.18 is 1.82", "a": 147.12, "b": 140, "c": 158.18, "op1": "+", "op2": "/", "result": 1.82}
{"question": "Solve: (154 * 106.02) * 162.66", "answer": "The result of (154 * 106.02) * 162.66 is 2655762.83", "a": 154, "b": 106.02, "c": 162.66, "op1": "*", "op2": "*", "result": 2655762.83}
{"question": "Solve: (61 + 101) * 25.34", "answer": "The result of (61 + 101) * 25.34 is 4105.08", "a": 61, "b": 101, "c": 25.34, "op1": "+", "op2": "*", "result": 4105.08}
{"question": "Solve: (149 - 12) - 76", "answer": "The result of (149 - 12) - 76 is 61", "a": 149, "b": 12, "c": 76, "op1": "-", "op2": "-", "result": 61}
{"question": "Solve: (159.82 / 46) * 64", "answer": "The result of (159.82 / 46) * 64 is 222.36", "a": 159.82, "b": 46, "c": 64, "op1": "/", "op2": "*", "result": 222.36}
{"question": "Solve: (89 - 65.48) - 187", "answer": "The result of (89 - 65.48) - 187 is -163.48", "a": 89, "b": 65.48, "c": 187, "op1": "-", "op2": "-", "result": -163.48}
{"question": "Solve: (124.78 - 144) - 178", "answer": "The result of (124.78 - 144) - 178 is -197.22", "a": 124.78, "b": 144, "c": 178, "op1": "-", "op2": "-", "result": -197.22}
{"question": "Solve: (27 / 94.18) + 178", "answer": "The result of (27 / 94.18) + 178 is 178.29", "a": 27, "b": 94.18, "c": 178, "op1": "/", "op2": "+", "result": 178.29}
{"question": "Solve: (132 + 160) - 59", "answer": "The result of (132 + 160) - 59 is 233", "a": 132, "b": 160, "c": 59, "op1": "+", "op2": "-", "result": 233}
{"question": "Solve: (167.6 * 148) * 50", "answer": "The result of (167.6 * 148) * 50 is 1240240.0", "a": 167.6, "b": 148, "c": 50, "op1": "*", "op2": "*", "result": 1240240.0}
{"question": "Solve: (98.28 + 105) - 45", "answer": "The result of (98.28 + 105) - 45 is 158.28", "a": 98.28, "b": 105, "c": 45, "op1": "+", "op2": "-", "result": 158.28}
{"question": "Solve: (85 + 26) + 59", "answer": "The result of (85 + 26) + 59 is 170", "a": 85, "b": 26, "c": 59, "op1": "+", "op2": "+", "result": 170}
{"question": "Solve: (13 + 4) * 196.01", "answer": "The result of (13 + 4) * 196.01 is 3332.17", "a": 13, "b": 4, "c": 196.01, "op1": "+", "op2": "*", "result": 3332.17}
{"question": "Solve: (88 + 147) - 25", "answer": "The result of (88 + 147) - 25 is 210", "a": 88, "b": 147, "c": 25, "op1": "+", "op2": "-", "result": 210}
{"question": "Solve: (28.89 - 33.51) / 36", "answer": "The result of (28.89 - 33.51) / 36 is -0.13", "a": 28.89, "b": 33.51, "c": 36, "op1": "-", "op2": "/", "result": -0.13}
{"question": "Solve: (120.46 * 72) * 148", "answer": "The result of (120.46 * 72) * 148 is 1283621.76", "a": 120.46, "b": 72, "c": 148, "op1": "*", "op2": "*", "result": 1283621.76}
{"question": "Solve: (64.93 * 159) - 27", "answer": "The result of (64.93 * 159) - 27 is 10296.87", "a": 64.93, "b": 159, "c": 27, "op1": "*", "op2": "-", "result": 10296.87}
{"question": "Solve: (16 * 163.75) + 141.19", "answer": "The result of (16 * 163.75) + 141.19 is 2761.19", "a": 16, "b": 163.75, "c": 141.19, "op1": "*", "op2": "+", "result": 2761.19}
{"question": "Solve: (17 + 75) - 88.13", "answer": "The result of (17 + 75) - 88.13 is 3.87", "a": 17, "b": 75, "c": 88.13, "op1": "+", "op2": "-", "result": 3.87}
{"question": "Solve: (130 / 84) + 195.35", "answer": "The result of (130 / 84) + 195.35 is 196.9", "a": 130, "b": 84, "c": 195.35, "op1": "/", "op2": "+", "result": 196.9}
{"question": "Solve: (179 - 71) + 142.22", "answer": "The result of (179 - 71) + 142.22 is 250.22", "a": 179, "b": 71, "c": 142.22, "op1": "-", "op2": "+", "result": 250.22}
{"question": "Solve: (151 - 7.82) + 190", "answer": "The result of (151 - 7.82) + 190 is 333.18", "a": 151, "b": 7.82, "c": 190, "op1": "-", "op2": "+", "result": 333.18}
{"question": "Solve: (143 + 88) + 55", "answer": "The result of (143 + 88) + 55 is 286", "a": 143, "b": 88, "c": 55, "op1": "+", "op2": "+", "result": 286}
{"question": "Solve: (123 + 197) * 178", "answer": "The result of (123 + 197) * 178 is 56960", "a": 123, "b": 197, "c": 178, "op1": "+", "op2": "*", "result": 56960}
{"question": "Solve: (58 - 69) - 147.58", "answer": "The result of (58 - 69) - 147.58 is -158.58", "a": 58, "b": 69, "c": 147.58, "op1": "-", "op2": "-", "result": -158.58}
{"question": "Solve: (27 * 126) - 51", "answer": "The result of (27 * 126) - 51 is 3351", "a": 27, "b": 126, "c": 51, "op1": "*", "op2": "-", "result": 3351}
{"question": "Solve: (47 - 54) * 114", "answer": "The result of (47 - 54) * 114 is -798", "a": 47, "b": 54, "c": 114, "op1": "-", "op2": "*", "result": -798}
{"question": "Solve: (151.69 * 23.07) + 155.19", "answer": "The result of (151.69 * 23.07) + 155.19 is 3654.68", "a": 151.69, "b": 23.07, "c": 155.19, "op1": "*", "op2": "+", "result": 3654.68}
{"question": "Solve: (112 / 170.44) * 142", "answer": "The result of (112 / 170.44) * 142 is 93.31", "a": 112, "b": 170.44, "c": 142, "op1": "/", "op2": "*", "result": 93.31}
{"question": "Solve: (19 - 78) * 37", "answer": "The result of (19 - 78) * 37 is -2183", "a": 19, "b": 78, "c": 37, "op1": "-", "op2": "*", "result": -2183}
{"question": "Solve: (170.05 * 144.21) * 168.15", "answer": "The result of (170.05 * 144.21) * 168.15 is 4123527.4", "a": 170.05, "b": 144.21, "c": 168.15, "op1": "*", "op2": "*", "result": 4123527.4}
{"question": "Solve: (127.89 + 80) + 17.51", "answer": "The result of (127.89 + 80) + 17.51 is 225.4", "a": 127.89, "b": 80, "c": 17.51, "op1": "+", "op2": "+", "result": 225.4}
{"question": "Solve: (197.77 + 100) * 44", "answer": "The result of (197.77 + 100) * 44 is 13101.88", "a": 197.77, "b": 100, "c": 44, "op1": "+", "op2": "*", "result": 13101.88}
{"question": "Solve: (30.48 - 82) + 44", "answer": "The result of (30.48 - 82) + 44 is -7.52", "a": 30.48, "b": 82, "c": 44, "op1": "-", "op2": "+", "result": -7.52}
{"question": "Solve: (178 / 22) + 121", "answer": "The result of (178 / 22) + 121 is 129.09", "a": 178, "b": 22, "c": 121, "op1": "/", "op2": "+", "result": 129.09}
{"question": "Solve: (107.49 * 117.51) * 113.9", "answer": "The result of (107.49 * 117.51) * 113.9 is 1438687.97", "a": 107.49, "b": 117.51, "c": 113.9, "op1": "*", "op2": "*", "result": 1438687.97}
{"question": "Solve: (109.41 * 149) + 68", "answer": "The result of (109.41 * 149) + 68 is 16370.09", "a": 109.41, "b": 149, "c": 68, "op1": "*", "op2": "+", "result": 16370.09}
{"question": "Solve: (56 * 144) + 9", "answer": "The result of (56 * 144) + 9 is 8073", "a": 56, "b": 144, "c": 9, "op1": "*", "op2": "+", "result": 8073}
{"question": "Solve: (50 / 66) * 37", "answer": "The result of (50 / 66) * 37 is 28.03", "a": 50, "b": 66, "c": 37, "op1": "/", "op2": "*", "result": 28.03}
{"question": "Solve: (4.83 - 92) + 43", "answer": "The result of (4.83 - 92) + 43 is -44.17", "a": 4.83, "b": 92, "c": 43, "op1": "-", "op2": "+", "result": -44.17}
{"question": "Solve: (66 + 13.55) - 171", "answer": "The result of (66 + 13.55) - 171 is -91.45", "a": 66, "b": 13.55, "c": 171, "op1": "+", "op2": "-", "result": -91.45}
{"question": "Solve: (82 + 120) / 200", "answer": "The result of (82 + 120) / 200 is 1.01", "a": 82, "b": 120, "c": 200, "op1": "+", "op2": "/", "result": 1.01}
{"question": "Solve: (108 + 194.85) + 56.25", "answer": "The result of (108 + 194.85) + 56.25 is 359.1", "a": 108, "b": 194.85, "c": 56.25, "op1": "+", "op2": "+", "result": 359.1}
{"question": "Solve: (188.27 + 170.58) * 105.34", "answer": "The result of (188.27 + 170.58) * 105.34 is 37801.26", "a": 188.27, "b": 170.58, "c": 105.34, "op1": "+", "op2": "*", "result": 37801.26}
{"question": "Solve: (29 * 111.97) / 1", "answer": "The result of (29 * 111.97) / 1 is 3247.13", "a": 29, "b": 111.97, "c": 1, "op1": "*", "op2": "/", "result": 3247.13}
{"question": "Solve: (91.99 + 154) * 84", "answer": "The result of (91.99 + 154) * 84 is 20663.16", "a": 91.99, "b": 154, "c": 84, "op1": "+", "op2": "*", "result": 20663.16}
{"question": "Solve: (3.01 / 8) + 129", "answer": "The result of (3.01 / 8) + 129 is 129.38", "a": 3.01, "b": 8, "c": 129, "op1": "/", "op2": "+", "result": 129.38}
{"question": "Solve: (29 + 162) * 74", "answer": "The result of (29 + 162) * 74 is 14134", "a": 29, "b": 162, "c": 74, "op1": "+", "op2": "*", "result": 14134}
{"question": "Solve: (177 + 35) - 105", "answer": "The result of (177 + 35) - 105 is 107", "a": 177, "b": 35, "c": 105, "op1": "+", "op2": "-", "result": 107}
{"question": "Solve: (44 + 73) * 198", "answer": "The result of (44 + 73) * 198 is 23166", "a": 44, "b": 73, "c": 198, "op1": "+", "op2": "*", "result": 23166}
{"question": "Solve: (109 * 118.37) + 82", "answer": "The result of (109 * 118.37) + 82 is 12984.33", "a": 109, "b": 118.37, "c": 82, "op1": "*", "op2": "+", "result": 12984.33}
{"question": "Solve: (32.16 + 200) * 167", "answer": "The result of (32.16 + 200) * 167 is 38770.72", "a": 32.16, "b": 200, "c": 167, "op1": "+", "op2": "*", "result": 38770.72}
{"question": "Solve: (74.32 + 60.49) - 36", "answer": "The result of (74.32 + 60.49) - 36 is 98.81", "a": 74.32, "b": 60.49, "c": 36, "op1": "+", "op2": "-", "result": 98.81}
{"question": "Solve: (91.8 - 172) * 80", "answer": "The result of (91.8 - 172) * 80 is -6416.0", "a": 91.8, "b": 172, "c": 80, "op1": "-", "op2": "*", "result": -6416.0}
{"question": "Solve: (178.85 * 84) + 132", "answer": "The result of (178.85 * 84) + 132 is 15155.4", "a": 178.85, "b": 84, "c": 132, "op1": "*", "op2": "+", "result": 15155.4}
{"question": "Solve: (121.15 - 111) + 11.4", "answer": "The result of (121.15 - 111) + 11.4 is 21.55", "a": 121.15, "b": 111, "c": 11.4, "op1": "-", "op2": "+", "result": 21.55}
{"question": "Solve: (59.37 * 21.07) * 151.42", "answer": "The result of (59.37 * 21.07) * 151.42 is 189415.2", "a": 59.37, "b": 21.07, "c": 151.42, "op1": "*", "op2": "*", "result": 189415.2}
{"question": "Solve: (170.88 + 43.81) - 174", "answer": "The result of (170.88 + 43.81) - 174 is 40.69", "a": 170.88, "b": 43.81, "c": 174, "op1": "+", "op2": "-", "result": 40.69}
{"question": "Solve: (164.85 + 23) + 131", "answer": "The result of (164.85 + 23) + 131 is 318.85", "a": 164.85, "b": 23, "c": 131, "op1": "+", "op2": "+", "result": 318.85}
{"question": "Solve: (141.42 / 188) + 17.84", "answer": "The result of (141.42 / 188) + 17.84 is 18.59", "a": 141.42, "b": 188, "c": 17.84, "op1": "/", "op2": "+", "result": 18.59}
{"question": "Solve: (196 + 7) + 120", "answer": "The result of (196 + 7) + 120 is 323", "a": 196, "b": 7, "c": 120, "op1": "+", "op2": "+", "result": 323}
{"question": "Solve: (50 - 161) * 162.83", "answer": "The result of (50 - 161) * 162.83 is -18074.13", "a": 50, "b": 161, "c": 162.83, "op1": "-", "op2": "*", "result": -18074.13}
{"question": "Solve: (160.77 - 187) - 145", "answer": "The result of (160.77 - 187) - 145 is -171.23", "a": 160.77, "b": 187, "c": 145, "op1": "-", "op2": "-", "result": -171.23}
{"question": "Solve: (129 * 95) + 123", "answer": "The result of (129 * 95) + 123 is 12378", "a": 129, "b": 95, "c": 123, "op1": "*", "op2": "+", "result": 12378}
{"question": "Solve: (168 * 132) * 115.7", "answer": "The result of (168 * 132) * 115.7 is 2565763.2", "a": 168, "b": 132, "c": 115.7, "op1": "*", "op2": "*", "result": 2565763.2}
{"question": "Solve: (24.23 + 44) * 77", "answer": "The result of (24.23 + 44) * 77 is 5253.71", "a": 24.23, "b": 44, "c": 77, "op1": "+", "op2": "*", "result": 5253.71}
{"question": "Solve: (17.51 + 35.3) - 23", "answer": "The result of (17.51 + 35.3) - 23 is 29.81", "a": 17.51, "b": 35.3, "c": 23, "op1": "+", "op2": "-", "result": 29.81}
{"question": "Solve: (166.25 - 128) / 52", "answer": "The result of (166.25 - 128) / 52 is 0.74", "a": 166.25, "b": 128, "c": 52, "op1": "-", "op2": "/", "result": 0.74}
{"question": "Solve: (100 / 1) - 67.29", "answer": "The result of (100 / 1) - 67.29 is 32.71", "a": 100, "b": 1, "c": 67.29, "op1": "/", "op2": "-", "result": 32.71}
{"question": "Solve: (199 - 156) - 142.55", "answer": "The result of (199 - 156) - 142.55 is -99.55", "a": 199, "b": 156, "c": 142.55, "op1": "-", "op2": "-", "result": -99.55}
{"question": "Solve: (70 * 154.9) - 80.42", "answer": "The result of (70 * 154.9) - 80.42 is 10762.58", "a": 70, "b": 154.9, "c": 80.42, "op1": "*", "op2": "-", "result": 10762.58}
{"question": "Solve: (68 - 121) - 114", "answer": "The result of (68 - 121) - 114 is -167", "a": 68, "b": 121, "c": 114, "op1": "-", "op2": "-", "result": -167}
{"question": "Solve: (2 + 83) / 169", "answer": "The result of (2 + 83) / 169 is 0.5", "a": 2, "b": 83, "c": 169, "op1": "+", "op2": "/", "result": 0.5}
{"question": "Solve: (130 - 171.78) / 73.34", "answer": "The result of (130 - 171.78) / 73.34 is -0.57", "a": 130, "b": 171.78, "c": 73.34, "op1": "-", "op2": "/", "result": -0.57}
{"question": "Solve: (191.23 - 108) * 28.06", "answer": "The result of (191.23 - 108) * 28.06 is 2335.43", "a": 191.23, "b": 108, "c": 28.06, "op1": "-", "op2": "*", "result": 2335.43}
{"question": "Solve: (154 / 107.69) - 19", "answer": "The result of (154 / 107.69) - 19 is -17.57", "a": 154, "b": 107.69, "c": 19, "op1": "/", "op2": "-", "result": -17.57}
{"question": "Solve: (193 - 199.59) + 142.17", "answer": "The result of (193 - 199.59) + 142.17 is 135.58", "a": 193, "b": 199.59, "c": 142.17, "op1": "-", "op2": "+", "result": 135.58}
{"question": "Solve: (187 - 61.19) + 179", "answer": "The result of (187 - 61.19) + 179 is 304.81", "a": 187, "b": 61.19, "c": 179, "op1": "-", "op2": "+", "result": 304.81}
{"question": "Solve: (86.37 - 83) - 101", "answer": "The result of (86.37 - 83) - 101 is -97.63", "a": 86.37, "b": 83, "c": 101, "op1": "-", "op2": "-", "result": -97.63}
{"question": "Solve: (7.56 + 99.14) / 117", "answer": "The result of (7.56 + 99.14) / 117 is 0.91", "a": 7.56, "b": 99.14, "c": 117, "op1": "+", "op2": "/", "result": 0.91}
{"question": "Solve: (152 * 49) / 42.33", "answer": "The result of (152 * 49) / 42.33 is 175.95", "a": 152, "b": 49, "c": 42.33, "op1": "*", "op2": "/", "result": 175.95}
{"question": "Solve: (44 + 186) - 32.83", "answer": "The result of (44 + 186) - 32.83 is 197.17", "a": 44, "b": 186, "c": 32.83, "op1": "+", "op2": "-", "result": 197.17}
{"question": "Solve: (11 + 48) - 163", "answer": "The result of (11 + 48) - 163 is -104", "a": 11, "b": 48, "c": 163, "op1": "+", "op2": "-", "result": -104}
{"question": "Solve: (27 * 152.16) - 72", "answer": "The result of (27 * 152.16) - 72 is 4036.32", "a": 27, "b": 152.16, "c": 72, "op1": "*", "op2": "-", "result": 4036.32}
{"question": "Solve: (39 + 144) / 172", "answer": "The result of (39 + 144) / 172 is 1.06", "a": 39, "b": 144, "c": 172, "op1": "+", "op2": "/", "result": 1.06}
{"question": "Solve: (188.6 - 98.19) - 152", "answer": "The result of (188.6 - 98.19) - 152 is -61.59", "a": 188.6, "b": 98.19, "c": 152, "op1": "-", "op2": "-", "result": -61.59}
{"question": "Solve: (184 - 81) * 19", "answer": "The result of (184 - 81) * 19 is 1957", "a": 184, "b": 81, "c": 19, "op1": "-", "op2": "*", "result": 1957}
{"question": "Solve: (45 - 161) - 162", "answer": "The result of (45 - 161) - 162 is -278", "a": 45, "b": 161, "c": 162, "op1": "-", "op2": "-", "result": -278}
{"question": "Solve: (63 + 194) / 33", "answer": "The result of (63 + 194) / 33 is 7.79", "a": 63, "b": 194, "c": 33, "op1": "+", "op2": "/", "result": 7.79}
{"question": "Solve: (41 - 97.87) * 56", "answer": "The result of (41 - 97.87) * 56 is -3184.72", "a": 41, "b": 97.87, "c": 56, "op1": "-", "op2": "*", "result": -3184.72}
{"question": "Solve: (42 - 22) - 131", "answer": "The result of (42 - 22) - 131 is -111", "a": 42, "b": 22, "c": 131, "op1": "-", "op2": "-", "result": -111}
{"question": "Solve: (70.0 * 42) - 192", "answer": "The result of (70.0 * 42) - 192 is 2748.0", "a": 70.0, "b": 42, "c": 192, "op1": "*", "op2": "-", "result": 2748.0}
{"question": "Solve: (197.57 / 98) * 63", "answer": "The result of (197.57 / 98) * 63 is 127.01", "a": 197.57, "b": 98, "c": 63, "op1": "/", "op2": "*", "result": 127.01}
{"question": "Solve: (176 - 98) - 195", "answer": "The result of (176 - 98) - 195 is -117", "a": 176, "b": 98, "c": 195, "op1": "-", "op2": "-", "result": -117}
{"question": "Solve: (79 / 114) * 49", "answer": "The result of (79 / 114) * 49 is 33.96", "a": 79, "b": 114, "c": 49, "op1": "/", "op2": "*", "result": 33.96}
{"question": "Solve: (43 / 144.28) + 95", "answer": "The result of (43 / 144.28) + 95 is 95.3", "a": 43, "b": 144.28, "c": 95, "op1": "/", "op2": "+", "result": 95.3}
{"question": "Solve: (137 * 51.51) - 167", "answer": "The result of (137 * 51.51) - 167 is 6889.87", "a": 137, "b": 51.51, "c": 167, "op1": "*", "op2": "-", "result": 6889.87}
{"question": "Solve: (115.54 * 24) + 189", "answer": "The result of (115.54 * 24) + 189 is 2961.96", "a": 115.54, "b": 24, "c": 189, "op1": "*", "op2": "+", "result": 2961.96}
{"question": "Solve: (137 + 53.83) - 128.98", "answer": "The result of (137 + 53.83) - 128.98 is 61.85", "a": 137, "b": 53.83, "c": 128.98, "op1": "+", "op2": "-", "result": 61.85}
{"question": "Solve: (155 - 144.41) + 98", "answer": "The result of (155 - 144.41) + 98 is 108.59", "a": 155, "b": 144.41, "c": 98, "op1": "-", "op2": "+", "result": 108.59}
{"question": "Solve: (39 + 194) / 70", "answer": "The result of (39 + 194) / 70 is 3.33", "a": 39, "b": 194, "c": 70, "op1": "+", "op2": "/", "result": 3.33}
{"question": "Solve: (99 / 4) * 75", "answer": "The result of (99 / 4) * 75 is 1856.25", "a": 99, "b": 4, "c": 75, "op1": "/", "op2": "*", "result": 1856.25}
{"question": "Solve: (96 - 186) + 144", "answer": "The result of (96 - 186) + 144 is 54", "a": 96, "b": 186, "c": 144, "op1": "-", "op2": "+", "result": 54}
{"question": "Solve: (1 * 195) / 95", "answer": "The result of (1 * 195) / 95 is 2.05", "a": 1, "b": 195, "c": 95, "op1": "*", "op2": "/", "result": 2.05}
{"question": "Solve: (200 + 158) / 49", "answer": "The result of (200 + 158) / 49 is 7.31", "a": 200, "b": 158, "c": 49, "op1": "+", "op2": "/", "result": 7.31}
{"question": "Solve: (173.52 * 52) + 164.57", "answer": "The result of (173.52 * 52) + 164.57 is 9187.61", "a": 173.52, "b": 52, "c": 164.57, "op1": "*", "op2": "+", "result": 9187.61}
{"question": "Solve: (110 - 66) + 103", "answer": "The result of (110 - 66) + 103 is 147", "a": 110, "b": 66, "c": 103, "op1": "-", "op2": "+", "result": 147}
{"question": "Solve: (152.43 + 186) - 6", "answer": "The result of (152.43 + 186) - 6 is 332.43", "a": 152.43, "b": 186, "c": 6, "op1": "+", "op2": "-", "result": 332.43}
{"question": "Solve: (40 * 43) * 53", "answer": "The result of (40 * 43) * 53 is 91160", "a": 40, "b": 43, "c": 53, "op1": "*", "op2": "*", "result": 91160}
{"question": "Solve: (128.85 / 23) + 80", "answer": "The result of (128.85 / 23) + 80 is 85.6", "a": 128.85, "b": 23, "c": 80, "op1": "/", "op2": "+", "result": 85.6}
{"question": "Solve: (7.39 - 80) - 180", "answer": "The result of (7.39 - 80) - 180 is -252.61", "a": 7.39, "b": 80, "c": 180, "op1": "-", "op2": "-", "result": -252.61}
{"question": "Solve: (146 * 116.79) - 132", "answer": "The result of (146 * 116.79) - 132 is 16919.34", "a": 146, "b": 116.79, "c": 132, "op1": "*", "op2": "-", "result": 16919.34}
{"question": "Solve: (94.48 + 57.63) + 200", "answer": "The result of (94.48 + 57.63) + 200 is 352.11", "a": 94.48, "b": 57.63, "c": 200, "op1": "+", "op2": "+", "result": 352.11}
{"question": "Solve: (156.22 * 27) + 116", "answer": "The result of (156.22 * 27) + 116 is 4333.94", "a": 156.22, "b": 27, "c": 116, "op1": "*", "op2": "+", "result": 4333.94}
{"question": "Solve: (16 + 47) * 3", "answer": "The result of (16 + 47) * 3 is 189", "a": 16, "b": 47, "c": 3, "op1": "+", "op2": "*", "result": 189}
{"question": "Solve: (156 * 139) + 130", "answer": "The result of (156 * 139) + 130 is 21814", "a": 156, "b": 139, "c": 130, "op1": "*", "op2": "+", "result": 21814}
{"question": "Solve: (178 / 64) * 146", "answer": "The result of (178 / 64) * 146 is 406.06", "a": 178, "b": 64, "c": 146, "op1": "/", "op2": "*", "result": 406.06}
{"question": "Solve: (119 + 74) * 98.76", "answer": "The result of (119 + 74) * 98.76 is 19060.68", "a": 119, "b": 74, "c": 98.76, "op1": "+", "op2": "*", "result": 19060.68}
{"question": "Solve: (99 - 3) + 77", "answer": "The result of (99 - 3) + 77 is 173", "a": 99, "b": 3, "c": 77, "op1": "-", "op2": "+", "result": 173}
{"question": "Solve: (187 * 42.46) * 23", "answer": "The result of (187 * 42.46) * 23 is 182620.46", "a": 187, "b": 42.46, "c": 23, "op1": "*", "op2": "*", "result": 182620.46}
{"question": "Solve: (165 / 111) / 176", "answer": "The result of (165 / 111) / 176 is 0.01", "a": 165, "b": 111, "c": 176, "op1": "/", "op2": "/", "result": 0.01}
{"question": "Solve: (193 - 199) + 73.99", "answer": "The result of (193 - 199) + 73.99 is 67.99", "a": 193, "b": 199, "c": 73.99, "op1": "-", "op2": "+", "result": 67.99}
{"question": "Solve: (57 + 54) * 187", "answer": "The result of (57 + 54) * 187 is 20757", "a": 57, "b": 54, "c": 187, "op1": "+", "op2": "*", "result": 20757}
{"question": "Solve: (136 - 79.98) * 57", "answer": "The result of (136 - 79.98) * 57 is 3193.14", "a": 136, "b": 79.98, "c": 57, "op1": "-", "op2": "*", "result": 3193.14}
{"question": "Solve: (61 * 99.26) / 86", "answer": "The result of (61 * 99.26) / 86 is 70.41", "a": 61, "b": 99.26, "c": 86, "op1": "*", "op2": "/", "result": 70.41}
{"question": "Solve: (94.07 - 164) + 46.83", "answer": "The result of (94.07 - 164) + 46.83 is -23.1", "a": 94.07, "b": 164, "c": 46.83, "op1": "-", "op2": "+", "result": -23.1}
{"question": "Solve: (83 * 157) + 173.31", "answer": "The result of (83 * 157) + 173.31 is 13204.31", "a": 83, "b": 157, "c": 173.31, "op1": "*", "op2": "+", "result": 13204.31}
{"question": "Solve: (134.4 - 115) / 32", "answer": "The result of (134.4 - 115) / 32 is 0.61", "a": 134.4, "b": 115, "c": 32, "op1": "-", "op2": "/", "result": 0.61}
{"question": "Solve: (151.0 - 28.38) + 68", "answer": "The result of (151.0 - 28.38) + 68 is 190.62", "a": 151.0, "b": 28.38, "c": 68, "op1": "-", "op2": "+", "result": 190.62}
{"question": "Solve: (14 - 51) + 151.41", "answer": "The result of (14 - 51) + 151.41 is 114.41", "a": 14, "b": 51, "c": 151.41, "op1": "-", "op2": "+", "result": 114.41}
{"question": "Solve: (116 + 115) / 27", "answer": "The result of (116 + 115) / 27 is 8.56", "a": 116, "b": 115, "c": 27, "op1": "+", "op2": "/", "result": 8.56}
{"question": "Solve: (70 + 6) / 195.08", "answer": "The result of (70 + 6) / 195.08 is 0.39", "a": 70, "b": 6, "c": 195.08, "op1": "+", "op2": "/", "result": 0.39}
{"question": "Solve: (3 / 167.69) * 20.36", "answer": "The result of (3 / 167.69) * 20.36 is 0.36", "a": 3, "b": 167.69, "c": 20.36, "op1": "/", "op2": "*", "result": 0.36}
{"question": "Solve: (3 + 131.34) + 48.31", "answer": "The result of (3 + 131.34) + 48.31 is 182.65", "a": 3, "b": 131.34, "c": 48.31, "op1": "+", "op2": "+", "result": 182.65}
{"question": "Solve: (49 + 190.58) + 85", "answer": "The result of (49 + 190.58) + 85 is 324.58", "a": 49, "b": 190.58, "c": 85, "op1": "+", "op2": "+", "result": 324.58}
{"question": "Solve: (137 * 194) / 142", "answer": "The result of (137 * 194) / 142 is 187.17", "a": 137, "b": 194, "c": 142, "op1": "*", "op2": "/", "result": 187.17}
{"question": "Solve: (56.89 - 137) * 178", "answer": "The result of (56.89 - 137) * 178 is -14259.58", "a": 56.89, "b": 137, "c": 178, "op1": "-", "op2": "*", "result": -14259.58}
{"question": "Solve: (103 * 137) + 61", "answer": "The result of (103 * 137) + 61 is 14172", "a": 103, "b": 137, "c": 61, "op1": "*", "op2": "+", "result": 14172}
{"question": "Solve: (163 + 25) * 69.44", "answer": "The result of (163 + 25) * 69.44 is 13054.72", "a": 163, "b": 25, "c": 69.44, "op1": "+", "op2": "*", "result": 13054.72}
{"question": "Solve: (3.15 + 145) * 66", "answer": "The result of (3.15 + 145) * 66 is 9777.9", "a": 3.15, "b": 145, "c": 66, "op1": "+", "op2": "*", "result": 9777.9}
{"question": "Solve: (72.48 - 139.11) / 195.07", "answer": "The result of (72.48 - 139.11) / 195.07 is -0.34", "a": 72.48, "b": 139.11, "c": 195.07, "op1": "-", "op2": "/", "result": -0.34}
{"question": "Solve: (185 / 50) + 62", "answer": "The result of (185 / 50) + 62 is 65.7", "a": 185, "b": 50, "c": 62, "op1": "/", "op2": "+", "result": 65.7}
{"question": "Solve: (76 * 198) - 41", "answer": "The result of (76 * 198) - 41 is 15007", "a": 76, "b": 198, "c": 41, "op1": "*", "op2": "-", "result": 15007}
{"question": "Solve: (88 + 189.54) - 126.27", "answer": "The result of (88 + 189.54) - 126.27 is 151.27", "a": 88, "b": 189.54, "c": 126.27, "op1": "+", "op2": "-", "result": 151.27}
{"question": "Solve: (6 / 193) + 180", "answer": "The result of (6 / 193) + 180 is 180.03", "a": 6, "b": 193, "c": 180, "op1": "/", "op2": "+", "result": 180.03}
{"question": "Solve: (115.43 / 113) + 19", "answer": "The result of (115.43 / 113) + 19 is 20.02", "a": 115.43, "b": 113, "c": 19, "op1": "/", "op2": "+", "result": 20.02}
{"question": "Solve: (8 / 56.51) / 97.03", "answer": "The result of (8 / 56.51) / 97.03 is 0.0", "a": 8, "b": 56.51, "c": 97.03, "op1": "/", "op2": "/", "result": 0.0}
{"question": "Solve: (199 - 15) + 92.88", "answer": "The result of (199 - 15) + 92.88 is 276.88", "a": 199, "b": 15, "c": 92.88, "op1": "-", "op2": "+", "result": 276.88}
{"question": "Solve: (115 * 119) + 80", "answer": "The result of (115 * 119) + 80 is 13765", "a": 115, "b": 119, "c": 80, "op1": "*", "op2": "+", "result": 13765}
{"question": "Solve: (90 * 190.7) / 188", "answer": "The result of (90 * 190.7) / 188 is 91.29", "a": 90, "b": 190.7, "c": 188, "op1": "*", "op2": "/", "result": 91.29}
{"question": "Solve: (97 + 176) * 145.14", "answer": "The result of (97 + 176) * 145.14 is 39623.22", "a": 97, "b": 176, "c": 145.14, "op1": "+", "op2": "*", "result": 39623.22}
{"question": "Solve: (175.24 - 46) + 48", "answer": "The result of (175.24 - 46) + 48 is 177.24", "a": 175.24, "b": 46, "c": 48, "op1": "-", "op2": "+", "result": 177.24}
{"question": "Solve: (172 - 154) + 17", "answer": "The result of (172 - 154) + 17 is 35", "a": 172, "b": 154, "c": 17, "op1": "-", "op2": "+", "result": 35}
{"question": "Solve: (21 + 22) * 29", "answer": "The result of (21 + 22) * 29 is 1247", "a": 21, "b": 22, "c": 29, "op1": "+", "op2": "*", "result": 1247}
{"question": "Solve: (22 * 19) * 118", "answer": "The result of (22 * 19) * 118 is 49324", "a": 22, "b": 19, "c": 118, "op1": "*", "op2": "*", "result": 49324}
{"question": "Solve: (73.66 - 43) * 196", "answer": "The result of (73.66 - 43) * 196 is 6009.36", "a": 73.66, "b": 43, "c": 196, "op1": "-", "op2": "*", "result": 6009.36}
{"question": "Solve: (139 + 167.93) * 125.65", "answer": "The result of (139 + 167.93) * 125.65 is 38565.75", "a": 139, "b": 167.93, "c": 125.65, "op1": "+", "op2": "*", "result": 38565.75}
{"question": "Solve: (37 * 103.91) + 97", "answer": "The result of (37 * 103.91) + 97 is 3941.67", "a": 37, "b": 103.91, "c": 97, "op1": "*", "op2": "+", "result": 3941.67}
{"question": "Solve: (8 * 93) * 180.31", "answer": "The result of (8 * 93) * 180.31 is 134150.64", "a": 8, "b": 93, "c": 180.31, "op1": "*", "op2": "*", "result": 134150.64}
{"question": "Solve: (139.61 + 196) * 61", "answer": "The result of (139.61 + 196) * 61 is 20472.21", "a": 139.61, "b": 196, "c": 61, "op1": "+", "op2": "*", "result": 20472.21}
{"question": "Solve: (52.48 + 176) * 116", "answer": "The result of (52.48 + 176) * 116 is 26503.68", "a": 52.48, "b": 176, "c": 116, "op1": "+", "op2": "*", "result": 26503.68}
{"question": "Solve: (102 * 6) + 75", "answer": "The result of (102 * 6) + 75 is 687", "a": 102, "b": 6, "c": 75, "op1": "*", "op2": "+", "result": 687}
{"question": "Solve: (139 + 81) - 2.86", "answer": "The result of (139 + 81) - 2.86 is 217.14", "a": 139, "b": 81, "c": 2.86, "op1": "+", "op2": "-", "result": 217.14}
{"question": "Solve: (84 * 42) - 164", "answer": "The result of (84 * 42) - 164 is 3364", "a": 84, "b": 42, "c": 164, "op1": "*", "op2": "-", "result": 3364}
{"question": "Solve: (175 + 96) / 42", "answer": "The result of (175 + 96) / 42 is 6.45", "a": 175, "b": 96, "c": 42, "op1": "+", "op2": "/", "result": 6.45}
{"question": "Solve: (56 * 5) * 90", "answer": "The result of (56 * 5) * 90 is 25200", "a": 56, "b": 5, "c": 90, "op1": "*", "op2": "*", "result": 25200}
{"question": "Solve: (151 - 104) + 22", "answer": "The result of (151 - 104) + 22 is 69", "a": 151, "b": 104, "c": 22, "op1": "-", "op2": "+", "result": 69}
{"question": "Solve: (140.29 - 15) + 128", "answer": "The result of (140.29 - 15) + 128 is 253.29", "a": 140.29, "b": 15, "c": 128, "op1": "-", "op2": "+", "result": 253.29}
{"question": "Solve: (163.72 - 6.39) / 184", "answer": "The result of (163.72 - 6.39) / 184 is 0.86", "a": 163.72, "b": 6.39, "c": 184, "op1": "-", "op2": "/", "result": 0.86}
{"question": "Solve: (63.05 / 77.25) / 83", "answer": "The result of (63.05 / 77.25) / 83 is 0.01", "a": 63.05, "b": 77.25, "c": 83, "op1": "/", "op2": "/", "result": 0.01}
{"question": "Solve: (70 * 12) - 29", "answer": "The result of (70 * 12) - 29 is 811", "a": 70, "b": 12, "c": 29, "op1": "*", "op2": "-", "result": 811}
{"question": "Solve: (11.94 - 21) - 144", "answer": "The result of (11.94 - 21) - 144 is -153.06", "a": 11.94, "b": 21, "c": 144, "op1": "-", "op2": "-", "result": -153.06}
{"question": "Solve: (139 * 3.4) - 105.83", "answer": "The result of (139 * 3.4) - 105.83 is 366.77", "a": 139, "b": 3.4, "c": 105.83, "op1": "*", "op2": "-", "result": 366.77}
{"question": "Solve: (196.69 + 141.5) - 133.04", "answer": "The result of (196.69 + 141.5) - 133.04 is 205.15", "a": 196.69, "b": 141.5, "c": 133.04, "op1": "+", "op2": "-", "result": 205.15}
{"question": "Solve: (114 - 181) / 145.82", "answer": "The result of (114 - 181) / 145.82 is -0.46", "a": 114, "b": 181, "c": 145.82, "op1": "-", "op2": "/", "result": -0.46}
{"question": "Solve: (42.82 * 162) * 138", "answer": "The result of (42.82 * 162) * 138 is 957283.92", "a": 42.82, "b": 162, "c": 138, "op1": "*", "op2": "*", "result": 957283.92}
{"question": "Solve: (193 - 46) + 8", "answer": "The result of (193 - 46) + 8 is 155", "a": 193, "b": 46, "c": 8, "op1": "-", "op2": "+", "result": 155}
{"question": "Solve: (193 * 78) * 27", "answer": "The result of (193 * 78) * 27 is 406458", "a": 193, "b": 78, "c": 27, "op1": "*", "op2": "*", "result": 406458}
{"question": "Solve: (57 / 156) * 75", "answer": "The result of (57 / 156) * 75 is 27.4", "a": 57, "b": 156, "c": 75, "op1": "/", "op2": "*", "result": 27.4}
{"question": "Solve: (3.94 + 129) + 187", "answer": "The result of (3.94 + 129) + 187 is 319.94", "a": 3.94, "b": 129, "c": 187, "op1": "+", "op2": "+", "result": 319.94}
{"question": "Solve: (51 - 27.55) / 37", "answer": "The result of (51 - 27.55) / 37 is 0.63", "a": 51, "b": 27.55, "c": 37, "op1": "-", "op2": "/", "result": 0.63}
{"question": "Solve: (30.32 - 4) + 36", "answer": "The result of (30.32 - 4) + 36 is 62.32", "a": 30.32, "b": 4, "c": 36, "op1": "-", "op2": "+", "result": 62.32}
{"question": "Solve: (56 - 178.49) + 182", "answer": "The result of (56 - 178.49) + 182 is 59.51", "a": 56, "b": 178.49, "c": 182, "op1": "-", "op2": "+", "result": 59.51}
{"question": "Solve: (127 + 56) + 195.79", "answer": "The result of (127 + 56) + 195.79 is 378.79", "a": 127, "b": 56, "c": 195.79, "op1": "+", "op2": "+", "result": 378.79}
{"question": "Solve: (96.48 - 6) + 163", "answer": "The result of (96.48 - 6) + 163 is 253.48", "a": 96.48, "b": 6, "c": 163, "op1": "-", "op2": "+", "result": 253.48}
{"question": "Solve: (123 - 97) * 134.02", "answer": "The result of (123 - 97) * 134.02 is 3484.52", "a": 123, "b": 97, "c": 134.02, "op1": "-", "op2": "*", "result": 3484.52}
{"question": "Solve: (121 - 159.66) / 184", "answer": "The result of (121 - 159.66) / 184 is -0.21", "a": 121, "b": 159.66, "c": 184, "op1": "-", "op2": "/", "result": -0.21}
{"question": "Solve: (89 + 81) * 60", "answer": "The result of (89 + 81) * 60 is 10200", "a": 89, "b": 81, "c": 60, "op1": "+", "op2": "*", "result": 10200}
{"question": "Solve: (67 - 20.81) / 199", "answer": "The result of (67 - 20.81) / 199 is 0.23", "a": 67, "b": 20.81, "c": 199, "op1": "-", "op2": "/", "result": 0.23}
{"question": "Solve: (30 / 81.76) - 187", "answer": "The result of (30 / 81.76) - 187 is -186.63", "a": 30, "b": 81.76, "c": 187, "op1": "/", "op2": "-", "result": -186.63}
{"question": "Solve: (32.08 + 148.4) + 58.61", "answer": "The result of (32.08 + 148.4) + 58.61 is 239.09", "a": 32.08, "b": 148.4, "c": 58.61, "op1": "+", "op2": "+", "result": 239.09}
{"question": "Solve: (18 * 89) + 35", "answer": "The result of (18 * 89) + 35 is 1637", "a": 18, "b": 89, "c": 35, "op1": "*", "op2": "+", "result": 1637}
{"question": "Solve: (102 * 140) - 80", "answer": "The result of (102 * 140) - 80 is 14200", "a": 102, "b": 140, "c": 80, "op1": "*", "op2": "-", "result": 14200}
{"question": "Solve: (137.16 + 121) + 137", "answer": "The result of (137.16 + 121) + 137 is 395.16", "a": 137.16, "b": 121, "c": 137, "op1": "+", "op2": "+", "result": 395.16}
{"question": "Solve: (42 + 35) + 45", "answer": "The result of (42 + 35) + 45 is 122", "a": 42, "b": 35, "c": 45, "op1": "+", "op2": "+", "result": 122}
{"question": "Solve: (29 + 7) * 116.28", "answer": "The result of (29 + 7) * 116.28 is 4186.08", "a": 29, "b": 7, "c": 116.28, "op1": "+", "op2": "*", "result": 4186.08}
{"question": "Solve: (154.84 + 165) + 50", "answer": "The result of (154.84 + 165) + 50 is 369.84", "a": 154.84, "b": 165, "c": 50, "op1": "+", "op2": "+", "result": 369.84}
{"question": "Solve: (141.81 * 75) + 104", "answer": "The result of (141.81 * 75) + 104 is 10739.75", "a": 141.81, "b": 75, "c": 104, "op1": "*", "op2": "+", "result": 10739.75}
{"question": "Solve: (6 - 24) * 193", "answer": "The result of (6 - 24) * 193 is -3474", "a": 6, "b": 24, "c": 193, "op1": "-", "op2": "*", "result": -3474}
{"question": "Solve: (77 * 39) * 173.19", "answer": "The result of (77 * 39) * 173.19 is 520089.57", "a": 77, "b": 39, "c": 173.19, "op1": "*", "op2": "*", "result": 520089.57}
{"question": "Solve: (83.16 + 172) + 127.54", "answer": "The result of (83.16 + 172) + 127.54 is 382.7", "a": 83.16, "b": 172, "c": 127.54, "op1": "+", "op2": "+", "result": 382.7}
{"question": "Solve: (179 - 97.33) * 200", "answer": "The result of (179 - 97.33) * 200 is 16334.0", "a": 179, "b": 97.33, "c": 200, "op1": "-", "op2": "*", "result": 16334.0}
{"question": "Solve: (191 - 3) / 129.63", "answer": "The result of (191 - 3) / 129.63 is 1.45", "a": 191, "b": 3, "c": 129.63, "op1": "-", "op2": "/", "result": 1.45}
{"question": "Solve: (7 * 157) + 147", "answer": "The result of (7 * 157) + 147 is 1246", "a": 7, "b": 157, "c": 147, "op1": "*", "op2": "+", "result": 1246}
{"question": "Solve: (65 - 147) - 96", "answer": "The result of (65 - 147) - 96 is -178", "a": 65, "b": 147, "c": 96, "op1": "-", "op2": "-", "result": -178}
{"question": "Solve: (20 - 112) + 16", "answer": "The result of (20 - 112) + 16 is -76", "a": 20, "b": 112, "c": 16, "op1": "-", "op2": "+", "result": -76}
{"question": "Solve: (137.61 - 103) - 120", "answer": "The result of (137.61 - 103) - 120 is -85.39", "a": 137.61, "b": 103, "c": 120, "op1": "-", "op2": "-", "result": -85.39}
{"question": "Solve: (195 + 87.92) + 41", "answer": "The result of (195 + 87.92) + 41 is 323.92", "a": 195, "b": 87.92, "c": 41, "op1": "+", "op2": "+", "result": 323.92}
{"question": "Solve: (173 * 88.24) * 44", "answer": "The result of (173 * 88.24) * 44 is 671682.88", "a": 173, "b": 88.24, "c": 44, "op1": "*", "op2": "*", "result": 671682.88}
{"question": "Solve: (27 - 131.66) - 47", "answer": "The result of (27 - 131.66) - 47 is -151.66", "a": 27, "b": 131.66, "c": 47, "op1": "-", "op2": "-", "result": -151.66}
{"question": "Solve: (7 + 8) * 29.74", "answer": "The result of (7 + 8) * 29.74 is 446.1", "a": 7, "b": 8, "c": 29.74, "op1": "+", "op2": "*", "result": 446.1}
{"question": "Solve: (132 - 140) + 118", "answer": "The result of (132 - 140) + 118 is 110", "a": 132, "b": 140, "c": 118, "op1": "-", "op2": "+", "result": 110}
{"question": "Solve: (124 * 62) - 53", "answer": "The result of (124 * 62) - 53 is 7635", "a": 124, "b": 62, "c": 53, "op1": "*", "op2": "-", "result": 7635}
{"question": "Solve: (155 / 195.65) - 105", "answer": "The result of (155 / 195.65) - 105 is -104.21", "a": 155, "b": 195.65, "c": 105, "op1": "/", "op2": "-", "result": -104.21}
{"question": "Solve: (27 + 112) - 158", "answer": "The result of (27 + 112) - 158 is -19", "a": 27, "b": 112, "c": 158, "op1": "+", "op2": "-", "result": -19}
{"question": "Solve: (54 - 61.24) / 198.08", "answer": "The result of (54 - 61.24) / 198.08 is -0.04", "a": 54, "b": 61.24, "c": 198.08, "op1": "-", "op2": "/", "result": -0.04}
{"question": "Solve: (114 + 119) - 129", "answer": "The result of (114 + 119) - 129 is 104", "a": 114, "b": 119, "c": 129, "op1": "+", "op2": "-", "result": 104}
{"question": "Solve: (171 + 119) * 40.57", "answer": "The result of (171 + 119) * 40.57 is 11765.3", "a": 171, "b": 119, "c": 40.57, "op1": "+", "op2": "*", "result": 11765.3}
{"question": "Solve: (64 - 27) - 20", "answer": "The result of (64 - 27) - 20 is 17", "a": 64, "b": 27, "c": 20, "op1": "-", "op2": "-", "result": 17}
{"question": "Solve: (102 + 45.33) + 32", "answer": "The result of (102 + 45.33) + 32 is 179.33", "a": 102, "b": 45.33, "c": 32, "op1": "+", "op2": "+", "result": 179.33}
{"question": "Solve: (155 - 84) * 80", "answer": "The result of (155 - 84) * 80 is 5680", "a": 155, "b": 84, "c": 80, "op1": "-", "op2": "*", "result": 5680}
{"question": "Solve: (191 / 182) / 168", "answer": "The result of (191 / 182) / 168 is 0.01", "a": 191, "b": 182, "c": 168, "op1": "/", "op2": "/", "result": 0.01}
{"question": "Solve: (186 * 187.9) - 54.98", "answer": "The result of (186 * 187.9) - 54.98 is 34894.42", "a": 186, "b": 187.9, "c": 54.98, "op1": "*", "op2": "-", "result": 34894.42}
{"question": "Solve: (105.51 - 88) + 47.37", "answer": "The result of (105.51 - 88) + 47.37 is 64.88", "a": 105.51, "b": 88, "c": 47.37, "op1": "-", "op2": "+", "result": 64.88}
{"question": "Solve: (55.06 - 79) + 100", "answer": "The result of (55.06 - 79) + 100 is 76.06", "a": 55.06, "b": 79, "c": 100, "op1": "-", "op2": "+", "result": 76.06}
{"question": "Solve: (17 - 92) + 139.72", "answer": "The result of (17 - 92) + 139.72 is 64.72", "a": 17, "b": 92, "c": 139.72, "op1": "-", "op2": "+", "result": 64.72}
{"question": "Solve: (6 + 183) + 16", "answer": "The result of (6 + 183) + 16 is 205", "a": 6, "b": 183, "c": 16, "op1": "+", "op2": "+", "result": 205}
{"question": "Solve: (143.53 - 54.06) * 30", "answer": "The result of (143.53 - 54.06) * 30 is 2684.1", "a": 143.53, "b": 54.06, "c": 30, "op1": "-", "op2": "*", "result": 2684.1}
{"question": "Solve: (69.84 * 21.27) + 190.98", "answer": "The result of (69.84 * 21.27) + 190.98 is 1676.48", "a": 69.84, "b": 21.27, "c": 190.98, "op1": "*", "op2": "+", "result": 1676.48}
{"question": "Solve: (148 - 3) - 58.33", "answer": "The result of (148 - 3) - 58.33 is 86.67", "a": 148, "b": 3, "c": 58.33, "op1": "-", "op2": "-", "result": 86.67}
{"question": "Solve: (188.09 - 14) * 41", "answer": "The result of (188.09 - 14) * 41 is 7137.69", "a": 188.09, "b": 14, "c": 41, "op1": "-", "op2": "*", "result": 7137.69}
{"question": "Solve: (121.78 + 55) / 177.37", "answer": "The result of (121.78 + 55) / 177.37 is 1.0", "a": 121.78, "b": 55, "c": 177.37, "op1": "+", "op2": "/", "result": 1.0}
{"question": "Solve: (107.3 / 80.55) - 133", "answer": "The result of (107.3 / 80.55) - 133 is -131.67", "a": 107.3, "b": 80.55, "c": 133, "op1": "/", "op2": "-", "result": -131.67}
{"question": "Solve: (133.65 - 54) - 68", "answer": "The result of (133.65 - 54) - 68 is 11.65", "a": 133.65, "b": 54, "c": 68, "op1": "-", "op2": "-", "result": 11.65}
{"question": "Solve: (99 / 190.38) - 23.36", "answer": "The result of (99 / 190.38) - 23.36 is -22.84", "a": 99, "b": 190.38, "c": 23.36, "op1": "/", "op2": "-", "result": -22.84}
{"question": "Solve: (119.14 - 113) + 18", "answer": "The result of (119.14 - 113) + 18 is 24.14", "a": 119.14, "b": 113, "c": 18, "op1": "-", "op2": "+", "result": 24.14}
{"question": "Solve: (174 + 90) + 64.55", "answer": "The result of (174 + 90) + 64.55 is 328.55", "a": 174, "b": 90, "c": 64.55, "op1": "+", "op2": "+", "result": 328.55}
{"question": "Solve: (58 / 75.21) - 191.49", "answer": "The result of (58 / 75.21) - 191.49 is -190.72", "a": 58, "b": 75.21, "c": 191.49, "op1": "/", "op2": "-", "result": -190.72}
{"question": "Solve: (114.11 - 153.25) * 25", "answer": "The result of (114.11 - 153.25) * 25 is -978.5", "a": 114.11, "b": 153.25, "c": 25, "op1": "-", "op2": "*", "result": -978.5}
{"question": "Solve: (56 / 199) + 108", "answer": "The result of (56 / 199) + 108 is 108.28", "a": 56, "b": 199, "c": 108, "op1": "/", "op2": "+", "result": 108.28}
{"question": "Solve: (177 + 80) + 47.42", "answer": "The result of (177 + 80) + 47.42 is 304.42", "a": 177, "b": 80, "c": 47.42, "op1": "+", "op2": "+", "result": 304.42}
{"question": "Solve: (26 - 160) * 78", "answer": "The result of (26 - 160) * 78 is -10452", "a": 26, "b": 160, "c": 78, "op1": "-", "op2": "*", "result": -10452}
{"question": "Solve: (177 * 98.62) - 61.62", "answer": "The result of (177 * 98.62) - 61.62 is 17394.12", "a": 177, "b": 98.62, "c": 61.62, "op1": "*", "op2": "-", "result": 17394.12}
{"question": "Solve: (197 * 185) - 14", "answer": "The result of (197 * 185) - 14 is 36431", "a": 197, "b": 185, "c": 14, "op1": "*", "op2": "-", "result": 36431}
{"question": "Solve: (107 - 189) * 74", "answer": "The result of (107 - 189) * 74 is -6068", "a": 107, "b": 189, "c": 74, "op1": "-", "op2": "*", "result": -6068}
{"question": "Solve: (169.0 + 57) - 90", "answer": "The result of (169.0 + 57) - 90 is 136.0", "a": 169.0, "b": 57, "c": 90, "op1": "+", "op2": "-", "result": 136.0}
{"question": "Solve: (155 / 181.27) / 177", "answer": "The result of (155 / 181.27) / 177 is 0.0", "a": 155, "b": 181.27, "c": 177, "op1": "/", "op2": "/", "result": 0.0}
{"question": "Solve: (66 + 147) * 71.28", "answer": "The result of (66 + 147) * 71.28 is 15182.64", "a": 66, "b": 147, "c": 71.28, "op1": "+", "op2": "*", "result": 15182.64}
{"question": "Solve: (143 - 163.9) / 41", "answer": "The result of (143 - 163.9) / 41 is -0.51", "a": 143, "b": 163.9, "c": 41, "op1": "-", "op2": "/", "result": -0.51}
{"question": "Solve: (191.29 - 118.67) - 105", "answer": "The result of (191.29 - 118.67) - 105 is -32.38", "a": 191.29, "b": 118.67, "c": 105, "op1": "-", "op2": "-", "result": -32.38}
{"question": "Solve: (156 + 37) / 144", "answer": "The result of (156 + 37) / 144 is 1.34", "a": 156, "b": 37, "c": 144, "op1": "+", "op2": "/", "result": 1.34}
{"question": "Solve: (52.94 * 4.23) * 70", "answer": "The result of (52.94 * 4.23) * 70 is 15675.53", "a": 52.94, "b": 4.23, "c": 70, "op1": "*", "op2": "*", "result": 15675.53}
{"question": "Solve: (194.81 - 17) - 193.47", "answer": "The result of (194.81 - 17) - 193.47 is -15.66", "a": 194.81, "b": 17, "c": 193.47, "op1": "-", "op2": "-", "result": -15.66}
{"question": "Solve: (126 - 20.81) + 99.81", "answer": "The result of (126 - 20.81) + 99.81 is 205.0", "a": 126, "b": 20.81, "c": 99.81, "op1": "-", "op2": "+", "result": 205.0}
{"question": "Solve: (12 * 2) + 152", "answer": "The result of (12 * 2) + 152 is 176", "a": 12, "b": 2, "c": 152, "op1": "*", "op2": "+", "result": 176}
{"question": "Solve: (90 + 7) / 56", "answer": "The result of (90 + 7) / 56 is 1.73", "a": 90, "b": 7, "c": 56, "op1": "+", "op2": "/", "result": 1.73}
{"question": "Solve: (194 + 192) / 25", "answer": "The result of (194 + 192) / 25 is 15.44", "a": 194, "b": 192, "c": 25, "op1": "+", "op2": "/", "result": 15.44}
{"question": "Solve: (17.67 * 127.79) - 5.19", "answer": "The result of (17.67 * 127.79) - 5.19 is 2252.86", "a": 17.67, "b": 127.79, "c": 5.19, "op1": "*", "op2": "-", "result": 2252.86}
{"question": "Solve: (75 + 73) * 102", "answer": "The result of (75 + 73) * 102 is 15096", "a": 75, "b": 73, "c": 102, "op1": "+", "op2": "*", "result": 15096}
{"question": "Solve: (27 * 17) - 40", "answer": "The result of (27 * 17) - 40 is 419", "a": 27, "b": 17, "c": 40, "op1": "*", "op2": "-", "result": 419}
{"question": "Solve: (149 / 130) * 6", "answer": "The result of (149 / 130) * 6 is 6.88", "a": 149, "b": 130, "c": 6, "op1": "/", "op2": "*", "result": 6.88}
{"question": "Solve: (74 + 187) / 102.17", "answer": "The result of (74 + 187) / 102.17 is 2.55", "a": 74, "b": 187, "c": 102.17, "op1": "+", "op2": "/", "result": 2.55}
{"question": "Solve: (2 - 38) + 114.12", "answer": "The result of (2 - 38) + 114.12 is 78.12", "a": 2, "b": 38, "c": 114.12, "op1": "-", "op2": "+", "result": 78.12}
{"question": "Solve: (21 * 61) * 84.83", "answer": "The result of (21 * 61) * 84.83 is 108667.23", "a": 21, "b": 61, "c": 84.83, "op1": "*", "op2": "*", "result": 108667.23}
{"question": "Solve: (64.68 + 37) + 190.69", "answer": "The result of (64.68 + 37) + 190.69 is 292.37", "a": 64.68, "b": 37, "c": 190.69, "op1": "+", "op2": "+", "result": 292.37}
{"question": "Solve: (97 - 12) / 83.88", "answer": "The result of (97 - 12) / 83.88 is 1.01", "a": 97, "b": 12, "c": 83.88, "op1": "-", "op2": "/", "result": 1.01}
{"question": "Solve: (26.87 * 97) / 166.95", "answer": "The result of (26.87 * 97) / 166.95 is 15.61", "a": 26.87, "b": 97, "c": 166.95, "op1": "*", "op2": "/", "result": 15.61}
{"question": "Solve: (18 - 129) + 33", "answer": "The result of (18 - 129) + 33 is -78", "a": 18, "b": 129, "c": 33, "op1": "-", "op2": "+", "result": -78}
{"question": "Solve: (93 + 188.58) - 93", "answer": "The result of (93 + 188.58) - 93 is 188.58", "a": 93, "b": 188.58, "c": 93, "op1": "+", "op2": "-", "result": 188.58}
{"question": "Solve: (165.22 + 129) + 54", "answer": "The result of (165.22 + 129) + 54 is 348.22", "a": 165.22, "b": 129, "c": 54, "op1": "+", "op2": "+", "result": 348.22}
{"question": "Solve: (88 - 32.89) + 199", "answer": "The result of (88 - 32.89) + 199 is 254.11", "a": 88, "b": 32.89, "c": 199, "op1": "-", "op2": "+", "result": 254.11}
{"question": "Solve: (134 + 28) / 186.75", "answer": "The result of (134 + 28) / 186.75 is 0.87", "a": 134, "b": 28, "c": 186.75, "op1": "+", "op2": "/", "result": 0.87}
{"question": "Solve: (130 + 40) + 29", "answer": "The result of (130 + 40) + 29 is 199", "a": 130, "b": 40, "c": 29, "op1": "+", "op2": "+", "result": 199}
{"question": "Solve: (59 * 108) + 61.19", "answer": "The result of (59 * 108) + 61.19 is 6433.19", "a": 59, "b": 108, "c": 61.19, "op1": "*", "op2": "+", "result": 6433.19}
{"question": "Solve: (67 - 27) / 155.68", "answer": "The result of (67 - 27) / 155.68 is 0.26", "a": 67, "b": 27, "c": 155.68, "op1": "-", "op2": "/", "result": 0.26}
{"question": "Solve: (5 / 73) + 104", "answer": "The result of (5 / 73) + 104 is 104.07", "a": 5, "b": 73, "c": 104, "op1": "/", "op2": "+", "result": 104.07}
{"question": "Solve: (48 / 49) / 170", "answer": "The result of (48 / 49) / 170 is 0.01", "a": 48, "b": 49, "c": 170, "op1": "/", "op2": "/", "result": 0.01}
{"question": "Solve: (189 * 162) + 47.46", "answer": "The result of (189 * 162) + 47.46 is 30665.46", "a": 189, "b": 162, "c": 47.46, "op1": "*", "op2": "+", "result": 30665.46}
{"question": "Solve: (133 * 146) / 16", "answer": "The result of (133 * 146) / 16 is 1213.62", "a": 133, "b": 146, "c": 16, "op1": "*", "op2": "/", "result": 1213.62}
{"question": "Solve: (82 + 199) + 57.12", "answer": "The result of (82 + 199) + 57.12 is 338.12", "a": 82, "b": 199, "c": 57.12, "op1": "+", "op2": "+", "result": 338.12}
{"question": "Solve: (170.6 * 197.73) + 55", "answer": "The result of (170.6 * 197.73) + 55 is 33787.74", "a": 170.6, "b": 197.73, "c": 55, "op1": "*", "op2": "+", "result": 33787.74}
{"question": "Solve: (77.14 * 179.91) - 53", "answer": "The result of (77.14 * 179.91) - 53 is 13825.26", "a": 77.14, "b": 179.91, "c": 53, "op1": "*", "op2": "-", "result": 13825.26}
{"question": "Solve: (19.32 * 111.87) - 161", "answer": "The result of (19.32 * 111.87) - 161 is 2000.33", "a": 19.32, "b": 111.87, "c": 161, "op1": "*", "op2": "-", "result": 2000.33}
{"question": "Solve: (108 * 151) + 46.73", "answer": "The result of (108 * 151) + 46.73 is 16354.73", "a": 108, "b": 151, "c": 46.73, "op1": "*", "op2": "+", "result": 16354.73}
{"question": "Solve: (167.39 - 149) / 29", "answer": "The result of (167.39 - 149) / 29 is 0.63", "a": 167.39, "b": 149, "c": 29, "op1": "-", "op2": "/", "result": 0.63}
{"question": "Solve: (22.98 + 92.81) * 152.23", "answer": "The result of (22.98 + 92.81) * 152.23 is 17626.71", "a": 22.98, "b": 92.81, "c": 152.23, "op1": "+", "op2": "*", "result": 17626.71}
{"question": "Solve: (21.72 * 192.28) * 39", "answer": "The result of (21.72 * 192.28) * 39 is 162876.54", "a": 21.72, "b": 192.28, "c": 39, "op1": "*", "op2": "*", "result": 162876.54}
{"question": "Solve: (2.03 * 118.27) - 159", "answer": "The result of (2.03 * 118.27) - 159 is 81.09", "a": 2.03, "b": 118.27, "c": 159, "op1": "*", "op2": "-", "result": 81.09}
{"question": "Solve: (128.67 - 83) - 155", "answer": "The result of (128.67 - 83) - 155 is -109.33", "a": 128.67, "b": 83, "c": 155, "op1": "-", "op2": "-", "result": -109.33}
{"question": "Solve: (188.12 * 125) * 9", "answer": "The result of (188.12 * 125) * 9 is 211635.0", "a": 188.12, "b": 125, "c": 9, "op1": "*", "op2": "*", "result": 211635.0}
{"question": "Solve: (197.55 - 195.45) * 105", "answer": "The result of (197.55 - 195.45) * 105 is 220.5", "a": 197.55, "b": 195.45, "c": 105, "op1": "-", "op2": "*", "result": 220.5}
{"question": "Solve: (116 / 172) * 23", "answer": "The result of (116 / 172) * 23 is 15.51", "a": 116, "b": 172, "c": 23, "op1": "/", "op2": "*", "result": 15.51}
{"question": "Solve: (28.98 * 131) * 88", "answer": "The result of (28.98 * 131) * 88 is 334081.44", "a": 28.98, "b": 131, "c": 88, "op1": "*", "op2": "*", "result": 334081.44}
{"question": "Solve: (176.41 / 7.08) * 29.08", "answer": "The result of (176.41 / 7.08) * 29.08 is 724.58", "a": 176.41, "b": 7.08, "c": 29.08, "op1": "/", "op2": "*", "result": 724.58}
{"question": "Solve: (78.86 + 104.29) - 109", "answer": "The result of (78.86 + 104.29) - 109 is 74.15", "a": 78.86, "b": 104.29, "c": 109, "op1": "+", "op2": "-", "result": 74.15}
{"question": "Solve: (163 - 94.97) / 107", "answer": "The result of (163 - 94.97) / 107 is 0.64", "a": 163, "b": 94.97, "c": 107, "op1": "-", "op2": "/", "result": 0.64}
{"question": "Solve: (92 + 165) / 109.19", "answer": "The result of (92 + 165) / 109.19 is 2.35", "a": 92, "b": 165, "c": 109.19, "op1": "+", "op2": "/", "result": 2.35}
{"question": "Solve: (127 * 140) + 45", "answer": "The result of (127 * 140) + 45 is 17825", "a": 127, "b": 140, "c": 45, "op1": "*", "op2": "+", "result": 17825}
{"question": "Solve: (153.15 + 148) - 115.79", "answer": "The result of (153.15 + 148) - 115.79 is 185.36", "a": 153.15, "b": 148, "c": 115.79, "op1": "+", "op2": "-", "result": 185.36}
{"question": "Solve: (124.44 - 167) + 128.09", "answer": "The result of (124.44 - 167) + 128.09 is 85.53", "a": 124.44, "b": 167, "c": 128.09, "op1": "-", "op2": "+", "result": 85.53}
{"question": "Solve: (186 / 60.27) - 78", "answer": "The result of (186 / 60.27) - 78 is -74.91", "a": 186, "b": 60.27, "c": 78, "op1": "/", "op2": "-", "result": -74.91}
{"question": "Solve: (121 + 179) - 186", "answer": "The result of (121 + 179) - 186 is 114", "a": 121, "b": 179, "c": 186, "op1": "+", "op2": "-", "result": 114}
{"question": "Solve: (10 * 88.16) + 5", "answer": "The result of (10 * 88.16) + 5 is 886.6", "a": 10, "b": 88.16, "c": 5, "op1": "*", "op2": "+", "result": 886.6}
{"question": "Solve: (57 / 19.39) + 73.56", "answer": "The result of (57 / 19.39) + 73.56 is 76.5", "a": 57, "b": 19.39, "c": 73.56, "op1": "/", "op2": "+", "result": 76.5}
{"question": "Solve: (13.63 - 5) * 107.98", "answer": "The result of (13.63 - 5) * 107.98 is 931.87", "a": 13.63, "b": 5, "c": 107.98, "op1": "-", "op2": "*", "result": 931.87}
{"question": "Solve: (195 + 70) + 63", "answer": "The result of (195 + 70) + 63 is 328", "a": 195, "b": 70, "c": 63, "op1": "+", "op2": "+", "result": 328}
{"question": "Solve: (173.13 - 15) * 113", "answer": "The result of (173.13 - 15) * 113 is 17868.69", "a": 173.13, "b": 15, "c": 113, "op1": "-", "op2": "*", "result": 17868.69}
{"question": "Solve: (20.1 - 103) + 9", "answer": "The result of (20.1 - 103) + 9 is -73.9", "a": 20.1, "b": 103, "c": 9, "op1": "-", "op2": "+", "result": -73.9}
{"question": "Solve: (180 - 157) + 82", "answer": "The result of (180 - 157) + 82 is 105", "a": 180, "b": 157, "c": 82, "op1": "-", "op2": "+", "result": 105}
{"question": "Solve: (17 + 86.0) - 186", "answer": "The result of (17 + 86.0) - 186 is -83.0", "a": 17, "b": 86.0, "c": 186, "op1": "+", "op2": "-", "result": -83.0}
{"question": "Solve: (44 + 23) + 111", "answer": "The result of (44 + 23) + 111 is 178", "a": 44, "b": 23, "c": 111, "op1": "+", "op2": "+", "result": 178}
{"question": "Solve: (22 * 115) / 199.54", "answer": "The result of (22 * 115) / 199.54 is 12.68", "a": 22, "b": 115, "c": 199.54, "op1": "*", "op2": "/", "result": 12.68}
{"question": "Solve: (41 + 8) - 192", "answer": "The result of (41 + 8) - 192 is -143", "a": 41, "b": 8, "c": 192, "op1": "+", "op2": "-", "result": -143}
{"question": "Solve: (150 + 3) + 48", "answer": "The result of (150 + 3) + 48 is 201", "a": 150, "b": 3, "c": 48, "op1": "+", "op2": "+", "result": 201}
{"question": "Solve: (51 - 187) * 20", "answer": "The result of (51 - 187) * 20 is -2720", "a": 51, "b": 187, "c": 20, "op1": "-", "op2": "*", "result": -2720}
{"question": "Solve: (81 * 86) - 53.57", "answer": "The result of (81 * 86) - 53.57 is 6912.43", "a": 81, "b": 86, "c": 53.57, "op1": "*", "op2": "-", "result": 6912.43}
{"question": "Solve: (10 + 113) / 167", "answer": "The result of (10 + 113) / 167 is 0.74", "a": 10, "b": 113, "c": 167, "op1": "+", "op2": "/", "result": 0.74}
{"question": "Solve: (46 + 161) + 43", "answer": "The result of (46 + 161) + 43 is 250", "a": 46, "b": 161, "c": 43, "op1": "+", "op2": "+", "result": 250}
{"question": "Solve: (158 / 106.79) - 180", "answer": "The result of (158 / 106.79) - 180 is -178.52", "a": 158, "b": 106.79, "c": 180, "op1": "/", "op2": "-", "result": -178.52}
{"question": "Solve: (111 - 103.98) + 24", "answer": "The result of (111 - 103.98) + 24 is 31.02", "a": 111, "b": 103.98, "c": 24, "op1": "-", "op2": "+", "result": 31.02}
{"question": "Solve: (88 - 181) + 75.97", "answer": "The result of (88 - 181) + 75.97 is -17.03", "a": 88, "b": 181, "c": 75.97, "op1": "-", "op2": "+", "result": -17.03}
{"question": "Solve: (196 - 1.7) + 85", "answer": "The result of (196 - 1.7) + 85 is 279.3", "a": 196, "b": 1.7, "c": 85, "op1": "-", "op2": "+", "result": 279.3}
{"question": "Solve: (28 + 39) + 196", "answer": "The result of (28 + 39) + 196 is 263", "a": 28, "b": 39, "c": 196, "op1": "+", "op2": "+", "result": 263}
{"question": "Solve: (165 - 159) - 94", "answer": "The result of (165 - 159) - 94 is -88", "a": 165, "b": 159, "c": 94, "op1": "-", "op2": "-", "result": -88}
{"question": "Solve: (4.96 / 125) * 199", "answer": "The result of (4.96 / 125) * 199 is 7.9", "a": 4.96, "b": 125, "c": 199, "op1": "/", "op2": "*", "result": 7.9}
{"question": "Solve: (32 * 113) + 93", "answer": "The result of (32 * 113) + 93 is 3709", "a": 32, "b": 113, "c": 93, "op1": "*", "op2": "+", "result": 3709}
{"question": "Solve: (124 - 194) * 138", "answer": "The result of (124 - 194) * 138 is -9660", "a": 124, "b": 194, "c": 138, "op1": "-", "op2": "*", "result": -9660}
{"question": "Solve: (98 - 83) + 109", "answer": "The result of (98 - 83) + 109 is 124", "a": 98, "b": 83, "c": 109, "op1": "-", "op2": "+", "result": 124}
{"question": "Solve: (7 * 200) * 169", "answer": "The result of (7 * 200) * 169 is 236600", "a": 7, "b": 200, "c": 169, "op1": "*", "op2": "*", "result": 236600}
{"question": "Solve: (17 * 88) + 25", "answer": "The result of (17 * 88) + 25 is 1521", "a": 17, "b": 88, "c": 25, "op1": "*", "op2": "+", "result": 1521}
{"question": "Solve: (52 * 18) - 106.93", "answer": "The result of (52 * 18) - 106.93 is 829.07", "a": 52, "b": 18, "c": 106.93, "op1": "*", "op2": "-", "result": 829.07}
{"question": "Solve: (193 + 34.06) + 79", "answer": "The result of (193 + 34.06) + 79 is 306.06", "a": 193, "b": 34.06, "c": 79, "op1": "+", "op2": "+", "result": 306.06}
{"question": "Solve: (116.13 * 101.07) - 66", "answer": "The result of (116.13 * 101.07) - 66 is 11671.26", "a": 116.13, "b": 101.07, "c": 66, "op1": "*", "op2": "-", "result": 11671.26}
{"question": "Solve: (89 - 23) / 168", "answer": "The result of (89 - 23) / 168 is 0.39", "a": 89, "b": 23, "c": 168, "op1": "-", "op2": "/", "result": 0.39}
{"question": "Solve: (22.64 + 177.24) - 169", "answer": "The result of (22.64 + 177.24) - 169 is 30.88", "a": 22.64, "b": 177.24, "c": 169, "op1": "+", "op2": "-", "result": 30.88}
{"question": "Solve: (185.26 - 172) / 134.69", "answer": "The result of (185.26 - 172) / 134.69 is 0.1", "a": 185.26, "b": 172, "c": 134.69, "op1": "-", "op2": "/", "result": 0.1}
{"question": "Solve: (26.88 - 27) + 62.36", "answer": "The result of (26.88 - 27) + 62.36 is 62.24", "a": 26.88, "b": 27, "c": 62.36, "op1": "-", "op2": "+", "result": 62.24}
{"question": "Solve: (179.89 - 35) * 161", "answer": "The result of (179.89 - 35) * 161 is 23327.29", "a": 179.89, "b": 35, "c": 161, "op1": "-", "op2": "*", "result": 23327.29}
{"question": "Solve: (130 * 116) - 135.17", "answer": "The result of (130 * 116) - 135.17 is 14944.83", "a": 130, "b": 116, "c": 135.17, "op1": "*", "op2": "-", "result": 14944.83}
{"question": "Solve: (13 + 131) * 98", "answer": "The result of (13 + 131) * 98 is 14112", "a": 13, "b": 131, "c": 98, "op1": "+", "op2": "*", "result": 14112}
{"question": "Solve: (52 / 18) * 24", "answer": "The result of (52 / 18) * 24 is 69.33", "a": 52, "b": 18, "c": 24, "op1": "/", "op2": "*", "result": 69.33}
{"question": "Solve: (116.2 + 165) - 154", "answer": "The result of (116.2 + 165) - 154 is 127.2", "a": 116.2, "b": 165, "c": 154, "op1": "+", "op2": "-", "result": 127.2}
{"question": "Solve: (35 / 64) + 72", "answer": "The result of (35 / 64) + 72 is 72.55", "a": 35, "b": 64, "c": 72, "op1": "/", "op2": "+", "result": 72.55}
{"question": "Solve: (22 / 39) + 1", "answer": "The result of (22 / 39) + 1 is 1.56", "a": 22, "b": 39, "c": 1, "op1": "/", "op2": "+", "result": 1.56}
{"question": "Solve: (4 - 34) / 94", "answer": "The result of (4 - 34) / 94 is -0.32", "a": 4, "b": 34, "c": 94, "op1": "-", "op2": "/", "result": -0.32}
{"question": "Solve: (62 + 25) * 70", "answer": "The result of (62 + 25) * 70 is 6090", "a": 62, "b": 25, "c": 70, "op1": "+", "op2": "*", "result": 6090}
{"question": "Solve: (77 + 91) - 137", "answer": "The result of (77 + 91) - 137 is 31", "a": 77, "b": 91, "c": 137, "op1": "+", "op2": "-", "result": 31}
{"question": "Solve: (178 - 157) + 61", "answer": "The result of (178 - 157) + 61 is 82", "a": 178, "b": 157, "c": 61, "op1": "-", "op2": "+", "result": 82}
{"question": "Solve: (153 * 116.02) + 82.14", "answer": "The result of (153 * 116.02) + 82.14 is 17833.2", "a": 153, "b": 116.02, "c": 82.14, "op1": "*", "op2": "+", "result": 17833.2}
{"question": "Solve: (99.73 + 65.62) - 12.08", "answer": "The result of (99.73 + 65.62) - 12.08 is 153.27", "a": 99.73, "b": 65.62, "c": 12.08, "op1": "+", "op2": "-", "result": 153.27}
{"question": "Solve: (161.44 - 155) - 26.97", "answer": "The result of (161.44 - 155) - 26.97 is -20.53", "a": 161.44, "b": 155, "c": 26.97, "op1": "-", "op2": "-", "result": -20.53}
{"question": "Solve: (149.93 * 45) - 161", "answer": "The result of (149.93 * 45) - 161 is 6585.85", "a": 149.93, "b": 45, "c": 161, "op1": "*", "op2": "-", "result": 6585.85}
{"question": "Solve: (55.7 + 68) / 155", "answer": "The result of (55.7 + 68) / 155 is 0.8", "a": 55.7, "b": 68, "c": 155, "op1": "+", "op2": "/", "result": 0.8}
{"question": "Solve: (156 + 73.11) + 128", "answer": "The result of (156 + 73.11) + 128 is 357.11", "a": 156, "b": 73.11, "c": 128, "op1": "+", "op2": "+", "result": 357.11}
{"question": "Solve: (95 * 110.0) + 107", "answer": "The result of (95 * 110.0) + 107 is 10557.0", "a": 95, "b": 110.0, "c": 107, "op1": "*", "op2": "+", "result": 10557.0}
{"question": "Solve: (19.21 + 120) - 26", "answer": "The result of (19.21 + 120) - 26 is 113.21", "a": 19.21, "b": 120, "c": 26, "op1": "+", "op2": "-", "result": 113.21}
{"question": "Solve: (153.22 + 56.19) * 152", "answer": "The result of (153.22 + 56.19) * 152 is 31830.32", "a": 153.22, "b": 56.19, "c": 152, "op1": "+", "op2": "*", "result": 31830.32}
{"question": "Solve: (25 / 37) + 175.75", "answer": "The result of (25 / 37) + 175.75 is 176.43", "a": 25, "b": 37, "c": 175.75, "op1": "/", "op2": "+", "result": 176.43}
{"question": "Solve: (166 / 38.75) - 90.6", "answer": "The result of (166 / 38.75) - 90.6 is -86.32", "a": 166, "b": 38.75, "c": 90.6, "op1": "/", "op2": "-", "result": -86.32}
{"question": "Solve: (149 + 29) - 47", "answer": "The result of (149 + 29) - 47 is 131", "a": 149, "b": 29, "c": 47, "op1": "+", "op2": "-", "result": 131}
{"question": "Solve: (120.18 * 97) - 149.05", "answer": "The result of (120.18 * 97) - 149.05 is 11508.41", "a": 120.18, "b": 97, "c": 149.05, "op1": "*", "op2": "-", "result": 11508.41}
{"question": "Solve: (158.34 / 192.45) / 144", "answer": "The result of (158.34 / 192.45) / 144 is 0.01", "a": 158.34, "b": 192.45, "c": 144, "op1": "/", "op2": "/", "result": 0.01}
{"question": "Solve: (147.81 * 199) - 163.97", "answer": "The result of (147.81 * 199) - 163.97 is 29250.22", "a": 147.81, "b": 199, "c": 163.97, "op1": "*", "op2": "-", "result": 29250.22}
{"question": "Solve: (76 + 164) - 6.62", "answer": "The result of (76 + 164) - 6.62 is 233.38", "a": 76, "b": 164, "c": 6.62, "op1": "+", "op2": "-", "result": 233.38}
{"question": "Solve: (26 * 45) * 165.99", "answer": "The result of (26 * 45) * 165.99 is 194208.3", "a": 26, "b": 45, "c": 165.99, "op1": "*", "op2": "*", "result": 194208.3}
{"question": "Solve: (22 * 130) + 179", "answer": "The result of (22 * 130) + 179 is 3039", "a": 22, "b": 130, "c": 179, "op1": "*", "op2": "+", "result": 3039}
{"question": "Solve: (111 - 169) - 1", "answer": "The result of (111 - 169) - 1 is -59", "a": 111, "b": 169, "c": 1, "op1": "-", "op2": "-", "result": -59}
{"question": "Solve: (164.19 + 186) - 46", "answer": "The result of (164.19 + 186) - 46 is 304.19", "a": 164.19, "b": 186, "c": 46, "op1": "+", "op2": "-", "result": 304.19}
{"question": "Solve: (183 + 4) - 99", "answer": "The result of (183 + 4) - 99 is 88", "a": 183, "b": 4, "c": 99, "op1": "+", "op2": "-", "result": 88}
{"question": "Solve: (129.22 / 23) - 65", "answer": "The result of (129.22 / 23) - 65 is -59.38", "a": 129.22, "b": 23, "c": 65, "op1": "/", "op2": "-", "result": -59.38}
{"question": "Solve: (79.39 * 134) * 165", "answer": "The result of (79.39 * 134) * 165 is 1755312.9", "a": 79.39, "b": 134, "c": 165, "op1": "*", "op2": "*", "result": 1755312.9}
{"question": "Solve: (23.42 / 72.09) + 155", "answer": "The result of (23.42 / 72.09) + 155 is 155.32", "a": 23.42, "b": 72.09, "c": 155, "op1": "/", "op2": "+", "result": 155.32}
{"question": "Solve: (53.46 + 87) + 13", "answer": "The result of (53.46 + 87) + 13 is 153.46", "a": 53.46, "b": 87, "c": 13, "op1": "+", "op2": "+", "result": 153.46}
{"question": "Solve: (116 - 166.21) / 164", "answer": "The result of (116 - 166.21) / 164 is -0.31", "a": 116, "b": 166.21, "c": 164, "op1": "-", "op2": "/", "result": -0.31}
{"question": "Solve: (81 - 103) / 118.87", "answer": "The result of (81 - 103) / 118.87 is -0.19", "a": 81, "b": 103, "c": 118.87, "op1": "-", "op2": "/", "result": -0.19}
{"question": "Solve: (173 * 38) + 59.88", "answer": "The result of (173 * 38) + 59.88 is 6633.88", "a": 173, "b": 38, "c": 59.88, "op1": "*", "op2": "+", "result": 6633.88}
{"question": "Solve: (159 - 172) * 48.67", "answer": "The result of (159 - 172) * 48.67 is -632.71", "a": 159, "b": 172, "c": 48.67, "op1": "-", "op2": "*", "result": -632.71}
{"question": "Solve: (11 - 9) + 79", "answer": "The result of (11 - 9) + 79 is 81", "a": 11, "b": 9, "c": 79, "op1": "-", "op2": "+", "result": 81}
{"question": "Solve: (1 * 11.6) * 173.5", "answer": "The result of (1 * 11.6) * 173.5 is 2012.6", "a": 1, "b": 11.6, "c": 173.5, "op1": "*", "op2": "*", "result": 2012.6}
{"question": "Solve: (187.41 + 104.51) * 8", "answer": "The result of (187.41 + 104.51) * 8 is 2335.36", "a": 187.41, "b": 104.51, "c": 8, "op1": "+", "op2": "*", "result": 2335.36}
{"question": "Solve: (170 - 5.21) - 130", "answer": "The result of (170 - 5.21) - 130 is 34.79", "a": 170, "b": 5.21, "c": 130, "op1": "-", "op2": "-", "result": 34.79}
{"question": "Solve: (165 - 53) * 75.51", "answer": "The result of (165 - 53) * 75.51 is 8457.12", "a": 165, "b": 53, "c": 75.51, "op1": "-", "op2": "*", "result": 8457.12}
{"question": "Solve: (129 / 138) * 38", "answer": "The result of (129 / 138) * 38 is 35.52", "a": 129, "b": 138, "c": 38, "op1": "/", "op2": "*", "result": 35.52}
{"question": "Solve: (157 + 50) + 117", "answer": "The result of (157 + 50) + 117 is 324", "a": 157, "b": 50, "c": 117, "op1": "+", "op2": "+", "result": 324}
{"question": "Solve: (114.81 / 108) * 139.55", "answer": "The result of (114.81 / 108) * 139.55 is 148.35", "a": 114.81, "b": 108, "c": 139.55, "op1": "/", "op2": "*", "result": 148.35}
{"question": "Solve: (126.92 / 74) * 118.52", "answer": "The result of (126.92 / 74) * 118.52 is 203.28", "a": 126.92, "b": 74, "c": 118.52, "op1": "/", "op2": "*", "result": 203.28}
{"question": "Solve: (40 + 8) + 19.48", "answer": "The result of (40 + 8) + 19.48 is 67.48", "a": 40, "b": 8, "c": 19.48, "op1": "+", "op2": "+", "result": 67.48}
{"question": "Solve: (114.21 * 84.36) * 147.91", "answer": "The result of (114.21 * 84.36) * 147.91 is 1425076.7", "a": 114.21, "b": 84.36, "c": 147.91, "op1": "*", "op2": "*", "result": 1425076.7}
{"question": "Solve: (157 + 47.83) * 5.63", "answer": "The result of (157 + 47.83) * 5.63 is 1153.19", "a": 157, "b": 47.83, "c": 5.63, "op1": "+", "op2": "*", "result": 1153.19}
{"question": "Solve: (41 * 32.19) * 60", "answer": "The result of (41 * 32.19) * 60 is 79187.4", "a": 41, "b": 32.19, "c": 60, "op1": "*", "op2": "*", "result": 79187.4}
{"question": "Solve: (48 / 109) + 35", "answer": "The result of (48 / 109) + 35 is 35.44", "a": 48, "b": 109, "c": 35, "op1": "/", "op2": "+", "result": 35.44}
{"question": "Solve: (97 * 134) * 40", "answer": "The result of (97 * 134) * 40 is 519920", "a": 97, "b": 134, "c": 40, "op1": "*", "op2": "*", "result": 519920}
{"question": "Solve: (101 - 34) + 92", "answer": "The result of (101 - 34) + 92 is 159", "a": 101, "b": 34, "c": 92, "op1": "-", "op2": "+", "result": 159}
{"question": "Solve: (84 + 40) + 192.05", "answer": "The result of (84 + 40) + 192.05 is 316.05", "a": 84, "b": 40, "c": 192.05, "op1": "+", "op2": "+", "result": 316.05}
{"question": "Solve: (97 * 19) / 70.82", "answer": "The result of (97 * 19) / 70.82 is 26.02", "a": 97, "b": 19, "c": 70.82, "op1": "*", "op2": "/", "result": 26.02}
{"question": "Solve: (174 + 119.87) + 66", "answer": "The result of (174 + 119.87) + 66 is 359.87", "a": 174, "b": 119.87, "c": 66, "op1": "+", "op2": "+", "result": 359.87}
{"question": "Solve: (54 + 24) * 158", "answer": "The result of (54 + 24) * 158 is 12324", "a": 54, "b": 24, "c": 158, "op1": "+", "op2": "*", "result": 12324}
{"question": "Solve: (99.96 * 79.65) * 74", "answer": "The result of (99.96 * 79.65) * 74 is 589174.24", "a": 99.96, "b": 79.65, "c": 74, "op1": "*", "op2": "*", "result": 589174.24}
{"question": "Solve: (136.86 * 67) * 25.96", "answer": "The result of (136.86 * 67) * 25.96 is 238043.34", "a": 136.86, "b": 67, "c": 25.96, "op1": "*", "op2": "*", "result": 238043.34}
{"question": "Solve: (125 - 146) * 28.99", "answer": "The result of (125 - 146) * 28.99 is -608.79", "a": 125, "b": 146, "c": 28.99, "op1": "-", "op2": "*", "result": -608.79}
{"question": "Solve: (29.18 - 23.49) - 26", "answer": "The result of (29.18 - 23.49) - 26 is -20.31", "a": 29.18, "b": 23.49, "c": 26, "op1": "-", "op2": "-", "result": -20.31}
{"question": "Solve: (159.0 - 145) / 27", "answer": "The result of (159.0 - 145) / 27 is 0.52", "a": 159.0, "b": 145, "c": 27, "op1": "-", "op2": "/", "result": 0.52}
{"question": "Solve: (103.27 + 90.18) / 82", "answer": "The result of (103.27 + 90.18) / 82 is 2.36", "a": 103.27, "b": 90.18, "c": 82, "op1": "+", "op2": "/", "result": 2.36}
{"question": "Solve: (64.92 + 38) * 138.74", "answer": "The result of (64.92 + 38) * 138.74 is 14279.12", "a": 64.92, "b": 38, "c": 138.74, "op1": "+", "op2": "*", "result": 14279.12}
{"question": "Solve: (12 / 159) * 119", "answer": "The result of (12 / 159) * 119 is 8.98", "a": 12, "b": 159, "c": 119, "op1": "/", "op2": "*", "result": 8.98}
{"question": "Solve: (162 * 35) * 155", "answer": "The result of (162 * 35) * 155 is 878850", "a": 162, "b": 35, "c": 155, "op1": "*", "op2": "*", "result": 878850}
{"question": "Solve: (78 + 72) - 40.27", "answer": "The result of (78 + 72) - 40.27 is 109.73", "a": 78, "b": 72, "c": 40.27, "op1": "+", "op2": "-", "result": 109.73}
{"question": "Solve: (200 - 198) - 133", "answer": "The result of (200 - 198) - 133 is -131", "a": 200, "b": 198, "c": 133, "op1": "-", "op2": "-", "result": -131}
{"question": "Solve: (189 - 177) / 18", "answer": "The result of (189 - 177) / 18 is 0.67", "a": 189, "b": 177, "c": 18, "op1": "-", "op2": "/", "result": 0.67}
{"question": "Solve: (72 + 184) + 21.41", "answer": "The result of (72 + 184) + 21.41 is 277.41", "a": 72, "b": 184, "c": 21.41, "op1": "+", "op2": "+", "result": 277.41}
{"question": "Solve: (54 - 49) * 49.92", "answer": "The result of (54 - 49) * 49.92 is 249.6", "a": 54, "b": 49, "c": 49.92, "op1": "-", "op2": "*", "result": 249.6}
{"question": "Solve: (75 - 3) + 96", "answer": "The result of (75 - 3) + 96 is 168", "a": 75, "b": 3, "c": 96, "op1": "-", "op2": "+", "result": 168}
{"question": "Solve: (191 * 141) + 135", "answer": "The result of (191 * 141) + 135 is 27066", "a": 191, "b": 141, "c": 135, "op1": "*", "op2": "+", "result": 27066}
{"question": "Solve: (5 - 53.8) + 143", "answer": "The result of (5 - 53.8) + 143 is 94.2", "a": 5, "b": 53.8, "c": 143, "op1": "-", "op2": "+", "result": 94.2}
{"question": "Solve: (11 / 194) - 194.72", "answer": "The result of (11 / 194) - 194.72 is -194.66", "a": 11, "b": 194, "c": 194.72, "op1": "/", "op2": "-", "result": -194.66}
{"question": "Solve: (117 + 85) + 169", "answer": "The result of (117 + 85) + 169 is 371", "a": 117, "b": 85, "c": 169, "op1": "+", "op2": "+", "result": 371}
{"question": "Solve: (61 * 147) + 73.1", "answer": "The result of (61 * 147) + 73.1 is 9040.1", "a": 61, "b": 147, "c": 73.1, "op1": "*", "op2": "+", "result": 9040.1}
{"question": "Solve: (187 * 70.61) / 141", "answer": "The result of (187 * 70.61) / 141 is 93.65", "a": 187, "b": 70.61, "c": 141, "op1": "*", "op2": "/", "result": 93.65}
{"question": "Solve: (102 - 145.39) + 15", "answer": "The result of (102 - 145.39) + 15 is -28.39", "a": 102, "b": 145.39, "c": 15, "op1": "-", "op2": "+", "result": -28.39}
{"question": "Solve: (52.1 * 22.39) - 87", "answer": "The result of (52.1 * 22.39) - 87 is 1079.52", "a": 52.1, "b": 22.39, "c": 87, "op1": "*", "op2": "-", "result": 1079.52}
{"question": "Solve: (115 + 15) - 185.63", "answer": "The result of (115 + 15) - 185.63 is -55.63", "a": 115, "b": 15, "c": 185.63, "op1": "+", "op2": "-", "result": -55.63}
{"question": "Solve: (86 * 152) - 191", "answer": "The result of (86 * 152) - 191 is 12881", "a": 86, "b": 152, "c": 191, "op1": "*", "op2": "-", "result": 12881}
{"question": "Solve: (190 - 98) - 188.92", "answer": "The result of (190 - 98) - 188.92 is -96.92", "a": 190, "b": 98, "c": 188.92, "op1": "-", "op2": "-", "result": -96.92}
{"question": "Solve: (95 + 55.25) * 113", "answer": "The result of (95 + 55.25) * 113 is 16978.25", "a": 95, "b": 55.25, "c": 113, "op1": "+", "op2": "*", "result": 16978.25}
{"question": "Solve: (163 + 86.55) * 175", "answer": "The result of (163 + 86.55) * 175 is 43671.25", "a": 163, "b": 86.55, "c": 175, "op1": "+", "op2": "*", "result": 43671.25}
{"question": "Solve: (36 + 114) / 130", "answer": "The result of (36 + 114) / 130 is 1.15", "a": 36, "b": 114, "c": 130, "op1": "+", "op2": "/", "result": 1.15}
{"question": "Solve: (199 + 164.86) + 57", "answer": "The result of (199 + 164.86) + 57 is 420.86", "a": 199, "b": 164.86, "c": 57, "op1": "+", "op2": "+", "result": 420.86}
{"question": "Solve: (115 * 88.46) * 149", "answer": "The result of (115 * 88.46) * 149 is 1515762.1", "a": 115, "b": 88.46, "c": 149, "op1": "*", "op2": "*", "result": 1515762.1}
{"question": "Solve: (12 * 126) * 43.14", "answer": "The result of (12 * 126) * 43.14 is 65227.68", "a": 12, "b": 126, "c": 43.14, "op1": "*", "op2": "*", "result": 65227.68}
{"question": "Solve: (10.04 - 196) * 119", "answer": "The result of (10.04 - 196) * 119 is -22129.24", "a": 10.04, "b": 196, "c": 119, "op1": "-", "op2": "*", "result": -22129.24}
{"question": "Solve: (149 + 194) - 108.85", "answer": "The result of (149 + 194) - 108.85 is 234.15", "a": 149, "b": 194, "c": 108.85, "op1": "+", "op2": "-", "result": 234.15}
{"question": "Solve: (19 - 122.7) * 174", "answer": "The result of (19 - 122.7) * 174 is -18043.8", "a": 19, "b": 122.7, "c": 174, "op1": "-", "op2": "*", "result": -18043.8}
{"question": "Solve: (30.39 - 173) * 174.49", "answer": "The result of (30.39 - 173) * 174.49 is -24884.02", "a": 30.39, "b": 173, "c": 174.49, "op1": "-", "op2": "*", "result": -24884.02}
{"question": "Solve: (44 + 60.56) + 165", "answer": "The result of (44 + 60.56) + 165 is 269.56", "a": 44, "b": 60.56, "c": 165, "op1": "+", "op2": "+", "result": 269.56}
{"question": "Solve: (118 * 183) * 1", "answer": "The result of (118 * 183) * 1 is 21594", "a": 118, "b": 183, "c": 1, "op1": "*", "op2": "*", "result": 21594}
{"question": "Solve: (173 * 160) - 76", "answer": "The result of (173 * 160) - 76 is 27604", "a": 173, "b": 160, "c": 76, "op1": "*", "op2": "-", "result": 27604}
{"question": "Solve: (2 / 200) + 163", "answer": "The result of (2 / 200) + 163 is 163.01", "a": 2, "b": 200, "c": 163, "op1": "/", "op2": "+", "result": 163.01}
{"question": "Solve: (50 - 195) * 104.31", "answer": "The result of (50 - 195) * 104.31 is -15124.95", "a": 50, "b": 195, "c": 104.31, "op1": "-", "op2": "*", "result": -15124.95}
{"question": "Solve: (2 * 90) + 171", "answer": "The result of (2 * 90) + 171 is 351", "a": 2, "b": 90, "c": 171, "op1": "*", "op2": "+", "result": 351}
{"question": "Solve: (188 - 145) + 96", "answer": "The result of (188 - 145) + 96 is 139", "a": 188, "b": 145, "c": 96, "op1": "-", "op2": "+", "result": 139}
{"question": "Solve: (148 * 116.27) - 174", "answer": "The result of (148 * 116.27) - 174 is 17033.96", "a": 148, "b": 116.27, "c": 174, "op1": "*", "op2": "-", "result": 17033.96}
{"question": "Solve: (147 - 142.99) - 113", "answer": "The result of (147 - 142.99) - 113 is -108.99", "a": 147, "b": 142.99, "c": 113, "op1": "-", "op2": "-", "result": -108.99}
{"question": "Solve: (122 - 2) + 190", "answer": "The result of (122 - 2) + 190 is 310", "a": 122, "b": 2, "c": 190, "op1": "-", "op2": "+", "result": 310}
{"question": "Solve: (13 + 190) - 53", "answer": "The result of (13 + 190) - 53 is 150", "a": 13, "b": 190, "c": 53, "op1": "+", "op2": "-", "result": 150}
{"question": "Solve: (28 - 71) / 191.64", "answer": "The result of (28 - 71) / 191.64 is -0.22", "a": 28, "b": 71, "c": 191.64, "op1": "-", "op2": "/", "result": -0.22}
{"question": "Solve: (157 / 19) + 110", "answer": "The result of (157 / 19) + 110 is 118.26", "a": 157, "b": 19, "c": 110, "op1": "/", "op2": "+", "result": 118.26}
{"question": "Solve: (120 + 103.1) - 66", "answer": "The result of (120 + 103.1) - 66 is 157.1", "a": 120, "b": 103.1, "c": 66, "op1": "+", "op2": "-", "result": 157.1}
{"question": "Solve: (171 - 193) / 195", "answer": "The result of (171 - 193) / 195 is -0.11", "a": 171, "b": 193, "c": 195, "op1": "-", "op2": "/", "result": -0.11}
{"question": "Solve: (160 * 97) + 107.57", "answer": "The result of (160 * 97) + 107.57 is 15627.57", "a": 160, "b": 97, "c": 107.57, "op1": "*", "op2": "+", "result": 15627.57}
{"question": "Solve: (179 + 2) * 67", "answer": "The result of (179 + 2) * 67 is 12127", "a": 179, "b": 2, "c": 67, "op1": "+", "op2": "*", "result": 12127}
{"question": "Solve: (1 * 196) - 105", "answer": "The result of (1 * 196) - 105 is 91", "a": 1, "b": 196, "c": 105, "op1": "*", "op2": "-", "result": 91}
{"question": "Solve: (31 - 21) / 163.9", "answer": "The result of (31 - 21) / 163.9 is 0.06", "a": 31, "b": 21, "c": 163.9, "op1": "-", "op2": "/", "result": 0.06}
{"question": "Solve: (181.69 - 166) / 33", "answer": "The result of (181.69 - 166) / 33 is 0.48", "a": 181.69, "b": 166, "c": 33, "op1": "-", "op2": "/", "result": 0.48}
{"question": "Solve: (197 + 10) + 175.85", "answer": "The result of (197 + 10) + 175.85 is 382.85", "a": 197, "b": 10, "c": 175.85, "op1": "+", "op2": "+", "result": 382.85}
{"question": "Solve: (164.15 - 114.02) / 130", "answer": "The result of (164.15 - 114.02) / 130 is 0.39", "a": 164.15, "b": 114.02, "c": 130, "op1": "-", "op2": "/", "result": 0.39}
{"question": "Solve: (14 / 45) * 184", "answer": "The result of (14 / 45) * 184 is 57.24", "a": 14, "b": 45, "c": 184, "op1": "/", "op2": "*", "result": 57.24}
{"question": "Solve: (144 * 121.28) + 33", "answer": "The result of (144 * 121.28) + 33 is 17497.32", "a": 144, "b": 121.28, "c": 33, "op1": "*", "op2": "+", "result": 17497.32}
{"question": "Solve: (102.15 - 162) - 172.77", "answer": "The result of (102.15 - 162) - 172.77 is -232.62", "a": 102.15, "b": 162, "c": 172.77, "op1": "-", "op2": "-", "result": -232.62}
{"question": "Solve: (190 - 178.14) - 73", "answer": "The result of (190 - 178.14) - 73 is -61.14", "a": 190, "b": 178.14, "c": 73, "op1": "-", "op2": "-", "result": -61.14}
{"question": "Solve: (196 / 109) - 9", "answer": "The result of (196 / 109) - 9 is -7.2", "a": 196, "b": 109, "c": 9, "op1": "/", "op2": "-", "result": -7.2}
{"question": "Solve: (170 + 107) + 126", "answer": "The result of (170 + 107) + 126 is 403", "a": 170, "b": 107, "c": 126, "op1": "+", "op2": "+", "result": 403}
{"question": "Solve: (78 / 74.59) + 29", "answer": "The result of (78 / 74.59) + 29 is 30.05", "a": 78, "b": 74.59, "c": 29, "op1": "/", "op2": "+", "result": 30.05}
{"question": "Solve: (147 * 63) - 97.88", "answer": "The result of (147 * 63) - 97.88 is 9163.12", "a": 147, "b": 63, "c": 97.88, "op1": "*", "op2": "-", "result": 9163.12}
{"question": "Solve: (39.18 - 138) + 124", "answer": "The result of (39.18 - 138) + 124 is 25.18", "a": 39.18, "b": 138, "c": 124, "op1": "-", "op2": "+", "result": 25.18}
{"question": "Solve: (94 / 97) * 77", "answer": "The result of (94 / 97) * 77 is 74.62", "a": 94, "b": 97, "c": 77, "op1": "/", "op2": "*", "result": 74.62}
{"question": "Solve: (57 / 57) - 194", "answer": "The result of (57 / 57) - 194 is -193.0", "a": 57, "b": 57, "c": 194, "op1": "/", "op2": "-", "result": -193.0}
{"question": "Solve: (134 + 81) + 94", "answer": "The result of (134 + 81) + 94 is 309", "a": 134, "b": 81, "c": 94, "op1": "+", "op2": "+", "result": 309}
{"question": "Solve: (24 - 150) * 54", "answer": "The result of (24 - 150) * 54 is -6804", "a": 24, "b": 150, "c": 54, "op1": "-", "op2": "*", "result": -6804}
{"question": "Solve: (142 * 31) - 165.73", "answer": "The result of (142 * 31) - 165.73 is 4236.27", "a": 142, "b": 31, "c": 165.73, "op1": "*", "op2": "-", "result": 4236.27}
{"question": "Solve: (100 * 126) + 161", "answer": "The result of (100 * 126) + 161 is 12761", "a": 100, "b": 126, "c": 161, "op1": "*", "op2": "+", "result": 12761}
{"question": "Solve: (8 * 62) * 26.68", "answer": "The result of (8 * 62) * 26.68 is 13233.28", "a": 8, "b": 62, "c": 26.68, "op1": "*", "op2": "*", "result": 13233.28}
{"question": "Solve: (128 * 102.21) * 122", "answer": "The result of (128 * 102.21) * 122 is 1596111.36", "a": 128, "b": 102.21, "c": 122, "op1": "*", "op2": "*", "result": 1596111.36}
{"question": "Solve: (193 - 38.06) + 107", "answer": "The result of (193 - 38.06) + 107 is 261.94", "a": 193, "b": 38.06, "c": 107, "op1": "-", "op2": "+", "result": 261.94}
{"question": "Solve: (182 + 79) - 179.49", "answer": "The result of (182 + 79) - 179.49 is 81.51", "a": 182, "b": 79, "c": 179.49, "op1": "+", "op2": "-", "result": 81.51}
{"question": "Solve: (191.42 * 128) - 48.05", "answer": "The result of (191.42 * 128) - 48.05 is 24453.71", "a": 191.42, "b": 128, "c": 48.05, "op1": "*", "op2": "-", "result": 24453.71}
{"question": "Solve: (186.4 * 145) - 3", "answer": "The result of (186.4 * 145) - 3 is 27025.0", "a": 186.4, "b": 145, "c": 3, "op1": "*", "op2": "-", "result": 27025.0}
{"question": "Solve: (54.02 - 80) / 122.41", "answer": "The result of (54.02 - 80) / 122.41 is -0.21", "a": 54.02, "b": 80, "c": 122.41, "op1": "-", "op2": "/", "result": -0.21}
{"question": "Solve: (111.5 + 75.5) / 109", "answer": "The result of (111.5 + 75.5) / 109 is 1.72", "a": 111.5, "b": 75.5, "c": 109, "op1": "+", "op2": "/", "result": 1.72}
{"question": "Solve: (34.3 * 60.61) / 1", "answer": "The result of (34.3 * 60.61) / 1 is 2078.92", "a": 34.3, "b": 60.61, "c": 1, "op1": "*", "op2": "/", "result": 2078.92}
{"question": "Solve: (143.51 - 112.36) - 22.47", "answer": "The result of (143.51 - 112.36) - 22.47 is 8.68", "a": 143.51, "b": 112.36, "c": 22.47, "op1": "-", "op2": "-", "result": 8.68}
{"question": "Solve: (60.05 * 148) * 59.83", "answer": "The result of (60.05 * 148) * 59.83 is 531733.14", "a": 60.05, "b": 148, "c": 59.83, "op1": "*", "op2": "*", "result": 531733.14}
{"question": "Solve: (167 / 93.97) + 35", "answer": "The result of (167 / 93.97) + 35 is 36.78", "a": 167, "b": 93.97, "c": 35, "op1": "/", "op2": "+", "result": 36.78}
{"question": "Solve: (24 - 91) * 142", "answer": "The result of (24 - 91) * 142 is -9514", "a": 24, "b": 91, "c": 142, "op1": "-", "op2": "*", "result": -9514}
{"question": "Solve: (194 + 167) - 24", "answer": "The result of (194 + 167) - 24 is 337", "a": 194, "b": 167, "c": 24, "op1": "+", "op2": "-", "result": 337}
{"question": "Solve: (72 - 56.59) - 66", "answer": "The result of (72 - 56.59) - 66 is -50.59", "a": 72, "b": 56.59, "c": 66, "op1": "-", "op2": "-", "result": -50.59}
{"question": "Solve: (163 - 64) - 17", "answer": "The result of (163 - 64) - 17 is 82", "a": 163, "b": 64, "c": 17, "op1": "-", "op2": "-", "result": 82}
{"question": "Solve: (171 - 200) + 116", "answer": "The result of (171 - 200) + 116 is 87", "a": 171, "b": 200, "c": 116, "op1": "-", "op2": "+", "result": 87}
{"question": "Solve: (158 - 190) * 130", "answer": "The result of (158 - 190) * 130 is -4160", "a": 158, "b": 190, "c": 130, "op1": "-", "op2": "*", "result": -4160}
{"question": "Solve: (113 - 178.16) * 110", "answer": "The result of (113 - 178.16) * 110 is -7167.6", "a": 113, "b": 178.16, "c": 110, "op1": "-", "op2": "*", "result": -7167.6}
{"question": "Solve: (10 - 126) + 191.42", "answer": "The result of (10 - 126) + 191.42 is 75.42", "a": 10, "b": 126, "c": 191.42, "op1": "-", "op2": "+", "result": 75.42}
{"question": "Solve: (131 - 116.52) + 57.74", "answer": "The result of (131 - 116.52) + 57.74 is 72.22", "a": 131, "b": 116.52, "c": 57.74, "op1": "-", "op2": "+", "result": 72.22}
{"question": "Solve: (85 * 115) + 154", "answer": "The result of (85 * 115) + 154 is 9929", "a": 85, "b": 115, "c": 154, "op1": "*", "op2": "+", "result": 9929}
{"question": "Solve: (3 / 64) * 155.75", "answer": "The result of (3 / 64) * 155.75 is 7.3", "a": 3, "b": 64, "c": 155.75, "op1": "/", "op2": "*", "result": 7.3}
{"question": "Solve: (9 + 182) * 4", "answer": "The result of (9 + 182) * 4 is 764", "a": 9, "b": 182, "c": 4, "op1": "+", "op2": "*", "result": 764}
{"question": "Solve: (122 + 43) - 58.32", "answer": "The result of (122 + 43) - 58.32 is 106.68", "a": 122, "b": 43, "c": 58.32, "op1": "+", "op2": "-", "result": 106.68}
{"question": "Solve: (86.76 + 93) - 2", "answer": "The result of (86.76 + 93) - 2 is 177.76", "a": 86.76, "b": 93, "c": 2, "op1": "+", "op2": "-", "result": 177.76}
{"question": "Solve: (68 / 84) + 195.75", "answer": "The result of (68 / 84) + 195.75 is 196.56", "a": 68, "b": 84, "c": 195.75, "op1": "/", "op2": "+", "result": 196.56}
{"question": "Solve: (35 + 25) - 5", "answer": "The result of (35 + 25) - 5 is 55", "a": 35, "b": 25, "c": 5, "op1": "+", "op2": "-", "result": 55}
{"question": "Solve: (181 + 93) * 67.34", "answer": "The result of (181 + 93) * 67.34 is 18451.16", "a": 181, "b": 93, "c": 67.34, "op1": "+", "op2": "*", "result": 18451.16}
{"question": "Solve: (129 / 125) - 121", "answer": "The result of (129 / 125) - 121 is -119.97", "a": 129, "b": 125, "c": 121, "op1": "/", "op2": "-", "result": -119.97}
{"question": "Solve: (93 - 91) * 104.91", "answer": "The result of (93 - 91) * 104.91 is 209.82", "a": 93, "b": 91, "c": 104.91, "op1": "-", "op2": "*", "result": 209.82}
{"question": "Solve: (18 + 45.9) * 8", "answer": "The result of (18 + 45.9) * 8 is 511.2", "a": 18, "b": 45.9, "c": 8, "op1": "+", "op2": "*", "result": 511.2}
{"question": "Solve: (4 / 51.25) / 187", "answer": "The result of (4 / 51.25) / 187 is 0.0", "a": 4, "b": 51.25, "c": 187, "op1": "/", "op2": "/", "result": 0.0}
{"question": "Solve: (100.81 + 12.89) + 102.69", "answer": "The result of (100.81 + 12.89) + 102.69 is 216.39", "a": 100.81, "b": 12.89, "c": 102.69, "op1": "+", "op2": "+", "result": 216.39}
{"question": "Solve: (71 * 100.26) + 34", "answer": "The result of (71 * 100.26) + 34 is 7152.46", "a": 71, "b": 100.26, "c": 34, "op1": "*", "op2": "+", "result": 7152.46}
{"question": "Solve: (83.57 - 189) - 79", "answer": "The result of (83.57 - 189) - 79 is -184.43", "a": 83.57, "b": 189, "c": 79, "op1": "-", "op2": "-", "result": -184.43}
{"question": "Solve: (80.47 * 92) - 160.26", "answer": "The result of (80.47 * 92) - 160.26 is 7242.98", "a": 80.47, "b": 92, "c": 160.26, "op1": "*", "op2": "-", "result": 7242.98}
{"question": "Solve: (45 * 5.81) * 73", "answer": "The result of (45 * 5.81) * 73 is 19085.85", "a": 45, "b": 5.81, "c": 73, "op1": "*", "op2": "*", "result": 19085.85}
{"question": "Solve: (33.74 + 23) * 191", "answer": "The result of (33.74 + 23) * 191 is 10837.34", "a": 33.74, "b": 23, "c": 191, "op1": "+", "op2": "*", "result": 10837.34}
{"question": "Solve: (25.59 - 128.14) - 30.84", "answer": "The result of (25.59 - 128.14) - 30.84 is -133.39", "a": 25.59, "b": 128.14, "c": 30.84, "op1": "-", "op2": "-", "result": -133.39}
{"question": "Solve: (88 - 189.1) + 47.96", "answer": "The result of (88 - 189.1) + 47.96 is -53.14", "a": 88, "b": 189.1, "c": 47.96, "op1": "-", "op2": "+", "result": -53.14}
{"question": "Solve: (122 - 64) - 156", "answer": "The result of (122 - 64) - 156 is -98", "a": 122, "b": 64, "c": 156, "op1": "-", "op2": "-", "result": -98}
{"question": "Solve: (161.68 + 24) + 108.44", "answer": "The result of (161.68 + 24) + 108.44 is 294.12", "a": 161.68, "b": 24, "c": 108.44, "op1": "+", "op2": "+", "result": 294.12}
{"question": "Solve: (140 * 127) * 10.79", "answer": "The result of (140 * 127) * 10.79 is 191846.2", "a": 140, "b": 127, "c": 10.79, "op1": "*", "op2": "*", "result": 191846.2}
{"question": "Solve: (141 / 141.29) * 60.51", "answer": "The result of (141 / 141.29) * 60.51 is 60.39", "a": 141, "b": 141.29, "c": 60.51, "op1": "/", "op2": "*", "result": 60.39}
{"question": "Solve: (198 - 77) - 192.31", "answer": "The result of (198 - 77) - 192.31 is -71.31", "a": 198, "b": 77, "c": 192.31, "op1": "-", "op2": "-", "result": -71.31}
{"question": "Solve: (28 / 165) + 10", "answer": "The result of (28 / 165) + 10 is 10.17", "a": 28, "b": 165, "c": 10, "op1": "/", "op2": "+", "result": 10.17}
{"question": "Solve: (9 * 99) - 45", "answer": "The result of (9 * 99) - 45 is 846", "a": 9, "b": 99, "c": 45, "op1": "*", "op2": "-", "result": 846}
{"question": "Solve: (124 + 11) + 72", "answer": "The result of (124 + 11) + 72 is 207", "a": 124, "b": 11, "c": 72, "op1": "+", "op2": "+", "result": 207}
{"question": "Solve: (130 - 194) - 51", "answer": "The result of (130 - 194) - 51 is -115", "a": 130, "b": 194, "c": 51, "op1": "-", "op2": "-", "result": -115}
{"question": "Solve: (155 / 21) * 86", "answer": "The result of (155 / 21) * 86 is 634.76", "a": 155, "b": 21, "c": 86, "op1": "/", "op2": "*", "result": 634.76}
{"question": "Solve: (138.27 / 172) - 52.91", "answer": "The result of (138.27 / 172) - 52.91 is -52.11", "a": 138.27, "b": 172, "c": 52.91, "op1": "/", "op2": "-", "result": -52.11}
{"question": "Solve: (122 * 121) / 125", "answer": "The result of (122 * 121) / 125 is 118.1", "a": 122, "b": 121, "c": 125, "op1": "*", "op2": "/", "result": 118.1}
{"question": "Solve: (3.19 - 60.16) + 200", "answer": "The result of (3.19 - 60.16) + 200 is 143.03", "a": 3.19, "b": 60.16, "c": 200, "op1": "-", "op2": "+", "result": 143.03}
{"question": "Solve: (28 + 142.28) + 138", "answer": "The result of (28 + 142.28) + 138 is 308.28", "a": 28, "b": 142.28, "c": 138, "op1": "+", "op2": "+", "result": 308.28}
{"question": "Solve: (121 - 91.83) - 96", "answer": "The result of (121 - 91.83) - 96 is -66.83", "a": 121, "b": 91.83, "c": 96, "op1": "-", "op2": "-", "result": -66.83}
{"question": "Solve: (44 + 42) + 170.21", "answer": "The result of (44 + 42) + 170.21 is 256.21", "a": 44, "b": 42, "c": 170.21, "op1": "+", "op2": "+", "result": 256.21}
{"question": "Solve: (141 - 177) - 64", "answer": "The result of (141 - 177) - 64 is -100", "a": 141, "b": 177, "c": 64, "op1": "-", "op2": "-", "result": -100}
{"question": "Solve: (134 * 125) * 46", "answer": "The result of (134 * 125) * 46 is 770500", "a": 134, "b": 125, "c": 46, "op1": "*", "op2": "*", "result": 770500}
{"question": "Solve: (184 - 185.45) + 55", "answer": "The result of (184 - 185.45) + 55 is 53.55", "a": 184, "b": 185.45, "c": 55, "op1": "-", "op2": "+", "result": 53.55}
{"question": "Solve: (105.5 * 160) / 52", "answer": "The result of (105.5 * 160) / 52 is 324.62", "a": 105.5, "b": 160, "c": 52, "op1": "*", "op2": "/", "result": 324.62}
{"question": "Solve: (59 * 76) + 48", "answer": "The result of (59 * 76) + 48 is 4532", "a": 59, "b": 76, "c": 48, "op1": "*", "op2": "+", "result": 4532}
{"question": "Solve: (148 * 77) - 48.75", "answer": "The result of (148 * 77) - 48.75 is 11347.25", "a": 148, "b": 77, "c": 48.75, "op1": "*", "op2": "-", "result": 11347.25}
{"question": "Solve: (152.43 / 135.1) * 65", "answer": "The result of (152.43 / 135.1) * 65 is 73.34", "a": 152.43, "b": 135.1, "c": 65, "op1": "/", "op2": "*", "result": 73.34}
{"question": "Solve: (193.19 + 190.36) * 74", "answer": "The result of (193.19 + 190.36) * 74 is 28382.7", "a": 193.19, "b": 190.36, "c": 74, "op1": "+", "op2": "*", "result": 28382.7}
{"question": "Solve: (59.67 + 123) * 62", "answer": "The result of (59.67 + 123) * 62 is 11325.54", "a": 59.67, "b": 123, "c": 62, "op1": "+", "op2": "*", "result": 11325.54}
{"question": "Solve: (145 * 102) / 59.93", "answer": "The result of (145 * 102) / 59.93 is 246.79", "a": 145, "b": 102, "c": 59.93, "op1": "*", "op2": "/", "result": 246.79}
{"question": "Solve: (168.32 - 139.07) * 171.44", "answer": "The result of (168.32 - 139.07) * 171.44 is 5014.62", "a": 168.32, "b": 139.07, "c": 171.44, "op1": "-", "op2": "*", "result": 5014.62}
{"question": "Solve: (159 - 154.24) + 94", "answer": "The result of (159 - 154.24) + 94 is 98.76", "a": 159, "b": 154.24, "c": 94, "op1": "-", "op2": "+", "result": 98.76}
{"question": "Solve: (115 * 162.08) * 5", "answer": "The result of (115 * 162.08) * 5 is 93196.0", "a": 115, "b": 162.08, "c": 5, "op1": "*", "op2": "*", "result": 93196.0}
{"question": "Solve: (104.0 - 32) + 196", "answer": "The result of (104.0 - 32) + 196 is 268.0", "a": 104.0, "b": 32, "c": 196, "op1": "-", "op2": "+", "result": 268.0}
{"question": "Solve: (70 - 91.97) * 129", "answer": "The result of (70 - 91.97) * 129 is -2834.13", "a": 70, "b": 91.97, "c": 129, "op1": "-", "op2": "*", "result": -2834.13}
{"question": "Solve: (108.66 + 172) + 109.51", "answer": "The result of (108.66 + 172) + 109.51 is 390.17", "a": 108.66, "b": 172, "c": 109.51, "op1": "+", "op2": "+", "result": 390.17}
{"question": "Solve: (33 * 188.77) / 87.97", "answer": "The result of (33 * 188.77) / 87.97 is 70.81", "a": 33, "b": 188.77, "c": 87.97, "op1": "*", "op2": "/", "result": 70.81}
{"question": "Solve: (136 - 100) - 181", "answer": "The result of (136 - 100) - 181 is -145", "a": 136, "b": 100, "c": 181, "op1": "-", "op2": "-", "result": -145}
{"question": "Solve: (10.63 - 165) * 158", "answer": "The result of (10.63 - 165) * 158 is -24390.46", "a": 10.63, "b": 165, "c": 158, "op1": "-", "op2": "*", "result": -24390.46}
{"question": "Solve: (56 / 47) * 170.81", "answer": "The result of (56 / 47) * 170.81 is 203.52", "a": 56, "b": 47, "c": 170.81, "op1": "/", "op2": "*", "result": 203.52}
{"question": "Solve: (175 + 43) / 164", "answer": "The result of (175 + 43) / 164 is 1.33", "a": 175, "b": 43, "c": 164, "op1": "+", "op2": "/", "result": 1.33}
{"question": "Solve: (158 + 112) - 75", "answer": "The result of (158 + 112) - 75 is 195", "a": 158, "b": 112, "c": 75, "op1": "+", "op2": "-", "result": 195}
{"question": "Solve: (180 + 73.72) - 125.01", "answer": "The result of (180 + 73.72) - 125.01 is 128.71", "a": 180, "b": 73.72, "c": 125.01, "op1": "+", "op2": "-", "result": 128.71}
{"question": "Solve: (36 / 153.27) * 18", "answer": "The result of (36 / 153.27) * 18 is 4.23", "a": 36, "b": 153.27, "c": 18, "op1": "/", "op2": "*", "result": 4.23}
{"question": "Solve: (190 * 57) - 195.28", "answer": "The result of (190 * 57) - 195.28 is 10634.72", "a": 190, "b": 57, "c": 195.28, "op1": "*", "op2": "-", "result": 10634.72}
{"question": "Solve: (111.5 - 150) / 102", "answer": "The result of (111.5 - 150) / 102 is -0.38", "a": 111.5, "b": 150, "c": 102, "op1": "-", "op2": "/", "result": -0.38}
{"question": "Solve: (144 * 177.84) + 11", "answer": "The result of (144 * 177.84) + 11 is 25619.96", "a": 144, "b": 177.84, "c": 11, "op1": "*", "op2": "+", "result": 25619.96}
{"question": "Solve: (33 / 14.71) + 56.79", "answer": "The result of (33 / 14.71) + 56.79 is 59.03", "a": 33, "b": 14.71, "c": 56.79, "op1": "/", "op2": "+", "result": 59.03}
{"question": "Solve: (89 * 160.86) / 180", "answer": "The result of (89 * 160.86) / 180 is 79.54", "a": 89, "b": 160.86, "c": 180, "op1": "*", "op2": "/", "result": 79.54}
{"question": "Solve: (179 / 27) + 171", "answer": "The result of (179 / 27) + 171 is 177.63", "a": 179, "b": 27, "c": 171, "op1": "/", "op2": "+", "result": 177.63}
{"question": "Solve: (115 + 29.51) - 125", "answer": "The result of (115 + 29.51) - 125 is 19.51", "a": 115, "b": 29.51, "c": 125, "op1": "+", "op2": "-", "result": 19.51}
{"question": "Solve: (78 - 5.8) + 150.17", "answer": "The result of (78 - 5.8) + 150.17 is 222.37", "a": 78, "b": 5.8, "c": 150.17, "op1": "-", "op2": "+", "result": 222.37}
{"question": "Solve: (153.44 + 18) + 49", "answer": "The result of (153.44 + 18) + 49 is 220.44", "a": 153.44, "b": 18, "c": 49, "op1": "+", "op2": "+", "result": 220.44}
{"question": "Solve: (79 - 31) + 3", "answer": "The result of (79 - 31) + 3 is 51", "a": 79, "b": 31, "c": 3, "op1": "-", "op2": "+", "result": 51}
{"question": "Solve: (68 * 189.38) / 199.62", "answer": "The result of (68 * 189.38) / 199.62 is 64.51", "a": 68, "b": 189.38, "c": 199.62, "op1": "*", "op2": "/", "result": 64.51}
{"question": "Solve: (158 - 38.71) - 60", "answer": "The result of (158 - 38.71) - 60 is 59.29", "a": 158, "b": 38.71, "c": 60, "op1": "-", "op2": "-", "result": 59.29}
{"question": "Solve: (117 + 65.89) + 38", "answer": "The result of (117 + 65.89) + 38 is 220.89", "a": 117, "b": 65.89, "c": 38, "op1": "+", "op2": "+", "result": 220.89}
{"question": "Solve: (40.06 + 30) * 48", "answer": "The result of (40.06 + 30) * 48 is 3362.88", "a": 40.06, "b": 30, "c": 48, "op1": "+", "op2": "*", "result": 3362.88}
{"question": "Solve: (137 - 108.88) + 43", "answer": "The result of (137 - 108.88) + 43 is 71.12", "a": 137, "b": 108.88, "c": 43, "op1": "-", "op2": "+", "result": 71.12}
{"question": "Solve: (104.42 + 36) - 180.89", "answer": "The result of (104.42 + 36) - 180.89 is -40.47", "a": 104.42, "b": 36, "c": 180.89, "op1": "+", "op2": "-", "result": -40.47}
{"question": "Solve: (167.94 - 66) - 163", "answer": "The result of (167.94 - 66) - 163 is -61.06", "a": 167.94, "b": 66, "c": 163, "op1": "-", "op2": "-", "result": -61.06}
{"question": "Solve: (67 - 162) * 111", "answer": "The result of (67 - 162) * 111 is -10545", "a": 67, "b": 162, "c": 111, "op1": "-", "op2": "*", "result": -10545}
{"question": "Solve: (77 * 144) / 16", "answer": "The result of (77 * 144) / 16 is 693.0", "a": 77, "b": 144, "c": 16, "op1": "*", "op2": "/", "result": 693.0}
{"question": "Solve: (93 + 168) * 92", "answer": "The result of (93 + 168) * 92 is 24012", "a": 93, "b": 168, "c": 92, "op1": "+", "op2": "*", "result": 24012}
{"question": "Solve: (88 / 180.26) - 95", "answer": "The result of (88 / 180.26) - 95 is -94.51", "a": 88, "b": 180.26, "c": 95, "op1": "/", "op2": "-", "result": -94.51}
{"question": "Solve: (62 / 124) - 124", "answer": "The result of (62 / 124) - 124 is -123.5", "a": 62, "b": 124, "c": 124, "op1": "/", "op2": "-", "result": -123.5}
{"question": "Solve: (22 * 22) - 199", "answer": "The result of (22 * 22) - 199 is 285", "a": 22, "b": 22, "c": 199, "op1": "*", "op2": "-", "result": 285}
{"question": "Solve: (50 / 152) - 161.63", "answer": "The result of (50 / 152) - 161.63 is -161.3", "a": 50, "b": 152, "c": 161.63, "op1": "/", "op2": "-", "result": -161.3}
{"question": "Solve: (97 - 79) - 174", "answer": "The result of (97 - 79) - 174 is -156", "a": 97, "b": 79, "c": 174, "op1": "-", "op2": "-", "result": -156}
{"question": "Solve: (67 / 156) + 120.37", "answer": "The result of (67 / 156) + 120.37 is 120.8", "a": 67, "b": 156, "c": 120.37, "op1": "/", "op2": "+", "result": 120.8}
{"question": "Solve: (2 / 1) * 123.95", "answer": "The result of (2 / 1) * 123.95 is 247.9", "a": 2, "b": 1, "c": 123.95, "op1": "/", "op2": "*", "result": 247.9}
{"question": "Solve: (40 - 169) / 131", "answer": "The result of (40 - 169) / 131 is -0.98", "a": 40, "b": 169, "c": 131, "op1": "-", "op2": "/", "result": -0.98}
{"question": "Solve: (151 + 160.04) + 172", "answer": "The result of (151 + 160.04) + 172 is 483.04", "a": 151, "b": 160.04, "c": 172, "op1": "+", "op2": "+", "result": 483.04}
{"question": "Solve: (106 * 99.62) * 137", "answer": "The result of (106 * 99.62) * 137 is 1446681.64", "a": 106, "b": 99.62, "c": 137, "op1": "*", "op2": "*", "result": 1446681.64}
{"question": "Solve: (31 * 139) * 174", "answer": "The result of (31 * 139) * 174 is 749766", "a": 31, "b": 139, "c": 174, "op1": "*", "op2": "*", "result": 749766}
{"question": "Solve: (44 - 182.4) / 194", "answer": "The result of (44 - 182.4) / 194 is -0.71", "a": 44, "b": 182.4, "c": 194, "op1": "-", "op2": "/", "result": -0.71}
{"question": "Solve: (35 + 125) / 163", "answer": "The result of (35 + 125) / 163 is 0.98", "a": 35, "b": 125, "c": 163, "op1": "+", "op2": "/", "result": 0.98}
{"question": "Solve: (27.41 * 115) - 194.15", "answer": "The result of (27.41 * 115) - 194.15 is 2958.0", "a": 27.41, "b": 115, "c": 194.15, "op1": "*", "op2": "-", "result": 2958.0}
{"question": "Solve: (12 * 35.44) - 153", "answer": "The result of (12 * 35.44) - 153 is 272.28", "a": 12, "b": 35.44, "c": 153, "op1": "*", "op2": "-", "result": 272.28}
{"question": "Solve: (18 + 17) + 14", "answer": "The result of (18 + 17) + 14 is 49", "a": 18, "b": 17, "c": 14, "op1": "+", "op2": "+", "result": 49}
{"question": "Solve: (32 * 109) - 51", "answer": "The result of (32 * 109) - 51 is 3437", "a": 32, "b": 109, "c": 51, "op1": "*", "op2": "-", "result": 3437}
{"question": "Solve: (2 + 184.93) * 178.8", "answer": "The result of (2 + 184.93) * 178.8 is 33423.08", "a": 2, "b": 184.93, "c": 178.8, "op1": "+", "op2": "*", "result": 33423.08}
{"question": "Solve: (164.62 + 144.7) * 19.7", "answer": "The result of (164.62 + 144.7) * 19.7 is 6093.6", "a": 164.62, "b": 144.7, "c": 19.7, "op1": "+", "op2": "*", "result": 6093.6}
{"question": "Solve: (49 - 14) * 28", "answer": "The result of (49 - 14) * 28 is 980", "a": 49, "b": 14, "c": 28, "op1": "-", "op2": "*", "result": 980}
{"question": "Solve: (24 + 114.69) * 69", "answer": "The result of (24 + 114.69) * 69 is 9569.61", "a": 24, "b": 114.69, "c": 69, "op1": "+", "op2": "*", "result": 9569.61}
{"question": "Solve: (98.75 - 97) * 41", "answer": "The result of (98.75 - 97) * 41 is 71.75", "a": 98.75, "b": 97, "c": 41, "op1": "-", "op2": "*", "result": 71.75}
{"question": "Solve: (48.76 * 198.38) * 35.77", "answer": "The result of (48.76 * 198.38) * 35.77 is 346003.52", "a": 48.76, "b": 198.38, "c": 35.77, "op1": "*", "op2": "*", "result": 346003.52}
{"question": "Solve: (56.94 + 138) - 114.47", "answer": "The result of (56.94 + 138) - 114.47 is 80.47", "a": 56.94, "b": 138, "c": 114.47, "op1": "+", "op2": "-", "result": 80.47}
{"question": "Solve: (98 + 159) + 65.27", "answer": "The result of (98 + 159) + 65.27 is 322.27", "a": 98, "b": 159, "c": 65.27, "op1": "+", "op2": "+", "result": 322.27}
{"question": "Solve: (44 / 129.79) * 184.33", "answer": "The result of (44 / 129.79) * 184.33 is 62.49", "a": 44, "b": 129.79, "c": 184.33, "op1": "/", "op2": "*", "result": 62.49}
{"question": "Solve: (178 - 77) / 146", "answer": "The result of (178 - 77) / 146 is 0.69", "a": 178, "b": 77, "c": 146, "op1": "-", "op2": "/", "result": 0.69}
{"question": "Solve: (179 - 159) + 155.66", "answer": "The result of (179 - 159) + 155.66 is 175.66", "a": 179, "b": 159, "c": 155.66, "op1": "-", "op2": "+", "result": 175.66}
{"question": "Solve: (28 / 200) * 175", "answer": "The result of (28 / 200) * 175 is 24.5", "a": 28, "b": 200, "c": 175, "op1": "/", "op2": "*", "result": 24.5}
{"question": "Solve: (177.48 + 66) + 68", "answer": "The result of (177.48 + 66) + 68 is 311.48", "a": 177.48, "b": 66, "c": 68, "op1": "+", "op2": "+", "result": 311.48}
{"question": "Solve: (19 + 43) + 132.34", "answer": "The result of (19 + 43) + 132.34 is 194.34", "a": 19, "b": 43, "c": 132.34, "op1": "+", "op2": "+", "result": 194.34}
{"question": "Solve: (3 / 6.44) * 26.68", "answer": "The result of (3 / 6.44) * 26.68 is 12.43", "a": 3, "b": 6.44, "c": 26.68, "op1": "/", "op2": "*", "result": 12.43}
{"question": "Solve: (93.34 * 58.32) * 189.12", "answer": "The result of (93.34 * 58.32) * 189.12 is 1029491.51", "a": 93.34, "b": 58.32, "c": 189.12, "op1": "*", "op2": "*", "result": 1029491.51}
{"question": "Solve: (126 * 43) + 94.61", "answer": "The result of (126 * 43) + 94.61 is 5512.61", "a": 126, "b": 43, "c": 94.61, "op1": "*", "op2": "+", "result": 5512.61}
{"question": "Solve: (43 + 7) + 128", "answer": "The result of (43 + 7) + 128 is 178", "a": 43, "b": 7, "c": 128, "op1": "+", "op2": "+", "result": 178}
{"question": "Solve: (133 * 99) * 37", "answer": "The result of (133 * 99) * 37 is 487179", "a": 133, "b": 99, "c": 37, "op1": "*", "op2": "*", "result": 487179}
{"question": "Solve: (20.33 + 99.21) + 60.28", "answer": "The result of (20.33 + 99.21) + 60.28 is 179.82", "a": 20.33, "b": 99.21, "c": 60.28, "op1": "+", "op2": "+", "result": 179.82}
{"question": "Solve: (4 / 112) - 41.11", "answer": "The result of (4 / 112) - 41.11 is -41.07", "a": 4, "b": 112, "c": 41.11, "op1": "/", "op2": "-", "result": -41.07}
{"question": "Solve: (30 / 61.29) - 124.38", "answer": "The result of (30 / 61.29) - 124.38 is -123.89", "a": 30, "b": 61.29, "c": 124.38, "op1": "/", "op2": "-", "result": -123.89}
{"question": "Solve: (66 - 101) + 2", "answer": "The result of (66 - 101) + 2 is -33", "a": 66, "b": 101, "c": 2, "op1": "-", "op2": "+", "result": -33}
{"question": "Solve: (145 * 31.52) + 124", "answer": "The result of (145 * 31.52) + 124 is 4694.4", "a": 145, "b": 31.52, "c": 124, "op1": "*", "op2": "+", "result": 4694.4}
{"question": "Solve: (199.6 - 106.78) * 142", "answer": "The result of (199.6 - 106.78) * 142 is 13180.44", "a": 199.6, "b": 106.78, "c": 142, "op1": "-", "op2": "*", "result": 13180.44}
{"question": "Solve: (195 * 133.67) * 75", "answer": "The result of (195 * 133.67) * 75 is 1954923.75", "a": 195, "b": 133.67, "c": 75, "op1": "*", "op2": "*", "result": 1954923.75}
{"question": "Solve: (31 + 43) / 33", "answer": "The result of (31 + 43) / 33 is 2.24", "a": 31, "b": 43, "c": 33, "op1": "+", "op2": "/", "result": 2.24}
{"question": "Solve: (46 - 184) * 86", "answer": "The result of (46 - 184) * 86 is -11868", "a": 46, "b": 184, "c": 86, "op1": "-", "op2": "*", "result": -11868}
{"question": "Solve: (80 * 92.15) - 48", "answer": "The result of (80 * 92.15) - 48 is 7324.0", "a": 80, "b": 92.15, "c": 48, "op1": "*", "op2": "-", "result": 7324.0}
{"question": "Solve: (15.62 * 75) + 151.77", "answer": "The result of (15.62 * 75) + 151.77 is 1323.27", "a": 15.62, "b": 75, "c": 151.77, "op1": "*", "op2": "+", "result": 1323.27}
{"question": "Solve: (111 - 68.96) + 68.64", "answer": "The result of (111 - 68.96) + 68.64 is 110.68", "a": 111, "b": 68.96, "c": 68.64, "op1": "-", "op2": "+", "result": 110.68}
{"question": "Solve: (128 / 90) * 165.78", "answer": "The result of (128 / 90) * 165.78 is 235.78", "a": 128, "b": 90, "c": 165.78, "op1": "/", "op2": "*", "result": 235.78}
{"question": "Solve: (155.98 - 138) + 182", "answer": "The result of (155.98 - 138) + 182 is 199.98", "a": 155.98, "b": 138, "c": 182, "op1": "-", "op2": "+", "result": 199.98}
{"question": "Solve: (99.22 + 134.26) - 68.04", "answer": "The result of (99.22 + 134.26) - 68.04 is 165.44", "a": 99.22, "b": 134.26, "c": 68.04, "op1": "+", "op2": "-", "result": 165.44}
{"question": "Solve: (1.47 + 5.29) * 51", "answer": "The result of (1.47 + 5.29) * 51 is 344.76", "a": 1.47, "b": 5.29, "c": 51, "op1": "+", "op2": "*", "result": 344.76}
{"question": "Solve: (99 + 59.5) - 31", "answer": "The result of (99 + 59.5) - 31 is 127.5", "a": 99, "b": 59.5, "c": 31, "op1": "+", "op2": "-", "result": 127.5}
{"question": "Solve: (110 * 163.03) + 102.73", "answer": "The result of (110 * 163.03) + 102.73 is 18036.03", "a": 110, "b": 163.03, "c": 102.73, "op1": "*", "op2": "+", "result": 18036.03}
{"question": "Solve: (76 * 145) + 37", "answer": "The result of (76 * 145) + 37 is 11057", "a": 76, "b": 145, "c": 37, "op1": "*", "op2": "+", "result": 11057}
{"question": "Solve: (95 - 155) - 64", "answer": "The result of (95 - 155) - 64 is -124", "a": 95, "b": 155, "c": 64, "op1": "-", "op2": "-", "result": -124}
{"question": "Solve: (129 / 111) / 1", "answer": "The result of (129 / 111) / 1 is 1.16", "a": 129, "b": 111, "c": 1, "op1": "/", "op2": "/", "result": 1.16}
{"question": "Solve: (106 / 43) - 97", "answer": "The result of (106 / 43) - 97 is -94.53", "a": 106, "b": 43, "c": 97, "op1": "/", "op2": "-", "result": -94.53}
{"question": "Solve: (194 - 174) * 136.45", "answer": "The result of (194 - 174) * 136.45 is 2729.0", "a": 194, "b": 174, "c": 136.45, "op1": "-", "op2": "*", "result": 2729.0}
{"question": "Solve: (29.56 - 163) - 193.78", "answer": "The result of (29.56 - 163) - 193.78 is -327.22", "a": 29.56, "b": 163, "c": 193.78, "op1": "-", "op2": "-", "result": -327.22}
{"question": "Solve: (40.22 - 57.2) + 116", "answer": "The result of (40.22 - 57.2) + 116 is 99.02", "a": 40.22, "b": 57.2, "c": 116, "op1": "-", "op2": "+", "result": 99.02}
{"question": "Solve: (83 + 200) + 197", "answer": "The result of (83 + 200) + 197 is 480", "a": 83, "b": 200, "c": 197, "op1": "+", "op2": "+", "result": 480}
{"question": "Solve: (81 - 12) * 11", "answer": "The result of (81 - 12) * 11 is 759", "a": 81, "b": 12, "c": 11, "op1": "-", "op2": "*", "result": 759}
{"question": "Solve: (33 - 99.08) - 19.85", "answer": "The result of (33 - 99.08) - 19.85 is -85.93", "a": 33, "b": 99.08, "c": 19.85, "op1": "-", "op2": "-", "result": -85.93}
{"question": "Solve: (27.77 / 116) + 187", "answer": "The result of (27.77 / 116) + 187 is 187.24", "a": 27.77, "b": 116, "c": 187, "op1": "/", "op2": "+", "result": 187.24}
{"question": "Solve: (62 / 118) - 64", "answer": "The result of (62 / 118) - 64 is -63.47", "a": 62, "b": 118, "c": 64, "op1": "/", "op2": "-", "result": -63.47}
{"question": "Solve: (148 - 69) - 99", "answer": "The result of (148 - 69) - 99 is -20", "a": 148, "b": 69, "c": 99, "op1": "-", "op2": "-", "result": -20}
{"question": "Solve: (124 / 19) + 177", "answer": "The result of (124 / 19) + 177 is 183.53", "a": 124, "b": 19, "c": 177, "op1": "/", "op2": "+", "result": 183.53}
{"question": "Solve: (46.38 * 51) - 175.2", "answer": "The result of (46.38 * 51) - 175.2 is 2190.18", "a": 46.38, "b": 51, "c": 175.2, "op1": "*", "op2": "-", "result": 2190.18}
{"question": "Solve: (13 - 20) + 194.06", "answer": "The result of (13 - 20) + 194.06 is 187.06", "a": 13, "b": 20, "c": 194.06, "op1": "-", "op2": "+", "result": 187.06}
{"question": "Solve: (8 - 66.96) + 190.68", "answer": "The result of (8 - 66.96) + 190.68 is 131.72", "a": 8, "b": 66.96, "c": 190.68, "op1": "-", "op2": "+", "result": 131.72}
{"question": "Solve: (119 * 14) - 59", "answer": "The result of (119 * 14) - 59 is 1607", "a": 119, "b": 14, "c": 59, "op1": "*", "op2": "-", "result": 1607}
{"question": "Solve: (77.78 * 48) * 107.09", "answer": "The result of (77.78 * 48) * 107.09 is 399814.09", "a": 77.78, "b": 48, "c": 107.09, "op1": "*", "op2": "*", "result": 399814.09}
{"question": "Solve: (170.26 - 181) - 182.06", "answer": "The result of (170.26 - 181) - 182.06 is -192.8", "a": 170.26, "b": 181, "c": 182.06, "op1": "-", "op2": "-", "result": -192.8}
{"question": "Solve: (69 - 135.29) * 30", "answer": "The result of (69 - 135.29) * 30 is -1988.7", "a": 69, "b": 135.29, "c": 30, "op1": "-", "op2": "*", "result": -1988.7}
{"question": "Solve: (69 + 135) - 91.04", "answer": "The result of (69 + 135) - 91.04 is 112.96", "a": 69, "b": 135, "c": 91.04, "op1": "+", "op2": "-", "result": 112.96}
{"question": "Solve: (6 + 23) - 83.12", "answer": "The result of (6 + 23) - 83.12 is -54.12", "a": 6, "b": 23, "c": 83.12, "op1": "+", "op2": "-", "result": -54.12}
{"question": "Solve: (161 * 82) - 138", "answer": "The result of (161 * 82) - 138 is 13064", "a": 161, "b": 82, "c": 138, "op1": "*", "op2": "-", "result": 13064}
{"question": "Solve: (41 + 107) + 83", "answer": "The result of (41 + 107) + 83 is 231", "a": 41, "b": 107, "c": 83, "op1": "+", "op2": "+", "result": 231}
{"question": "Solve: (59 + 96) + 183.95", "answer": "The result of (59 + 96) + 183.95 is 338.95", "a": 59, "b": 96, "c": 183.95, "op1": "+", "op2": "+", "result": 338.95}
{"question": "Solve: (190.08 * 30) * 59", "answer": "The result of (190.08 * 30) * 59 is 336441.6", "a": 190.08, "b": 30, "c": 59, "op1": "*", "op2": "*", "result": 336441.6}
{"question": "Solve: (157.53 * 42) + 160.26", "answer": "The result of (157.53 * 42) + 160.26 is 6776.52", "a": 157.53, "b": 42, "c": 160.26, "op1": "*", "op2": "+", "result": 6776.52}
{"question": "Solve: (118.7 + 18) - 135", "answer": "The result of (118.7 + 18) - 135 is 1.7", "a": 118.7, "b": 18, "c": 135, "op1": "+", "op2": "-", "result": 1.7}
{"question": "Solve: (66 + 45) + 182", "answer": "The result of (66 + 45) + 182 is 293", "a": 66, "b": 45, "c": 182, "op1": "+", "op2": "+", "result": 293}
{"question": "Solve: (131 / 185.65) / 4.28", "answer": "The result of (131 / 185.65) / 4.28 is 0.16", "a": 131, "b": 185.65, "c": 4.28, "op1": "/", "op2": "/", "result": 0.16}
{"question": "Solve: (63 + 117.41) + 153", "answer": "The result of (63 + 117.41) + 153 is 333.41", "a": 63, "b": 117.41, "c": 153, "op1": "+", "op2": "+", "result": 333.41}
{"question": "Solve: (177 / 111) * 64", "answer": "The result of (177 / 111) * 64 is 102.05", "a": 177, "b": 111, "c": 64, "op1": "/", "op2": "*", "result": 102.05}
{"question": "Solve: (63.17 * 80) - 187.82", "answer": "The result of (63.17 * 80) - 187.82 is 4865.78", "a": 63.17, "b": 80, "c": 187.82, "op1": "*", "op2": "-", "result": 4865.78}
{"question": "Solve: (113 * 169.06) + 36", "answer": "The result of (113 * 169.06) + 36 is 19139.78", "a": 113, "b": 169.06, "c": 36, "op1": "*", "op2": "+", "result": 19139.78}
{"question": "Solve: (147 - 91) + 84", "answer": "The result of (147 - 91) + 84 is 140", "a": 147, "b": 91, "c": 84, "op1": "-", "op2": "+", "result": 140}
{"question": "Solve: (39 - 3) * 194", "answer": "The result of (39 - 3) * 194 is 6984", "a": 39, "b": 3, "c": 194, "op1": "-", "op2": "*", "result": 6984}
{"question": "Solve: (57.15 + 147) + 186.09", "answer": "The result of (57.15 + 147) + 186.09 is 390.24", "a": 57.15, "b": 147, "c": 186.09, "op1": "+", "op2": "+", "result": 390.24}
{"question": "Solve: (168 - 125.17) * 86", "answer": "The result of (168 - 125.17) * 86 is 3683.38", "a": 168, "b": 125.17, "c": 86, "op1": "-", "op2": "*", "result": 3683.38}
{"question": "Solve: (1.65 - 159) + 140", "answer": "The result of (1.65 - 159) + 140 is -17.35", "a": 1.65, "b": 159, "c": 140, "op1": "-", "op2": "+", "result": -17.35}
{"question": "Solve: (51.1 + 113) / 189", "answer": "The result of (51.1 + 113) / 189 is 0.87", "a": 51.1, "b": 113, "c": 189, "op1": "+", "op2": "/", "result": 0.87}
{"question": "Solve: (200 + 169) / 65.92", "answer": "The result of (200 + 169) / 65.92 is 5.6", "a": 200, "b": 169, "c": 65.92, "op1": "+", "op2": "/", "result": 5.6}
{"question": "Solve: (56 - 55) / 162.76", "answer": "The result of (56 - 55) / 162.76 is 0.01", "a": 56, "b": 55, "c": 162.76, "op1": "-", "op2": "/", "result": 0.01}
{"question": "Solve: (16 + 71) * 176", "answer": "The result of (16 + 71) * 176 is 15312", "a": 16, "b": 71, "c": 176, "op1": "+", "op2": "*", "result": 15312}
{"question": "Solve: (123 * 21.58) * 56.35", "answer": "The result of (123 * 21.58) * 56.35 is 149572.06", "a": 123, "b": 21.58, "c": 56.35, "op1": "*", "op2": "*", "result": 149572.06}
{"question": "Solve: (30 * 200) - 6", "answer": "The result of (30 * 200) - 6 is 5994", "a": 30, "b": 200, "c": 6, "op1": "*", "op2": "-", "result": 5994}
{"question": "Solve: (36 * 181) + 118", "answer": "The result of (36 * 181) + 118 is 6634", "a": 36, "b": 181, "c": 118, "op1": "*", "op2": "+", "result": 6634}
{"question": "Solve: (27 * 199.85) / 88", "answer": "The result of (27 * 199.85) / 88 is 61.32", "a": 27, "b": 199.85, "c": 88, "op1": "*", "op2": "/", "result": 61.32}
{"question": "Solve: (181 - 6.61) / 137", "answer": "The result of (181 - 6.61) / 137 is 1.27", "a": 181, "b": 6.61, "c": 137, "op1": "-", "op2": "/", "result": 1.27}
{"question": "Solve: (147.0 * 65) * 163", "answer": "The result of (147.0 * 65) * 163 is 1557465.0", "a": 147.0, "b": 65, "c": 163, "op1": "*", "op2": "*", "result": 1557465.0}
{"question": "Solve: (83 + 162) * 112.3", "answer": "The result of (83 + 162) * 112.3 is 27513.5", "a": 83, "b": 162, "c": 112.3, "op1": "+", "op2": "*", "result": 27513.5}
{"question": "Solve: (12.1 + 187) * 132", "answer": "The result of (12.1 + 187) * 132 is 26281.2", "a": 12.1, "b": 187, "c": 132, "op1": "+", "op2": "*", "result": 26281.2}
{"question": "Solve: (31 - 5) + 135", "answer": "The result of (31 - 5) + 135 is 161", "a": 31, "b": 5, "c": 135, "op1": "-", "op2": "+", "result": 161}
{"question": "Solve: (168 + 164.44) + 141.96", "answer": "The result of (168 + 164.44) + 141.96 is 474.4", "a": 168, "b": 164.44, "c": 141.96, "op1": "+", "op2": "+", "result": 474.4}
{"question": "Solve: (70 * 194) - 42", "answer": "The result of (70 * 194) - 42 is 13538", "a": 70, "b": 194, "c": 42, "op1": "*", "op2": "-", "result": 13538}
{"question": "Solve: (154.89 - 195) * 121", "answer": "The result of (154.89 - 195) * 121 is -4853.31", "a": 154.89, "b": 195, "c": 121, "op1": "-", "op2": "*", "result": -4853.31}
{"question": "Solve: (164 + 98) + 21", "answer": "The result of (164 + 98) + 21 is 283", "a": 164, "b": 98, "c": 21, "op1": "+", "op2": "+", "result": 283}
{"question": "Solve: (100 + 36.95) - 85", "answer": "The result of (100 + 36.95) - 85 is 51.95", "a": 100, "b": 36.95, "c": 85, "op1": "+", "op2": "-", "result": 51.95}
{"question": "Solve: (164.31 + 96) - 116.5", "answer": "The result of (164.31 + 96) - 116.5 is 143.81", "a": 164.31, "b": 96, "c": 116.5, "op1": "+", "op2": "-", "result": 143.81}
{"question": "Solve: (114 * 128) - 102.09", "answer": "The result of (114 * 128) - 102.09 is 14489.91", "a": 114, "b": 128, "c": 102.09, "op1": "*", "op2": "-", "result": 14489.91}
{"question": "Solve: (58.4 - 54.97) - 89", "answer": "The result of (58.4 - 54.97) - 89 is -85.57", "a": 58.4, "b": 54.97, "c": 89, "op1": "-", "op2": "-", "result": -85.57}
{"question": "Solve: (93.21 * 77) + 80", "answer": "The result of (93.21 * 77) + 80 is 7257.17", "a": 93.21, "b": 77, "c": 80, "op1": "*", "op2": "+", "result": 7257.17}
{"question": "Solve: (193 * 145) - 198", "answer": "The result of (193 * 145) - 198 is 27787", "a": 193, "b": 145, "c": 198, "op1": "*", "op2": "-", "result": 27787}
{"question": "Solve: (80 / 75.09) / 5", "answer": "The result of (80 / 75.09) / 5 is 0.21", "a": 80, "b": 75.09, "c": 5, "op1": "/", "op2": "/", "result": 0.21}
{"question": "Solve: (93 * 45.8) / 47", "answer": "The result of (93 * 45.8) / 47 is 90.63", "a": 93, "b": 45.8, "c": 47, "op1": "*", "op2": "/", "result": 90.63}
{"question": "Solve: (189 * 130) - 61", "answer": "The result of (189 * 130) - 61 is 24509", "a": 189, "b": 130, "c": 61, "op1": "*", "op2": "-", "result": 24509}
{"question": "Solve: (179.24 * 140) - 160", "answer": "The result of (179.24 * 140) - 160 is 24933.6", "a": 179.24, "b": 140, "c": 160, "op1": "*", "op2": "-", "result": 24933.6}
{"question": "Solve: (29 + 53) - 104", "answer": "The result of (29 + 53) - 104 is -22", "a": 29, "b": 53, "c": 104, "op1": "+", "op2": "-", "result": -22}
{"question": "Solve: (77.69 + 169.44) - 116", "answer": "The result of (77.69 + 169.44) - 116 is 131.13", "a": 77.69, "b": 169.44, "c": 116, "op1": "+", "op2": "-", "result": 131.13}
{"question": "Solve: (42.28 * 56) * 44.88", "answer": "The result of (42.28 * 56) * 44.88 is 106261.48", "a": 42.28, "b": 56, "c": 44.88, "op1": "*", "op2": "*", "result": 106261.48}
{"question": "Solve: (146.53 - 156) - 187", "answer": "The result of (146.53 - 156) - 187 is -196.47", "a": 146.53, "b": 156, "c": 187, "op1": "-", "op2": "-", "result": -196.47}
{"question": "Solve: (170.4 + 42) - 142", "answer": "The result of (170.4 + 42) - 142 is 70.4", "a": 170.4, "b": 42, "c": 142, "op1": "+", "op2": "-", "result": 70.4}
{"question": "Solve: (175 + 89.65) * 93", "answer": "The result of (175 + 89.65) * 93 is 24612.45", "a": 175, "b": 89.65, "c": 93, "op1": "+", "op2": "*", "result": 24612.45}
{"question": "Solve: (21 - 133) * 188", "answer": "The result of (21 - 133) * 188 is -21056", "a": 21, "b": 133, "c": 188, "op1": "-", "op2": "*", "result": -21056}
{"question": "Solve: (134 - 14) - 148.67", "answer": "The result of (134 - 14) - 148.67 is -28.67", "a": 134, "b": 14, "c": 148.67, "op1": "-", "op2": "-", "result": -28.67}
{"question": "Solve: (67 * 2) - 126", "answer": "The result of (67 * 2) - 126 is 8", "a": 67, "b": 2, "c": 126, "op1": "*", "op2": "-", "result": 8}
{"question": "Solve: (46 - 148.72) + 48", "answer": "The result of (46 - 148.72) + 48 is -54.72", "a": 46, "b": 148.72, "c": 48, "op1": "-", "op2": "+", "result": -54.72}
{"question": "Solve: (196 - 128.89) - 48.56", "answer": "The result of (196 - 128.89) - 48.56 is 18.55", "a": 196, "b": 128.89, "c": 48.56, "op1": "-", "op2": "-", "result": 18.55}
{"question": "Solve: (167 + 111.94) / 67.91", "answer": "The result of (167 + 111.94) / 67.91 is 4.11", "a": 167, "b": 111.94, "c": 67.91, "op1": "+", "op2": "/", "result": 4.11}
{"question": "Solve: (161 + 189) * 13.2", "answer": "The result of (161 + 189) * 13.2 is 4620.0", "a": 161, "b": 189, "c": 13.2, "op1": "+", "op2": "*", "result": 4620.0}
{"question": "Solve: (157 * 145.6) - 167.24", "answer": "The result of (157 * 145.6) - 167.24 is 22691.96", "a": 157, "b": 145.6, "c": 167.24, "op1": "*", "op2": "-", "result": 22691.96}
{"question": "Solve: (69 * 77) / 26.11", "answer": "The result of (69 * 77) / 26.11 is 203.49", "a": 69, "b": 77, "c": 26.11, "op1": "*", "op2": "/", "result": 203.49}
{"question": "Solve: (154.29 - 146) - 145", "answer": "The result of (154.29 - 146) - 145 is -136.71", "a": 154.29, "b": 146, "c": 145, "op1": "-", "op2": "-", "result": -136.71}
{"question": "Solve: (112 / 64.74) * 30", "answer": "The result of (112 / 64.74) * 30 is 51.9", "a": 112, "b": 64.74, "c": 30, "op1": "/", "op2": "*", "result": 51.9}
{"question": "Solve: (177 - 103) + 186", "answer": "The result of (177 - 103) + 186 is 260", "a": 177, "b": 103, "c": 186, "op1": "-", "op2": "+", "result": 260}
{"question": "Solve: (180 + 22) * 188.26", "answer": "The result of (180 + 22) * 188.26 is 38028.52", "a": 180, "b": 22, "c": 188.26, "op1": "+", "op2": "*", "result": 38028.52}
{"question": "Solve: (37 / 178) - 150.52", "answer": "The result of (37 / 178) - 150.52 is -150.31", "a": 37, "b": 178, "c": 150.52, "op1": "/", "op2": "-", "result": -150.31}
{"question": "Solve: (81 * 194) + 97", "answer": "The result of (81 * 194) + 97 is 15811", "a": 81, "b": 194, "c": 97, "op1": "*", "op2": "+", "result": 15811}
{"question": "Solve: (156 - 109.09) + 147", "answer": "The result of (156 - 109.09) + 147 is 193.91", "a": 156, "b": 109.09, "c": 147, "op1": "-", "op2": "+", "result": 193.91}
{"question": "Solve: (160 - 53.85) / 17.0", "answer": "The result of (160 - 53.85) / 17.0 is 6.24", "a": 160, "b": 53.85, "c": 17.0, "op1": "-", "op2": "/", "result": 6.24}
{"question": "Solve: (64.23 + 116) / 141", "answer": "The result of (64.23 + 116) / 141 is 1.28", "a": 64.23, "b": 116, "c": 141, "op1": "+", "op2": "/", "result": 1.28}
{"question": "Solve: (144 - 86) / 156", "answer": "The result of (144 - 86) / 156 is 0.37", "a": 144, "b": 86, "c": 156, "op1": "-", "op2": "/", "result": 0.37}
{"question": "Solve: (53 + 193) * 79", "answer": "The result of (53 + 193) * 79 is 19434", "a": 53, "b": 193, "c": 79, "op1": "+", "op2": "*", "result": 19434}
{"question": "Solve: (65 - 81) - 177.39", "answer": "The result of (65 - 81) - 177.39 is -193.39", "a": 65, "b": 81, "c": 177.39, "op1": "-", "op2": "-", "result": -193.39}
{"question": "Solve: (178 + 164) + 12.84", "answer": "The result of (178 + 164) + 12.84 is 354.84", "a": 178, "b": 164, "c": 12.84, "op1": "+", "op2": "+", "result": 354.84}
{"question": "Solve: (15 - 34) * 171", "answer": "The result of (15 - 34) * 171 is -3249", "a": 15, "b": 34, "c": 171, "op1": "-", "op2": "*", "result": -3249}
{"question": "Solve: (40 + 28) / 59.87", "answer": "The result of (40 + 28) / 59.87 is 1.14", "a": 40, "b": 28, "c": 59.87, "op1": "+", "op2": "/", "result": 1.14}
{"question": "Solve: (144 - 174.18) + 101", "answer": "The result of (144 - 174.18) + 101 is 70.82", "a": 144, "b": 174.18, "c": 101, "op1": "-", "op2": "+", "result": 70.82}
{"question": "Solve: (86 / 37) + 33.7", "answer": "The result of (86 / 37) + 33.7 is 36.02", "a": 86, "b": 37, "c": 33.7, "op1": "/", "op2": "+", "result": 36.02}
{"question": "Solve: (18.5 + 184) / 71", "answer": "The result of (18.5 + 184) / 71 is 2.85", "a": 18.5, "b": 184, "c": 71, "op1": "+", "op2": "/", "result": 2.85}
{"question": "Solve: (125 + 80) + 92", "answer": "The result of (125 + 80) + 92 is 297", "a": 125, "b": 80, "c": 92, "op1": "+", "op2": "+", "result": 297}
{"question": "Solve: (86 + 51.64) + 92.13", "answer": "The result of (86 + 51.64) + 92.13 is 229.77", "a": 86, "b": 51.64, "c": 92.13, "op1": "+", "op2": "+", "result": 229.77}
{"question": "Solve: (47.08 + 137) / 128", "answer": "The result of (47.08 + 137) / 128 is 1.44", "a": 47.08, "b": 137, "c": 128, "op1": "+", "op2": "/", "result": 1.44}
{"question": "Solve: (34 - 125) + 11", "answer": "The result of (34 - 125) + 11 is -80", "a": 34, "b": 125, "c": 11, "op1": "-", "op2": "+", "result": -80}
{"question": "Solve: (38 - 186) + 73.7", "answer": "The result of (38 - 186) + 73.7 is -74.3", "a": 38, "b": 186, "c": 73.7, "op1": "-", "op2": "+", "result": -74.3}
{"question": "Solve: (166 * 143.51) + 177.4", "answer": "The result of (166 * 143.51) + 177.4 is 24000.06", "a": 166, "b": 143.51, "c": 177.4, "op1": "*", "op2": "+", "result": 24000.06}
{"question": "Solve: (173 / 108.95) / 143", "answer": "The result of (173 / 108.95) / 143 is 0.01", "a": 173, "b": 108.95, "c": 143, "op1": "/", "op2": "/", "result": 0.01}
{"question": "Solve: (174.72 - 39) + 70.0", "answer": "The result of (174.72 - 39) + 70.0 is 205.72", "a": 174.72, "b": 39, "c": 70.0, "op1": "-", "op2": "+", "result": 205.72}
{"question": "Solve: (176 + 150.66) - 135.49", "answer": "The result of (176 + 150.66) - 135.49 is 191.17", "a": 176, "b": 150.66, "c": 135.49, "op1": "+", "op2": "-", "result": 191.17}
{"question": "Solve: (74 / 153) + 135", "answer": "The result of (74 / 153) + 135 is 135.48", "a": 74, "b": 153, "c": 135, "op1": "/", "op2": "+", "result": 135.48}
{"question": "Solve: (127 * 161) + 190", "answer": "The result of (127 * 161) + 190 is 20637", "a": 127, "b": 161, "c": 190, "op1": "*", "op2": "+", "result": 20637}
{"question": "Solve: (171.69 / 140) * 20.6", "answer": "The result of (171.69 / 140) * 20.6 is 25.26", "a": 171.69, "b": 140, "c": 20.6, "op1": "/", "op2": "*", "result": 25.26}
{"question": "Solve: (153.15 * 195.4) + 169.94", "answer": "The result of (153.15 * 195.4) + 169.94 is 30095.45", "a": 153.15, "b": 195.4, "c": 169.94, "op1": "*", "op2": "+", "result": 30095.45}
{"question": "Solve: (162.51 - 71) - 40", "answer": "The result of (162.51 - 71) - 40 is 51.51", "a": 162.51, "b": 71, "c": 40, "op1": "-", "op2": "-", "result": 51.51}
{"question": "Solve: (10 - 98) + 87.75", "answer": "The result of (10 - 98) + 87.75 is -0.25", "a": 10, "b": 98, "c": 87.75, "op1": "-", "op2": "+", "result": -0.25}
{"question": "Solve: (20 - 5.46) + 21", "answer": "The result of (20 - 5.46) + 21 is 35.54", "a": 20, "b": 5.46, "c": 21, "op1": "-", "op2": "+", "result": 35.54}
{"question": "Solve: (53 + 5) - 89.01", "answer": "The result of (53 + 5) - 89.01 is -31.01", "a": 53, "b": 5, "c": 89.01, "op1": "+", "op2": "-", "result": -31.01}
{"question": "Solve: (199 - 119.61) + 144", "answer": "The result of (199 - 119.61) + 144 is 223.39", "a": 199, "b": 119.61, "c": 144, "op1": "-", "op2": "+", "result": 223.39}
{"question": "Solve: (40 + 124.13) + 89", "answer": "The result of (40 + 124.13) + 89 is 253.13", "a": 40, "b": 124.13, "c": 89, "op1": "+", "op2": "+", "result": 253.13}
{"question": "Solve: (67 * 91.99) / 170", "answer": "The result of (67 * 91.99) / 170 is 36.25", "a": 67, "b": 91.99, "c": 170, "op1": "*", "op2": "/", "result": 36.25}
{"question": "Solve: (23.75 - 119) + 106", "answer": "The result of (23.75 - 119) + 106 is 10.75", "a": 23.75, "b": 119, "c": 106, "op1": "-", "op2": "+", "result": 10.75}
{"question": "Solve: (8.33 + 169) - 192.83", "answer": "The result of (8.33 + 169) - 192.83 is -15.5", "a": 8.33, "b": 169, "c": 192.83, "op1": "+", "op2": "-", "result": -15.5}
{"question": "Solve: (118 * 125) / 46.86", "answer": "The result of (118 * 125) / 46.86 is 314.77", "a": 118, "b": 125, "c": 46.86, "op1": "*", "op2": "/", "result": 314.77}
{"question": "Solve: (103 - 175) - 127", "answer": "The result of (103 - 175) - 127 is -199", "a": 103, "b": 175, "c": 127, "op1": "-", "op2": "-", "result": -199}
{"question": "Solve: (33.42 * 102.39) + 24", "answer": "The result of (33.42 * 102.39) + 24 is 3445.87", "a": 33.42, "b": 102.39, "c": 24, "op1": "*", "op2": "+", "result": 3445.87}
{"question": "Solve: (19 + 105.64) * 70", "answer": "The result of (19 + 105.64) * 70 is 8724.8", "a": 19, "b": 105.64, "c": 70, "op1": "+", "op2": "*", "result": 8724.8}
{"question": "Solve: (125.32 / 15) + 1", "answer": "The result of (125.32 / 15) + 1 is 9.35", "a": 125.32, "b": 15, "c": 1, "op1": "/", "op2": "+", "result": 9.35}
{"question": "Solve: (181 / 188) * 173", "answer": "The result of (181 / 188) * 173 is 166.56", "a": 181, "b": 188, "c": 173, "op1": "/", "op2": "*", "result": 166.56}
{"question": "Solve: (137 + 104) / 187", "answer": "The result of (137 + 104) / 187 is 1.29", "a": 137, "b": 104, "c": 187, "op1": "+", "op2": "/", "result": 1.29}
{"question": "Solve: (156 - 124.99) - 90", "answer": "The result of (156 - 124.99) - 90 is -58.99", "a": 156, "b": 124.99, "c": 90, "op1": "-", "op2": "-", "result": -58.99}
{"question": "Solve: (63.95 * 30) - 12", "answer": "The result of (63.95 * 30) - 12 is 1906.5", "a": 63.95, "b": 30, "c": 12, "op1": "*", "op2": "-", "result": 1906.5}
{"question": "Solve: (98 * 85.23) - 85", "answer": "The result of (98 * 85.23) - 85 is 8267.54", "a": 98, "b": 85.23, "c": 85, "op1": "*", "op2": "-", "result": 8267.54}
{"question": "Solve: (189 + 124) - 69", "answer": "The result of (189 + 124) - 69 is 244", "a": 189, "b": 124, "c": 69, "op1": "+", "op2": "-", "result": 244}
{"question": "Solve: (177 + 84.08) + 198", "answer": "The result of (177 + 84.08) + 198 is 459.08", "a": 177, "b": 84.08, "c": 198, "op1": "+", "op2": "+", "result": 459.08}
{"question": "Solve: (124 - 69) + 191.31", "answer": "The result of (124 - 69) + 191.31 is 246.31", "a": 124, "b": 69, "c": 191.31, "op1": "-", "op2": "+", "result": 246.31}
{"question": "Solve: (46 / 104) / 56.76", "answer": "The result of (46 / 104) / 56.76 is 0.01", "a": 46, "b": 104, "c": 56.76, "op1": "/", "op2": "/", "result": 0.01}
{"question": "Solve: (79 / 46) - 27.42", "answer": "The result of (79 / 46) - 27.42 is -25.7", "a": 79, "b": 46, "c": 27.42, "op1": "/", "op2": "-", "result": -25.7}
{"question": "Solve: (113 + 188) - 79", "answer": "The result of (113 + 188) - 79 is 222", "a": 113, "b": 188, "c": 79, "op1": "+", "op2": "-", "result": 222}
{"question": "Solve: (49 - 174) - 91", "answer": "The result of (49 - 174) - 91 is -216", "a": 49, "b": 174, "c": 91, "op1": "-", "op2": "-", "result": -216}
{"question": "Solve: (170.13 + 32.56) - 26.18", "answer": "The result of (170.13 + 32.56) - 26.18 is 176.51", "a": 170.13, "b": 32.56, "c": 26.18, "op1": "+", "op2": "-", "result": 176.51}
{"question": "Solve: (122 / 72.76) * 137", "answer": "The result of (122 / 72.76) * 137 is 229.71", "a": 122, "b": 72.76, "c": 137, "op1": "/", "op2": "*", "result": 229.71}
{"question": "Solve: (94.71 * 30) * 52", "answer": "The result of (94.71 * 30) * 52 is 147747.6", "a": 94.71, "b": 30, "c": 52, "op1": "*", "op2": "*", "result": 147747.6}
{"question": "Solve: (126.43 * 72) * 81", "answer": "The result of (126.43 * 72) * 81 is 737339.76", "a": 126.43, "b": 72, "c": 81, "op1": "*", "op2": "*", "result": 737339.76}
{"question": "Solve: (178 - 187) - 12", "answer": "The result of (178 - 187) - 12 is -21", "a": 178, "b": 187, "c": 12, "op1": "-", "op2": "-", "result": -21}
{"question": "Solve: (116 / 88) - 153", "answer": "The result of (116 / 88) - 153 is -151.68", "a": 116, "b": 88, "c": 153, "op1": "/", "op2": "-", "result": -151.68}
{"question": "Solve: (166 * 160) + 200", "answer": "The result of (166 * 160) + 200 is 26760", "a": 166, "b": 160, "c": 200, "op1": "*", "op2": "+", "result": 26760}
{"question": "Solve: (180.7 / 41.77) - 34", "answer": "The result of (180.7 / 41.77) - 34 is -29.67", "a": 180.7, "b": 41.77, "c": 34, "op1": "/", "op2": "-", "result": -29.67}
{"question": "Solve: (105.79 + 176.61) * 64.73", "answer": "The result of (105.79 + 176.61) * 64.73 is 18279.75", "a": 105.79, "b": 176.61, "c": 64.73, "op1": "+", "op2": "*", "result": 18279.75}
{"question": "Solve: (148 + 127) / 49", "answer": "The result of (148 + 127) / 49 is 5.61", "a": 148, "b": 127, "c": 49, "op1": "+", "op2": "/", "result": 5.61}
{"question": "Solve: (59 + 173) + 76", "answer": "The result of (59 + 173) + 76 is 308", "a": 59, "b": 173, "c": 76, "op1": "+", "op2": "+", "result": 308}
{"question": "Solve: (133.1 * 19.37) / 148", "answer": "The result of (133.1 * 19.37) / 148 is 17.42", "a": 133.1, "b": 19.37, "c": 148, "op1": "*", "op2": "/", "result": 17.42}
{"question": "Solve: (194 * 97.44) + 110", "answer": "The result of (194 * 97.44) + 110 is 19013.36", "a": 194, "b": 97.44, "c": 110, "op1": "*", "op2": "+", "result": 19013.36}
{"question": "Solve: (53.91 * 80) + 57", "answer": "The result of (53.91 * 80) + 57 is 4369.8", "a": 53.91, "b": 80, "c": 57, "op1": "*", "op2": "+", "result": 4369.8}
{"question": "Solve: (63.31 - 36) - 106", "answer": "The result of (63.31 - 36) - 106 is -78.69", "a": 63.31, "b": 36, "c": 106, "op1": "-", "op2": "-", "result": -78.69}
{"question": "Solve: (188 - 96.04) - 36", "answer": "The result of (188 - 96.04) - 36 is 55.96", "a": 188, "b": 96.04, "c": 36, "op1": "-", "op2": "-", "result": 55.96}
{"question": "Solve: (96.87 * 46) + 127", "answer": "The result of (96.87 * 46) + 127 is 4583.02", "a": 96.87, "b": 46, "c": 127, "op1": "*", "op2": "+", "result": 4583.02}
{"question": "Solve: (141 + 93) * 29", "answer": "The result of (141 + 93) * 29 is 6786", "a": 141, "b": 93, "c": 29, "op1": "+", "op2": "*", "result": 6786}
{"question": "Solve: (162 - 65) / 77.52", "answer": "The result of (162 - 65) / 77.52 is 1.25", "a": 162, "b": 65, "c": 77.52, "op1": "-", "op2": "/", "result": 1.25}
{"question": "Solve: (3.38 + 83) * 159", "answer": "The result of (3.38 + 83) * 159 is 13734.42", "a": 3.38, "b": 83, "c": 159, "op1": "+", "op2": "*", "result": 13734.42}
{"question": "Solve: (43 + 71) * 74", "answer": "The result of (43 + 71) * 74 is 8436", "a": 43, "b": 71, "c": 74, "op1": "+", "op2": "*", "result": 8436}
{"question": "Solve: (22.85 + 13) / 1", "answer": "The result of (22.85 + 13) / 1 is 35.85", "a": 22.85, "b": 13, "c": 1, "op1": "+", "op2": "/", "result": 35.85}
{"question": "Solve: (113 - 118.89) * 124", "answer": "The result of (113 - 118.89) * 124 is -730.36", "a": 113, "b": 118.89, "c": 124, "op1": "-", "op2": "*", "result": -730.36}
{"question": "Solve: (147 + 125) - 185", "answer": "The result of (147 + 125) - 185 is 87", "a": 147, "b": 125, "c": 185, "op1": "+", "op2": "-", "result": 87}
{"question": "Solve: (47 + 75) + 79", "answer": "The result of (47 + 75) + 79 is 201", "a": 47, "b": 75, "c": 79, "op1": "+", "op2": "+", "result": 201}
{"question": "Solve: (14 + 154) + 71.91", "answer": "The result of (14 + 154) + 71.91 is 239.91", "a": 14, "b": 154, "c": 71.91, "op1": "+", "op2": "+", "result": 239.91}
{"question": "Solve: (90 - 195) / 108", "answer": "The result of (90 - 195) / 108 is -0.97", "a": 90, "b": 195, "c": 108, "op1": "-", "op2": "/", "result": -0.97}
{"question": "Solve: (82 / 62) + 16", "answer": "The result of (82 / 62) + 16 is 17.32", "a": 82, "b": 62, "c": 16, "op1": "/", "op2": "+", "result": 17.32}
{"question": "Solve: (106 * 30.76) * 55", "answer": "The result of (106 * 30.76) * 55 is 179330.8", "a": 106, "b": 30.76, "c": 55, "op1": "*", "op2": "*", "result": 179330.8}
{"question": "Solve: (127 - 64) - 90", "answer": "The result of (127 - 64) - 90 is -27", "a": 127, "b": 64, "c": 90, "op1": "-", "op2": "-", "result": -27}
{"question": "Solve: (183.29 + 153) * 76", "answer": "The result of (183.29 + 153) * 76 is 25558.04", "a": 183.29, "b": 153, "c": 76, "op1": "+", "op2": "*", "result": 25558.04}
{"question": "Solve: (103.38 * 57) + 88", "answer": "The result of (103.38 * 57) + 88 is 5980.66", "a": 103.38, "b": 57, "c": 88, "op1": "*", "op2": "+", "result": 5980.66}
{"question": "Solve: (77.14 + 64) * 96", "answer": "The result of (77.14 + 64) * 96 is 13549.44", "a": 77.14, "b": 64, "c": 96, "op1": "+", "op2": "*", "result": 13549.44}
{"question": "Solve: (19 + 42) / 17", "answer": "The result of (19 + 42) / 17 is 3.59", "a": 19, "b": 42, "c": 17, "op1": "+", "op2": "/", "result": 3.59}
{"question": "Solve: (105 - 168) / 125", "answer": "The result of (105 - 168) / 125 is -0.5", "a": 105, "b": 168, "c": 125, "op1": "-", "op2": "/", "result": -0.5}
{"question": "Solve: (140 + 134) / 141.92", "answer": "The result of (140 + 134) / 141.92 is 1.93", "a": 140, "b": 134, "c": 141.92, "op1": "+", "op2": "/", "result": 1.93}
{"question": "Solve: (15 + 51) - 51", "answer": "The result of (15 + 51) - 51 is 15", "a": 15, "b": 51, "c": 51, "op1": "+", "op2": "-", "result": 15}
{"question": "Solve: (40 - 169) * 40", "answer": "The result of (40 - 169) * 40 is -5160", "a": 40, "b": 169, "c": 40, "op1": "-", "op2": "*", "result": -5160}
{"question": "Solve: (199.63 * 178) - 178.82", "answer": "The result of (199.63 * 178) - 178.82 is 35355.32", "a": 199.63, "b": 178, "c": 178.82, "op1": "*", "op2": "-", "result": 35355.32}
{"question": "Solve: (184.51 + 136) - 47.32", "answer": "The result of (184.51 + 136) - 47.32 is 273.19", "a": 184.51, "b": 136, "c": 47.32, "op1": "+", "op2": "-", "result": 273.19}
{"question": "Solve: (56.7 / 58.86) + 106", "answer": "The result of (56.7 / 58.86) + 106 is 106.96", "a": 56.7, "b": 58.86, "c": 106, "op1": "/", "op2": "+", "result": 106.96}
{"question": "Solve: (200 - 141.02) - 137", "answer": "The result of (200 - 141.02) - 137 is -78.02", "a": 200, "b": 141.02, "c": 137, "op1": "-", "op2": "-", "result": -78.02}
{"question": "Solve: (36 + 140) * 56.68", "answer": "The result of (36 + 140) * 56.68 is 9975.68", "a": 36, "b": 140, "c": 56.68, "op1": "+", "op2": "*", "result": 9975.68}
{"question": "Solve: (118 + 179) + 136", "answer": "The result of (118 + 179) + 136 is 433", "a": 118, "b": 179, "c": 136, "op1": "+", "op2": "+", "result": 433}
{"question": "Solve: (69 * 15.15) + 14.7", "answer": "The result of (69 * 15.15) + 14.7 is 1060.05", "a": 69, "b": 15.15, "c": 14.7, "op1": "*", "op2": "+", "result": 1060.05}
{"question": "Solve: (30.35 - 171) - 154", "answer": "The result of (30.35 - 171) - 154 is -294.65", "a": 30.35, "b": 171, "c": 154, "op1": "-", "op2": "-", "result": -294.65}
{"question": "Solve: (59 - 177) / 176", "answer": "The result of (59 - 177) / 176 is -0.67", "a": 59, "b": 177, "c": 176, "op1": "-", "op2": "/", "result": -0.67}
{"question": "Solve: (96 / 52.04) - 20", "answer": "The result of (96 / 52.04) - 20 is -18.16", "a": 96, "b": 52.04, "c": 20, "op1": "/", "op2": "-", "result": -18.16}
{"question": "Solve: (136 / 91.47) - 20.25", "answer": "The result of (136 / 91.47) - 20.25 is -18.76", "a": 136, "b": 91.47, "c": 20.25, "op1": "/", "op2": "-", "result": -18.76}
{"question": "Solve: (26 * 55.77) + 35", "answer": "The result of (26 * 55.77) + 35 is 1485.02", "a": 26, "b": 55.77, "c": 35, "op1": "*", "op2": "+", "result": 1485.02}
{"question": "Solve: (38.8 + 99) + 140", "answer": "The result of (38.8 + 99) + 140 is 277.8", "a": 38.8, "b": 99, "c": 140, "op1": "+", "op2": "+", "result": 277.8}
{"question": "Solve: (22 * 12) * 153", "answer": "The result of (22 * 12) * 153 is 40392", "a": 22, "b": 12, "c": 153, "op1": "*", "op2": "*", "result": 40392}
{"question": "Solve: (81 / 44.7) / 130", "answer": "The result of (81 / 44.7) / 130 is 0.01", "a": 81, "b": 44.7, "c": 130, "op1": "/", "op2": "/", "result": 0.01}
{"question": "Solve: (7 * 97.11) + 126", "answer": "The result of (7 * 97.11) + 126 is 805.77", "a": 7, "b": 97.11, "c": 126, "op1": "*", "op2": "+", "result": 805.77}
{"question": "Solve: (199 * 114) / 169", "answer": "The result of (199 * 114) / 169 is 134.24", "a": 199, "b": 114, "c": 169, "op1": "*", "op2": "/", "result": 134.24}
{"question": "Solve: (4 * 158.76) - 181", "answer": "The result of (4 * 158.76) - 181 is 454.04", "a": 4, "b": 158.76, "c": 181, "op1": "*", "op2": "-", "result": 454.04}
{"question": "Solve: (117 + 172) + 72", "answer": "The result of (117 + 172) + 72 is 361", "a": 117, "b": 172, "c": 72, "op1": "+", "op2": "+", "result": 361}
{"question": "Solve: (133.83 - 50) + 16", "answer": "The result of (133.83 - 50) + 16 is 99.83", "a": 133.83, "b": 50, "c": 16, "op1": "-", "op2": "+", "result": 99.83}
{"question": "Solve: (158 + 64) - 58.59", "answer": "The result of (158 + 64) - 58.59 is 163.41", "a": 158, "b": 64, "c": 58.59, "op1": "+", "op2": "-", "result": 163.41}
{"question": "Solve: (21 + 78) + 15", "answer": "The result of (21 + 78) + 15 is 114", "a": 21, "b": 78, "c": 15, "op1": "+", "op2": "+", "result": 114}
{"question": "Solve: (80 - 98) + 142", "answer": "The result of (80 - 98) + 142 is 124", "a": 80, "b": 98, "c": 142, "op1": "-", "op2": "+", "result": 124}
{"question": "Solve: (4 - 119) - 135", "answer": "The result of (4 - 119) - 135 is -250", "a": 4, "b": 119, "c": 135, "op1": "-", "op2": "-", "result": -250}
{"question": "Solve: (174 / 43) + 93", "answer": "The result of (174 / 43) + 93 is 97.05", "a": 174, "b": 43, "c": 93, "op1": "/", "op2": "+", "result": 97.05}
{"question": "Solve: (161 + 2) + 6.15", "answer": "The result of (161 + 2) + 6.15 is 169.15", "a": 161, "b": 2, "c": 6.15, "op1": "+", "op2": "+", "result": 169.15}
{"question": "Solve: (164 * 86) + 28", "answer": "The result of (164 * 86) + 28 is 14132", "a": 164, "b": 86, "c": 28, "op1": "*", "op2": "+", "result": 14132}
{"question": "Solve: (22 / 78.61) + 142.97", "answer": "The result of (22 / 78.61) + 142.97 is 143.25", "a": 22, "b": 78.61, "c": 142.97, "op1": "/", "op2": "+", "result": 143.25}
{"question": "Solve: (133 - 154) - 62", "answer": "The result of (133 - 154) - 62 is -83", "a": 133, "b": 154, "c": 62, "op1": "-", "op2": "-", "result": -83}
{"question": "Solve: (45 / 170) - 118", "answer": "The result of (45 / 170) - 118 is -117.74", "a": 45, "b": 170, "c": 118, "op1": "/", "op2": "-", "result": -117.74}
{"question": "Solve: (69 / 66) / 171", "answer": "The result of (69 / 66) / 171 is 0.01", "a": 69, "b": 66, "c": 171, "op1": "/", "op2": "/", "result": 0.01}
{"question": "Solve: (184 + 131) * 191", "answer": "The result of (184 + 131) * 191 is 60165", "a": 184, "b": 131, "c": 191, "op1": "+", "op2": "*", "result": 60165}
{"question": "Solve: (74 + 108) - 5", "answer": "The result of (74 + 108) - 5 is 177", "a": 74, "b": 108, "c": 5, "op1": "+", "op2": "-", "result": 177}
{"question": "Solve: (27 + 51.58) + 103.72", "answer": "The result of (27 + 51.58) + 103.72 is 182.3", "a": 27, "b": 51.58, "c": 103.72, "op1": "+", "op2": "+", "result": 182.3}
{"question": "Solve: (134.11 + 122) / 15", "answer": "The result of (134.11 + 122) / 15 is 17.07", "a": 134.11, "b": 122, "c": 15, "op1": "+", "op2": "/", "result": 17.07}
{"question": "Solve: (172 * 36) + 46", "answer": "The result of (172 * 36) + 46 is 6238", "a": 172, "b": 36, "c": 46, "op1": "*", "op2": "+", "result": 6238}
{"question": "Solve: (200 - 1) - 31", "answer": "The result of (200 - 1) - 31 is 168", "a": 200, "b": 1, "c": 31, "op1": "-", "op2": "-", "result": 168}
{"question": "Solve: (170 * 108) / 109", "answer": "The result of (170 * 108) / 109 is 168.44", "a": 170, "b": 108, "c": 109, "op1": "*", "op2": "/", "result": 168.44}
{"question": "Solve: (60.18 + 196.66) - 118", "answer": "The result of (60.18 + 196.66) - 118 is 138.84", "a": 60.18, "b": 196.66, "c": 118, "op1": "+", "op2": "-", "result": 138.84}
{"question": "Solve: (141 - 78) + 173.68", "answer": "The result of (141 - 78) + 173.68 is 236.68", "a": 141, "b": 78, "c": 173.68, "op1": "-", "op2": "+", "result": 236.68}
{"question": "Solve: (48.45 + 18) * 120", "answer": "The result of (48.45 + 18) * 120 is 7974.0", "a": 48.45, "b": 18, "c": 120, "op1": "+", "op2": "*", "result": 7974.0}
{"question": "Solve: (43 + 75) + 100", "answer": "The result of (43 + 75) + 100 is 218", "a": 43, "b": 75, "c": 100, "op1": "+", "op2": "+", "result": 218}
{"question": "Solve: (74 * 57) / 18", "answer": "The result of (74 * 57) / 18 is 234.33", "a": 74, "b": 57, "c": 18, "op1": "*", "op2": "/", "result": 234.33}
{"question": "Solve: (31 + 123) / 158", "answer": "The result of (31 + 123) / 158 is 0.97", "a": 31, "b": 123, "c": 158, "op1": "+", "op2": "/", "result": 0.97}
{"question": "Solve: (192 - 45.15) + 10", "answer": "The result of (192 - 45.15) + 10 is 156.85", "a": 192, "b": 45.15, "c": 10, "op1": "-", "op2": "+", "result": 156.85}
{"question": "Solve: (193 * 162) + 16", "answer": "The result of (193 * 162) + 16 is 31282", "a": 193, "b": 162, "c": 16, "op1": "*", "op2": "+", "result": 31282}
{"question": "Solve: (45 - 147) - 180.74", "answer": "The result of (45 - 147) - 180.74 is -282.74", "a": 45, "b": 147, "c": 180.74, "op1": "-", "op2": "-", "result": -282.74}
{"question": "Solve: (184 - 157.88) - 96", "answer": "The result of (184 - 157.88) - 96 is -69.88", "a": 184, "b": 157.88, "c": 96, "op1": "-", "op2": "-", "result": -69.88}
{"question": "Solve: (153 - 197.89) + 124", "answer": "The result of (153 - 197.89) + 124 is 79.11", "a": 153, "b": 197.89, "c": 124, "op1": "-", "op2": "+", "result": 79.11}
{"question": "Solve: (142.29 / 146.64) + 185", "answer": "The result of (142.29 / 146.64) + 185 is 185.97", "a": 142.29, "b": 146.64, "c": 185, "op1": "/", "op2": "+", "result": 185.97}
{"question": "Solve: (191.48 + 68) + 165.42", "answer": "The result of (191.48 + 68) + 165.42 is 424.9", "a": 191.48, "b": 68, "c": 165.42, "op1": "+", "op2": "+", "result": 424.9}
{"question": "Solve: (81.75 - 83) + 28", "answer": "The result of (81.75 - 83) + 28 is 26.75", "a": 81.75, "b": 83, "c": 28, "op1": "-", "op2": "+", "result": 26.75}
{"question": "Solve: (169 - 145) + 14.29", "answer": "The result of (169 - 145) + 14.29 is 38.29", "a": 169, "b": 145, "c": 14.29, "op1": "-", "op2": "+", "result": 38.29}
{"question": "Solve: (95 + 2) - 86", "answer": "The result of (95 + 2) - 86 is 11", "a": 95, "b": 2, "c": 86, "op1": "+", "op2": "-", "result": 11}
{"question": "Solve: (182 - 77) / 1", "answer": "The result of (182 - 77) / 1 is 105.0", "a": 182, "b": 77, "c": 1, "op1": "-", "op2": "/", "result": 105.0}
{"question": "Solve: (111 + 127) * 142", "answer": "The result of (111 + 127) * 142 is 33796", "a": 111, "b": 127, "c": 142, "op1": "+", "op2": "*", "result": 33796}
{"question": "Solve: (50 - 15) - 187.89", "answer": "The result of (50 - 15) - 187.89 is -152.89", "a": 50, "b": 15, "c": 187.89, "op1": "-", "op2": "-", "result": -152.89}
{"question": "Solve: (165 + 34.1) - 185", "answer": "The result of (165 + 34.1) - 185 is 14.1", "a": 165, "b": 34.1, "c": 185, "op1": "+", "op2": "-", "result": 14.1}
{"question": "Solve: (61 + 8) / 125.07", "answer": "The result of (61 + 8) / 125.07 is 0.55", "a": 61, "b": 8, "c": 125.07, "op1": "+", "op2": "/", "result": 0.55}
{"question": "Solve: (71 / 192) * 151", "answer": "The result of (71 / 192) * 151 is 55.84", "a": 71, "b": 192, "c": 151, "op1": "/", "op2": "*", "result": 55.84}
{"question": "Solve: (129 - 90) * 129", "answer": "The result of (129 - 90) * 129 is 5031", "a": 129, "b": 90, "c": 129, "op1": "-", "op2": "*", "result": 5031}
{"question": "Solve: (137 * 199.76) + 188", "answer": "The result of (137 * 199.76) + 188 is 27555.12", "a": 137, "b": 199.76, "c": 188, "op1": "*", "op2": "+", "result": 27555.12}
{"question": "Solve: (58 * 175) + 39", "answer": "The result of (58 * 175) + 39 is 10189", "a": 58, "b": 175, "c": 39, "op1": "*", "op2": "+", "result": 10189}
{"question": "Solve: (19 / 104) - 35", "answer": "The result of (19 / 104) - 35 is -34.82", "a": 19, "b": 104, "c": 35, "op1": "/", "op2": "-", "result": -34.82}
{"question": "Solve: (6 / 156) * 57", "answer": "The result of (6 / 156) * 57 is 2.19", "a": 6, "b": 156, "c": 57, "op1": "/", "op2": "*", "result": 2.19}
{"question": "Solve: (10.59 + 31) / 66", "answer": "The result of (10.59 + 31) / 66 is 0.63", "a": 10.59, "b": 31, "c": 66, "op1": "+", "op2": "/", "result": 0.63}
{"question": "Solve: (184 + 199) / 146.75", "answer": "The result of (184 + 199) / 146.75 is 2.61", "a": 184, "b": 199, "c": 146.75, "op1": "+", "op2": "/", "result": 2.61}
{"question": "Solve: (97.38 + 176) * 150", "answer": "The result of (97.38 + 176) * 150 is 41007.0", "a": 97.38, "b": 176, "c": 150, "op1": "+", "op2": "*", "result": 41007.0}
{"question": "Solve: (138.11 - 200) / 104", "answer": "The result of (138.11 - 200) / 104 is -0.6", "a": 138.11, "b": 200, "c": 104, "op1": "-", "op2": "/", "result": -0.6}
{"question": "Solve: (91 - 97) / 160", "answer": "The result of (91 - 97) / 160 is -0.04", "a": 91, "b": 97, "c": 160, "op1": "-", "op2": "/", "result": -0.04}
{"question": "Solve: (199.08 - 97.06) / 162.12", "answer": "The result of (199.08 - 97.06) / 162.12 is 0.63", "a": 199.08, "b": 97.06, "c": 162.12, "op1": "-", "op2": "/", "result": 0.63}
{"question": "Solve: (65 * 13) * 4", "answer": "The result of (65 * 13) * 4 is 3380", "a": 65, "b": 13, "c": 4, "op1": "*", "op2": "*", "result": 3380}
{"question": "Solve: (194 - 79.39) / 34", "answer": "The result of (194 - 79.39) / 34 is 3.37", "a": 194, "b": 79.39, "c": 34, "op1": "-", "op2": "/", "result": 3.37}
{"question": "Solve: (11.05 * 139) + 59", "answer": "The result of (11.05 * 139) + 59 is 1594.95", "a": 11.05, "b": 139, "c": 59, "op1": "*", "op2": "+", "result": 1594.95}
{"question": "Solve: (53 - 40) + 200", "answer": "The result of (53 - 40) + 200 is 213", "a": 53, "b": 40, "c": 200, "op1": "-", "op2": "+", "result": 213}
{"question": "Solve: (124 - 79) - 165", "answer": "The result of (124 - 79) - 165 is -120", "a": 124, "b": 79, "c": 165, "op1": "-", "op2": "-", "result": -120}
{"question": "Solve: (170 + 26) - 5", "answer": "The result of (170 + 26) - 5 is 191", "a": 170, "b": 26, "c": 5, "op1": "+", "op2": "-", "result": 191}
{"question": "Solve: (35.97 + 143) + 67", "answer": "The result of (35.97 + 143) + 67 is 245.97", "a": 35.97, "b": 143, "c": 67, "op1": "+", "op2": "+", "result": 245.97}
{"question": "Solve: (101 - 114.67) + 88", "answer": "The result of (101 - 114.67) + 88 is 74.33", "a": 101, "b": 114.67, "c": 88, "op1": "-", "op2": "+", "result": 74.33}
{"question": "Solve: (132 * 38) + 200", "answer": "The result of (132 * 38) + 200 is 5216", "a": 132, "b": 38, "c": 200, "op1": "*", "op2": "+", "result": 5216}
{"question": "Solve: (135 * 118) * 59", "answer": "The result of (135 * 118) * 59 is 939870", "a": 135, "b": 118, "c": 59, "op1": "*", "op2": "*", "result": 939870}
{"question": "Solve: (116.6 + 74.17) + 67", "answer": "The result of (116.6 + 74.17) + 67 is 257.77", "a": 116.6, "b": 74.17, "c": 67, "op1": "+", "op2": "+", "result": 257.77}
{"question": "Solve: (169.91 / 51.11) * 180", "answer": "The result of (169.91 / 51.11) * 180 is 598.39", "a": 169.91, "b": 51.11, "c": 180, "op1": "/", "op2": "*", "result": 598.39}
{"question": "Solve: (29 * 149) - 190", "answer": "The result of (29 * 149) - 190 is 4131", "a": 29, "b": 149, "c": 190, "op1": "*", "op2": "-", "result": 4131}
{"question": "Solve: (82.82 - 165) * 167.55", "answer": "The result of (82.82 - 165) * 167.55 is -13769.26", "a": 82.82, "b": 165, "c": 167.55, "op1": "-", "op2": "*", "result": -13769.26}
{"question": "Solve: (40 / 16) + 93", "answer": "The result of (40 / 16) + 93 is 95.5", "a": 40, "b": 16, "c": 93, "op1": "/", "op2": "+", "result": 95.5}
{"question": "Solve: (120 * 129.69) * 53", "answer": "The result of (120 * 129.69) * 53 is 824828.4", "a": 120, "b": 129.69, "c": 53, "op1": "*", "op2": "*", "result": 824828.4}
{"question": "Solve: (25.83 - 89) + 183", "answer": "The result of (25.83 - 89) + 183 is 119.83", "a": 25.83, "b": 89, "c": 183, "op1": "-", "op2": "+", "result": 119.83}
{"question": "Solve: (199.49 + 71.36) - 43", "answer": "The result of (199.49 + 71.36) - 43 is 227.85", "a": 199.49, "b": 71.36, "c": 43, "op1": "+", "op2": "-", "result": 227.85}
{"question": "Solve: (73 - 124) - 141.7", "answer": "The result of (73 - 124) - 141.7 is -192.7", "a": 73, "b": 124, "c": 141.7, "op1": "-", "op2": "-", "result": -192.7}
{"question": "Solve: (68.37 / 12.59) - 106", "answer": "The result of (68.37 / 12.59) - 106 is -100.57", "a": 68.37, "b": 12.59, "c": 106, "op1": "/", "op2": "-", "result": -100.57}
{"question": "Solve: (13 - 98) / 92.74", "answer": "The result of (13 - 98) / 92.74 is -0.92", "a": 13, "b": 98, "c": 92.74, "op1": "-", "op2": "/", "result": -0.92}
{"question": "Solve: (25 * 78.31) - 146", "answer": "The result of (25 * 78.31) - 146 is 1811.75", "a": 25, "b": 78.31, "c": 146, "op1": "*", "op2": "-", "result": 1811.75}
{"question": "Solve: (178.29 + 29) + 101", "answer": "The result of (178.29 + 29) + 101 is 308.29", "a": 178.29, "b": 29, "c": 101, "op1": "+", "op2": "+", "result": 308.29}
{"question": "Solve: (2 - 63) - 46", "answer": "The result of (2 - 63) - 46 is -107", "a": 2, "b": 63, "c": 46, "op1": "-", "op2": "-", "result": -107}
{"question": "Solve: (114 - 25) + 115", "answer": "The result of (114 - 25) + 115 is 204", "a": 114, "b": 25, "c": 115, "op1": "-", "op2": "+", "result": 204}
{"question": "Solve: (29 * 34) + 30", "answer": "The result of (29 * 34) + 30 is 1016", "a": 29, "b": 34, "c": 30, "op1": "*", "op2": "+", "result": 1016}
{"question": "Solve: (54 + 47) * 114", "answer": "The result of (54 + 47) * 114 is 11514", "a": 54, "b": 47, "c": 114, "op1": "+", "op2": "*", "result": 11514}
{"question": "Solve: (66 - 166.21) + 143", "answer": "The result of (66 - 166.21) + 143 is 42.79", "a": 66, "b": 166.21, "c": 143, "op1": "-", "op2": "+", "result": 42.79}
{"question": "Solve: (28 - 112) / 2.04", "answer": "The result of (28 - 112) / 2.04 is -41.18", "a": 28, "b": 112, "c": 2.04, "op1": "-", "op2": "/", "result": -41.18}
{"question": "Solve: (44.7 * 196) + 25.71", "answer": "The result of (44.7 * 196) + 25.71 is 8786.91", "a": 44.7, "b": 196, "c": 25.71, "op1": "*", "op2": "+", "result": 8786.91}
{"question": "Solve: (65 * 111) * 107.13", "answer": "The result of (65 * 111) * 107.13 is 772942.95", "a": 65, "b": 111, "c": 107.13, "op1": "*", "op2": "*", "result": 772942.95}
{"question": "Solve: (111.28 - 64.21) - 145", "answer": "The result of (111.28 - 64.21) - 145 is -97.93", "a": 111.28, "b": 64.21, "c": 145, "op1": "-", "op2": "-", "result": -97.93}
{"question": "Solve: (85 + 87) - 187", "answer": "The result of (85 + 87) - 187 is -15", "a": 85, "b": 87, "c": 187, "op1": "+", "op2": "-", "result": -15}
{"question": "Solve: (104.08 / 91.66) * 147", "answer": "The result of (104.08 / 91.66) * 147 is 166.92", "a": 104.08, "b": 91.66, "c": 147, "op1": "/", "op2": "*", "result": 166.92}
{"question": "Solve: (95.75 / 123) - 65", "answer": "The result of (95.75 / 123) - 65 is -64.22", "a": 95.75, "b": 123, "c": 65, "op1": "/", "op2": "-", "result": -64.22}
{"question": "Solve: (71 - 46) + 50", "answer": "The result of (71 - 46) + 50 is 75", "a": 71, "b": 46, "c": 50, "op1": "-", "op2": "+", "result": 75}
{"question": "Solve: (44 - 96) + 22.04", "answer": "The result of (44 - 96) + 22.04 is -29.96", "a": 44, "b": 96, "c": 22.04, "op1": "-", "op2": "+", "result": -29.96}
{"question": "Solve: (20 * 81) * 173.31", "answer": "The result of (20 * 81) * 173.31 is 280762.2", "a": 20, "b": 81, "c": 173.31, "op1": "*", "op2": "*", "result": 280762.2}
{"question": "Solve: (132.44 + 1) + 129", "answer": "The result of (132.44 + 1) + 129 is 262.44", "a": 132.44, "b": 1, "c": 129, "op1": "+", "op2": "+", "result": 262.44}
{"question": "Solve: (144 / 140) / 56", "answer": "The result of (144 / 140) / 56 is 0.02", "a": 144, "b": 140, "c": 56, "op1": "/", "op2": "/", "result": 0.02}
{"question": "Solve: (19 / 161) * 78", "answer": "The result of (19 / 161) * 78 is 9.2", "a": 19, "b": 161, "c": 78, "op1": "/", "op2": "*", "result": 9.2}
{"question": "Solve: (46.1 / 123.27) + 125", "answer": "The result of (46.1 / 123.27) + 125 is 125.37", "a": 46.1, "b": 123.27, "c": 125, "op1": "/", "op2": "+", "result": 125.37}
{"question": "Solve: (17 + 73.68) * 19", "answer": "The result of (17 + 73.68) * 19 is 1722.92", "a": 17, "b": 73.68, "c": 19, "op1": "+", "op2": "*", "result": 1722.92}
{"question": "Solve: (17.03 * 152) * 87", "answer": "The result of (17.03 * 152) * 87 is 225204.72", "a": 17.03, "b": 152, "c": 87, "op1": "*", "op2": "*", "result": 225204.72}
{"question": "Solve: (124 + 173) * 52", "answer": "The result of (124 + 173) * 52 is 15444", "a": 124, "b": 173, "c": 52, "op1": "+", "op2": "*", "result": 15444}
{"question": "Solve: (79 - 131) - 129", "answer": "The result of (79 - 131) - 129 is -181", "a": 79, "b": 131, "c": 129, "op1": "-", "op2": "-", "result": -181}
{"question": "Solve: (41 - 65) + 192.57", "answer": "The result of (41 - 65) + 192.57 is 168.57", "a": 41, "b": 65, "c": 192.57, "op1": "-", "op2": "+", "result": 168.57}
{"question": "Solve: (137.06 + 37) / 86", "answer": "The result of (137.06 + 37) / 86 is 2.02", "a": 137.06, "b": 37, "c": 86, "op1": "+", "op2": "/", "result": 2.02}
{"question": "Solve: (51.94 + 95) - 157", "answer": "The result of (51.94 + 95) - 157 is -10.06", "a": 51.94, "b": 95, "c": 157, "op1": "+", "op2": "-", "result": -10.06}
{"question": "Solve: (56.28 - 88) - 125", "answer": "The result of (56.28 - 88) - 125 is -156.72", "a": 56.28, "b": 88, "c": 125, "op1": "-", "op2": "-", "result": -156.72}
{"question": "Solve: (93 - 118) * 53.42", "answer": "The result of (93 - 118) * 53.42 is -1335.5", "a": 93, "b": 118, "c": 53.42, "op1": "-", "op2": "*", "result": -1335.5}
{"question": "Solve: (63 - 88.56) / 77", "answer": "The result of (63 - 88.56) / 77 is -0.33", "a": 63, "b": 88.56, "c": 77, "op1": "-", "op2": "/", "result": -0.33}
{"question": "Solve: (118 - 73.1) - 19", "answer": "The result of (118 - 73.1) - 19 is 25.9", "a": 118, "b": 73.1, "c": 19, "op1": "-", "op2": "-", "result": 25.9}
{"question": "Solve: (98 - 71) * 122.85", "answer": "The result of (98 - 71) * 122.85 is 3316.95", "a": 98, "b": 71, "c": 122.85, "op1": "-", "op2": "*", "result": 3316.95}
{"question": "Solve: (178.33 / 73.11) * 22.63", "answer": "The result of (178.33 / 73.11) * 22.63 is 55.2", "a": 178.33, "b": 73.11, "c": 22.63, "op1": "/", "op2": "*", "result": 55.2}
{"question": "Solve: (46.38 + 72) + 24", "answer": "The result of (46.38 + 72) + 24 is 142.38", "a": 46.38, "b": 72, "c": 24, "op1": "+", "op2": "+", "result": 142.38}
{"question": "Solve: (144.8 + 120.18) - 160", "answer": "The result of (144.8 + 120.18) - 160 is 104.98", "a": 144.8, "b": 120.18, "c": 160, "op1": "+", "op2": "-", "result": 104.98}
{"question": "Solve: (151 + 154.27) - 14.21", "answer": "The result of (151 + 154.27) - 14.21 is 291.06", "a": 151, "b": 154.27, "c": 14.21, "op1": "+", "op2": "-", "result": 291.06}
{"question": "Solve: (84 - 54) + 21", "answer": "The result of (84 - 54) + 21 is 51", "a": 84, "b": 54, "c": 21, "op1": "-", "op2": "+", "result": 51}
{"question": "Solve: (27.39 + 26.52) * 136", "answer": "The result of (27.39 + 26.52) * 136 is 7331.76", "a": 27.39, "b": 26.52, "c": 136, "op1": "+", "op2": "*", "result": 7331.76}
{"question": "Solve: (173 / 56) - 37", "answer": "The result of (173 / 56) - 37 is -33.91", "a": 173, "b": 56, "c": 37, "op1": "/", "op2": "-", "result": -33.91}
{"question": "Solve: (133 - 153) + 23", "answer": "The result of (133 - 153) + 23 is 3", "a": 133, "b": 153, "c": 23, "op1": "-", "op2": "+", "result": 3}
{"question": "Solve: (68 + 142) - 111.13", "answer": "The result of (68 + 142) - 111.13 is 98.87", "a": 68, "b": 142, "c": 111.13, "op1": "+", "op2": "-", "result": 98.87}
{"question": "Solve: (29 + 105.31) + 79.56", "answer": "The result of (29 + 105.31) + 79.56 is 213.87", "a": 29, "b": 105.31, "c": 79.56, "op1": "+", "op2": "+", "result": 213.87}
{"question": "Solve: (188 + 13) + 25.51", "answer": "The result of (188 + 13) + 25.51 is 226.51", "a": 188, "b": 13, "c": 25.51, "op1": "+", "op2": "+", "result": 226.51}
{"question": "Solve: (159.91 / 86) + 65.16", "answer": "The result of (159.91 / 86) + 65.16 is 67.02", "a": 159.91, "b": 86, "c": 65.16, "op1": "/", "op2": "+", "result": 67.02}
{"question": "Solve: (179.61 * 94) * 186.16", "answer": "The result of (179.61 * 94) * 186.16 is 3143002.57", "a": 179.61, "b": 94, "c": 186.16, "op1": "*", "op2": "*", "result": 3143002.57}
{"question": "Solve: (130 + 137.97) - 24", "answer": "The result of (130 + 137.97) - 24 is 243.97", "a": 130, "b": 137.97, "c": 24, "op1": "+", "op2": "-", "result": 243.97}
{"question": "Solve: (83.84 + 96.28) * 25.27", "answer": "The result of (83.84 + 96.28) * 25.27 is 4551.63", "a": 83.84, "b": 96.28, "c": 25.27, "op1": "+", "op2": "*", "result": 4551.63}
{"question": "Solve: (137 / 127.22) + 127", "answer": "The result of (137 / 127.22) + 127 is 128.08", "a": 137, "b": 127.22, "c": 127, "op1": "/", "op2": "+", "result": 128.08}
{"question": "Solve: (177 / 190) + 173.92", "answer": "The result of (177 / 190) + 173.92 is 174.85", "a": 177, "b": 190, "c": 173.92, "op1": "/", "op2": "+", "result": 174.85}
{"question": "Solve: (191 + 109) * 37.05", "answer": "The result of (191 + 109) * 37.05 is 11115.0", "a": 191, "b": 109, "c": 37.05, "op1": "+", "op2": "*", "result": 11115.0}
{"question": "Solve: (104.99 / 119.91) / 34", "answer": "The result of (104.99 / 119.91) / 34 is 0.03", "a": 104.99, "b": 119.91, "c": 34, "op1": "/", "op2": "/", "result": 0.03}
{"question": "Solve: (43 / 117) - 177.06", "answer": "The result of (43 / 117) - 177.06 is -176.69", "a": 43, "b": 117, "c": 177.06, "op1": "/", "op2": "-", "result": -176.69}
{"question": "Solve: (183 + 141.34) * 184", "answer": "The result of (183 + 141.34) * 184 is 59678.56", "a": 183, "b": 141.34, "c": 184, "op1": "+", "op2": "*", "result": 59678.56}
{"question": "Solve: (194.02 * 145) * 165.47", "answer": "The result of (194.02 * 145) * 165.47 is 4655150.96", "a": 194.02, "b": 145, "c": 165.47, "op1": "*", "op2": "*", "result": 4655150.96}
{"question": "Solve: (4 - 23) + 175", "answer": "The result of (4 - 23) + 175 is 156", "a": 4, "b": 23, "c": 175, "op1": "-", "op2": "+", "result": 156}
{"question": "Solve: (38 - 194) * 5", "answer": "The result of (38 - 194) * 5 is -780", "a": 38, "b": 194, "c": 5, "op1": "-", "op2": "*", "result": -780}
{"question": "Solve: (9 + 177.19) - 97", "answer": "The result of (9 + 177.19) - 97 is 89.19", "a": 9, "b": 177.19, "c": 97, "op1": "+", "op2": "-", "result": 89.19}
{"question": "Solve: (2.21 - 51) - 137", "answer": "The result of (2.21 - 51) - 137 is -185.79", "a": 2.21, "b": 51, "c": 137, "op1": "-", "op2": "-", "result": -185.79}
{"question": "Solve: (79 * 74.9) + 85", "answer": "The result of (79 * 74.9) + 85 is 6002.1", "a": 79, "b": 74.9, "c": 85, "op1": "*", "op2": "+", "result": 6002.1}
{"question": "Solve: (102 * 191.81) + 103.99", "answer": "The result of (102 * 191.81) + 103.99 is 19668.61", "a": 102, "b": 191.81, "c": 103.99, "op1": "*", "op2": "+", "result": 19668.61}
{"question": "Solve: (161 * 154) - 158.95", "answer": "The result of (161 * 154) - 158.95 is 24635.05", "a": 161, "b": 154, "c": 158.95, "op1": "*", "op2": "-", "result": 24635.05}
{"question": "Solve: (68 * 136) - 102.58", "answer": "The result of (68 * 136) - 102.58 is 9145.42", "a": 68, "b": 136, "c": 102.58, "op1": "*", "op2": "-", "result": 9145.42}
{"question": "Solve: (105.78 - 46.57) / 36.86", "answer": "The result of (105.78 - 46.57) / 36.86 is 1.61", "a": 105.78, "b": 46.57, "c": 36.86, "op1": "-", "op2": "/", "result": 1.61}
{"question": "Solve: (44 - 32.97) - 152", "answer": "The result of (44 - 32.97) - 152 is -140.97", "a": 44, "b": 32.97, "c": 152, "op1": "-", "op2": "-", "result": -140.97}
{"question": "Solve: (71.47 + 145.6) * 92.93", "answer": "The result of (71.47 + 145.6) * 92.93 is 20172.32", "a": 71.47, "b": 145.6, "c": 92.93, "op1": "+", "op2": "*", "result": 20172.32}
{"question": "Solve: (16.79 - 102) + 33", "answer": "The result of (16.79 - 102) + 33 is -52.21", "a": 16.79, "b": 102, "c": 33, "op1": "-", "op2": "+", "result": -52.21}
{"question": "Solve: (133.77 - 62) * 39", "answer": "The result of (133.77 - 62) * 39 is 2799.03", "a": 133.77, "b": 62, "c": 39, "op1": "-", "op2": "*", "result": 2799.03}
{"question": "Solve: (108 - 179) / 60", "answer": "The result of (108 - 179) / 60 is -1.18", "a": 108, "b": 179, "c": 60, "op1": "-", "op2": "/", "result": -1.18}
{"question": "Solve: (12 - 88.81) + 170.89", "answer": "The result of (12 - 88.81) + 170.89 is 94.08", "a": 12, "b": 88.81, "c": 170.89, "op1": "-", "op2": "+", "result": 94.08}
{"question": "Solve: (188 * 43) * 31", "answer": "The result of (188 * 43) * 31 is 250604", "a": 188, "b": 43, "c": 31, "op1": "*", "op2": "*", "result": 250604}
{"question": "Solve: (102.39 - 67) + 196", "answer": "The result of (102.39 - 67) + 196 is 231.39", "a": 102.39, "b": 67, "c": 196, "op1": "-", "op2": "+", "result": 231.39}
{"question": "Solve: (154 - 165) / 114", "answer": "The result of (154 - 165) / 114 is -0.1", "a": 154, "b": 165, "c": 114, "op1": "-", "op2": "/", "result": -0.1}
{"question": "Solve: (102.41 - 160) - 1", "answer": "The result of (102.41 - 160) - 1 is -58.59", "a": 102.41, "b": 160, "c": 1, "op1": "-", "op2": "-", "result": -58.59}
